(The following content may not be suitable for viewers under 15.)
(Viewer discretion is advised.)
(Episode 10)
Dad.
It's been a long while.
I'm sorry, Dad.
Forgive me.
I was...
I was a terrible son.
I didn't know you were sick. I was selfish.
I'm the worst.
It's not your fault.
I can still see,
and I can still move freely.
And I kept it a secret because I wanted to sort things out myself.
You must have looked into it,
but what I have can't be treated or cured.
If it can't be done here,
we can go abroad and get help there.
Our eyes grow dim with age and our hearing weakens.
It happens to us all.
It's nothing.
It's not worth making a fuss about.
I'm a man.
Dad.
How is your mum?
She was worried at first,
but now,
she wants you to return after fulfilling your wish.
She still worries, though.
She wonders if you eat regularly,
if you sleep in comfort,
and if you have enough money with you.
I'll return home soon.
So tell her not to worry too much.
Tell her she can relax.
Why don't you just come home with me tonight?
I'm almost done.
I'll come home when I'm finished.
- Mum and Dong Sook should know... - It's no rush.
- I'll tell them when I get back. - Dad.
Them finding out about my illness won't change anything.
Please keep it a secret...
until I come home and tell them myself.
Do me a favour.
Did you sell the tailor shop?
Sam Do decided to take over.
He started working today.
- Sam Do? - Yes.
After you left home,
he worried more than I did about you and about the store.
I owe him a lot.
He's a very rare man.
I was quite surprised.
I never imagined...
you'd be so calm and relaxed.
Aren't you afraid or frightened?
For a tailor to lose his sight...
is like a death sentence.
Of course I felt all sorts of emotions.
I was afraid and frightened.
But then again, I thought about it for a while.
My whole life,
I got to see all the greatest suits in the world.
My eyes saw many beautiful things.
I guess the world is just telling me that I've seen enough.
I saw more than enough,
so now I've been given time to prepare for the end.
That's why...
I'm doing what I considered doing for a long time.
You have no idea how nice it is to be able to put my life in order.
I know you're making suits for the less fortunate.
But you can do that from home. I will help you.
This is something I have to do alone.
If I were to say I wanted to continue the family business,
would that make you happy?
I've given up on that.
I don't want you to continue the family business.
I want you to do what you want.
To be honest, I don't know what I want...
or what I should do that will...
make me happy.
I know this much about you, my son.
You aren't a fool who would give up...
something valuable so you could succeed or gain fame.
Will you promise me something?
Promise me that...
by the time I return home, you will have found...
what makes you happy.
When I grow up,
I'll make you a suit, too. I promise.
You make promises with a lot of other people with your pinky,
so make your promise to me with your thumb.
This is how we make promises.
- Hello. - Where are you?
I said I'd drive you.
It's just a short taxi ride.
- Dong Jin. - Yes?
Keep your promise.
I believe that by the time I come home, you'll have found...
what you want to do...
and what you should do to make yourself happy.
Your uncle got a divorce?
- Are you sure? - Be quiet. Grandma might hear you.
Hyo Won told me this evening.
Who will you call?
Who do you think? I need to check.
Uncle Dong Jin must feel bad as it is. Leave him alone.
Why would they get a divorce?
Is your aunt seeing someone?
Stop it, Mum.
No? What else could it be?
- Is Da Jeong home? - You scared me.
Why are you so surprised? Were you two gossiping?
Why would we be gossiping?
We weren't expecting you to come out of the room so suddenly.
I didn't say hi because Mum said you were asleep.
I'm home.
I don't understand why I feel asleep so early today.
Where's the spinach soup?
- I forgot. - What a useless mum you are.
I'll warm the soup up for you.
- Wait a little bit. - Okay, Grandma.
- We should be careful. - You should be careful.
A little rat keeps stealing our food whenever he comes and goes.
I just can't dare leave the house.
Don't be so mean. It's just food.
I'm not one to complain about such issues,
but look at this. He ate over half the chicken.
He'd have eaten it all if I hadn't come up in time.
No wonder there's so little meat. I thought this was a chick.
The rat has a huge appetite.
I should get a few traps from the store tomorrow.
There's nothing but sauce left.
The chicken wasn't worth this kind of insult. Stupid me.
Just get married.
Eat your wife's cooking.
Leave our food alone.
Dong Sook's a great girl with just one flaw.
She can't cook to save her life.
They keep mentioning her.
- Are you glue? - What do you mean?
Why do you keep trying to stick me and Dong Sook together?
She isn't my type.
- What's so bad about her? - Exactly.
She's the one who should be rejecting you, you know.
- Dock it from the repair fee. - Dock what?
The price of the chicken stew.
Dock it from the 100 dollars you owe me this month.
Okay, then I'll wire you 70 dollars this month.
70 dollars?
Does that mean I ate 30 dollars' worth of chicken?
That's daylight robbery.
You're unarmed, but you're still a thief.
The chicken stew you had...
follows a recipe that came down from my great-grandmother,
and it also includes my own special and secret sauce.
You even said it was the best.
Even so, I didn't eat the whole chicken.
I only ate a drumstick and breast meat which was very dry.
You can't charge 30 dollars for that.
You made us pay 1,000 dollars to fix your guitar.
- That's robbery, too. - It is.
- I want a drumstick. - Okay.
You two are quite the team. Are you in this together now?
Hey. How could you do that?
You can't just steal the drumstick.
I don't want to eat it.
But I'm force-feeding myself to eat 30 dollars' worth of food.
It's not because it's tasty.
I don't believe this. How can someone be so shameless?
It's fine. I've had enough, and I lost my appetite anyway.
Leave it. Don't get angry over nothing.
- What a jerk. - Let's go inside.
This is unbelievable.
Finish up and do the dishes.
Let's go to bed, Honey.
My gosh.
Now, it's worth 30 dollars.
What are you doing? Get your face out of the way.
I saved your life. Shouldn't you at least thank me for it?
Do you really want to show off?
I'm not showing off.
You should thank your lifesaver. It's basic manners.
Okay, then. Thank you so much.
I still don't believe what he said.
I should've let him struggle in the water.
Why aren't you asleep?
You said you have to leave at dawn.
Sleep well, Mother.
Leave the scissors alone, Dong Jin.
You'll hurt yourself.
Shall we do it together, then?
Yes.
Hold it tight.
Let's begin.
Cut straight down.
In a straight line. That's it.
Well done.
I saw a happy little boy cutting through...
and playing around with leftover pieces of fabric.
I hadn't had such a nice dream in a while.
I left you to search for happiness, Dad.
But why do I think that I feel truly happy...
when I'm close to you?
Will I become happy, Dad, if I return to the store...
like I did in the dream?
How could you, Hyo Joo?
Why didn't you call me or my mum to tell us that you got a divorce?
Did you call this early to complain about that?
What do you mean complain?
Don't say that.
My father passed away,
and now I'm a divorcee.
Do you think I'd be in the right mind...
to call and report that I divorced your brother?
I really don't like how you word things.
Where is Dong Jin?
How would I know that?
Call and ask him yourself.
I called you because he isn't picking up.
I am...
no longer his wife.
Don't call me to ask about him any more.
Don't you worry about him?
Why should I?
He has you and Mother.
I have no one.
- What? - I'm alone now.
No one's on my side.
Why did you get divorced, then?
You'll never find another man like Dong Jin.
It's your fault for kicking away a blessing.
What did you just say?
Dong Jin got divorced?
Mum, let me explain.
Oh, gosh.
What's this about a divorce? What's going on?
I'm sorry.
Divorce isn't child's play.
It's not something you can just go and do on your own.
Put Dong Jin on the phone.
He signed the papers last night...
and packed up and left.
You two came over and had dinner.
That wasn't so long ago.
Why did you suddenly get divorced?
What on earth happened?
He resigned from Meesa.
Why would Dong Jin...
quit work? Why would he do that?
That's what I don't understand.
I told him to get back what my stepmother and Hyo Sang had taken,
but he just quit.
How could I entrust him with our future?
Slow down. Let me get this straight.
Your stepmother and brother plotted against him...
and kicked him out of the company, is that it?
Yes, that's right.
How dare they.
Let's not talk over the phone. We should talk in person.
Come over right now.
I have nothing to say to you. I have no hard feelings, either.
You were nice to me, and I thank you for that.
Goodbye.
Hyo Joo. Hyo Joo.
Mum, try to relax.
You can't faint. Not again.
Sam Do. Sam Do.
Mum.
What is it? What's wrong?
- Well... - Take her to her room first.
Get on my back. I'll take you inside.
Take my hand, then.
Careful.
Mum.
This should help you relax. Chew it nice and slowly.
What was that for?
When your sister-in-law came over, you should've treated her kindly.
You were always so mean to her.
Are you saying they got divorced because I was mean to Hyo Joo?
Do you think I let her be because I don't know how to be mean?
I let her do as she pleased...
for Dong Jin's sake so she wouldn't nag at him.
This is insane.
You must be so happy I got divorced and moved back in.
- Who else would you blame? - What?
Don't take it out on Dong Sook.
It can't be her fault they split up.
My poor boy...
Don't just sit there.
Hurry up and call Dong Jin.
Your poor boy turned his phone off.
You little...
I'm sure they signed the papers out of anger.
I don't think they mean to get divorced. Don't worry.
You know what Dong Jin is like.
Once he makes up his mind,
he sticks to his guns whatever happens.
All this...
happened because of the ghastly Ms Ko.
What did she do?
She plotted with her son and made Dong Jin leave the company.
What? Dong Jin lost his job?
She's a freak.
She lured a married man and took over the house,
and now she's even taking control of the company.
She lured a married man and took over what?
Was Dong Jin's mother-in-law the other woman?
Didn't you know?
She had an affair with the now dead chairman...
long before his first wife, Dong Jin's wife's mum, died.
Why didn't you tell me?
Why should I tell you that?
Any woman who makes the wife cry...
needs to learn a lesson.
I can't waste time like this.
Where will you go?
All this is Ms Ko's fault.
I can't sit and do nothing.
I shall pull all her hair out.
She's really angry.
Wait for me.
Where are you going?
I'm good at pulling hair out.
Stay out of it.
Any witch who stole another woman's husband...
has to be plucked like a chicken.
She deserves to be bald or worse. Let go.
This is insane. Sun Nyeo!
- Slow down. - Taxi.
- Taxi. - Taxi.
Get in the back.
(Empty)
Take us to Pyeongchang-dong.
Okay.
Stop, stop. Stop.
- What is it? - I'm coming.
Why are you coming along?
You can't leave me out.
There's a special way of dealing with husband-stealers.
I know what I'm doing. Don't you worry, Ms Choi.
There's no time. Let's go.
Okay.
My gosh.
This doesn't look good.
What if something bad happens?
Good morning.
I had a really strange dream.
I didn't sleep a wink.
- Where are the kids? - They left for work.
Hyo Joo went to see a lawyer.
I don't have an appetite.
It must be because I didn't get much sleep.
This is nice.
As if you'd have no appetite.
Fry me an egg.
An egg? What for?
- Because I don't have an appetite. - I see.
I know you're her stepmother,
but how can you eat when your daughter's getting a divorce?
Were you talking about me?
No. I didn't say a thing.
I wonder who that could be.
My goodness, that woman. What a snake.
They must be worried about what's going on.
Welcome.
Who is it?
It's Dong Jin's mother.
Dong Jin's mother?
- My in-laws? - Yes.
- Don't let them in. - I already did.
Welcome.
What brings you here so early in the morning?
- Hello, Dong Sook. - Where's Hyo Joo?
She's out to see a lawyer.
You look familiar. Who are you?
I'm Bae Sam Do's wife.
That's right. I kind of remember seeing you at the wedding.
What are you three doing here?
You should know.
You kicked my precious son out of the company...
and made him get a divorce, as well?
I think there's a misunderstanding.
I was against the divorce. I strongly advised them not to.
I know you didn't give birth to her,
but how could you ruin Hyo Joo's life at every turn?
She lost her mother at a young age...
and then her father.
Did you have to...
take the company and kick her husband out?
I really don't like what I'm hearing.
Why are you blaming me for them not being able to get along?
Is their divorce my responsibility?
I can't believe you said that. I hear things, too.
All this happened because you manipulated your senile husband...
and stole his company from under his nose.
It's a competitive economy. If you can't win, you lose.
Is it my fault?
It's his fault for not being able to hold onto it.
Don't say that.
You know better than anyone that Dong Jin's a borderline genius.
Getting good grades doesn't equal being a good CEO.
You are so thick.
Gosh, whatever.
Keep talking nonsense...
- and I'll sue you for libel. - Libel?
What about how you ruined Dong Jin's name?
Sue me.
Sue us all so we can...
go to a judge and figure out who's in the wrong.
How dare you point at me.
- You might actually hit me. - I'd love to.
If I think about how you treated Dong Jin,
I could hit you 100 times and still not feel any guilt.
- You evil... - Mum.
- Relax, Mum. - Get her out of here.
If you don't, I'll report you all for trespassing.
Trespassing?
We're visiting an in-law. That's not trespassing.
We are no longer in-laws.
I get it now.
You couldn't wait for the two to get divorced.
- Where's you conscience? - I did nothing to feel bad about.
Did you not? Really?
30 years ago. My poor little brother.
You went and ruined the life of an innocent and naive young man.
And now, you went and ruined Dong Jin's life.
What do you have against my family...
that you're going after all the men in my life?
His death isn't on me!
He killed himself because he couldn't handle his own emotions!
What did you just say?
He killed himself because he couldn't handle his own emotions?
Then...
are you saying I told him to kill himself?
- Is that it? - How dare you.
Fine.
- Let's fight to the death! - Let go.
- Get away from me. - Mum.
Did you just push her?
She started it.
Hey.
What are you doing? Let go of me.
I was born on a poultry farm,
and I've lived around chicken for 45 years.
I know a thing or two about plucking feathers.
I'll show you what I can do.
Don't just stand there.
Hurry up and call the police.
- Sure thing. Bye. - Let go.
- Let go of me. - Go on.
- My goodness. - Ms Choi.
How much hair should she lose to make you feel better?
- Give me a number. - What for?
Pull it all out.
Okay. A woman who stole someone else's husband...
needs a really good lesson.
Gosh, my back.
The phone has been turned off.
- Please leave... - Why won't she pick up?
Something bad is happening for sure.
Why should she get involved in Dong Jin's business?
You're early.
Did you get to Anseong and back safely?
Yes, thanks to you.
- Would you like some coffee? - That would be nice.
- I won't be long. - Okay.
Dong Jin? It's me, Sam Do.
I have bad news. They heard about your divorce.
Your mum, Dong Sook and my wife went to your wife's home.
Divorce?
Here you go.
I don't care if we were once in-laws.
I'll see a doctor about my injuries and sue you.
All three of you are going to jail. Look forward to that.
They did nothing wrong.
I brought them here.
If you want to sue someone, sue me.
You're too old to do time.
I pulled out all that hair, and I tripped her up.
You can sue me.
You did nothing wrong. I'm the one who started it.
This is all so touching.
You three can all go to prison together.
- Dong Jin. - Dong Jin.
What are you doing here?
I won't let this slide.
I will get Lawyer Choi to sue them all.
Be prepared.
She's overreacting.
We didn't do that much damage.
What should we do now? We made things worse for you.
- I didn't think this through. - Get in the car.
Don't cry, Mum. You'll make Dong Jin feel bad.
I'm a useless mum.
Don't blame yourself.
It wasn't your fault.
Are you saying it's my fault, then?
You should've just scared her, not pull out a chunk of hair.
She even hurt her back.
You can't say that.
You told me to pull out all her hair.
I was angry at the time.
You shouldn't have taken me seriously.
I spent all my energy to fight on your behalf.
But instead of a thank-you, you blame me for the mess?
We shouldn't have brought you along.
You fought like an MMA fighter. That was so crass.
- Stop saying I'm crass. - Will you two be quiet?
Dong Jin's patient and thoughtful.
If he decided to get divorced,
it means he went through enough to justify it.
He took as much as he could handle,
and when he'd finally had enough, he gave in.
Isn't that what you did?
I'm fine, Mum.
Mum, here.
(Wolgyesu Tailor Shop)
If we sew it like this instead of using glue...
like ready-made suits do, it fits and moves more naturally.
And the suit doesn't lose its shape after time.
Just like us humans, clothes also have to breathe.
Doing this helps air circulate through the fabric...
and makes it become more resistant to abrasion.
I see.
A good suit has to feel three-dimensional.
Using the padding stitch technique like this...
adds a three-dimensional feel to the suit,
which makes the lapel look and feel fuller.
Dong Jin.
Hello.
Hey, how did it go?
I just dropped Mum, Dong Sook and Sun Nyeo off at our place.
Let's step out for a quick chat, Sam Do.
What? There are no customers right now, so we can talk here.
- Let's go somewhere quiet. - All right.
I'll be back shortly.
Okay.
Is he worried that I'd eavesdrop on their conversation?
I have no interest in your business, okay?
How is Ms Choi holding up?
She's upset, of course.
Frankly, I think about getting divorced a dozen times a day.
But as you know, getting divorced isn't that simple.
Consider all factors carefully.
To her, I was...
never really a husband.
I think she just...
thought of me as her guardian or butler.
No, you're being too cynical. She'd never think of you as...
I can't tell you all the details,
but she's made me feel that way throughout our marriage.
It sounds like you're exhausted.
Yes.
I want to be free now.
I want to free myself from my greed and ambition...
and leave her in order to find peace of mind.
All right.
I actually...
met up with my dad last night.
You met up with Mr Lee? How?
I managed to talk to him on the phone, and we met up.
Then...
you should've brought him home.
You know how stubborn he is. I couldn't persuade him.
Then you should've called me!
Is he okay?
Please keep my illness a secret...
until I come home and tell them myself.
Do me a favour.
Yes. He seemed to be doing all right.
He was happy to hear about you working as a tailor again.
He told me to tell you how grateful he is.
Goodness.
I should've been there to see him. I'm sad I wasn't there.
I was surprised because he looked so happy.
I've never seen him looking that content.
He said he's been wandering around and working without a proper home,
so I thought he'd be extremely exhausted, but I was wrong.
What exactly do suits...
mean to him?
Mr Lee...
doesn't just make suits.
He builds lives.
I'm not sure how you view him, but he isn't...
a mere tailor. He's a philosopher.
That's what I think at least.
Is making suits...
that much of a grand job? You're comparing it to building lives.
I'm not sure if I can say that it's grand,
but the job certainly makes you happy.
I'll be sure to become a tailor again in my next life.
If I work at the tailor shop,
will I...
also be happy?
Dong Jin, you want to work at the tailor shop?
People swarmed over like bees yesterday,
but today was pretty horrible.
I didn't even make enough for a burger.
Mr Kang, please do something.
What do you want me to do?
I've been out of that industry for over a decade.
Right, so come back and work with me.
We used to be such a great team.
After you fell hard for that woman and ran away to the States,
our agency had to pay the penalties for breaking all the contracts.
You know all that.
How can you say that we were a great team?
Back then, I was...
I was immature then.
That will never happen again.
I'll make sure there are no scandals whatsoever. So please...
I'll give you a call when I hear of any events you can perform at.
I have to go. Bye.
Mr Kang. Hey.
Shall I look for a new agency?
The job I did yesterday was sweet.
What was it?
What was his name?
He used to be a famous singer. I went to his busking performance...
and screamed and cheered for him for an hour.
I got 50 dollars for it.
- My goodness. That's a sweet job. - That woman...
came to my performance yesterday.
How was the performance?
It was horrible.
Was it that bad? What's his name?
What was it?
I think it was a two-syllable name.
Sung Jun.
Yes, Sung Jun.
My goodness!
Who gave you that job?
I've been neglecting my store because of Jun.
I guess that's why I don't see a single soul here.
Shall I run some sort of promotional events?
Hi, Jun! What brings you here at this hour?
Is your performance already done?
Do you think I'm a joke?
What are you talking about?
I heard that you paid those people who came...
to watch my performance.
- Who said such nonsense? - I heard it...
directly from one of the people you hired, so don't even try to lie.
Well... I'm sorry, Jun.
I didn't mean to upset you or anything.
I couldn't bear to watch you performing with no audience.
I just wanted to cheer you up...
Why do you make me feel so pathetic?
Why do you feel pathetic? I wanted to encourage you.
I'm...
not pathetic enough to need your pity.
This is a warning!
Do not meddle in my business ever again.
Got it?
Jun, Jun!
Hello.
I knew it. I was wondering what was going on.
I was a fool to let myself get all excited about it.
Excuse me.
Aren't you...
Mr Sung Jun?
Who are you?
I'm the executive director of Hyesung Entertainment, Oh Chang Soo.
Why did you want to speak to me?
Mr Oh really wanted to meet with you after hearing that you're back...
in Korea now working on making a comeback.
We heard that your office is in this area,
so we've been looking all over for you for a few days now.
Then are you...
here to offer me a contract?
Of course.
You took the music scene by storm as soon as you debuted 15 years ago.
Then you disappeared like the wind at the peak of your prime.
I was a huge fan of yours, so it utterly broke my heart.
That was the biggest mistake of my life.
You're back now, and you want to make a comeback.
I have to be the one producing your new album.
It's very nice to meet you.
The payment for your student loan is overdue.
If you fail to make the payment, it could affect your credit rating.
- Please make the payment soon. - It's overdue?
Is it already past the deadline?
So you'd like to see if the deadline can be extended?
Yes. I haven't found a job yet.
But I see that you've already extended it once.
Only one deadline extension is allowed per person,
so it cannot be extended further.
I'm unable to pay the interest and the minimum payment right now.
Is there anything you can do?
I'm sorry.
What now?
You're so cold.
We haven't talked in a while. Can you be a little warmer towards me?
Hang up unless you have something specific to talk about.
No! Don't hang up. I'm calling you for a reason.
- What is it? - I'm off tomorrow.
Let's go to the movies together.
I'll buy lunch as well as popcorn.
I'm busy.
Why are you always so busy when you don't even have a job?
Unemployed people are busier than employed ones. Bye.
Wait, Tae Yang. Don't hang up. Hello? Tae Yang?
I guess he's still trying to be hard to get.
Gosh, you startled me. Did you just eavesdrop on my conversation?
It wasn't intentional.
I was walking here and overheard it.
So is he still being hard to get?
He's being so difficult.
Who is he? How can he treat someone like you that way?
It even sounded like he's jobless right now.
So many young people are unemployed these days.
He's doing his best to get a job, so I'm sure he'll land one soon.
Had I known that he'd stay unemployed for this long,
I would've helped him when you asked me.
No thanks.
What's the point in saying that now?
Whatever.
How's your grandmother?
She took some pills and is resting.
How's your mother? Did she go to the hospital?
She got checked out, but there's nothing wrong with her.
She exaggerates a lot.
By the way, if my sister and your uncle get a divorce,
does that mean our friendship is over?
- What friendship? - What?
I thought we became really close.
Was I wrong?
I don't think we're that close,
but I won't hold grudges even if they get divorced.
- That's a relief. - Let's go back in now.
Sit here.
I told you not to take a picture since I don't have makeup on.
- Why did you take a picture? - I'm sorry.
I have a friend who wants to be an announcer.
You're her role model.
- She wanted a picture of you. - That's none of my business.
That's a violation of my portrait rights.
Aren't you supposed to know that?
- She's the person who tripped me. - That's her.
Choi Ji Yun of KBC. She's so rude.
I'm sorry.
It's her first day at work.
She wasn't aware of our system. It was an honest mistake.
I'll knock some sense into her.
That won't cut it.
Who would come to this place if you invade people's privacy like this?
I'm sorry. It won't happen again.
I'm really sorry.
This is common sense. This isn't some local barber shop.
What?
Hey, you. She says it's her first day at work.
It was an honest mistake. What's the big deal?
Come on.
If you don't want people taking pictures of you, quit your job.
- Then nobody will be interested. - What did you say?
You look the same with or without makeup anyway.
Stop making a fuss.
- Are you done talking? - Yes.
- Did you want to hear some more? - Excuse me?
- I have to shampoo my hair. - This way.
What a crazy woman.
(Min Hyo Sang)
- It's me. - I'm really sorry.
I can't make it tonight.
Why not? Is there trouble at the office?
My mum's sick. I think I should go see her.
Is it serious?
It's not that serious.
I think she strained her back.
It's okay with me. Look after your mother.
Okay, call me later.
I thought he was going to propose to me tonight.
Come to think of it, why is he always talking about his mum?
Is he some kind of mummy's boy?
You're here.
You should go to the hospital. What are you doing here?
Doctor Kim said I'll be okay if I rest for a few days.
How can Ms Choi be like that?
She even splashed juice on you last time.
We need to teach her a lesson. Let's sue her.
We're in-laws after all. That would be too much.
Hyo Joo and Dong Jin are about to get a divorce. You're not in-laws.
Even then, once in-laws are forever in-laws.
You're weird.
Why are you always so scared of Ms Choi?
- What does she have on you? - There's no such thing.
Do I look like someone who lets people do that to me?
My back.
Oh, my head.
- They didn't call you, did they? - Who?
You know who.
- I'm talking about Ms Ko. - Why?
Are you afraid she might sue you?
She can't sue me.
After everything she's done to me.
Where is Dong Jin during all this?
- Call him up. - Fine.
Hey, Dong Sook. How's Mum?
What do you think? She's sick in bed.
- Where are you? - I'm at a hotel.
- He says he's at a hotel. - What's he doing there?
Give me the phone.
- It's your mother. - Hey, Mum.
I was about to call you.
Why are you at a hotel when you can stay at home?
You should come to me.
I'll make doenjang jjigae, your favourite.
Hurry back home.
Why would you eat outside?
Why aren't you saying anything?
- Dong Jin. - Yes, Mum. I'll be on my way.
Okay, hurry back. I'll be waiting for you.
Dong Jin is better than pills. He got that headband off.
Go to the grocery store and get me some chadolbagi.
What do you need chadolbagi for?
Dong Jin loves chadolbagi in his doenjang jjigae.
Don't get frozen chadolbagi. Get the highest quality ones.
Sung Jun is probably drinking by himself.
- Hurry, Dong Sook. - I'm going.
The fabric is the flesh.
The thread is the bone.
Then if you want to make clothes that fit the body perfectly,
you'll need to do a lot of needlework, right?
- Of course. - That's why it has to be handmade.
It's called a bespoke suit. It's custom-made.
It fits perfectly and feels better when you put it on.
It requires much more skills and effort than ready-made clothes.
In that sense,
the handmade suits of Wolgyesu Tailor Shop...
are equivalent to pure gold.
It's not 14K or 18K.
I couldn't stop thinking that...
your explanation is so on point.
You won't get this lecture from anywhere else.
I know that.
- Welcome. - Hello.
I'm here.
Great going.
Why would you make things worse for Ms Choi and Dong Sook?
She made the late chairman's wife suffer by taking her place.
I had to give her a piece of my mind as a woman.
What does it have to do with you whether she suffers or not?
- I'm sorry. - You're here.
What's wrong with your forehead?
I got a minor injury.
Your temper always gets you in trouble.
Eun Sook's even thinking about filing a lawsuit because of you.
She's just playing her cards.
- It's all bluff. - Don't talk back to me.
Don't do this in front of them. This is embarrassing.
I can't even be embarrassed any more.
- Take it easy. - Yes, calm down.
Send them home.
- Good job, everyone. - We'll get going.
- Let's go. - I'll see you tomorrow.
I forgot to tell you something.
Starting next week,
Dong Jin will start working here.
- Dong Jin? - Dong Jin?
You can't be serious.
Isn't he really smart and well-off?
Why would he work at a tailor shop?
This is wrong. This can't be happening.
He didn't even listen to Mr Lee when he wanted him to take over.
Mr Lee isn't even here right now.
Why would he start this now?
This is wrong. This can't be happening.
I'm sure of it.
It came as a surprise to me, too.
He must have changed his mind after Mr Lee ran away from home.
- He shouldn't have. - What's that?
Never mind, it's nothing.
Why does everything go so wrong?
Hey, it's me.
I knew you were cold-hearted,
but not as much as this.
How could you sign the divorce paper right away like that?
You're the one who always talked about getting a divorce.
Where are you right now? Come here at once.
Let's talk later. I'm on my way to see my mum.
I'm sure he's going to boss me around...
once he starts working there. What should I do?
It's a thief!
- Why don't you just stop? - What?
You're selfish, but you pretend to be naive in front of others.
You hypocrite.
Gargoyle Eyes!
Why that...
Even if I was angry, I still shouldn't have called him that.
You made a big mistake, Na Yun Shil.
You fool.
- Sir! - Help!
Move!
- Here! - Sir!
But still, he won't be mean to his life-saver, will he?
Are you in there?
Why don't you pick up the phone?
Were you going to eat ramyeon?
I was bringing you saengtae jjigae, but you didn't answer.
- So I just came in. - The phone didn't ring.
Oh, my bag.
I must have left it at work.
Where's your head at? Take this.
- Thank you. - Bye.
I'll have to go back to the shop.
Here it is.
Why is that down there?
What's he doing here?
(Wolgyesu Tailor Shop)
Mum's waiting for me. Get straight to the point.
You hurt my pride.
I've been thinking.
I know I'm the one who said we should get a divorce first,
but you signed the paper right on the spot.
It makes me feel like...
I'm the one who got divorced, not you.
What did you expect?
Did you think I would beg you not to divorce me?
I didn't expect you to beg.
But I didn't know you would end things so easily.
Am I no use to you...
now that my dad died?
Is that it?
Is that why you were willing to give up so easily?
I did everything you wanted me to.
It looks like that still hurt your pride.
How dare you hurt my pride.
If your pride is precious,
you should know that the same goes for everyone else.
People who care about their pride...
tend to only care about themselves and no one else.
Sure, I used to be like that, too.
But I don't want to live like that any more.
I didn't have the luxury to care for your pride.
I'm sorry if I hurt you.
You seem drunk, so go home.
You horrible man.
You cruel man.
Get it together.
Listen to me carefully.
You being like this won't work any more.
We're strangers now.
We have nothing to do with each other now, okay?
Hey.
Hey, wake up.
Hyo Joo.
Who's there?
It's me.
What are you doing here?
- I can explain. - Have you been eavesdropping?
No, that's not it.
Excuse me for a second.
Hey, Tae Yang.
I'll call you back later.
Yes, I'm sorry.
Why were you down there and listening to our conversation?
What do you think you're doing?
I know this can be misleading,
but I didn't do it on purpose.
I left my bag at work.
I just happened to be at the wrong place at a wrong time.
I know it's none of my business.
Why would I eavesdrop on a domestic dispute?
I'm not an idle person like that.
Whatever. I really don't like you.
Drive safely.
I just can't stop getting myself in trouble, can I?
Why am I like this?
Oh, I almost forgot.
Did I call you at a bad time?
Not at all. I just had to talk to someone.
- Where are you? - I'm at work.
Hey, Yun Shil.
What?
Don't forget to eat.
I was just calling to check on you.
It's been long since I heard your voice.
Okay, get some rest.
I didn't even pay her back from last time.
I can't ask for more money.
Everyone, get back to work. Start moving.
Mr Kang. Go back to your station.
Yes, on my way.
The traffic is so heavy. I'm on my way.
You brat.
Aren't you supposed to drive me to the hospital...
and nurse me by my side?
What are you doing out?
Stop exaggerating.
What did you say?
Okay, relax. I'm going.
Looks like something's under construction.
You want to work at the tailor shop?
What are you talking about?
I thought hard about the decision.
Please allow it, Mum.
I'm guessing you're doing this...
because you feel responsible for your dad leaving home.
But it's not your fault.
It had nothing to do with you. He did it on his own will.
It's not because of him.
I want to be happy.
What are you saying?
I've been working non-stop for a successful career.
But I'm a mess now.
I'm tired of competition and deception.
I don't want to abandon my family for money.
I'm tired of all that. I can't do it any more.
But still, you're my perfect son.
On top of getting a divorce,
you're going to make suits for the rest of your life?
That's not how I raised you.
I can't allow it.
Don't you think you should go in there, Dong Sook?
Leave them be. They need some alone time together.
Today just isn't the day for Mum.
I am here.
Susanna.
Why did he get so drunk?
Sung Jun.
Oh, gosh.
- Susanna. - It's not here.
- Not here. - Oh, I see.
What's wrong with him this time?
He must've gotten free drinks from somewhere.
Here I am.
- My precious - I'll take that.
Lay down.
Susanna
I guess he drank a lot because of me.
Poor Sung Jun.
Oh, my.
How did he end up like this?
Eat it while it's still hot.
You may have your reasons,
but you working at the tailor shop is the last thing I want.
I still can't get over the fact that my son got a divorce.
How can you even tell me that you want to work at the tailor shop?
Don't you pity me?
- I'm sorry. - Then don't do it.
Eat up.
Slow down. You don't want it going down the wrong pipe.
I haven't had a meal in peace for so long.
Is that how you've been all along?
I should have come to you sooner.
I was stupid not to.
Eat up.
Eat.
(Wolgyesu Tailor Shop)
Dong Jin will work here starting tomorrow.
He'll be the owner of the tailor shop...
until Mr Lee comes back.
(Wolgyesu Tailor Shop)
Congratulations on your first day at work, Mr Lee.
Is it too obvious?
Welcome to Wolgyesu Tailor Shop.
Oh, no.
My gosh, what do I do?
(Wolgyesu Tailor Shop)
Congratulations, congratulations
Congratulations on your first day at work, Mr Lee
Welcome, Mr Lee.
What is this?
I'm congratulating you on your first day at work.
I don't need it.
- Listen to me carefully. - Yes, Mr Lee.
As of today, you're fired.
What?
(The Gentlemen of Wolgyesu Tailor Shop)
Why would you fire Yun Shil? She's doing just fine.
I have no idea what's going on.
Do you want me to call Ms Choi?
You have some guts.
How dare you sue me.
I'm going to do this by law, so be prepared.
Sam Do won't forgive me for this. What should I do?
What did you do this time?
Is he really going to work at the tailor shop?
You need a wife to get your coat, not your mother.
I'm figuring out how to make myself happy.
Have some patience, Mum.