[Episode 13]
Oh..!
Ooooooh...!
Ah!
Hey.
Are you asleep?
Why that annoying...
Whatever.
Why is she so heavy?
Sir!
You can't just go.
You need to pay first.
Excuse me?
Here!
Ma'am!
Yun Shil, please wake up.
You need to tell me where
you live so I can take you.
She's just incredible.
My back.
Hold on.
I think I heard that she
lives in Ms Geum's building.
(Ms Geum)
The phone has been turned off...
Why is her phone off?
Hey.
Hey, Yun Shil. Wake up.
She isn't asleep. She's
practically passed out.
Darn it.
She looks skinny.
Why is she so heavy?
Is something wrong with her?
The family will think something is up.
Hey, Yun Shil.
Wake up, will you?
You're pretending to be asleep
to mess with me, aren't you?
Wake up, will you?
This is insane.
I'm home.
Why are you out here in the cold?
I'm too angry to sit inside.
Why? What happened now?
Let's talk inside.
I saw your wife this afternoon.
Why did you do that?
I wanted to talk some sense into her,
but she wouldn't listen at
all and lashed out at me.
What do you mean?
She says you're a losing lottery ticket.
She bought you thinking
you'd win the jackpot,
but you turned out to be a bust.
She said she relied on you,
but you disappointed her,
so she can't live with you.
That wicked brat.
She loses all rationality
when she doesn't get her way.
I realised...
my baby must have suffered all these years,
putting up with that wicked temper.
My heart was aching and
breaking all day long.
It's all in the past.
A spouse...
is supposed to be a person
you can depend on for life.
If you don't get along,
you should break up.
I'm not that unreasonable,
so do what you want.
Okay?
Okay. I'm sorry for worrying you.
You make me write an apology
letter and bring you honey water.
You're treating me like a slave.
You're out of control.
I drank because...
I thought I'd cause trouble if I didn't.
So stop nagging, little Sam Do.
Little Sam Do?
I'm your husband, not a kid.
You've totally lost it.
Tell me the truth.
If I go to jail,
will you remain true to
me until I get released?
You'll pretend to work out
and show off your muscles,
show your dashing smile,
flirt and date around, won't you?
I'm so stunned, I'm speechless.
See? You can't answer me.
If I end up in jail,
you'll jump for joy and thank the stars.
Right? Answer me.
- First, go to jail.
- What?
That way, I can cheat or get
married again or something.
I know you can't trust anyone,
but how can you do this to me?
I've lived for you...
and sold the chicken shop
and followed you to Seoul.
How could you do this to me?
My gosh. My gosh. My gosh.
You pathetic woman.
If you're drunk, go to sleep.
Stop being stupid.
Then swear to me...
that you'll be true to
me until I get released.
Fine, I will.
I, Sam Do, will be true to Sun Nyeo
until the day I die. Happy now?
No flexing your muscles.
You're so annoying. Fine! I won't!
You'd better...
- You'd better not.
- My goodness.
What a mess.
I'm going to change first.
It's too hot.
He's struggling with writing
music and I'm of no help.
I'm sorry.
I should've gotten a fat
alimony when I got divorced.
How is she?
She just fell asleep.
She must be very angry at Mum and me.
In her opinion, she thought she
was family and fought for you,
so she's shocked at what happened.
I've talked to Mum several times
about the written apology,
but she flipped out.
Of course. Think of her age.
Eun Sook was out of line.
What should we do?
I heard she has to go to the police
for questioning in two days.
We'll think of something.
Anyway, why did Leather
Jacket get plastered?
He's looking for investors
to release his second album,
but it must be difficult.
Let me say this just in case,
but don't you fall for his
tricks and invest in him.
Come on. He isn't like that.
Hey. Money lies, not people.
Don't get soft and fall
for punks like that.
I don't even have money to
pay rent for the store.
Stop worrying.
I'm leaving.
Heed my warning, okay?
That punk.
Look at him sleeping.
He's so annoying.
Hey.
Yun Shil.
Hey, Bucket Head!
I can't leave her here all night.
What should I do?
Darn it.
You're home late.
- Did you eat?
- I did.
How's working at the tailor shop?
It's just the beginning.
You must be tired. Wash up and go to bed.
Dong Sook.
I was expecting a package today.
A package? Nothing came.
I'm sure I told them to leave
it in front of the gate.
I didn't see anything.
I'll check.
Okay.
Oh, my gosh. Oh, my gosh.
What's wrong with her?
Yun Shil. Yun Shil. Wake up. Yun Shil!
- Dong Jin!
- Yes?
Look who this is.
Isn't this Yun Shil?
Yes. I came to look for the package,
and she was passed out here.
What? Why that...
Let's bring her inside.
Okay.
Dong Sook. Get some drinks.
- What?
- It seems like...
this is a night for the women
of our family to drink.
We should have some, too.
I'm really going to get the drinks.
Why did Yun Shil drink so much?
Her husband is in prison, and she
was fired from the tailor shop.
Who can blame her for being upset?
You're right.
Why did you fire someone
who was working hard?
You were completely in the wrong, Dong Jin.
If she got drunk, why didn't she go home?
Why was she passed out
in front of our gate?
I know.
I'm tired, so I'm going to bed.
- Good night.
- Okay.
She says you're a losing lottery ticket.
She bought you thinking
you'd win the jackpot,
but you turned out to be a bust.
A losing lottery ticket?
Hi.
Don't forget we're going to court tomorrow.
What? Did you think I'd forget?
Just in case.
I was worried that you'd be
focused in making suits...
that you might lose track of time.
That's why I wanted to check.
Don't worry.
I've been waiting for this day
too, almost as much as you have.
- What?
- I'll see you in court.
"I've been waiting for this day
too, almost as much as you have"?
Jerk.
Hey, Miss!
Miss!
What is it? Is something wrong?
Send these to my in-laws.
Mr Lee's clothes? All of them?
Don't leave a single
underwear or sock behind.
Get rid of them all.
Look at that temper.
What a brat.
That jerk.
Hyo Won, are you still sleeping?
Goodness.
She must have been tired.
She's asleep already.
I wonder which one is his girlfriend.
Then who was the person that
was with me during surgery?
Are you Mr Kang Tae Yang?
Yes, I am.
Hello. We're from Hangook Life.
How are you feeling?
I'm better.
The accident was caused by
one of our policy holders,
so we came to resolve the matter.
I will cut through the chase.
If you decide to take this to court,
it will cost both you and
us a lot of time and money.
Why don't you take our settlement
offer and settle out of court?
(Hangook Life)
Sorry.
I forgot I had urgent work to take care of.
I'm okay. You should get to work.
Okay.
You know where she lives, right?
Take her home.
Yes, Sir.
I'll call later.
It's really big.
Just how big it it?
Shall we go?
Okay.
Oh, my gosh. Oh, my gosh.
I must have lost my mind.
Who is it?
- I'm sorry.
- Why are you in here?
Are you insane?
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
Dong Jin, are you up?
- Yes, Mother.
- I'm coming in.
What do I do?
I made kale and apple juice. Have some.
I will. Please put it there.
I'm so tired. Let me sleep
for five more minutes.
Okay. Sure.
But...
why do you look like that?
- What?
- You look yellow.
What's wrong?
What? Oh, actually,
it's probably because I didn't sleep well.
Sure. How could you sleep well?
Drink this, okay?
I will.
I'm so, so sorry. Please
forgive me this once.
If my mother saw you in here,
she would've had a stroke.
I know. But I didn't do it on purpose.
I was just too drunk and...
I have no excuse.
Bad things happen when we're together,
so let's not meet as
much as possible, okay?
Okay. Okay, Of course.
Get out. Now.
But...
are you the one who brought
me here, Gargoyle...
Mr Lee?
I blacked out last night,
so I don't remember at all.
Why would I bring you home?
Stop the nonsense and get out.
Okay. I'll get out. I'm leaving.
You're sure...
you didn't carry me here, right?
I have better things to do.
Stop the nonsense and get out of my sight.
I can't like her even if I try.
I'm going to lose my mind.
Hi, Dong Sook.
Where are you? Mum's looking
for you to have breakfast.
I'm on my way home.
I'm really sorry for last night.
Okay.
Yun Shil is on her way home.
I made bean sprout soup to help with
the hangover. Why did she leave?
She has to make deliveries
and she probably felt bad...
and rushed out.
What is there to feel bad about?
She's family.
But Mum,
may I bring some of the
soup upstairs as well?
Why?
Do you want to bring it to Sung Jun?
Mum!
No, that's not it.
You were quite a sight last night.
The way you were helping that
drunk Leather Jacket home...
You practically looked like his wife.
You can never be with him. Never.
It's not like that.
I'm just helping him as a good neighbour.
You said it. You're just
neighbours, got it?
If you change your tune later,
I'll shave your head...
and put a leash around your
neck and send you to a temple.
The soup is so good.
What a sight.
What are you doing?
What else? I'm setting the table.
Did you make the bean sprout soup yourself?
No. Ms Choi sent it up...
for the brother and sister.
- Brother and sister?
Don't you remember?
I heard you decided to
become brother and sister.
- Us?
- You were arm-in-arm,
singing at the top of your lungs
walking through the neighbourhood...
about Susanna's handkerchief
or foot towel or something.
What's Susanna's foot towel?
Not foot towel. Handkerchief.
I taught you last night.
I need to get to work,
so the brother and sister can eat together.
We should eat first.
Susanna
I will be
By your side
I won't let you go
Let us
You're making me lose my appetite.
Sung Jun, the Best New
Artist of the year 2000.
Rock ballad's Terius with
outstanding singing skills...
and a heart-wrenching voice.
You'll hit the jackpot if you invest in me.
Look.
I'm going to the police
tomorrow for questioning...
and am going to jail. I can't invest.
Come on, Sun Nyeo, my sister.
Why am I your sister?
He said we became
brother-and-sister last night.
I don't remember any of
that, so eat quietly.
I won't charge you for breakfast today.
Come on.
Okay, I'll eat.
Darn it.
That tastes good.
Madam will be right out.
What a palace.
Hi.
How long has it been, Sam Do?
I'm sorry for not keeping in touch.
Oh, my gosh. How did you
know I like cosmos flowers?
How could I not? We spent
so many years together.
Whenever the tailor shop was closed,
you and I would take the train...
and walk along the tracks
surrounded by cosmos flowers.
That's right. We did.
But Eun Sook,
do you...
eat preservatives instead of rice?
- What?
- How are you exactly the same?
You're so good at saying
things you don't mean.
What do you mean?
You know I never lie, even
with a gun to my head.
Have a seat.
What would you like to drink?
Oh, my gosh.
What are you doing?
Please save a life. Please forgive my wife.
Because I'm an incompetent husband,
she had to provide for us
ever since she was young...
and ran a fried chicken place.
She has a tender heart inside,
but she became rough and stubborn
because of her loser husband.
She must have a lot of rage in her.
She gets angry easily...
and acts with her fist first.
Sam Do, you poor thing.
To be honest,
I wasn't going to report her to the police.
I got angry because Ms Choi kept
disrespecting me and yelling at me.
So let's forget about the
written apology. Okay?
But...
I have one condition.
A condition?
After what she did,
of course, she couldn't come back here.
Is anyone in?
Welcome to Wolgyesu. How may I help you?
Is Yun Shil not in yet?
Yun Shil left the company not long ago.
There she is. Yun Shil!
- Ma'am.
- Hi.
What brings you here?
My grandson tore his uniform
while playing soccer.
I need to stitch it up for
him, but I just can't see.
Would you use that sewing machine
and stitch it up for me?
Of course, I will.
May I use the sewing machine?
It'll only take three minutes.
Fine.
- It's all done.
- Let me see.
My goodness.
You can't tell at all.
Here, take this.
It's okay. I can't charge you for that.
I just feel bad, that's all.
It's okay, so let's go.
Okay. Let's go.
Sir.
You'll be blessed.
Bring these to your grandson.
It's okay. You wouldn't even let
me pay for fixing the pants.
He needs to eat well to
have energy to study hard.
You're always so nice. I feel so bad.
It's because you remind me
of my late grandmother.
It's because I want to, so don't feel bad.
- Thank you.
- That busy-body.
- My gosh.
- Drink them with your grandson.
Okay. Thank you very much.
Great.
My gosh.
Thank you. Come again.
Hi, Tae Yang. How do you feel?
Hold on.
Here you go.
Thank you for settling.
We've given you the most we could.
- We wish you a quick recovery.
- Thank you.
Sorry. I had some visitors.
Who? Ji Yun?
Why would she come here?
But Yun Shil,
I'm rich now.
What do you mean?
I can pay off my student
loan and two months rent.
What are you talking about?
Did money fall from the sky?
The insurance company
gave me money to settle.
Oh, so that's what you mean.
"Who knew it was so easy to make money?"
"One more accident, and I can
have money in my bank account."
I keep having bad thoughts like this.
I'm so pathetic.
(Balance 10,385 dollars)
- What are you hiding?
- Nothing.
Don't lie. Give it to me.
- Stop.
- Give it.
Isn't this a bank book?
My savings matured.
- How much?
- 10,000 dollars!
Oh, my gosh.
I'm so proud of my daughter.
I'm going to use this as seed money...
and open my own hair salon in 10 years.
You're better than your mum.
How did I give birth to someone so smart?
You cute thing.
Stop that, will you?
I just want to help my sister.
Don't stop me.
You can kiss up all you want.
You won't get a penny from me,
so don't waste your time.
If you're locked up in prison, you
won't be able make money at all.
Just invest 50,000 dollars in me,
and I'll multiply that by 10.
By the time you're released, your 50,000...
- would've jumped to 500,000.
- Seriously...
Are you trying to anger me?
What?
- What are you doing?
- Are you?
- Are you trying to anger me?
- Why are you throwing salt at me?
I'm angry as it is.
What are you doing?
What's the ruckus?
Oh, my goodness.
Why are you making so much kimchi?
Sam Do needs to eat...
while I'm in prison.
You're going overboard.
You haven't even undergone
police investigation.
Why do you keep talking about jail?
It's easy for you to say.
Why are you doing that to yourself?
I told you not to worry.
Sure. Sure.
While I'm eating cold rice
in a cold prison cell,
you and Dong Sook can
sit in your warm room,
eating hot rice and...
the kimchi that I make.
Knock yourselves out.
Why that...
I'm going to work.
Don't you dare go near this man.
Okay.
I'll see you later, Grandma.
- Okay.
- Bye.
Are you working the afternoon shift today?
She is so cold. She isn't
like her mum at all.
Why are you home at this hour?
Ms Choi, I need to talk
to you about something.
Let's go in.
Sit down and continue what you were doing.
Let's make kimchi.
Fine. I'll stop.
I left the stove on.
- Is it ready?
- Yes, of course.
You wait here.
- Let's go.
- Yes, Ma'am.
Are you okay?
Be careful.
Oh, my gosh. Look who's here?
What brings you here, Madam?
What else?
Sam Do came this morning
and begged profusely,
so I came for his sake.
My husband went to see you?
You got yourself a good husband.
- Where's Ms Choi?
- She's in her room.
Ms Choi! Please come out! You
have an important guest!
Hi, Eun Sook.
Is she inside?
Yes. Come in.
- Let's go in.
- Yes, Ma'am.
Oh, my goodness.
Hold on.
Careful.
You went to see her?
I had no idea.
You're the best.
I'll grill up some eel tonight.
You crazy woman. This is
no time to talk about eel.
Hi, Eun Sook.
Long time no see.
I'm here.
Mum, Eun Sook is here.
Sit down.
Who is he?
He's our lawyer.
It's not some big case. Why
did you bring your lawyer?
Because of...
your history together, Ms Ko has offered...
to drop the charges against
Ms Bok Sun Nyeo...
if Ms Choi would write an
affidavit with an apology.
Then you won't need to
be punished by the law.
Really?
It went from a written
apology to an affidavit.
Thank you so much.
You are very lucky.
It is because Ms Ko is
very kind and giving...
that you're getting off this easily.
Why don't you open your eyes?
Yes, Mum.
Just write it for her
and put an end to this.
Yes, Ms Choi. You shouldn't
drag these things out.
Stop it.
I can't write an affidavit and
offer it to you at my age.
I'll say it, so you can write it down...
or listen as you wish.
This isn't what was promised.
She's right, Eun Sook.
Let's end it nicely here.
It'll be bad for both parties
if you drag this out.
Okay. Fine.
But everyone leave other than Mr Choi.
That's not right.
One of us should remain, too.
Then Sam Do, you stay.
Hi, Dong Jin.
It's Dong Sook. Can you come home?
Why? What is it now?
Your mother-in-law... I
mean, Eun Sook is here.
She wants Mum to write an affidavit.
I think you should be here.
Okay. I'll be right there.
I need to go home for a bit.
Okay.
Ever since Mr Lee left home,
they've never been at peace.
You just have to read this
as sincerely as you can.
I'll begin recording.
Wait, wait, wait.
I can't go ahead with it. I
can't put Ms Choi through this.
Just throw my wife in prison
if that's what's needed.
Let's end it all right here.
This is nothing.
It's fine. I'll read and be over with it.
Apologise sincerely.
Why is this so complicated?
"I, Choi Gok Ji,"
"on October 8, 2016,"
"apologise sincerely to Ko Eun Sook..."
"for the assault I've caused."
"I swear that nothing of the
sort will happen again."
(Choi Gok Ji)
Thank you, Ms Choi.
Is that it?
- No. Promise me one more thing.
- What?
Mr Choi and Sam Do, can you excuse us?
Yes, Ma'am.
What happened?
She signed the affidavit.
They wanted to talk in private.
I'd hide in a hole if there was one.
Is there one?
I want you to...
promise me that you'll never mention...
Gok Nam again.
What did you say?
I turn 60 soon, and my son's
old enough to get married.
You scream at me because of
what happened years ago.
It's stressing me out.
How can you say that...
when my only brother died
early because of you?
I told you time and again
that it wasn't my fault.
He was the one who waited
outside my room so late...
and got in an accident.
Just because you can speak, doesn't
mean you can say nonsense.
Then...
shall I delete this?
Hello again. It's been a while.
What are you doing here?
Why are you here?
That's the home of the CEO of
the tailor store I work at.
Oh, I see.
I was just there on business.
Do you deliver milk?
It's almost over. Hang in
there just a bit longer.
Your husband will be sentenced soon.
Yes.
Mr Min Hyo Sang is doing all
he can for your husband.
He'll only get about six months.
The prosecutor won't appeal.
Once your husband's released,
he'll become a store manager.
You won't have to deliver milk...
and people will call you
"Ma'am" out of respect.
So that was it.
You gave me an expensive
handbag with a wad of cheques,
and you bribed Gi Pyo with the
prospect of owning a store.
How could you say that?
We didn't bribe anyone.
Why is Mr Min doing so much
to help my husband then?
- That's because...
- You wanted my boss' son gone.
Do you think I don't know
that's why you used him?
You people are really rotten.
Gi Pyo broke the law, so
he deserves to do time,
but my boss' son had nothing to do with it.
I won't settle for anything below one
million, so don't do this again.
Lady.
Only Mr Min can help your husband now.
You haven't been playing nice,
but it won't do him any good.
Did you just threaten me?
It's not a threat. It's advice.
You need to face reality.
- Hello.
- Hey.
Did you have a nice chat?
Yes. I guess.
I was making kimchi. It'll
ripen in a few days.
Shall I bring you some, Madam?
Yes.
If you wish.
We meet again.
- Hello.
- Are you going to court today?
- Yes.
- I tried...
talking to Hyo Joo, but you
know she never listens to me.
It's best you get over the
past and start fresh.
Don't try to be so nice when it's
your fault they got divorced.
Goodbye, Ms Choi.
Goodbye.
What a witch.
- My goodness.
- There!
"I was making kimchi. Shall
I bring you some, Madam?"
Isn't that what you said?
I did it to survive, okay?
It's better to grovel and
brown-nose than end up behind bars.
Is Mum inside?
Yes.
I'm so sorry I had to put
you though that, Ms Choi.
Don't say that.
All sorts of things happen
when you live long enough.
Ms Choi.
Here's a sedative. Chew it
well before swallowing.
Are you teasing her?
I'm sorry.
You should get a vitamin IV drip and rest.
I don't need an IV drip.
You can all leave now.
I'll be fine after a nap.
Could you tell me who signed
the form for my surgery?
Just a moment.
Here you go.
Thanks.
(Surgery Consent Form)
(Min Hyo Won)
"Min Hyo Won"?
Who is that?
Why do I keep thinking of them?
It's so annoying. It's really annoying.
Hello?
Is that Min Hyo Won's number?
It is. I'm she. Who's calling?
I'm Kang Tae Yang.
Hello?
Yes. I'm listening.
You signed the consent form for my surgery.
I got curious.
Do you know me?
Yes. I know you very well.
You know me very well?
You'll recognise me the second you see me.
Let's not just talk.
We should meet up.
Let me see.
Yun Shil found the exact fabric we needed.
She knows Dongdaemun Market
like the back of her hand.
Where is she? I'd like
to treat her to lunch.
She has an interview.
An interview?
A tailor store she applied to asked
her to come for an interview.
Which store?
Someone might not be happy
to hear this again,
but Yun Shil is irreplaceable.
See how she found the exact fabric we need?
That's what I've always been saying.
It's such a loss.
Yun Shil.
Where are you going?
To a job interview. Why?
I can't believe you're going to
an interview looking like that.
Your cheeks are flaming red.
No one into fashion would want to hire you.
What?
You obviously won't get the job.
Forget about it.
What a jerk.
Tell me if you fail.
I'll find you a job.
Are you praying that I don't get hired?
That's just mean.
Ouch. That hurt.
How dare he...
What a scumbag.
You sewed by hand...
and with a machine at Wolgyesu Tailor Shop.
Yes.
The Wolgyesu Tailor Shop
run by Mr Lee Man Sool?
That's the one.
I learned from Mr Lee in person.
He taught me in detail how
to cut and sew cloth...
Too bad.
We don't do things like he does.
We don't make the suits here by hand.
We only take measurements and
design the suit for the factory.
Do you not make the suits in person?
We can't make a profit that way.
What use is a tailor store
that doesn't make suits?
Darling.
You aren't surprised. Where's Dong Jin?
In court.
Right. To finalise his divorce?
You should be careful.
Of what?
You'll end up in the same court
if you keep getting into trouble.
If I hadn't gone and begged
Eun Sook this morning,
the police would question you and
cart you right off to prison.
That's why I'm so grateful
for what you did.
I bought you some fresh eel.
I'll marinade it nicely and
grill it up for dinner.
Eat it on your own.
I have to work night and day to
get this suit ready for fitting.
- I'm suspicious.
- About that?
What's your relationship with Eun Sook?
- What do you mean?
- Look.
How close must you two be...
for the cold-hearted woman
who ignored everyone else...
to change her mind and come
over in person to settle?
What are you implying?
I heard you worked with her in this store.
Did you two have something
more than just a friendship?
You really drive me crazy.
You are terminal.
I say this all the time,
but you're delusional.
Your delusional jealousy requires
hospitalisation and long-term care.
Did you really not do anything?
We didn't, I swear. Am I crazy?
But then, she isn't your type, is she?
What is my type?
Women like me...
with a body that curves in
and out in the right places.
You like sexy and wholesome women.
You have such high standards.
I really can't take this any more.
Come home early. I'll be
waiting with the eel.
Stop talking about the eel.
Don't wink.
It's not just any agency.
It's Hyesung Entertainment.
Mr Kang, you know them.
It's one of the top three
agencies in Korea.
They want to release me album.
This is a winning lottery ticket.
Can't you really lend me anything?
Okay.
I get it. You can't lend
me what you don't have.
Bye.
Let's talk soon.
- Did he say no?
- Yes.
He's not doing too well.
I feel so bad for you.
You said you'll never get
another chance like this.
If I try hard enough,
I'll get another shot.
Susanna
I will be
By your side
I won't let go of your hands
Don't cry.
I cry if you cry.
I didn't think it would be
this hard to make a comeback.
Had I known it would be this tough,
I wouldn't have come back.
My poor Jun...
Who are you?
Did we just talk on the phone?
Yes. I'm Min Hyo Won.
Have a seat.
Don't you remember me?
Have we met before?
Do you really...
not remember me?
I don't.
How can you not remember me?
We met outside of Meesa Apparel's restroom.
Meesa Apparel's restroom?
When you threw up the day of the interview.
I was right there.
I don't know.
I remember the situation,
but not your face. Sorry.
I called you a few times after that.
Don't you remember?
- Is this Kang Tae Yang?
- That's me.
Why do you care if I get drunk or not?
You really need help!
You can't waste your life away!
You can't be so negative.
What do you mean?
Here's your soju.
Are you drinking again?
What's wrong with you?
Don't live like that!
Don't waste your one-and-only life!
Sorry.
Are you pretending because
you feel embarrassed?
No. I really don't remember you.
How did you recognise me at the hospital?
How did you end up signing the consent...
- You jerk!
- What?
You gorilla, chimpanzee,
man-eating shark, sloth!
- Hey.
- You cheat...
on multiple women,
so how can you not remember me?
Just a moment, Moon Hyo Won.
It's Min Hyo Won, not Moon Hyo Won!
I shouldn't have signed the form.
I should've left you with
whatever broken limb it was.
What's wrong with her? What did I do wrong?
Hey.
What got into her?
Thanks anyway!
Yun Shil.
- Did they release you already?
- Yes, just now.
Should you be out so soon?
I have a follow-up appointment every week.
You look upset. Is something wrong?
I just went to a job interview.
I failed.
Anyone would welcome someone
with your skill-set.
The store doesn't make their own suits.
They take measurements and decide
on a design for the factory.
Do they do that?
Most places do, apparently.
Handmade suits don't turn a profit.
If my mother-in-law finds
out I lost my job,
she'll scream at me to move
in with her right away.
You can't do that. Don't give in.
I won't.
- Let's cross.
- Okay.
You're too sure of yourself.
(Seoul District Court)
Being a hypocrite and pretending
you don't care about money...
will bite you in the backside.
I wasn't there for you until the end.
I'm sorry.
I should also apologise to your father.
I don't need your money.
You show off to the end.
I can't say we were happy together,
but I'm grateful.
I hope you can be free and happy.
You know,
I used to feel bad that I didn't love you.
Now I think it was all for the best.
You didn't deserve my love.
You're a weak and foolish loser who...
It's over now.
Let's stop.
That's the least we can do for each other.
How can you say that after
you ruined my life?
I decided not to wonder where...
it all went wrong.
I won't look back at the past. I'll
look forward towards happiness.
I think you should, too.
What? Happiness?
You crushed my self-esteem.
People now point and laugh at me.
Don't talk about happiness.
You really care about...
nothing but yourself.
I should go. Drive safely.
Lee Dong Jin!
Please leave a message.
It's me, Dad.
I quit Meesa a while ago.
And now, I work at your store.
Also,
I just divorced my wife, too.
Am I...
a failure?
I worked harder than most...
and never stopped for a break.
Is what I'm facing now...
what failure looks like?
Dong Jin.
Life, you know,
isn't about changing faces.
It's about changing your facial expression.
You just passed a certain
point in your life.
If you give in now, you will fail.
If you get up and keep going,
it will become an experience.
There is one thing...
you must remember.
No one can help you get up.
Your mum and I will watch and
cheer you on with all our hearts,
but you must get up yourself.
I want you to get back on your feet,
return to your loved ones,
and stride proudly into the world again.
I'll work at your store for a while.
I'll take a good look at my
life and pull myself together.
Could you come back soon?
I'm almost done here.
I'll be back soon.
Remember this.
Dong Jin.
You have not failed.
(Wolgyesu Tailor Shop)
Good morning.
You're here early.
Do you want coffee?
Yes, please.
Where's Yun Shil?
Isn't she here?
She found a job. Today's her first day.
Really?
She said she had an interview.
I guess she got the job.
It's not at a tailor store.
It's at the supermarket.
What?
Why would she work there?
People like us who barely make a
living can't afford to be picky.
We have to earn our keep.
She needs to earn whatever she can.
She's only a part-timer.
We have pork belly from Jeju Island.
Come and try some.
It's nice and chewy.
Try some. You don't have to buy any.
Hello, Ma'am. Why don't you try some?
Doesn't it taste better
than the usual pork belly?
I can't tell after just one piece.
Slow down. You might get indigestion.
Are you criticising me for eating too much?
No, I'm not criticising you.
I'm just worried you'll get sick.
Hey!
How dare you get oil on this blouse!
Have you lost your mind?
I apologise. I'm really sorry.
What will you do about this grease?
What will you do about this?
Can you please calm down? I'll
pay for it to get cleaned.
Do you know how much this costs?
Dry-cleaning isn't the issue here!
Get on your knees and beg!
On my knees?
What the customer says goes.
Get on your knees!
This costs a fortune.
That's a blouse from Agnes
Allen's 2014 FW collection.
Right?
This should be enough to get you
another one at an outlet store.
You can relax.
Two drops of grease?
Come back to the store.
- What?
- I'll let you work there.
Don't you get it?
You can come back.
No thanks.
What?
I'm not bored enough to come and go...
whenever you give the order.
I won't come back.
(The Gentlemen of Wolgyesu Tailor Shop)
Why is she playing hard to get?
Should I have taken the
job when he offered it?
I trust you, okay?
Why do you still want a kid at our age?
Your wife is very eager,
so I can safely say you have a good chance.
Can you sleep elsewhere tonight?
Wait for me, everyone!
Sung Jun's coming back!
I have a bad feeling.
Don't tell anyone that I quit the store.
Welcome to Wolgyesu Tailor Shop.
I'm here to see my daughter-in-law.
She's at the tailor shop?