(The following content may not be suitable for viewers under 15.)
(Viewer discretion is advised.)
(Episode 19)
Hello, this is Yun Shil's phone. Hold on a minute.
- Who are you? - I'm sorry?
Why are you answering for her?
I work with her.
Who should I tell is calling her?
Me?
I'm her husband.
Who would you be?
By any chance, are you the store owner's son?
The man who visited me with Yun Shil?
Yes.
It's odd how we keep crossing paths.
I get out in a few months.
Look after my wife until then.
Just a moment. I'll put her on.
I answered it because you weren't here.
Hello, this is Yun Shil.
It's me.
- Hello. - I almost forgot your voice.
Don't you care if I'm dead or alive?
Sorry. I was busy at work.
Why are you always so busy?
Are you hiding something from me?
What do you mean by that?
Do you think I don't know what's going on just because I'm in here?
I do. I know everything you do...
as if you're right in front of me.
Watch yourself. Don't make me angry.
- I did nothing wrong. - Oh, really?
Why am I hearing things, then?
You told your boys to spy on me.
Stop it right now.
- Then quit your job. - What?
Your boss' son.
He gets on my nerves.
Quit working there right now.
Will you just stop it?
Leave me alone, will you?
- What's that? - Is she on the phone?
- I'll check on her. - No, I will.
(Wolgyesu Tailor Shop)
Who are you?
- Who's he? - He's here to help you.
Answer his questions truthfully.
Who are you to help me?
- Come clean now and I'll offer... - Get lost!
"I should go and visit him today."
I tell myself that every day.
But it's harder than it sounds.
My dad and I owe Gi Pyo so much...
considering what he did for us.
He suffered from all sorts of complications,
and his body ached whenever it rained.
He struggled a lot.
I shouldn't be like this.
Aren't I mean?
She's stupidly good-natured.
I'm sorry I yelled.
It's fine.
Yun Shil.
I'll say this as a big brother, so don't take it the wrong way.
I heard what Gi Pyo did for you, but I think...
you should leave him.
You never got to the end of the wedding ceremony,
and you don't have a marriage licence.
- You aren't legally married. - He's right.
He forced you to marry him.
I've dealt with such men before.
They never change.
They act like a lowlife for the rest of their lives.
They torment others.
I'm sorry for causing such trouble.
Think about it objectively, okay?
What's that?
I bought it from the truck outside. Have some.
This looks great. I'd skipped breakfast.
I wasn't feeling well because I had coffee on an empty stomach.
This is perfect.
Don't you want some?
I'm full.
Did you eat breakfast? Then I'll have one more.
Have a bite while it's still warm. Go on.
It's nice and hot. Eat it and cheer up.
We have a competition to prepare for.
It's full of egg. You love egg.
Thank you.
Everyone makes mistakes.
How dare he ridicule me when he should comfort me.
Sam Do.
You really went too far this time.
Didn't you go out to work? Why are you back?
The captain sent me home.
- I can't work with wounded hand. - Too bad.
You should've been careful.
You didn't give Sam Do any breakfast,
but look at this.
Radish kimchi, eggplant, squash, carrot and a fried egg?
That's a nice serving of bibimbap.
Does it look good?
It does.
- Pick the right side. - What?
If you want to eat my food, take my side,
not Sam Do's.
He did go a bit too far this time.
You can imagine things if you want it badly enough.
He shouldn't have said you embarrassed him...
or mocked him.
- No man should say that. - Exactly.
I will pay him a visit at work later...
and talk to him.
- Try to forgive him. - Tell him this.
If he expects to eat my food again, he has to see a doctor with me.
Okay.
I will talk to him and make sure that...
he accompanies you tomorrow.
I like what I hear.
Here's a spoon.
Thanks.
I liked your chicken stew, but your bibimbap's killer, too.
People who make a mean sujebi can cook noodles,
and chicken stew experts make great bibimbap.
You're right.
I hope I marry...
a woman who can cook as well as you.
Too bad. Dong Sook can't cook to save her life.
But then again,
she's off to meet the rich man from Jongno today.
You don't have to worry.
Does she have a blind date today?
You saw Ms Choi make her promise.
I didn't think she'd go on the date so soon.
Are you done?
Did hearing about the blind date ruin your appetite?
Why would it?
It's none of my business anyway.
Where are you going?
I should start looking for a job.
I can't waste time.
She's right.
Are you off work already?
No, I don't work any more.
I handed the store over to the new owner.
Why do you look so gloomy?
Do you eat well?
I'm not hungry.
You're a terrible judge of men.
How will you survive the harsh world?
How could you think of selling your store...
for someone like Leather Jacket?
- Stop bringing up the past. - Listen.
Leather Jacket...
is stuffing his face with the bibimbap...
I was eating.
- He's eating bibimbap? - Yes.
He's such a noisy eater.
It was gross.
Is she naive or stupid?
What a pity.
- What do you want? - You're in.
I made this doing community service.
I'll pay you back whenever I make anything.
Forget it. I won't take so little at a time.
I have no use for so little cash.
Pay me back in one go when you have the 30,000 dollars.
"Little cash"?
If that's what you think, okay.
Step away from my daughter this instant.
You gave me your word just a few days ago,
and you're already whispering to her in my kitchen?
I wasn't whispering. We had something to discuss.
Get out while you still can.
Or else, I might just throw you out of this house again.
Right. I'll leave you, then.
Don't just stand there.
Go to the sauna and get cleaned up.
Then, go and get your hair done at a salon.
- I can't be bothered to. - Don't say that.
You need to look as young as you can to make him like you.
Forget it. If he doesn't want an old wife, he can stuff it.
You brat.
How dare you say that.
Okay, fine, I'll go.
How is work? Is it manageable?
Yes, but I'm busy right now. Let's talk later if it's not urgent.
Just a moment.
I wasn't going to tell you this,
but I think my uncle's ex brother in-law...
is going to marry Choi Ji Yun.
I overheard my uncle's ex mother-in-law...
talk about it with my boss.
That's none of your business. I'm hanging up.
Why is it none of my business?
If Ji Yun marries someone else,
you and I can start dating.
Even if Ji Yun marries someone else,
I don't plan on dating you.
You're just a close friend. I'm hanging up.
Hello? Don't...
Hello.
What are you doing here?
I was out for a meeting and came by for a massage...
because I had a headache.
Is something wrong?
You don't look happy.
I just...
got rejected.
By that man you told me about?
You said his girlfriend dumped him for a rich man.
Isn't it game over, then?
He said that...
even if she leaves him, he won't date me.
What? How dare a jobless man reject someone like you.
He isn't jobless any more. He recently started working.
- At your company. - My company?
What's his name?
I'd like to see the face of the jerk who's giving you such a hard time.
- What's his name? - Kang Tae Yang.
What? Kang Tae Yang?
- Do you know him? - What?
Yes.
I think I saw him a few times at work.
Wait.
He's seeing someone else now?
I wondered why she looked familiar.
It was you.
I guess there are some things you can't have...
even if you try your best.
I constantly tried to win his heart, but he won't budge.
I think that means he really doesn't care about you.
I'm too good for this.
I'll find myself a man that's 100 times better than him.
Will you really? That's the spirit.
I'm so relieved.
Why are you relieved?
It's nothing.
Where is Ms Min?
She left for a meeting.
I doubt that. I bet she's at a spa.
Who would do that during work hours?
We'd never dream of it,
but she's the chairman's daughter.
- She's what? - Didn't you know?
She's the youngest daughter of the late Chairman Min.
Is she really?
I thought you knew that because the CEO hired you.
Do you mean Ms Min is CEO Min Hyo Sang's younger sister?
Of course.
Did something good happen while you were out?
You look happy.
I am. I'm in a great mood today.
Shall we go out for a team dinner?
- Really? - A team dinner?
Do you have plans, Mr Kang?
What?
No.
What did you say?
The blind date is on again?
Gwangan Group's chairman's wife changed her mind.
This is unbelievable.
Does she expect my son to show up or not...
depending on how she feels?
What makes her think she has the right to mock us?
Calm down and hear me out.
Miss. Miss, get me some aspirin.
Yes, Madam.
Here you go.
I know that you feel upset and rightly so,
but their daughter...
seems to have a great interest in your son.
- She does? - Yes.
Her mother is reluctant to let her daughter meet your son...
because of the rumours surrounding your past,
but her daughter seems to have met your son...
a few times while she was studying abroad.
Really?
I heard that she's had a thing for your son ever since.
Things have changed.
We should leave it up to the young couple.
I think it's a done deal, Madam Ko.
It's not your place to butt in.
Of course, Madam Ko.
What shall I tell them? Shall I say the date is off?
If her daughter has a thing for Hyo Sang,
I'll let her see him just once.
Hello, Ji Yun.
We cancelled a restaurant reservation last time.
I was wondering if I should make another one.
I'd like that.
I'll text you the details, then.
Okay. See you soon.
She must feel very rushed if she's willing to...
make the reservations.
Come in.
Is the collaboration going well as planned?
Yes, their chief designer Mr Moravia...
will visit next week, and we're working on the itinerary.
What's on so far?
On day one, he'll meet you and the executives...
to discuss the details of the collaboration.
On day two, he'll visit our factory...
and check our production line and the level of our technology.
On day three, he'll judge the tailoring competition.
- He's a judge? - Yes.
He contacted the Tailor Society and requested...
to be a judge so he could...
see for himself how skilled Korean tailors are.
I see.
- Thanks. - Sure.
(Tailor Society)
- This is for the preliminary round. - I'll take it.
- Thank you. - Have a nice day.
Look at this mannequin.
It has a curved back and the left shoulder's slightly lower.
The goal is to make a suit for a slightly hunched man.
Men who work in front of a computer for long hours have this posture.
That means he's a white collar.
Mr Lee, you're a white collar man. Recommend a style.
The single button is this season's trend, so go with that.
Choose a formal colour...
and a slim fit to accentuate the silhouette.
Okay, those were valid points.
What lapel should we go for?
Since it's a slim-fit single-button suit,
instead of an aggressive peaked lapel,
a formal notched lapel would work better.
- Okay. - We could add something to that.
How about going with striped fabric?
I like that. I'm getting some great ideas from all you experts.
We have the basics, so it's time to design the suit.
Yun Shil and Ms Geum are better at sewing than I am,
- so... - Yun Shil...
will do all the sewing for this competition.
I have to work on our customer's suits.
- I'll do my best, Master Bae. - Okay, I like that attitude.
I talked to your father earlier.
He said he's doing just fine.
Don't worry.
Shall we get to work?
- Yun Shil, get the fabric samples. - Yes, Master Bae.
She was so downcast earlier, but the competition...
seems to have cheered her up.
She's born to make suits.
(Daehan City Hospital)
Mi Soon.
You and I are both old and wrinkled,
but you still have...
that faint smile you always used to have.
I'm losing my eyesight a little bit every day.
I can still see at the moment,
but very soon, dusk will fall and it'll become dark.
I prayed that I'd be able to...
see you one last time to tell you that I'm sorry.
I'm glad that...
I managed to meet you while I can still see.
You had a hard life.
It's time you rest in peace.
- Hello? - It's me, Gok Ji.
You sound so weak.
- Are you sick? - No.
I called because I miss you.
You always say you'll come home soon,
but when will that be?
I'm nearly done.
I'll wrap things up and come home in a few days.
I called to tell you that.
- Is that true? - Yes.
Once I return,
I'll make up for all the trouble...
I caused you.
I'll hold your hand and kiss you often.
Don't be silly.
- Are you feeling well? - I'm perfectly fine.
I have no problems other than that I miss you.
Honey.
Don't fall ill.
I need you to stay with me for a long, long time.
Why are you saying such things all of a sudden?
Is something wrong?
I miss you even more so today.
That's all.
I really do.
You're a terrible liar.
You wouldn't have left like that if you really loved me.
Brace yourself.
Once you come home,
I'll nag you like I've never nagged before.
Take care.
Call me often.
Should I make some dongchimi?
It's his favourite.
I heard you need help in the kitchen.
- Have you done this before? - Of course I have.
I fried chicken half my life.
My mother sold fried chicken.
Then you'll know what to do.
I'm known as the chicken expert.
That's how good I was.
I owned and managed a fried chicken stall...
in a market in Daejeon until a few months ago.
Oh, my goodness.
Why are you so dressed up?
Oh, right. You have a blind date.
- Yes. - Why do you look like...
you're going to a slaughter house?
No man would like a woman...
who looks so gloomy.
Sun Nyeo.
Can you go instead?
- Go where? - Where else?
The blind date.
What do you mean?
I'll pay you.
50 dollars. No.
100 dollars.
100 dollars?
I can't do that. I'm married.
No way.
You don't have to date him.
Just go to the blind date instead of me.
Just eat the food he buys you.
It's no big deal.
Your mother will have a fit if she finds out.
How would she know?
She'll never find out if we both keep our mouths shut.
- Well, that's true. - Is it a deal?
I'll pay you double.
200 dollars.
- Deal? - Deal.
- Mr Park Dae Sub? - No.
Are you Ms Lee Dong Sook?
- No. - Apologies.
- Mr Park Dae Sub? - No.
Are you Lee Dong Sook?
Yes.
Nice to meet you.
I'm Lee Dong Sook. I hope we get along.
I'll sit back down.
The thing is,
the matchmaker told me that...
- you were tall. - Right.
She also said that...
- you had a slim figure. - Right.
Most importantly,
I was told that you're prettier than...
most actresses, and that's why I'm here.
Don't you think...
I look nicer than most actresses?
Hey, hey, hey
What's so wrong with how I look?
Most actresses would slap themselves when they look at me
All that singing made me thirsty.
I'll order a cold drink.
Excuse me, can you take my order?
Thanks.
Miss.
Can I have...
the most bitter coffee you have?
I need to wake up.
I'll have a hot chocolate,
- a cheesecake and a cream cake. - Sure.
That's a lot.
Do you have any questions for me?
No.
- Don't you want to know about me? - I don't.
Don't you want to know my hobbies or personality?
No.
What about my measurements?
I almost died.
I was kidding.
You must be quite shy.
24.
18.
16.
Seven.
(Wolgyesu Tailor Shop)
Are you off to buy the fabric?
- Yes. - Let's go together.
You want to go the market with me?
I want to study about fabrics.
What's that look? You don't want me to come?
No, that's not it. It'd be fun if you come with me.
Let's go, then. Oh, right.
- Dinner is on you. - Sorry?
I bought you toast this morning.
It's only fair that you buy me dinner.
Just a moment.
I see a credit card right there. Let's go.
- Hello. - Hello.
(Imported Fabric Store)
This looks great.
Hang on a second.
- Thank you. - Thank you.
Have a great day. I hope to see you soon.
- Let's eat. - Oh, my.
- Eat more. - This is already a lot of food.
That store over there has so many fabrics.
Pardon? Where?
What? I think our bowls got switched.
- Eat up. - All right.
Isn't it delicious? I come here often.
- Really? - Yes. Do you want something else?
Are you feeling all right?
You seemed to be in a bad mood this morning.
Browsing through the fabric stores at the market always cheers me up.
I feel completely recharged.
I'm happy to hear that.
I felt bad thinking that I probably shouldn't have answered that call.
Don't worry. I should've visited him sooner.
It's all my fault.
I'm going to visit him as soon as we finish the first design.
Why do you always...
blame yourself for everything?
I don't think you've done anything wrong.
I don't understand why you think everything is your fault.
Are you taking my side?
I'm not taking any sides.
I'm just giving you my objective opinion.
I know what you're saying, but I can't think that way.
Gi Pyo made so many sacrifices for me.
I sound like a fool, don't I?
You do. I mean, you have no problem talking back to me.
You yell at me and give me a hard time.
You also call me Gargoyle Eyes and teased me.
You almost look like a different person...
when you talk to Gi Pyo and his mother.
I also don't know why...
I can't speak up in front of him and his mother.
Let's not talk about serious stuff.
We should enjoy this gorgeous weather.
Hold on a second.
We have many pretty shoes. Please feel free to browse.
Are you looking for something for your girlfriend?
- No, no. - I'm not his girlfriend.
We work together.
I see.
Please recommend something for me.
What's your shoe size?
280mm.
How about this one?
I like it.
Sir. Will you give me a discount if I buy two pairs of shoes?
Of course. I'll give you three dollars off per pair.
Nice. Pick something.
No, I'm okay.
He's saying that he can give us six dollars off.
I'm really okay.
What are you talking about? He's offering us a great discount.
You're not money-conscious, are you?
I guess you like to splurge. I didn't think you'd be like that.
That's not what I meant.
Then pick something.
It seems like 240mm should fit you.
You two should get matching trainers.
- Gosh, we're not a couple. - We're not a couple.
You don't have to be a couple to wear the same trainers.
This is the most popular design right now.
Try it on. It'll look good on you.
I think these should fit you.
Please try them on.
How is it?
I think they fit, but I should...
- tie the laces to see... - I'll do it.
- No, I can do it. - I'll just do it for you.
You're wearing a skirt.
They say that giving shoes as a gift to someone you love...
makes the person run away.
I hope you don't run away, Miss.
- We're not a couple... - We're not dating...
Thanks for everything today.
I just did my work.
Thanks for these trainers.
I had to take advantage of the discount, you know.
- Thank you. - Get some rest.
I will. Drive safely.
I thought he'd only buy high-end things,
but he couldn't give up the six-dollar discount.
There's an unexpected side to him.
What are you doing here?
Hey.
I just stepped out to get some fresh air.
I've been writing songs in my room all day, so I had to get out.
All right.
Just a second.
Well...
It looks like Dong Sook...
went on a blind date today, but she's not home yet.
I told you to stop being nosy about her business.
I'm not being nosy. I'm just asking because I just thought of her.
Go in.
I had a good time today, Dae Sub.
Where's your place? Go in. Bye.
- Just a second. - Yes.
Don't contact me directly to ask me out on a second date.
Please let the matchmaker know first.
Pardon me?
All right. I'll keep that in mind. Bye now.
Who is that bloke?
The dinner was so delicious,
and the wine you ordered went fantastically well with the food.
See you again!
You startled me.
- Who is he? - Who?
Who do you think? That weasel.
That guy who just drove off in his car.
Oh, he's Mr Park.
Mr Park?
My acquaintance introduced me to him today for my business.
He's very different from someone I know. He's well-mannered and kind.
He certainly has class.
Class? Whatever. He looks like a weasel.
Looks aren't everything.
Are you criticising me now?
- You got it right. - Tell me the truth. Who is he?
He's in love with my fried chicken and wants to be my business partner.
I met him to discuss business.
Business? Whatever. You're not cut out for running a business.
Don't you dare undermine me.
You belittle me all the time because I'm a fish you already caught,
but many guys are interested in me. Don't underestimate me.
Cut it out. I'm hungry. Let's go in and eat something.
I thought I made myself clear.
I'm not cooking for you until you come with me to see my obstetrician.
- Are you going to be like this? - I'm just copying you.
Let me make it clear to you.
If you want to eat my food,
you have to come see the doctor with me.
Forget it. I won't eat your food.
Bae Sam Do.
We'll see how long you last.
- What are you doing here? - Just getting some air.
- Did you eat dinner? - Not yet.
- Come. I'm ordering jjajangmyeon. - What?
Jjajangmyeon is such a huge temptation.
Hey.
Sun Nyeo.
- Are you getting home now? - Yes.
You were with him for a long time.
Dae Sub got us a bottle of wine for dinner.
I had a feast.
Dong Sook.
I think we're in trouble.
I think he likes me.
He couldn't take his eyes off of me all night.
He's totally into me.
I only went in your place as a favour,
but what will I do if he asks me out again?
I have a family.
Don't worry. I'll take care of it.
He looked like a nice guy.
He's going to be upset when he gets dumped.
Don't worry about that.
Thanks for your help today.
It was nothing.
I got to eat good food and even earned money for it.
Thank you.
Why are you smirking?
I don't like it.
- We need to change clothes. - Oh, right.
- Come here. - That's impossible.
He doesn't like how she looks?
Dong Sook...
is prettier than any girl there is.
He sure has high standards.
My goodness, I'm speechless.
I'm home.
All right. I'm hanging up for now.
My daughter just came home.
I want to talk to her.
Okay.
Did they call?
Yes.
He likes your personality,
but he doesn't like how you look.
He says you're not his style.
Are you serious?
What's wrong with my face?
That's what I mean.
- What is it, Mum? - By any chance,
did you draw something on your face before going out?
My goodness. Come on, Mum.
- I was with him until minutes ago. - My goodness.
What a strange man.
I'm not being biased because you're my daughter,
but you're genuinely a pretty girl. How can he say such a thing?
Maybe he already likes someone.
- They why would he go on a date? - That's what I mean.
My goodness. What a jerk.
Stop humming. Why are you humming?
Do I even need your permission to hum?
Wake up, you foolish woman.
I bet that man was trying to get your money.
- He just wants to rip you off. - What do you mean?
He has two buildings in Jongno. He's a rich guy.
Rich? No way.
He's trying to do business with you...
because you look like you have money.
You'll end up losing all your money...
and getting a divorce.
Look who's talking.
Mr Park isn't like that.
Mr Park?
He cut my meat for me and poured wine, too.
He was such a gentlemen, I almost cried.
That's what those men do. It's their strategy.
I don't care.
If he's nice to me, that's fine.
Have you gone crazy?
What's with her?
I'm speechless.
Thanks to you, Ms Min, we got to eat great food.
We had a nice dinner, and also,
- we're even drinking at a nice bar. - That's right.
I should have done something like this earlier.
I just had a lot on my mind,
so it got delayed.
Today...
is for us to build a stronger teamwork,
while welcoming Mr Kang Tae Yang to the team.
Please drink as much as you want.
- Cheers. - Cheers.
Hold on.
Princess Loner seems drunk. Should we stop her?
Leave her be. She can control herself.
What is Princess Loner?
That's Ms Min's nickname. She's a princess and a loner.
Why is she a loner?
She's always slow and catches things late.
- She also acts the way she wants. - I see.
All right.
Since today's a special day,
we need a special event.
That's why I prepared something.
- Ta-da. - What is that?
- It's a lie detector. - Yes.
Let's play the truth game.
- What? - The truth game?
Kang Tae Yang, you're first.
Put your hand on the machine.
Me?
Go, go.
I'll ask you questions now.
Answer them honestly.
Okay.
Do you...
have a woman that you love right now or not?
I did, but we broke up recently.
- Gosh. - My goodness.
- He's telling the truth. - Gosh.
Have you ever cheated on someone?
No. Never.
- It's the truth. - Wow.
Then what type of girl...
do you want to date?
A pure person.
Someone who understands how precious love is.
- That's so sweet. - That's my ideal woman, too.
- Liar. - I'm telling you the truth.
- Really? - No way.
You're probably like...
all the other men who look at a girl's background or her looks.
I bet you're the same.
You just know how to sweet talk.
All men are the same.
They're all the same.
Don't you agree?
She's at it again.
If we're unlucky, we'll be stuck here until 2am.
All right, all right. Let's go.
Let me ask you one more time.
Kang Tae Yang.
What is your ideal type?
Why do you want to know?
I don't know.
Why do you think?
I'm not sure,
but the important thing is that I'm curious.
It's fine as long as...
it's not someone like you.
You lied.
That means your ideal woman...
is someone like me.
No way, that doesn't make sense.
Gosh.
This is really amazing.
It's a misunderstanding. It's not true.
What do you mean?
The lie detector just said...
that your ideal type of woman is me.
It seems like you have good taste in women.
After I'm back from the washroom, we'll have the second round.
Round two. Excuse me for a moment.
This must be fake.
Right?
Where did everyone go?
Tae Yang, we're leaving.
Make sure you get Princess Loner home safe.
That's the job for the youngest.
Have a good night.
- That's so cruel. - Let's go to a karaoke room.
Where are we?
I heard the staff are drinking here.
I came to pick up the tab and join in for a drink.
Okay, let's go.
There they are.
Where did everyone go?
- What brings you here? - I heard your team came here,
so I dropped by to pay.
Why are you alone?
Everyone else already left,
and Ms Min went to the washroom.
We're going to leave once she returns.
I see. Is it okay...
- if we join you for a while? - Sure.
Aren't you going to say hello?
You two have met before.
Hello. We seem to be running into each other quite often.
Hello.
Do you have a girlfriend?
Pardon?
You're a nice guy with good looks.
I'm sure you have a girlfriend.
Your girlfriend must have been happy for you when you got the job.
Are you thinking about marrying her?
I need to go to the washroom.
Sure.
Look who it is.
Do announcers come to places like this to drink?
You hate it when people take pictures of your naked face.
Aren't you afraid they'll take pictures of you drinking?
I'm not in the mood right now. Don't try me.
Gosh, you're scaring me.
Why are you not in the mood today?
Are you going to keep this up?
What do you think you're doing right now?
Don't try to start things with me. Do you understand?
Why you little...
Let go of me. I said let go!
I don't feel like arguing with someone like you. Get out.
What do you mean, "someone like me"?
You're twisted because nothing's going well for you.
What?
- Are you talking about me? - Yes, you.
That witch...
Hey.
Get out of there.
You little...
I'm letting you off the hook today because I'm drunk.
I won't go easy on you the next time I see you.
Consider yourself lucky.
Today's not my day.
Cheers.
Next time, you and your girlfriend...
should join us two for a meal.
Pardon?
I need to see you in front of the washroom.
Will you excuse me for a second?
Okay.
Hey.
What are you doing here?
Have you been drinking?
A little bit.
Where's Tae Yang? Where did he go?
Where did he go?
Did he go home?
Listen to yourself slurring.
Have you been drinking alone, Hyo Won?
Why are you the only one drunk?
I'm not...
drunk at all.
Sure.
You... My goodness. Hey.
I wish other people could see this.
Yes, it's me. Come pick up Hyo Won.
Okay.
We weren't done playing the truth game.
Bring me Tae Yang.
What are you babbling on about?
Get yourself together.
What did you tell Hyo Sang about us?
I didn't tell him anything.
How do you explain this, then?
This isn't mere coincidence how we keep running into each other.
Did you really not tell him anything about us?
Do I look like someone that low?
Why did you have to get a job there and put me in this spot?
It's not too late to quit your job.
You don't care about anyone else other than yourself, do you?
I can't do that.
Tae Yang.
Aren't you afraid your boyfriend might see you here with me?
He'll get suspicious if you don't go back.
You jerk.
Who was that?
- Your son is here. - Is that right?
I'm home.
I hope you had a great day, my son.
Where's Hyo Won?
I just put her to bed. She was drunk as a skunk.
You seem to be in a good mood.
I heard from Gwangan Group. They want to arrange a date.
Gosh, I don't feel like it.
Their daughter says she saw you in New York.
- She saw me? - Yes.
I think she fell for you back then.
Don't you have any pride?
- What did you say? - I thought they refused...
to arrange a date when they found out you're the second wife.
Did you crawl back to them...
just because they changed their mind?
Is that the truth?
Well, it is,
but they had every right to think that way.
I can understand that.
Oh, my.
You can understand that?
I never heard you saying anything like that.
My gosh. How generous of you.
- My goodness. She's crazy. - How funny.
Let me make it clear. I'm not going on an arranged date.
Hyo Sang. Don't be upset and just hear me out.
Are you that jealous...
that Hyo Sang might marry a daughter from a wealthy background?
I told you not to get greedy.
I'm just looking out for you.
How did she end up with someone like that to be so miserable?
Honey?
- What? - The dress shirts.
What about them?
There aren't any washed ones in the wardrobe.
Why are you asking me that?
Should I ask the neighbour about that?
I told you. I'm on a strike...
until you go to the hospital with me.
Is this how you're going to handle the situation?
You're not being a good husband. Why should I be a good wife?
Gosh.
Who's calling me at this time of the day?
Hello?
This is the fried chicken place you got interviewed for.
- Hello, Boss. - "Boss"?
Can you work starting today?
Are you serious?
Yes, I understand.
I'll see you soon.
Who was that? It was that guy from yesterday, wasn't it?
Are you out of your mind?
Are you being jealous?
Are you kidding me?
Why would I be jealous?
Okay. Never mind, then.
Is she really cheating on me?
No way. No way.
She's cheating on me?
Good morning, Dong Sook.
- What are you doing? - I'm exercising.
How did the date go yesterday?
What do you care?
My blind date has nothing to do with you.
I know, but I'm just curious.
I'm warning you.
Don't take interest in me...
and don't be curious about me, either.
You're nobody to me, now.
She's got a point. What do I care if she goes on a date or not?
You're out early.
Yes, I have to prepare for the competition.
They're pretty.
Hello, there.
What is it this time?
You should come with us.
Gi Pyo must miss you a lot.
Let's go pay him a visit.
I was going to go on the weekend.
Can't you see I'm on my way to work?
- Let's not do this hard way. - Let go of me.
Let go!
I'll go on my own even if I have to.
- This is some nice fabric. - Yun Shil got it.
- She has a good eye for fabric. - You're here early.
- Where's Yun Shil? - She wasn't home.
I thought she had already left. Is she not here yet?
She must be making a detour.
Let me make a phone call.
People are waiting for me at work. They deserve to know.
It's going through, but she's not picking up.
Is she in trouble?
- This is Wolgyesu Tailor Shop. - It's me.
Where are you right now? Why aren't you at work?
- Is there something wrong? - I'm on my way to visit Gi Pyo.
Why all of a sudden?
Hello?
- Who are you? - Me?
I'm Yun Shil's brother.
I'll be safely escorting her to the penitentiary.
I'll make sure you get her back in one piece. Don't worry.
Hello? Hello?
What was that about?
It was from Yun Shil.
She says she's on her way to visit her husband.
That's a relief. I thought she got into an accident.
Why didn't she tell us about it? This is so unlike her.
I got so worried. Where is this penitentiary?
I don't remember.
- I need to go out. - Where to?
I'll tell you when I get back.
- What's wrong with him? - I don't know.
Long time no see, Yun Shil.
I almost forgot your face from not seeing you for so long.
I've been busy with work at the tailor shop.
You've been busy with work?
Are you sure you weren't busy fooling around with your boss?
- What are you talking about? - I told you.
Even if I'm stuck in here,
I know exactly what you're doing and what you're up to.
(The Gentlemen of Wolgyesu Tailor Shop)
She has high fever and coughs. I need medication for her cold.
Why is she eating alone with him?
Did you ask her out for lunch?
I know Hyo Won can be immature sometimes,
but she's not going to date a jerk like Kang Tae Yang.
Do you want to start dating?
This is such nonsense.
What did you do to Mr Park?
Dong Sook, you're exactly my type.
It's only been hours since they met. What do you mean "marriage"?
- Don't you think you're rushing? - Poor Sung Jun.
What time is it? I think it's time for the announcement.
This is Wolgyesu Tailor Shop.