(The following content may not be suitable for viewers under 15.)
(Viewer discretion is advised.)
(Episode 20)
I've been busy with work at the tailor shop.
You've been busy with work?
Are you sure you weren't busy fooling around with your boss?
What are you talking about?
I told you.
Even if I'm stuck in here, I know exactly...
what you're doing and what you're up to.
I don't know who's been telling you what,
but I did nothing to make you doubt me.
- Really? - Yes, really.
Why do you let him drive you around to eat and go shopping?
The shoes you're wearing. Didn't he buy them for you?
Did you have someone follow me around?
I told you.
I know everything you're doing.
I'm warning you.
If I notice someone following me around once more,
I'll run away to a place where you can't find me.
- Yun Shil. - I mean it.
I'll tell you again. My boss' son and I...
aren't up to what you think we are.
Stop doubting or suspecting me.
Then don't do anything to make me suspect you.
Quit your job and I won't have to doubt you,
and you'll be free of doubt.
I won't quit working there.
You know that my last remaining dream is to make suits.
I'll leave for today.
I'll visit when I can,
so don't send your minions to bring me here.
Yun Shil.
I...
I'm sorry. My anger got the better of me.
I'll stop.
Don't hate me too much, okay?
Go on inside.
I really enjoyed the dinner.
The wine we drank was amazing, too.
See you again.
What on earth is this woman up to? She's acting weird.
- Hello? - Isn't this Bok Sun Nyeo's phone?
Yes, it is. Just a moment.
- Mrs Bok. - Yes?
- It's for you. - Okay.
(My Love Sam Do)
What are you calling me about?
- Where are you? - I'm outside.
Why aren't you at home like a normal housewife?
Who answered your phone?
He's a man I do business with.
Are you seeing the man I saw you with last time? What for?
I said I have business with him. How many times must I tell you?
Come to the tailor store right now.
I can't right now.
You do as your husband says, okay?
What a joke.
If you want to be respected, do your duty as a husband.
You know what I mean.
Hello? Hello? Bok Sun Nyeo!
Mrs Bok. You really are a good cook.
The ingredients are the same. Why does your chicken taste better?
I told you before that...
everyone in Daejeon knew about my chicken.
Why don't you...
work for me as a full-time employee?
I'll pay you well enough.
I can't do that.
My husband's like a big baby and can't do anything without me.
I have to be at home when he gets off work.
You must get along famously with your husband.
He can't get enough of me.
Is she really having an affair?
Sorry I'm late.
You didn't say anything about it yesterday.
Why did you suddenly visit him today?
Gi Pyo suddenly wanted to see me.
Sorry.
We were all so worried because we couldn't reach you.
I accidentally left my phone at home. I'm really sorry.
Where were you, Dong Jin?
A friend of mine needed my help.
- You're back. - We have so much work to do.
I'm so sorry.
We can catch up. Don't worry.
I can't concentrate. Let's eat lunch first.
I didn't eat breakfast today,
so my stomach's been growling.
To pay for being late, I'll buy you all jjajangmyeon.
Okay, you do that.
- Can I order a double? - Of course.
Let me ask you one more time.
Kang Tae Yang. What is your ideal type?
It's fine as long as...
it's not someone like you.
You lied.
That means your ideal woman...
is someone like me.
What's wrong with her?
Let's all go to lunch.
- Okay. - Okay.
What shall we eat?
Mr Kang.
- Me? - Do you have plans?
No.
- Actually, I do. - Cancel and join me.
What?
Is all this for me?
I didn't know what you like, so I ordered one of each.
Eat what you like.
We'll give the leftovers to the staff as a snack.
But...
Shall I order French fries?
No, don't. I'm not a fan of greasy foods.
Oh, I see.
You don't like greasy foods.
Did your mother cook you hangover soup?
She lives in the countryside.
I live alone.
Oh, I see.
You live in Seoul alone.
You like bulgogi burgers.
Aren't you eating?
Don't worry about me. Eat all you want.
Why are you looking at me like that?
Because I want to look at you.
Don't worry about me. Focus on the burger.
How adorable.
Ms Min.
Do you buy lunch for everyone on your team?
Of course not.
I'm treating you specially.
Why is that?
I don't know. I just...
want to be nice to you.
What? Are you done?
I can't eat because of how you're staring at me.
- I'll eat the rest at my desk. - Don't be so picky.
Okay, fine, I won't look.
There. Can you eat now?
- The doors are closing. - Wait.
Take the next one.
Hello.
- Where were you? - We had lunch.
I didn't ask you, you brat.
Are you the only one on her team?
Why was it just the two of you?
Did you...
- ask her to join you? - Pardon?
What's wrong with you?
- I asked him to join me. - Why not the others, then?
- What if people gossip? - Stop it.
Don't make a fuss out of nothing.
Stop it.
I will tell you again, just to make it clear.
Hyo Won isn't the average employee, so treat her properly.
Don't cause a scandal...
that will make her and our family look bad.
You'll be the death of me.
- Get off, Mum. - What floor is this?
I'm going to see your brother.
Just get off.
- Remember what I said. - He doesn't have to.
- Forget about it, Tae Yang. - Hey.
Goodbye.
This is so confusing.
What's going on?
Let go.
You drive me up the wall.
- Why? - Tae Yang saw it all.
I didn't say anything wrong, did I?
What's going on?
What's wrong?
I caught her alone with a male employee...
and gave him a warning, and that set her off.
Who? Kang Tae Yang?
Yes. I sensed something fishy, so I told him to back off,
and she's complaining that I embarrassed her.
- You're so crass and rude! - What?
Mum.
Hyo Won's immature and all that,
but she'd never fall for someone like him.
- She has standards. - What's wrong with him?
He has nothing to his name.
His dad died when he was young, and his mum's a farmer.
He has nowhere to stay, so he lives in a gosiwon.
How do you know that?
I happened to overhear some staff talk about him.
My goodness. He looked rich, so I had my hopes up,
but he's just useless.
Anyway,
stay out of my business.
How dare you.
Something's going on.
Don't be silly.
Hyo Won's naive and silly and all that,
but she wouldn't fall for Tae Yang.
Don't worry.
Don't forget you have a blind date today.
I said no.
Is it because of that announcer?
It's because of my pride.
I don't want to meet a woman whose mum looks down on us.
- The woman adores you. - Mum!
I'm not telling you to marry her. Just meet her.
Think about how I raised you.
The whole world mocked and ridiculed me,
but you were my only hope and strength.
Can't you do this for me?
(Gwang Sashimi)
Are you going out?
"Going out"?
I'll be working part-time at my friend's clothes store...
to sell clothes, okay?
What are you doing out here?
Me?
Yes, you. Who else would I be talking to?
You're right. Well, I'm here...
working at a karaoke bar.
- Part-time? - Yes.
I can sing all I want and earn money.
I can kill 2 birds with 1 stone.
I hope you become rich.
Wait.
Yesterday's blind date.
Did it go well?
Of course it did.
The man fell for me right away,
and we're discussing marriage already.
Just a few hours after you met?
Aren't you rushing it?
You can't and shouldn't rush such things.
Why do you care if we discuss...
marriage or an engagement?
That is true. It's none of my business.
You are unbelievable.
Bye.
(All For You)
I didn't care for her before, so why do I now?
She looks prettier now.
She actually has a great figure, too.
Shoot, that's so cold.
- Hello. - Hi.
Hello.
I hope we get along, Boss.
Don't call me that. We're friends.
You used to run your own store.
Are you sure you can manage working for someone else?
I can't afford to be picky.
- Come with me. - Okay.
He's such a mess.
What?
Nothing. What should I do first?
When Dong Sook was young, people wanted her to enter pageants.
At least five beauty parlour owners came to ask for my permission.
I can't believe that a man rejected her...
because she looked ugly.
Everyone has different standards.
Even then.
This doesn't make sense.
It wasn't just her looks.
Apparently, she ate like a starved woman the whole evening.
They had meat, and she ate three portions of rib eye.
Then she ate a bowl of naengmyeon.
Dong Sook never finished a bowl of rice in her life.
That's impossible.
That's not all.
After dinner, she ate cake and coffee.
Mr Park spent over 300 dollars on food alone.
He said he'd never seen a woman...
eat so much in his whole life.
Are you sick?
I'm fine.
Let me see.
You aren't fine. You're boiling up.
Tell Dong Jin that you'll take the rest of the day off.
Shall I tell him?
I'm coming down with a cold. I just need to take some medicine.
Don't worry.
I'll get you something.
I'll go myself once I finish this.
Seeing Gi Pyo must've stressed you out.
What did he say to you this time?
He didn't say anything.
I'm sure he did. I know what he's like.
Hello. What can I get for you?
The coughing and fever is from a cold, I think.
I need something for that.
Sure.
Here you go.
Something for indigestion and headaches, too.
Headaches and indigestion.
What else is there? Multivitamins, please.
Antiseptic ointment, please.
Do you have a sedative?
Do you have anything for especially weak people?
- You must be going abroad. - What?
You're buying all sorts of things.
I'm just replenishing my medicine cabinet.
I see.
It looks like you have a cold.
- Yes. - You should...
see a doctor.
It's not that serious. I just need to take some medicine.
I just got back from a pharmacy.
Do you want some medicine?
Are you feeling unwell?
I think I have indigestion. Here you go.
Let me see.
These are multivitamins. Do you want one?
No thanks.
This is for headaches and this is for indigestion.
This is for when you need to calm down.
The pharmacist said this is good for you when you feel weak.
- Take this. - No thanks.
It's good for you. Take it.
You can keep it all.
Why are you giving me all this?
I have all this at home. Keep it for emergencies.
Why did you buy all this if you already have some at home?
I bought it in case someone in the store would need it,
but I think you should keep it for yourself.
Sam Do and Ms Geum are very healthy.
They don't need medicine.
I'm off.
Why did he buy so much?
I'm off, Ms Min.
- Bye. - See you tomorrow.
- See you. - Bye.
Mr Kang.
Do you have dinner plans?
No, I don't.
Great. Will you have dinner with me?
What do you like?
Dinner's on me.
No thanks.
Why?
I said it's on me.
I do work for you, but I still have a private life.
I'd like to avoid being with you unless it's for work.
I also want to avoid scandals.
If it's about what my mum said, just forget about it.
She tends to worry about things that aren't worth...
I should go.
You said you don't have plans.
Why won't you eat with me?
Is this...
about her?
Who do you mean?
Your ex-girlfriend who left you...
for a rich man.
How do you know about that?
Da Jeong told me.
Da Jeong?
Lee Da Jeong?
She's my brother-in-law's niece.
Forget about her.
She chose money over you.
Don't waste time agonising over her.
That's just silly.
Find someone much better than her,
and show her that you're happy.
Does being the chairman's daughter...
mean you can be rude to your employees?
I may work for you,
but I'd rather you stay out of my private life.
If I upset you,
I apologise.
I was worried for you.
I never asked you to worry for me.
I ask you again.
Other than for work,
I hope I don't have to spend time with you.
I have to go.
Is he upset that I badmouthed her?
What's wrong with him?
I'm Choi Ji Yun from KBC.
I wanted to interview you before we tape the show.
I see.
Congratulations on making a comeback...
- after injuring your finger. - Thank you.
I heard you're going to perform Bach's violin sonatas...
and partitas which are considered...
the Old Testament of violin music.
They're both something that all violinists wish to perform...
at least once in their lifetime.
Yes. We have to rely solely on the violin itself to bring to life...
Bach's deep understanding of music...
without the accompaniment of a piano or an organ.
It's impossible...
unless you truly understand the music.
Who's she?
Are you Jo An Na from the Gwangan Group's family?
Yes, that's me.
I've always wanted to meet you.
The matchmaker couldn't praise you enough.
- You make a nice first impression. - Thank you.
My mum has issues with your background,
but I insisted on meeting you.
- My background? - I don't think it's important...
whether your mother was the wife or the mistress.
Your mother...
must be a very charming lady.
I decided to be positive about it.
In that sense,
I must say you take after your mother.
The Korean students knew you as a playboy...
when you used to study abroad.
I always had...
a certain level of curiosity or affection for you.
What do all the women find so charming about you?
I was curious.
I'm not up to par with your background, so I'll leave.
By the way, let's split the bill.
Why are you here?
I was here for an interview,
then I waited to say hi to you.
Did the blind date go well, Mr Min?
- No, it's not what you think. - You jerk.
- Let's talk. - I have nothing to say.
- Ji Yun. - Let go.
What a mess.
(Wolgyesu Tailor Shop)
Thanks, everyone.
I really appreciated your help with the competition suit, Yun Shil.
I think you should finish padding the shoulder.
I'm not good enough to do that yet.
Okay.
We all worked late.
- How about dinner? - I have to rush home.
I'm not feeling well. I think I should go to bed early.
You and I can have dinner, then.
- Us two? - Yes.
A new beef-bone soup opened,
and I heard the soup's really good.
Shall we eat there?
Let's all go there for lunch tomorrow.
I should go.
Fine, then.
Let's go.
- See you tomorrow. - But...
(Wolgyesu Tailor Shop)
Honey.
Honey. Honey?
Sun Nyeo.
Where is she?
- What? - "What?"
What's wrong with you? Why aren't you at home?
I told you that I'm out on business.
Are you still with that jerk?
Will you stop calling him that?
Are you actually defending him? Come home right now!
I have to stay until my time's up. Stop being so clingy.
Hello? Hello? Hello?
Is it an affair?
What now?
I think she's cheating on me.
Hello and welcome.
- Hello. - I don't feel like singing.
It's your first day at work. Let's celebrate.
We haven't done this in a few months.
I don't feel like it.
- Is there a room? - Of course.
Go into room four. How long will you stay?
- One hour for starters. - Okay.
I'll give you 20 more minutes for free.
- Let's go. - Okay.
How embarrassing.
I wonder if she'll like this.
I should give her extra.
Enjoy yourselves.
Excuse me.
- Yes? - Aren't you a singer?
I'm not. You're mistaken.
I'm not mistaken.
He looks like the singer...
- you used to like in high school. - No.
That was someone else.
I remember him, though.
What was that song he sang? It was about a handkerchief.
Why would a singer be working here?
- You should get back to work. - I should.
Enjoy yourselves.
That's it.
Sung Jun's "Susanna's Handkerchief".
"Susanna's Handkerchief"? I never heard of that song before.
That's because you're young.
He was famous back in my day.
I haven't seen you on TV at all.
- Do you own a karaoke bar? - Yes, well...
Seeing that we met,
could you please sing...
- "Susanna's Handkerchief"? - What?
How could you ask him such a thing?
It's good to see someone from our era.
Sing it for us.
I found the song.
Sing for us. Sing for us.
Sing for us.
I'll willingly sing for my fans.
Thank you.
When I looked at your beautiful face.
It brought tears to my eyes.
That's when you would silently.
Hand me your handkerchief.
- You used to always tell me - Mister.
- My goodness. - Why are you here? We're busy.
They asked me to sing a song.
You can't leave the counter unattended.
I'll be right there.
I'll sing for you some other time.
Have a good time.
Why did you give them so much popcorn?
They're regulars, okay?
It's my business, not yours.
What should I do with him?
- Mum. - Come home right now.
Now?
Hello, Mum.
- What's going on? - Sit down.
- About Mr Park. - Who's that?
Your blind date.
Oh, the Mr Park I went on a date with?
- What about him? - The matchmaker said...
on the day you two met,
you ate three portions of meat, a bowl of naengmyeon,
cake and coffee.
He spent over 300 dollars just on food.
- Is that true? - What?
Oh, yes. It's all true.
You're a picky eater with almost no appetite.
How can you eat over 300 dollars' worth of food?
You know that...
I haven't been eating well because I was stressed.
Mr Park took me to a barbecue place,
and the food there was so delicious.
Still, it's very unlike you.
Aren't 3 servings too much food for 1 person?
You know how those high-end restaurants are.
One serving was less than a handful of food.
Wait a second. Didn't he complain about my looks the other day?
Is he now saying that I eat like a glutton?
Goodness, you're such a fool.
If you were hungry, you should've just waited until you got home.
You met him for the first time that day.
How can you eat three servings of meat in front of him?
That was a blind date, not a barbecue feast!
I didn't expect this outcome.
I'm home, Honey.
Why are you getting home just now?
How can a housewife neglect housework...
and stay out until this late hour?
I'm sorry.
I had a busy day due to my business.
Business? What business?
What kind of business is keeping you busy? Are you cheating on me?
Cheating? What are you talking about?
Why would you be out until this late if you're not cheating on me?
Give me his number.
- Who? - Who do you think?
That weasel who gave you a ride the other day.
I see. Mr Park? Why do you want his number?
I need to see what kind of weasel is shaking its tail...
to seduce my wife with my own two eyes.
This is a serious case of delusional jealousy.
This is why marrying someone in your league is important.
You were too greedy for your own good...
Because you married someone like me.
That's why you're always anxious and nervous.
In short, you're living in chronic, habitual paranoia.
You're living in chronic, habitual paranoia.
Gosh, I'm so tired.
I need to get some rest.
Honey, wait. I'm not done yet.
Who were you with? What did you do? Answer me!
Don't be so lame and clingy. Let go!
Is she traumatised from the false pregnancy?
What should I do?
Gosh, what am I supposed to do?
Tae Yang, I shouldn't have talked about your ex-girlfriend.
Forgive me.
You look the most handsome when you smile, so don't be angry.
I'll see you tomorrow.
Why is she being like this to me?
- Dad. - Hey.
How are your eyes?
I feel less burdened because I was able to accomplish what I had to do.
I feel like I can see better now because of it.
The weather has gotten quite chilly,
so I bought a sweater for you. I hope you like it.
It feels very nice.
The size is also perfect for me.
I see that you've adapted yourself to the tailoring business now.
Oh, we decided to participate in the Bespoke Suit Tailoring Competition.
I see. I'm glad to hear that.
Sam Do hesitated because he didn't want to disgrace your reputation,
but the other employees and I persuaded him.
I trust that Sam Do can do it.
Yes. We're currently working on the suit for the preliminaries.
Sam Do is in charge of the design and tailoring...
while Yun Shil is taking care of the actual sewing.
I know how meticulous Yun Shil is when she sews.
You'll certainly pass the preliminary round.
I wish you could come to the finals and cheer for us.
By the way, how is your friend doing?
Doctors say that she can pass away any day now.
But since she has many regrets,
it's hard for her to let go of her life.
I told her to stop tormenting herself and to just let it go.
Dad.
What did you love about her?
I loved her bright smile.
Her smile used to brighten up the entire world around her.
Your mum is prettier than her,
but she had the most beautiful smile I've ever seen.
Do you regret parting ways with her?
I don't regret it because I met your mum,
but I ran away like a coward instead of making a decision.
I can't stop beating myself up for that.
Dong Jin, a man must not...
take a step back when he has to muster up his courage.
Nothing in life comes for free.
When you truly want something,
you must be willing to overcome obstacles to make it yours.
This looks great here.
Gosh, it's so chilly now.
- Good morning, Ms Geum. - Where is Yun Shil?
She caught a bad cold, so I don't think she can work today.
I went upstairs to check on her, and she has a high fever.
- Shouldn't she go see a doctor? - I told her that I'd take her,
but she kept saying she's fine because she took medicine.
I heard that the cold that's going around now is a really bad one.
I guess she was stressed out about visiting Gi Pyo yesterday.
She's become so sick all of a sudden.
I can't just leave her like that. I'll take her to a doctor.
It's okay. I'll take her.
- You will? - Really?
We're backed up on orders, so you two should work. I'll be back soon.
Yun Shil. It's me, Dong Jin. Let me in.
Are you there? Please open the door.
Is she not home?
It's open.
Yun Shil.
Is she unconscious?
Yun Shil, wake up.
It looks like she's unconscious.
Yun Shil.
Is she asleep?
- Oh, my goodness! - Gosh, you startled me.
Ouch, my head! What are you doing here?
I'm sorry. Is your head okay?
Yes, I'm fine.
What brings you here by the way?
Master Bae sent me here to take you to a doctor.
Let me take you to a hospital.
I'm fine.
You don't look fine. You're coughing.
I felt really sick until this morning,
but I feel much better now because I had a good sleep.
I still think you should go see a doctor.
I'm really okay. I feel totally fine now.
That cold medicine you gave me yesterday must've been effective.
I brought you some porridge. You should eat it now.
It's not like I really wanted to buy it for you.
I just want you to get better soon so that you can work on that suit.
I'll eat it later. I don't have any appetite right now.
It's porridge, so just swallow it down.
Gosh, your corny joke is giving me the chills.
I think it was funny.
Come on out!
You really didn't have to do this.
You must eat well when you're sick.
Chew well and eat all the porridge.
How is it? Is it good?
Yes, it's delicious.
Eat the side dishes, too.
Gosh, I said you should eat it with the side dishes.
Goodness.
Here.
Gosh, what is wrong with me?
I tear up whenever I eat something delicious.
It's an odd habit of mine.
I'm silly, aren't I?
Everyone already knows how silly you are.
There's no need to be embarrassed.
I see.
You don't mind eating together in the cafeteria, do you?
You probably don't get to eat much at your gosiwon.
I'm fine.
I know you like bulgogi burgers.
You must also like bulgogi.
Am I right?
I've had enough.
I think there's a misunderstanding.
I don't take you lightly because I'm the chairman's daughter.
I'm not that immature.
I'm a really nice person. You'll see once you get to know me.
I'm done. I'll get going now.
Do you want to go out with me?
- What was that for? - I'm sorry.
Here.
Gosh.
Why are you so surprised?
What's so surprising about that?
Stop joking around, Ms Min.
I'm not joking.
I'm serious.
It doesn't make sense for us to go out.
Why does it not make sense?
I'm surely your type of woman.
I never said anything like that.
The lie detector did, though.
It malfunctioned.
I don't fall for people like you.
What kind of person am I?
You're self-centred. You have everything your way.
I don't like people like that.
I admit that I can be like that at times,
but that's not all there is to me.
- Stop being so judgmental. - I'll pretend I didn't...
hear what you just said.
How can he talk like that in front of my face?
Does he hate me that much?
- Hello. - Hello.
Does he get any work done?
Yes, he's quite competent.
He has a good reputation among his colleagues, and he works hard.
He's basically running the TF team.
I see.
Where is he?
I just got a call from Ms Kim.
I think they like you.
That woman is a psycho.
- Don't say that. - I'm a crazy person myself,
but she's 10 times worse.
She'll drive our family into ruins...
if she becomes your daughter-in-law.
Is she that bad?
I'd rather live forever alone.
I won't marry someone like that.
- Mum, give Ji Yun a chance. - Hyo Sang!
It's a little harsh of you to disapprove when you haven't met her.
I thought about breaking up with her after taking your advice,
but I can't. I just can't do that.
Please, Mum? Please?
I'm sorry about yesterday.
Give me a chance to explain what happened.
Jerk.
Are you Choi Ji Yun?
Yes, that's me.
This is from Mr Min Hyo Sang of Meesa Apparel.
Is that from your boyfriend?
Ji Yun.
I heard rumours about you and Meesa Apparel.
I guess they were true.
It's not like that.
I'm sorry. Let's meet up and talk.
Did you think some flowers would make me forgive you?
I'm not as easy as you think, Hyo Sang.
Dong Jin's late.
Looks like he got caught up at the hospital.
Let's take a lunch break. I can't work when I'm hungry.
You can eat.
I have to get back home.
Why? Is something wrong with Sun Nyeo?
I wouldn't put it like that.
I need to check on something.
If she's not home at this time of the day,
she has to be cheating.
Hello, Dong Sook.
What are you doing here, Dae Sub?
- Your mother said... - I said you should...
ask about future dates through the middle-person.
You can't be coming here to where I live.
- It's not like that, Dong Sook. - Let's not do this here.
Let's go somewhere quiet and talk.
What are you talking about? I'm not here to see you.
I'm here to see your mother.
Did you like me that much? We only met once.
You can't meet Ms... I mean, you can't meet my mum already.
Don't you think you're rushing things?
We just met once. Don't you think your overreacting?
My gosh.
- It's not like that. - Well, whatever it is,
- let's just go somewhere quiet. - What are you talking about?
Stop right there.
- Oh, no. - Who are you?
What are you doing here, Honey?
What did you say? Did you call him, "Honey"?
- What's going on? - I got you now.
You live off by backstabbing innocent women, don't you?
That's why you're hitting on my wife, isn't it?
"Wife"?
- You two are married? - Yes.
- My goodness. - That woman is my wife.
Let go of me.
- You're a gold-digger, aren't you? - What did you say?
How dare you talk that way about a charming woman like her.
- Get your hands off of me. - How dare you call her that.
- My gosh, get off of me. - Take it easy, you two.
Listen to what I have to say.
- I can explain. - Let go of me.
- What are you trying to do? - I'm going to break his legs.
You're going to hit me? Please help!
Call the police!
Call the police! He's trying to beat me!
- What's going on? - Stop it, Honey.
- Call the police, everyone. - Hold still.
- What's going on here? - Who are you supposed to be?
- Who am I? Who are you? - I'm Park Dae Sub. Who are you?
- I'm the Terius of rock-ballad. - What does that mean?
Hold him tight.
Are you okay? I didn't mean to do that.
Mr Park?
- Hello. - Do you know him?
He's Mr Park who went on a date with Dong Sook.
This is the guy...
who went on a date with Dong Sook?
Did he confuse her for Dong Sook?
Are you cheating on Dong Sook?
- What's going on here? - Look here.
Did you set me up on a date...
with a married woman?
How could you do this to me?
Who are you talking about?
- I don't understand. - I'm talking about Dong Sook.
What are you all doing out here?
There you are, Dong Sook.
This is Dong Sook?
- I thought she was Dong Sook. - What are you talking about?
This is my daughter, Lee Dong Sook.
- Who's this then? - That's Bok Sun Nyeo.
She lives upstairs.
What?
Who's that? Do you know him?
I knew something wasn't right...
when you said you don't like how she looks...
and that she eats like a baby.
I sensed something went wrong.
That's why I called Mr Park over to our house.
I wanted to talk to him to see if everything was true.
It's all my fault. I'm really sorry, Ms Choi.
- I'm sorry. - I'm sorry, Mum.
Arranged dates aren't a joke. This is nonsense.
What have you done to Mr Park?
I give you my sincere apologies on behalf of these young kids.
I'm terribly sorry.
Right.
Things like this can happen once in a while. I'm fine.
Thank you for being so understanding.
All things aside,
the fact that the real Dong Sook isn't her,
but is her,
is making me feel much better now.
It's such a relief. I'm very glad about this.
What are you talking about?
Dong Sook.
You're my type of woman.
What?
My goodness.
Please accept my bow, Ma'am.
Gosh.
What's gotten into you?
Would you please allow me to marry your daughter?
What are you talking about?
You've just met her. Are you kidding me?
This guy is out of his mind.
Shut your mouth. This is our family business, not yours.
When I laid my eyes on her,
I fell in love right away.
Please allow me to marry her.
I won't let her go through any kind of hardship.
I'll treat her like a queen.
I want you to be my mother-in-law.
What are you going to do next time?
You never stop surprising me with that interesting brain of yours.
I wanted to make you jealous so you'd go to the hospital with me.
You really are terrible.
You looked really nervous back there.
Your eyes looked fiery when you were grabbing him by the collar.
What are you talking about?
Wait a minute. If you weren't seeing him,
where did you go every night?
I started working part-time at a fried-chicken restaurant.
A fried-chicken restaurant?
Don't take this the wrong way. It's not because I don't like you,
but I'm not thinking of getting married again any time soon.
Just give me...
three dates.
"I want to get married again so much."
I'll make you say that.
You're a confident guy.
That's right. I have money.
And look at how good I look.
I have every right to be confident.
So give me an answer.
All I'm asking for is three dates.
Sure. Give me a call later.
Thank you, Dong Sook.
I'll take you to somewhere nice.
Watch it. Stop holding her hands.
Who's this guy?
He's a hard working man who lives on rent upstairs.
You don't have to worry about him at all.
Thanks for the food.
Thank you.
Getting proper rest is important when you have a cold.
Don't worry about the shop. Get some rest. I'll get going.
Don't come out.
It's fine.
Why did you come out? It's cold outside.
The sink is broken. I have to wash the dishes here.
You have a cold. You shouldn't do that.
It'll only take a couple of minutes.
I'll fix the sink. Do you have the tools?
This is nothing.
The water's leaking because the plastic hose got worn out.
I'll fix it in no time.
Wrench.
This is a screwdriver. Give me a wrench.
This is a plier.
Don't you know anything about tools?
This is the wrench.
You must have a way with tools.
I'm a man. It's natural for me to know.
I'll fix it in no time.
- Oh, my gosh. - My gosh, it's cold!
- Oh, gosh. - What happened?
It broke. It broke. Oh, my.
Oh, gosh.
Oh, no.
This place will get flooded.
Something's not right. There's something wrong with it.
Here.
Block it with this.
- What? What do I do? - Over there.
This isn't going to do the job.
Just do it.
- I blocked it. - Nice.
- My gosh. - That's good.
Look at this.
Don't you have anything bigger?
That's the biggest one I have.
That should do it.
Okay.
- Thank you so much. - No problem.
Plumbing is much more complicated than it looks.
Most guys would easily fix something like this.
You just forgot to...
turn the water off before you started.
It's common sense, really.
I'm back.
You're late. Did you drop her off at the hospital?
She was feeling better, so I didn't take her to the hospital.
I see.
What are you wearing inside?
My goodness. Did something happen?
It's nothing.
Can you give me a shirt I can change into?
You should be able to find something in the back.
Okay.
Why did I say I could fix it? This is so embarrassing.
Gosh, I'm so embarrassed.
These are the 30 suits that made it to the final round.
Now that we have a judge who studied fashion abroad,
I'm sure it'll be a fair competition.
What do I know?
You can evaluate the tailoring and the needlework.
I'll evaluate the design of the clothes.
Let's get started.
The tailoring and needlework are nicely done.
This looks spotless.
The sewing is perfect, too.
What do you think, Ms Min?
I don't know anything about suits,
but this one does stand out.
It has a perfect balance and harmony.
It's very vivid.
No wonder it's so perfect.
It's Wolgyesu Tailor Shop's work.
Wolgyesu Tailor Shop?
(Wolgyesu Tailor Shop?)
What time is it? I think it's time for the announcement.
You should've done the needlework, Master Bae.
I don't have a good feeling about this.
Nonsense.
Don't say that. It's bad luck.
This is Wolgyesu Tailor Shop.
Yes.
Yes, I understand.
Okay.
Did we fail?
There's no way.
He's not saying anything.
It looks like we didn't make it.
My gosh, what do we do?
Well...
We passed.
Okay.
- Good work. - Good job, Master Bae.
Good work, Ms Geum.
Thanks you, Mr Lee!
(The Gentlemen of Wolgyesu Tailor Shop)
It's nothing much. It's a show of appreciation.
What's wrong with my heart?
It hurts so much right here. I just want to die.
Was I too harsh?
Do you like Yun Shil that much?
She's nice and considerate. She's like my own daughter.
We've all been through a lot. Let's not waste time.
This is what you call dating violence.
Should I just get surgery done?
You already know how much I want kids.
How could you do this to me?
Stop making me worry about you.