(The following content may not be suitable for viewers under 15.)
(Viewer discretion is advised.)
(Episode 21)
- Hello. - Hello.
Make me proud.
(Wolgyesu Tailor Shop)
Thank you.
I thought it was flawless.
It figures. It's from Wolgyesu Tailor Shop.
Wolgyesu Tailor Shop?
Hello, this is Wolgyesu Tailor Shop.
I see.
I understand.
Were we eliminated?
Well...
We passed.
Okay.
Good work.
Good work, Master.
Good work, Ms Geum.
Thank you, Mr Lee.
Do you not feel well?
No, I'm fine.
We only passed the preliminary round.
- Why are you so worked up? - I know.
With Sam Do, passing the preliminary round is a given.
Ms Na worked hard sewing. Her skills are impressive.
Next time, Ms Na can represent Wolgyesu all on her own.
No way. That's ridiculous.
I mean it.
What's wrong with my heart?
Maybe I should get a check-up.
Do you want some coffee?
Are you all right?
I'm fine.
I'm fine, so don't mind me.
What... What's wrong?
It's nothing.
I just... I...
Mr Lee.
- Dong Jin. - Yes?
Yes? Did you say something?
What are you thinking about?
- Is something wrong? - No, no.
Are you sick?
No.
You've been acting weird.
What? What do you mean?
You're totally out of it. What's wrong?
It's nothing much.
I think I'm just tired.
Hi, Dong Sook, what's up?
Hi. If you aren't busy, I need you to come right away.
Why? What is it?
I can't say it over the phone.
Come to the coffee shop across the street from the shop.
Is it urgent?
Yes, it's very urgent,
so come running.
Okay. I'll be waiting.
I couldn't sleep...
a wink last night because I was so infuriated.
Coming to the blind date impersonating Dong Sook...
is a crime in itself,
but how...
How could you eat up 300 dollars of my money?
What? 300 dollars?
All I did was eat some meat and have coffee.
"Some meat"?
That's why I brought this.
It's the receipt for what you ate that day. Look.
Why are you so cheap?
I've never met a man this cheap before in my life.
What's the receipt for?
It's the receipt from the restaurant for what I ate at the blind date.
- This is too much. - Dong Sook.
If you had eaten it,
forget 300 dollars. I wouldn't mind spending 3,000 dollars.
But this lady...
This lady's mouth...
ate up my 300 dollars.
Just thinking that makes me...
I'm getting upset again.
Fine, I'll give you the 300 dollars.
This isn't about the money.
I'm acting like this because...
I'm so angry about how she acted that day.
Look.
Dong Sook asked me to go on the blind date for her.
That's all I did.
Even if she had asked, you should not have done it.
If you have a conscience, you should not have come.
Conscience?
Look. Look.
Do you have anything alike?
Look and see if you have even 0.01 percent similarity.
I don't know how you had the guts to show up there.
Also, how will you compensate me for the emotional distress?
Are you the only one who was distressed?
I'm used to seeing my handsome husband's face,
but I was distressed having to look at that nasty face of yours.
I almost died because it made my blood pressure spike.
Give me a break.
Let's stop the nonsense.
Give me my 300 dollars, and let's end it here.
I will never give you the money. Over my dead body.
I'm Park Dae Sub. Park Dae Sub of Jongno.
I've never wasted money,
and even if I did, I always got it back.
I always get my money back.
My nickname...
was Jungang Market's Queen Salt.
I won't give you 3 cents, let alone 300 dollars.
The sun will set at this rate. Let's settle this and end it.
- Over here. - Hey.
Why? What is it?
I can't believe the insult, Honey.
What is it?
We meet again.
Let's talk, man to man.
I own two buildings in Jongno. I'm a building owner.
I see. And?
You know building owners are higher up than normal people.
I didn't buy...
two buildings by going around wasting money.
That's a long introduction.
Please get to the point.
The point? Fine.
I will make sure...
that I get back...
the 300 dollars that I spent...
on your wife on the day we had the blind date.
Did you really eat 300 dollars' worth of food?
Take a look.
This is the receipt from that day.
You shouldn't have given him the entire 300 dollars.
You should've offered half and told him to take off.
This is humiliating. Stop talking.
I've never met someone so rude before in my life.
He's a total monster.
You have no right to talk.
How could a married woman go on a blind date?
Are you out of your mind?
I kept asking you to go to the OBGYN, but you refused,
so I lost my senses.
I'm sorry.
And if you went, you should've just had some tea.
How could you eat 300 dollars' worth of food?
You like free things way too much.
I was wrong. I won't do it again.
How embarrassing.
What now?
Since you're here anyway, let's stop by the hospital.
The hospital?
The OB...
I thought we were done talking about that.
We are not.
I'm going to have a son that looks just like you, no matter what.
I told you.
I'll break up with you, so look for someone else.
Maybe you're the one...
who wants to leave me and have kids with another woman.
That's why you're saying that, aren't you?
I'm done listening.
- Honey. Sam Do. - Stop whining.
This is the last time I'll say this.
Don't talk about kids in front of me ever again.
(Urologist)
Should I just...
get surgery?
What's wrong with me?
- Excuse me. Oh, my gosh. - Oh, my gosh.
Why are you so jumpy?
It's nothing.
What is it?
I wanted to give you this.
(Lee Dong Jin)
- This is... - It isn't much, but it's a token...
of my appreciation.
I'm thankful that you let me work here again,
and I owe you a lot.
To be honest, I made it a while back,
but I didn't think you'd like it.
I'm finally giving it to you.
Did you embroider this yourself?
Yes, of course.
Thank you.
I didn't do anything for you.
I don't know if I can accept this.
Don't feel bad.
I made one each for Master...
and Ms Geum, too.
So...
it wasn't just for me?
You gave the same one to Sam Do and Ms Geum, too?
Yes. I made it for them a while ago.
Why am I only getting it now?
Well, you and I were always fighting...
whenever we saw each other.
We didn't have a relationship in which we exchanged gifts.
Well, that's true.
Wear them on your arms while you work.
But I don't know if it'll fit well.
It's okay.
But... Okay.
I'll go then.
(Lee Dong Jin)
I thought she had made it specially for me.
It fits perfectly.
How sick is Ms Min that she's out?
I don't know, but she sounded terrible...
when I spoke to her on the phone.
I don't like people...
who are stubborn and must have everything their way.
I know there's a small part of me that's like that,
but I also have a lot of good qualities once you get to know me.
Maybe I was too harsh.
Where does it hurt?
It's burning up right here, and I feel like...
someone's stabbing me right there.
Why does it hurt there?
I don't know. I have no idea.
I brought your favourite, corn soup. Get up and have some.
No thank you. I have no appetite.
Just why don't you have an appetite?
I have no appetite,
and I have no desire to live.
Tears just keep flowing.
Why are tears flowing?
Did something happen at work?
No.
Did that brat Hyo Joo say something to you?
Then why are you suddenly like this?
What is it?
I'm just so sad.
My heart aches so much.
I just want to die.
How could you say that in front of your mum?
Whatever. I want to be alone, so leave me alone.
Should I call the doctor?
I don't need him.
I want to be alone! Please leave!
What's wrong with her?
I just can't understand.
It sounds like she's having rage issues.
Why? She's just a kid.
What does she lack? My goodness.
I have a recording in half an hour.
Please get to the point.
Are you still angry?
- Do you think I'm angry? - Then what?
I'm just disappointed in you.
Disappointed?
I didn't take you for a cheater.
I guess I was wrong.
But then again, I should've seen the signs when you pushed off...
introducing me to your family.
Hyo Sang,
I have no intention of clinging onto you,
so meet many women with good backgrounds.
If you call going on one blind date, "cheating",
what about you, who dated...
Kang Tae Yang for four years and even met him recently?
What are you talking about?
I'm sure you know...
exactly what I'm talking about.
My mum said it was her wish, so I went on one blind date.
That is all.
But even after you met me, you went back and forth...
between me and Kang Tae Yang.
Who do you think is worse?
Did you hire him,
when you already knew everything?
- Why? - I wanted to know...
who he was and if he was worthy of being compared to me.
He is pretty smart, but he's no match for me.
That's why I was more disappointed in your taste in men.
So that's why you made him and me meet so many times.
You wanted to see how I'd react.
I've always been very mischievous.
You played me.
You shouldn't be getting angry right now.
You should be asking me for forgiveness.
If you leave right now,
it'll really be over between us.
Ms Min.
Look how happy you are to see me.
You must be so excited to see me, that you don't know what to do.
Right? Right?
You smiled.
Tae Yang smiled at me.
Weren't you out because you were sick?
I was.
I was so angry, thanks so someone,
that my heart ached too much to come to work.
That's right. You got me sick.
- Ms Min... - You got me sick,
so you need to heal me.
- Look. - I starved all day. I'm hungry.
- Buy me food. - What?
I always bought, so you buy me food this time.
Ms Min.
My name isn't "Ms Min".
It's Min Hyo Won.
Call me by my first name outside of the office from now on.
It smells great.
(Beansprout soup, four dollars)
Can you eat this?
I'm not a picky eater.
This is seonji, right?
The broth is very dense.
Can you really eat it?
You said this is your regular spot.
Didn't you bring me here because it's good?
I thought the chairman's daughter wouldn't be able to eat this.
Is that why you brought me here?
You're terrible.
Why are you so mean to me?
Why do you hate me so much?
Am I not your type?
Or do you hate my voice?
Or what do I do that annoys you?
Tell me, and I'll fix everything you say.
I...
am not worthy of your affection.
I'm poor, and my family has nothing to offer.
I won't get much better, either.
That isn't your fault.
Is there another reason why we can't date?
I have no intention of dating Mr Min Hyo Sang's sister.
That's not a problem. I'll remove myself from the family registry.
- What? - Well,
I can't stand my mum and brother most of the time anyway.
So I've been begging to be removed from the family registry.
Are you kidding me?
I'm not kidding.
That's so good. I feel so much better now.
May I have some more broth, please?
This is the best I can treat you to...
by using up my month's living expense.
I really enjoyed it. Thank you.
The world you live in and the one I live in are very different.
Being different isn't wrong.
If they're different, we can just adjust to each other.
I won't do anything you don't like.
I won't bad-mouth your ex-girlfriend,
and I won't be selfish and do whatever I want.
So let's date.
I don't understand why you, who lacks nothing, is doing this.
I know you may laugh,
but I think it's fate.
Ever since the first time I saw you,
I just liked you.
Are you always this easy?
My gosh, I've never heard anyone say I was easy before.
I'm not an easy girl.
I have high standards.
Then why are you doing this to me?
You...
don't seem to know what a great guy you are.
You are very attractive and alluring.
Enough for me to fall for you at first sight.
So...
have confidence. Okay?
How can someone who doesn't love himself love someone else?
- Cheers. - Goodness.
Let's drink a little tonight...
to celebrate advancing past the preliminary round.
Once we make the final round, let's go somewhere nice.
- Okay? - Of course.
Thank you, Yun Shil, for your hard work.
You really showed off your sewing skills...
that you learned from Mr Lee.
Not at all. You helped a lot.
If we advance into the final round,
I'm sure Mr Lee Man Sool would be so happy.
It's getting cold now. I'm worried about him.
I was confident and said...
I'd get Mr Lee to come back within a month if I took over the shop.
- Should I get some soju? - It's okay.
I have some stuff to take care of.
I'm going to go home early.
Is something wrong?
No. I think I'll be late tomorrow. Maybe an hour or two. I'm sorry.
Don't be. You've been working late a lot lately.
Nothing's wrong, right?
No, I'll tell you later. It's nothing serious.
I'll go with you.
The kids should be home soon.
I'll go too, then.
Let's drink more. We have a lot of beer left.
Yes. Drink more. It's a happy occasion.
I'll see you.
See you tomorrow.
- Drink. - Okay.
I'll carry you home again if you get drunk, so don't worry.
What? So it was you...
who carried me home last time after all, wasn't it?
Yes, it was.
Then why did you lie that it wasn't?
I don't know. Maybe I was afraid that if I told you the truth,
you'd be moved and like me.
You and your corny jokes.
You are so random.
(Wolgyesu Tailor Shop)
We should go, too.
We drank a lot.
Yes, we should.
Excuse me.
Hello.
I went to see him not long ago.
Yes, of course. He's doing well.
Everything's fine, so don't worry.
Right now?
I finished work and came home.
Yes. I go home early, so don't worry.
Okay. Good night.
She'd worry if I told her I was drinking,
so I lied that I was home.
Why are you so stupid?
- What? - You don't need to live like that.
You're the one losing out.
Why are you always so apologetic and submissive?
He's the one who committed a crime and got arrested during the wedding.
She's the one who is is rude...
for acting like your mother-in-law when you didn't even get married.
Why can't you be confident and speak up for yourself?
You know my situation.
Your late father is your father. You are you.
How long will you let that hold you down and silence you?
Who in this day and age is that stupid?
Why are you getting angry all of a sudden?
It's because I feel bad.
It bothers me, that's all.
Whenever I see you,
I feel bad. So please don't make me worry.
I'll take care of myself,
so don't worry about me.
Whatever.
Please be wise.
Don't think about others. Think about yourself.
I'll go now.
I'm talking right now. That's rude.
You said to think about only me.
I'm tired, so I'm going to go home and get some rest.
I can go alone. You should go home.
I can't let a woman walk home alone at night.
It isn't that way.
- What? - It isn't that way.
It's this way.
Oh, is it?
You seem drunk. You should go home.
I can go on my own.
I'm fine. Stop saying I'm drunk.
Don't be too upset...
about what I said earlier. I was just upset, that's all.
I know you were just being thoughtful.
You're right.
I was being thoughtful of you.
I think a lot about you.
True. Even I think I'm pathetic.
I'm sure it must be frustrating for you to watch.
I can see why you're worried.
That's not it.
Never mind. Forget it.
Why don't you dress more warmly?
- I'm fine. - You always say you're fine.
Is that all you know how to say?
I'm fine.
You are not fine. You're sniffling.
I'm not fine, that's why.
I'm really fine. Thank you.
The sneakers are comfortable, too.
That's good.
Why don't you wear your sneakers?
When would I wear sneakers when I wear suits all the time?
Then why did you buy those sneakers?
I bought them for when I exercise.
I see.
Stupid.
Thank you for tonight. Get home safely.
It's cold. Go in.
After you leave.
Go first. It's dark. Be careful going up the stairs.
Okay. Good night.
His scarf.
He must have left already.
He hasn't left yet.
- Are you still here? - What?
- Yes. - What are you doing in the cold?
I wanted to sober up first. I'm leaving now.
Wait a second.
What? What are you doing?
I want to give you your scarf back.
It's okay. I'll take it.
Get home safely.
Why is he angry now?
Why are you home so late?
We passed the preliminary round of the competition,
so we had a drink.
Sam Do came home a while ago.
Yes. He said he had something to do early tomorrow,
- so he left early. - Then...
were you drinking with Ms Geum and Yun Shil?
Yes.
- Yun Shil is a good worker, right? - Yes, she is.
Your dad used to compliment her that she was good with her hands.
So even if you're not that fond of her,
be nice to her.
You seem to really like her a lot.
She's a kind-hearted girl,
and she treats both me and your dad with respect.
I'd love to find her a husband...
before that good-for-nothing fool gets out of prison.
(Gamjatang)
This place is the best.
Dong Sook, have some coffee.
Did you enjoy your meal?
Yes, kind of.
This restaurant is famous. All the drivers in Korea know it.
It's known for its good food.
It caters to drivers, but now most of the customers are like us.
For just six dollars, you get stir-fried pork, seafood pancake,
japchae, ricecakes, sikhye and coffee.
Where else can you get a full-course meal at that price?
It's a rarity in Seoul.
It's the best.
I see.
Are you...
a bit upset because I took you to a cheap place on our first date?
Do you think I bought two buildings in Jongno...
by spending money like everyone else?
A landlord is the highest power ever.
I save up to buy buildings.
Get in.
So...
I planned the whole course since it was our first date.
I wonder if you enjoyed yourself.
I should go inside. Have a good night.
- Dong Sook. - What are you doing?
We aren't children. We're adults,
and we've been through a lot, so let's not waste time.
I won't beat around the bush.
Let's get straight to the point.
What point?
Don't act like you don't know. What do a couple do after a date?
Close your eyes and relax your lips. I'll move in and do the work.
- Dong Sook. - Stop right there!
Hands down.
Is it you again?
- You need to control your hands. - What do you mean?
Last time, you grabbed her hand without her permission,
and now it's a hug.
This is assault.
It's what? What are you talking about?
Dong Sook, did I really do anything to assault you?
No.
No?
He tried to hug you without asking for your permission.
That's none of your business.
Drive home safely.
Dong Sook. I... Dong Sook!
I almost... I was just about to...
Why you little...
Did you see that? I held back.
If you get between us once more, I won't hold back then, okay?
I almost...
That was so close.
She's serious about this.
But then, he looks okay, and he owns two buildings in Jongno.
Any woman would like that.
Why did you shower for so long?
I showered thoroughly to prepare for an important event.
An important event? Shall we do our homework?
Don't get excited when I'm not even in the mood.
The OBGYN called earlier today.
We have an appointment for tomorrow.
Do we?
Tomorrow will be the last time we talk about that.
What does that mean?
- Are you going to bed already? - Yes. I'm tired.
Why? You didn't do anything.
This needs to be dry-cleaned.
What's this?
(Post-vasectomy guidelines)
"Post-vasectomy guidelines"?
What has he done?
Get up.
Get up right now.
Will you just let me sleep?
Get up before I count to three.
In 1, 2, 3!
What is it this time?
- What's this? - What's that?
What did you do behind my back?
That's because... I tried talking to you so many times,
but you wouldn't stop talking about having a baby...
So what?
Did you see a doctor without talking to me?
Then...
are you useless now?
That's not how it works.
You jerk!
Sam Do. How... How could you do this to me?
- You scumbag! - It's not like that.
How dare you. How dare you.
Stop it. It hurts.
Does it? I'll beat you to a pulp tonight.
You know my lifelong dream is to become a mum.
How could you get a vasectomy without talking to me first?
Stop it. It hurts.
You should respect your husband.
You don't deserve respect.
- Stop it. - You deserve a beating.
Don't stop me.
It really hurts. Stop it.
I hit to hurt, not to tickle.
- I'll call the police. - Call them!
They'll have a murder-suicide on their hands.
You can't hit me there.
Save me! Is anyone there?
What's going on?
Sam Do.
Save me. Get my wife off me.
What?
What's going on?
Sun Nyeo, what happened?
It's between us. Get out.
- That's enough. - Calm down.
Relax. Let's see if we can talk this out.
Stay down. I'm not done with you!
I said stop. There's a limit to my patience.
You know how much I want to have a baby.
How could you do this?
How could you do something so cruel to me?
What's wrong? What did you do?
Each time she gets so stubborn,
I really think I'd rather die.
I should be saying that!
Can we please face reality?
We're both too old to go on wanting a baby.
I'm afraid that...
you'll go on about it until I'm 60 unless I get a vasectomy.
Is it wrong for me to want to get it done?
Did you get your tunnel tied?
No, not yet. I just made an appointment.
You aren't a husband.
Think about how you punched and kicked me.
You aren't a wife.
I won't let you off so easily!
Sun Nyeo.
Try to calm down a bit.
Drink this and cool down.
Her reaction didn't surprise me much.
Her lifelong dream is to have a son that looks like you.
You're just...
dashing her hopes in one swoop.
I know how she feels.
But she keeps getting her hopes up only to get disappointed.
She gets so stressed, and seeing her...
get upset when it doesn't work out...
It breaks my heart.
It's hard on me, too.
I got so worked up that I booked for the procedure...
so we could stop getting our hopes up altogether.
It may be impossible,
but that dream...
could be the strength that keeps her going.
Just like...
how my dream of making a successful comeback...
gives me the strength to keep going.
Sun Nyeo will have to give up as time goes by.
So...
let her dream until then.
Let her be.
You're more thoughtful than I am.
I went through a lot, you see.
Sam Do.
You really didn't get the surgery done, right?
Not yet. Shall I show you?
It's still intact.
I only made a reservation.
Okay, then.
Thank you.
It was the perfect date.
It wasn't a date.
We had dinner and tea together.
Then you brought me home.
What is it if it's not a date?
The dinner and tea was to make up for what you bought me.
I brought you home because...
you insisted you wouldn't take a taxi.
I came along because I couldn't let you walk alone.
You never let me have the last word.
Look who's here. It's Kang Tae Yang.
I wasn't feeling well,
so I asked him to bring me home.
Didn't you stay home today?
I went in for a bit this afternoon.
I should go.
What's going on?
- What? - Do you...
have a crush on him?
What's wrong with you?
Where did you go? Why did you ignore my calls?
I went to work.
What for? You were half-dead.
I had some paperwork to take care of.
Mum.
I think she's up to something.
- What do you mean? - Kang Tae Yang.
He brought her home tonight.
Who's he?
- That employee of hers? - Yes.
- He came to our door? - I saw them together.
I should teach her a lesson.
Mum.
Don't get involved. It'll only backfire.
- I'll deal with it. - Will you?
I have a plan.
What are you doing here?
I have something to say.
If you want to tell me to quit my job,
just go home.
Hyo Sang...
knew everything.
He knew about our relationship.
- What? - He knew everything,
and that's why he gave you the job.
- Is that true? - It is.
I just found out.
Why did he give me a job when he knew who I was?
He wanted to know about you.
He wanted to see if you were a worthy competitor or not.
I bet he had fun...
watching us try to pretend to be strangers when he knew...
all about our past.
- What? - Unless you want to act a fool,
quit your job.
That's what I wanted to say.
What about you?
What will you do?
Nothing will change.
He said he'll forgive me and let everything slide.
I'll go back.
You didn't do anything to deserve forgiveness.
Someone of his status can meet and date women...
who are way better than me.
But he still chose me.
Unlike what he expected,
I have a shameful past.
Do you think that makes sense?
Are you out of your mind?
Whether it makes sense or not isn't important.
I will marry Hyo Sang at all costs.
That's how...
I'll escape my disgusting reality.
I won't ask you to come back to me.
But you can't marry someone like him.
If you hadn't agreed to work at Meesa Apparel,
things wouldn't have gotten this twisted.
Hyo Sang will use our relationship to blackmail me forever.
I'll think of it as something I have to go through for leaving you.
He seemed quite drunk.
Did he get home safely?
Should I give him a call?
I'm sure he got home safely.
My goodness.
- Hello? - It's me.
Is something the matter?
Where are your manners?
What do you mean?
- Did I do something wrong? - You bet you did.
I hadn't sobered up when I left your place.
You could've called to check on me.
Isn't that basic manners towards one of your coworkers?
I am your interim boss,
but do I have to give you instructions for everything?
I was actually just wondering if you had...
gotten home safely.
Were you?
Are you saying that because you feel bad?
I'm not.
Fine, then. See you tomorrow.
What was that about?
So she was worried.
I was really surprised to hear that you volunteered to be a judge...
even during your tight schedule.
I wanted to check how the Korean tailors are doing,
and also see if there are any artisan tailors we can partner with.
Artisan tailors. Exactly my point. You know Meesa Apparel.
We're the ones who possess the best tailors in the country.
You might have the best technicians,
but I'm not sure if you have the best tailors, as well.
In fact, Mr Lee said he was going to show us...
how to prepare for the artisan tailors.
I'm afraid Mr Lee no longer works for Meesa Apparel any more.
Mr Lee resigned from Meesa Apparel?
Yes.
- Oh, hello, Mr Lee. - Mr Moravia.
It's a pleasure to see you again.
- It's been a while, Dong Jin. - Yes. It has been a while.
President Min said you resigned from Meesa Apparel.
Yes. I returned to my father's tailor shop.
- Your father owns a tailor shop? - That's right.
It's an inherited family business.
It will be 100 years old next year. It's a very traditional tailor shop.
100 years old?
I didn't know there was a 100-year-old tailor shop in Korea.
- He's the Master Tailor, Sam Do. - Nice to meet you.
Hello.
We like the same colours.
And this is Yun Shil who takes care of the sewing.
- Nice to meet you. - Nice to meet you.
(Bespoke Suit Tailoring Competition)
(Bae Sam Do, Wolgyesu Tailor Shop)
Master, don't get too nervous.
Do as you always do, and you'll take the Grand Prize.
We shall begin...
the 31st Bespoke Suit Tailoring Competition...
hosted by Korea's Tailor Society and sponsored by Meesa Apparel.
Let me introduce the guest of honours...
who helped make this event possible.
Mr Park In Woo, the President of Korea's Tailor Society.
President Park Bong Tae.
Mr Min Hyo Sang, CEO of Meesa Apparel.
Ms Min Hyo Joo, Board President of Meesa Foundation.
There's also a gentleman...
who came all the way from Italy just to attend this event.
Please welcome Mr Gianni Moravia, the head designer of Tonelli,
the greatest bespoke suit company in Italy.
This is the first day of the competition.
Let it begin.
Let's go, Wolgyesu Tailor Shop.
Watch your step.
I'm going to make a quick phone call.
- Okay? - Okay.
(Bespoke Suit Tailoring Competition)
It's me.
There's something you need to take care of.
Excuse me.
Haven't we met before?
- Yes. - Do you still work there?
- Yes. - Ms Choi...
had asked me to find you a nice job.
If you learned from Mr Lee, you must be a talented seamstress.
I'll find you a job at Meesa.
Send me your resume.
She's a crucial member of my team.
I can't let you do that.
It's been a while.
It's nice to see both you and Hyo Sang today.
You look like you're doing well.
Do I? Thanks.
Your mother...
asked me to find this woman a job.
She has a name. It's Na Yun Shil.
- What? - She's a talented...
and important employee of our tailor shop.
I wouldn't exchange her with anyone at Meesa Apparel.
Is that so? You think very highly of her.
It was good to see you.
Let's go inside.
Yes, Sir.
Was that all for show?
Hyo Sang knew everything.
He knew about our relationship.
- What? - He knew everything,
and that's why he gave you the job.
(Letter of Resignation)
Mr Kang?
Yes, Sir?
The PR Team needs help.
We're sponsoring the Bespoke Suit Tailoring Competition,
and we need video footage.
Do you know how to use a camcorder?
Yes.
Good. Get over there, then.
Okay.
Where is Mr Kang?
I sent him out to do something for the PR Team.
- Without my permission? - Pardon?
Any one of you four could've gone instead.
Why did you send Mr Kang?
(Bespoke Suit Tailoring Competition)
Hello.
- Tae Yang. - Why are you here?
The PR Team asked me to take some video footage.
Hello, Sam Do.
- Hi there. - Good luck.
Okay.
(Ms Min Hyo Won)
(Bespoke Suit Tailoring Competition)
Hello?
Why did you leave without my permission?
The PR Team said it was urgent.
Come back right now.
Now? Is something wrong?
It's urgent. Get back here immediately.
What is it this time?
Yun Shil, I have to go back on some urgent business.
Watch the camcorder for me.
Okay.
Where is everyone else?
I sent them all out.
Why did you call me back?
I wanted to talk about our future.
Or rather, I wanted to talk about the future of Meesa Apparel.
What?
Let's not do this here. Shall we go to a nice cafe?
My treat.
(Letter of Resignation)
What is this?
My letter of resignation.
Do you mean you're going to quit?
Yes.
- Is it because of me? - No.
Then why do you want to quit?
I can't tell you the details,
but I'll leave as soon as I finish my current project.
Is this a joke?
How can you quit on a whim?
Are you that irresponsible?
I'm sorry.
Kang...
Thank you very much.
The contestants can put your finished jackets...
on the mannequins and then leave the hall.
Aren't you tired?
That feels good.
Well done.
- Thanks. - No problem.
You did really well.
I gave it my best, but I'm not sure if we'll win.
I thought your suit was the best.
I agree. Your jackets drop in a very elegant line.
I'm not sure how to deal with such praise.
Shall we eat dinner on the way back?
My mum said she'd have dinner waiting for us.
Join us.
I have to go somewhere else. You can go without me.
Okay, then. Let's go, I'm starving.
- Bye. - Okay.
Mr Lee.
Yun Shil.
I didn't call ahead because I knew you'd just tell me...
not to come by.
Today was the first day of the competition. I came right over.
Did everything go well?
Yes. Our suit was the best, even from a distance.
How is she doing?
You need to come inside. She isn't well.
Are you all right?
It must've been a long day. Eat all you want.
- Thank you. I will. - Good.
She cooked gochujeon, your favourite.
It's seedless, like you.
What do you mean?
She doesn't mean anything.
Why didn't you bring Yun Shil with you?
It would've been nice if she joined us.
She had to be somewhere.
Don't sigh like it's the end of the world.
Is this about Leather Jacket?
It's not.
Don't blame an innocent man.
Should I have invited Mr Park, too?
Why would you do that?
- I won't eat if you do. - Me, neither.
I won't eat if you invite him.
What's the matter?
Hello?
It's me.
Is something wrong?
How is she?
She just passed away.
And my father?
He's inside.
If it hadn't been for you, Mi Soon,
I might not have...
become a tailor at all.
You were the first customer...
who believed in me and praised me.
I promised to make you an outfit you could wear...
on an outing.
Thank you for letting me keep that promise.
Goodbye.
(Bespoke Suit Tailoring Competition)
Sam Do.
- Why are you here? - It's the last day.
I'm here to cheer you on. Good luck.
Thanks.
Keep it up.
I'm not doing anything.
- It's been a while. - It's good to see you.
We shall begin...
the procedures of the last day of the competition.
The contestants...
will now take their places and prepare to get to work.
- Good luck. - Good luck.
Good luck.
You're the best.
What's this?
What's wrong?
I didn't make this.
What do you mean?
Someone swapped the suit.
(The Gentlemen of Wolgyesu Tailor Shop)
What do you mean someone swapped the jacket?
I think something weird happened.
Please check for us.
How about we go and have some fun?
Sun Nyeo's incredible.
What if Sam Do finds out?
- Dong Jin's changed completely. - What a failure.
- What was that? - I affixed my seal.
I'm saying you're mine.
I'm back, Gok Ji.
Do you know how worried I was?
Don't you think Mr Lee's been acting strange?
I think he likes you.
Wait.