(The following content may not be suitable for viewers under 15.)
SUBBED BY VIU/SA143 (Viewer discretion is advised.)
We shall begin the procedures of the last day of the competition.
The contestants will now take their places and prepare to get to work.
Wish me luck.
- Good luck. - Good luck.
You're the best.
What's this?
What's wrong?
I didn't make this.
What do you mean?
I didn't make this. Someone swapped the suit.
What do you mean someone swapped the suit?
This isn't mine, Dong Jin.
Look carefully. You must be mistaken.
I'm not an idiot. Wouldn't I recognise what I made yesterday?
This is an imitation of mine made by a novice.
This seam is warped, and it's too close to the shoulder.
The lapels are also shaped differently.
You're right.
Someone switched this on purpose.
Who on earth stole Sam Do's jacket?
- Who is it? - Calm down.
It's not here.
What?
It's not in here.
(Bespoke Suit Tailoring Competition)
- Over there. - That way?
Can I help you?
We represent Wolgyesu Tailor Shop in the competition.
- Is something wrong? - The jacket I made...
got swapped out.
That's impossible.
After the contestants left at the end of the day,
we locked the hall and restricted entry.
Do you think the jacket walked out on its own two feet?
Someone liked how ours looked and swapped it out.
Don't make such accusations without any evidence.
I made suits for 30 years.
Do you think I can't tell my work from someone else's?
I think something weird happened. Please check for us.
There's no way a jacket got swapped out.
How many times must I tell you?
The jacket on my mannequin isn't my work!
The security camera footage. Check that.
Do you have cameras?
Nothing was taped at that time last night.
What do you mean?
The cameras were turned off.
How did that happen? Was there a power glitch?
A power glitch?
The other cameras recorded just fine.
Why would only the competition hall have a problem?
See? Someone liked the jacket that Sam Do had made...
and turned off the cameras so he could steal it.
Where's the man who was in charge last night?
He went home this morning after an all-night shift.
Call him.
His phone's off. He must be asleep.
I can't and won't let this pass by.
I demand you investigate what happened and why.
Don't make demands without proof.
If you lost confidence, abstain.
What did you say? I won't abstain.
There's nothing we can do for you.
Hey, you!
He really doesn't care what happens.
Let's call the police.
Even if we report this,
they won't catch the culprit within the day.
This competition...
is over for us.
- Yun Shil. - Hey there.
Is something wrong? You look upset.
Where's Sam Do?
I think someone swapped the jacket that Sam Do made.
They went to the office.
The jacket got swapped? What are you talking about?
Did you check the security footage?
They were turned off.
Something smells fishy.
Someone did this in cahoots with the organiser.
No one could have pulled this off unless it was planned by...
someone who knows the procedures.
Wait.
Meesa's PR Team asked me to tape the competition.
I set things up and then went back.
That's right. You asked me to keep an eye on it, but I forgot.
It should still be rolling.
It might have caught something the security cameras didn't.
Where is it? Let's check.
This man...
Do you know him?
It's Mr Kim, one of Meesa Apparel's chief directors.
He's Hyo Sang's right-hand man.
Are you saying that Meesa Apparel stole my jacket?
What for?
Can you send this to my email?
- Sure. - My goodness.
Did you take care of it?
Mr Lee's team will be throwing a fit right about now.
What's this?
It's evidence of the theft you put Mr Kim up to.
What are you talking about?
The rat's taking off.
- Wait up. - Rats love to run.
We're coming for you.
Do you still fear me?
Why are you doing this?
I don't know anything about it. Leave me out of it.
Your childish bouts of jealousy...
aren't even worth making a fuss about.
Recuse yourself from the panel...
and give back the jacket you stole.
What are you talking about?
I said I know nothing.
Really?
Then I'll hand this over to the competition organisers.
Gianni Moravia will end up watching it.
Dong Jin, we caught the rat.
- He had the jacket. - We got it back.
Nothing's working out.
- I didn't... - Be quiet.
I don't know what he's been eating, but he's really heavy.
What's he doing with them anyway?
What should I do with this?
I think we should do as you said.
Someone who knows about suits should be on the judging panel.
I'm just a businessman.
I know nothing about suits.
You found a new boyfriend.
Why the long face?
Would you want to date a man like him?
I meet up with him because Mum wants me to,
but it's so frustrating.
- I can see why. - I envy you.
You married Sam Do. What more could you want from a man?
The grass is always greener on the other side.
The weather is so beautiful.
It is.
The sky's so blue.
Didn't you get a job at a friend's clothes store starting today?
I have to get going.
Didn't you get a job frying chicken?
I should get going, too.
- I really don't want to go. - I really don't want to go.
Hey.
How about we go and have some fun?
Shall we?
We didn't come here to look at cheap stuff.
Let's go and see...
what luxury brands look like.
What's wrong with you?
I said I decided to change the way I live.
There's no reason to slave away to save up.
I'll buy what I want and eat what I want.
How will you afford all that?
You're going too far.
Be quiet and come with me.
It looks like an expensive place. Are you sure about this?
It's just a meal. It can't cost more than a grand or two.
You're really incredible.
Hello, ladies. Do you have a reservation?
- No. - Come with me.
Thank you.
- Get my chair, too. - Sure, Ma'am.
- Let's leave. - Why?
It's way too expensive here. It's out of our league.
Did dating Cheapskate Park turn you into one, too?
I won't ask you to pay.
Eat whatever you want.
It's too expensive.
Are you ready to order?
- Are you the manager? - Yes, I am.
Could you recommend us something?
Something you think we'd like.
Oh, we'll each have a glass of wine, too.
It's good to have money.
Everything tastes so good.
I'll enjoy the meal and all that,
but don't ask me to split the bill once you see the receipt.
You know that...
I have no money.
Don't worry. I said it's on me.
Designer brands...
really are worth the money.
It is really pretty,
but won't Sam Do yell at you?
He wouldn't dare.
He has no right to.
Did you two argue?
Did he upset you again?
Without telling me, he secretly...
What?
How could he think of doing that behind your back?
Exactly my point.
I got so angry that I covered him with a blanket...
and punched and kicked him for a while.
- Did you really? - My lifelong dream...
is to have a handsome little boy.
I lost the will to live.
I feel just the same.
You might marry a man who owns two buildings in Jongno.
What's wrong?
So what if he's loaded? He has no soul.
What's that?
He's not a romantic like Jun is, and he doesn't show emotion.
- He lacks the artistic spirit. - Poor you.
Art doesn't put food on the table.
I wanted a love like a character in a romance novel.
Other husbands put their wives on pedestals.
Why don't our men know what we want?
My point exactly.
Let's drink.
(Bespoke Suit Tailoring Competition)
The other contestants are almost done.
Shouldn't we ask the organiser for an extension?
Sam Do can do this. Let's trust him.
He would've won hands down if it hadn't been for...
the thieving Meesa rats.
This is a disaster.
Keep going, Sam Do.
I guess I'm not too late.
- Dad. - Mr Lee.
Here you are.
Hello, Sir. I'm Tae Yang, Yun Shil's friend.
You made me a suit for my job interview.
It's been a while since we last met.
Hello, Sir, I'm Sung Jun.
I rent a room on the second floor of your house.
Hello.
Where's Sam Do?
Right here.
Hello, Sam Do.
Mr Lee.
You're doing well.
Is it really you?
Dong Jin, am I hallucinating?
I know it's been a while, but don't act like you saw a ghost.
I'm sorry. I wasn't expecting to see you.
Thank you for coming back.
Let's catch up later.
How is it going?
I'll explain later, but there was a mishap.
I'm not sure I can finish it in time.
- Can I have a look? - Sure.
You did well.
Just one thing.
Push the shoulder line just a bit...
to the outside.
That will change the centre of gravity...
and prevent the suit from sagging to the back.
It's good that you kept extra fabric in the shoulder and back.
Make sure that those parts...
and the collar overlap smoothly,
and lean a bit to the front instead of pushing back.
That will add to the comfort.
I will do exactly as you said.
(Bespoke Suit Tailoring Competition)
The tips you just gave Sam Do.
It's a technique that Italian tailors use.
Did someone teach you?
Of course not.
It's something I picked up during my career as a tailor.
When I worked at Meesa Apparel,
I tried to incorporate the technique in our ready-to-wear suits.
We couldn't because it complicated the manufacturing process.
Yet you...
have been doing it for many years.
Making a comfortable suit is the goal of...
any tailor, whether he's from Asia or Europe.
May all the contestants...
put the finishing touches...
and leave the hall.
Thank you for your hard work during the competition.
I wish you the best of luck.
(Bespoke Suit Tailoring Competition)
You're the best.
(Letter of Resignation: Kang Tae Yang)
Did he hate me enough to quit his job?
How could he make me feel this distraught?
Hello?
Where are you?
I'm out, taking care of something.
- Let's meet up. - I just told you that...
I'm taking care of something.
Plus, it's the weekend.
I haven't had anything to eat or drink all day.
How can you be doing things?
How could you?
How can you think of...
resigning just because you don't like me?
I said it's not because of you.
Then why did you resign?
It's personal, so I can't tell you.
I'll hang up.
Wait. Hello?
It's personal?
- Where are you going? - What?
To see a friend.
- Which friend? - You don't know them all.
- Are you off to see him? - Him who?
I see right through you.
You're going out to see that Tae Yang boy.
You can't fool me.
I told you that...
Tae Yang and I aren't in that kind of relationship.
Whatever.
Hyo Sang told me that he was at our front gate a few days ago.
Is that why? Did you tell him to resign?
Did he resign?
Yes. He quit.
- Great. - How is that great?
A perfectly nice guy lost his job because of me.
Are you going to beg him to come back to work?
No. I won't.
You're not going anywhere.
That hurts, Mum.
Go straight back upstairs.
- Let go of me first. - Go.
"That hurts"?
(Bespoke Suit Tailoring Competition)
Ji Yun.
Why are you here?
I'm hosting the fashion show.
I'm glad we met. I wanted to see you.
Can we talk?
I have nothing to say to you.
I don't want to be too nosy,
but I feel sorry for you.
It's between Tae Yang and me. The third person can butt out.
- Ji Yun. - Don't try to give advice.
Just talk to Tae Yang for me.
Nothing in the world can bring us...
back together again.
How can you say that? I know how much you loved each other.
I don't have the time or patience to listen to your lectures.
Call me whatever you want. I don't care.
Is she the Ji Yun I used to know?
How can someone change so drastically?
Now for the winner of the Grand Prize.
For the elegant design and outstanding comfort,
it's CK Tailor.
(Bespoke Suit Tailoring Competition)
If it's not the Grand Prize,
maybe you won Grand Honours.
Don't get ahead of yourself.
It's time to announce who won the Grand Honours prize.
The award will be presented by Meesa Apparel's CEO Min Hyo Sang...
and Head Designer of world-famous Italian suit brand Tonelli,
Mr Gianni Moravia.
The 31st...
Bespoke Suit Tailoring Competition.
The Grand Honours goes to...
My heart's about to explode.
Relax.
The suit with the ideal proportions and ergonomic design...
shows that it was made by a great master.
Congratulations, Wolgyesu Tailor Shop.
You did it!
I told you so.
Was he actually capable of smiling like that?
May the winner...
- please take the stage? - Good job.
Go on.
You won the award. It should be you.
Yes, Sam Do.
Come with me, Dong Jin.
- What? - I'm feel nervous.
- Come along. - Go on.
(Bespoke Suit Tailoring Competition)
Wolgyesu Tailor Shop had the most impressive suits.
In fact, I'm excited to see that Korea has a tailor shop...
that's as nice as Wolgyesu.
I would love to work with you if I have an opportunity.
What did he say?
He said that our suit was the best.
He was very impressed and wants to work with us.
Thank you. Thank you.
The fashion show begins at 7pm.
It will be broadcast live via satellite to 23 countries...
and will show the world how great and stylish Korean suits are.
I will see you shortly. Thank you.
The fashion show starts soon.
This award is yours, Sir.
Thank you.
Dad.
No, give it to her.
Thank you.
How about we cheer for the winner?
- Wolgyesu... - Wolgyesu...
- Hooray! - Hooray!
- Wolgye, Wolgye, Wolgye, Wolgye - Wolgye, Wolgye, Wolgye, Wolgye
- Ready? - Yes.
Smile.
Hold the certificate higher.
- Like this? - Yes.
Try to look chic.
You look good.
Are you ready?
Run.
Hello? Dong Jin?
What happened?
Did you win the best prize?
Well done.
That is great news.
I'll cook something nice for dinner. Bring everyone with you.
Okay. Well done.
My goodness.
Man Sool would be so happy if only he knew they won.
I wonder where he is.
Where's Dong Sook?
I haven't seen her all day.
- Welcome. - Welcome.
Have you lost your mind?
We're both feeling a little down. Let's do something to cheer up.
No thanks. Have fun alone.
I feel that I lost out because Sam Do's the only man I ever loved.
Can't you play along?
Hello, beautiful ladies.
- Welcome. - How is it?
It's looking good tonight. There are cuties everywhere.
Come on in.
He said there are cuties everywhere.
Let's dance to just one song. I'll pay for everything.
I've never been to a place like this before.
You're so naive.
I used to dance the nights away when I was in school.
I'll take care of everything.
- So let's go in. - Come along.
I'm not sure about this.
My goodness.
Is this what they call a nightclub?
You're so old-fashioned.
I can't believe you've never been here.
Who is it?
(Mum)
I got a few missed calls from Mum.
Let's go home.
We can't leave as soon as we came in.
We paid the entrance fee.
Ladies.
The gentlemen over there want to meet you.
Say no. We have high standards.
Don't you like them?
Sam Do set the bar way too high.
Average-looking men don't do anything for me.
Let's just go home.
If he won't act like a husband, I won't act like a wife.
I'm going enjoy myself tonight.
- Let's warm up. - What?
I'm fine. Go and enjoy yourself.
Okay. I'll light the stage on fire.
Who's she?
What's wrong with her?
Who are you?
Lady!
Get lost, all of you.
The Bespoke Suit Fashion Show will begin shortly.
This is being broadcast live via satellite to 23 countries.
The tailor suit fashion show will begin shortly.
This fashion show will be broadcast live by satellite in 23 countries.
So now, let's give our undivided attention...
to the work of master tailors representing Korea.
We're the only amateurs among the professional models.
What if we ruin the fashion show?
Out of the four of us here, you look the most like a model.
Are you sure we should do this?
Yes. Anyone who can show off their suit the best is allowed...
to walk on stage, even if he's not a professional model.
Let's be honest.
You, you and you.
Your looks and my figure together...
means we can take on any professional model.
Look.
In 1, 2, 3, turn.
That's not your average walk.
You're awesome.
Have you done this before?
You still don't believe me, do you?
I used to be huge both on stage and off.
How many times...
would we get a chance to model, wearing suits that I made myself?
- Let's do our best. - Sam Do's right.
It's a once-in-a-lifetime event.
Let's make this a lasting memory, Ddong Jin.
I will. Just don't call me that.
- Okay, Ddong Jin. - I feel great.
It's my day.
Seeing you like this...
made me realise that you look great in suits.
You're right. We should make him model our suits.
If it's for Wolgyesu, I'll model for free.
Sam Do, make me a suit, and I'll model forever.
Forget it. I don't need you.
Get ready, everyone.
- It's time. - This is it.
Ma'am, Ma'am.
I said I don't want any dates. I just want to dance.
No one wants to date you.
Can you get off the stage? You're getting in everyone's way.
What?
You're taking up the whole stage.
People are complaining that they can't dance.
What's their problem?
They can dance in their corner, and I can dance in mine.
- Leave me alone. - I can't.
Sun Nyeo, let's go home.
- Already? - What do you mean?
You've been here for over an hour.
Let's stay for just one more hour.
It's Sam Do.
What's he doing up there?
He's doing all sorts of things now.
Why has he changed so much?
All that dancing helped me blow off some stress.
Don't worry too much about the baby.
It's fine if Sam Do says it is.
I'm afraid...
he'll end up having a son with another woman.
That's nonsense.
He would never do that.
You never know.
He says it's okay now,
but he might change his mind when he gets older.
You worry about things you shouldn't have to.
I'd have no worry in the world if I had a husband like him.
Dong Sook.
Leather Jacket might be good to date, but he's not for marriage.
Try to make it work with Mr Park.
Listen to me. I'm older, and I know better.
Hang on.
Who's that?
Where?
We know them all.
What's he doing there?
Sir, can you stop the car?
Today's the last day of the tailor competition.
They held a fashion show.
We should've gone there instead of the nightclub.
I could've cheered for Jun.
You're way too easy.
After all the trouble he put you through,
do you still want to support him?
You're right, but...
Let's play hard to get.
Be confident, okay?
Okay.
He looks so different in a suit.
Mr Park looks so ugly compared to my Jun.
He really is...
the best-looking man in Korea.
So what if he is?
He gives me such a hard time. What a waste of good looks.
- Did you get off work together? - Yes.
Hey.
Why are you two so late?
They did a fashion show after the competition,
so we couldn't leave.
- Dong Jin looked so different. - What?
Could you please bring me a glass of water?
Sure.
What do you mean by that?
He looks much happier now. He smiles a lot, too.
He even walked the runway as a model.
- Who? Dong Jin? - Yes.
Goodness. I find it very hard to believe.
He's so square. What has gotten into him?
I know, right? I wonder if he's already seeing someone.
He looks so much happier compared to a few months ago.
Shut it.
You have no taste.
You look dashing.
You look much more dashing than me.
We're here.
Mr Lee, are you happy to be home after being away for so long?
Of course. I'm very happy.
You haven't told Ms Choi that Mr Lee is coming home today, have you?
No, I haven't.
She won't be able to believe her eyes.
All right. Let's go in.
We're home, Ms Choi!
Welcome home. It must've been a long day for you guys.
I'm back, Gok Ji.
I'm here now.
Who told you that you can come back here?
You leave and come back as you wish.
I hate you so much. Goodness.
Then shall I leave again?
Not a chance.
I won't let you go anywhere. Never.
I'm sorry that I worried you.
I promise you that I'll never break your heart again.
How can you just write a letter and leave like that?
Do you know how worried I've been?
I'm sorry.
But...
you don't look well.
Are you sick?
No, I'm fine.
I missed you too much. That's probably why I don't look well.
Goodness, don't be silly.
Gosh, seriously. You're too much. You're such a handful.
I'm sorry to interrupt,
but please save the lovers' spat for later.
Go in and let us greet you properly.
- Okay. - Yes, please.
Let's go inside. Come in.
I'm so happy and grateful that you're back, Mr Lee.
I'm the one who should thank you.
You came back to the shop...
and helped us win such a renowned award.
I just did my job.
Move over a little.
- Why? - Come on.
Please take my bow.
Hold on.
Why are you bowing to my husband?
What does it mean?
Oh, nothing special.
I just wanted to do it to show him my respect as a tenant.
You want to be part of everything, don't you?
Everyone, let's go. Dinner is ready.
- All right. - Okay.
That looks heavy. Give it to me.
It's a late dinner.
There aren't many dishes, but I hope you enjoy everything.
Eat up, Honey.
Okay. Let's eat, everyone.
It looks delicious.
Mr Lee. May I ask what your favourite song is?
I'd like to welcome you and celebrate your safe return...
by singing your favourite song for you.
We're having dinner, so we should focus on eating.
Just eat your food and go to your room.
Okay, I will.
Ms Choi, I'm here.
Ms Choi? Oh, there you are.
Why is that bloke here again?
It's good to see you.
Mr Park is dating Dong Sook.
I invited him because I thought you should meet him.
Hello, Mr Lee. My name is Park Dae Sub.
Please take my bow.
I'll join you if that's okay.
- Gosh, please. - Hey. Ouch...
My gosh.
I even like the way you bow.
Why is he acting all friendly as if he has met Mr Lee before?
Don't you think he's too much?
He's going way overboard.
Yun Shil, can you bring a bowl of rice and soup for Mr Park?
Sure, that's no problem.
Oh, do you need something?
No. The rice is in here, right?
Don't worry. It's okay.
I can do this much.
You two look like a newly-wed couple.
- That's nonsense. - What are you talking about?
Why do you guys look so serious?
I was just kidding. I don't know why you're taking it so seriously.
Gosh, that wasn't even funny. Why did you come here?
I can't swallow my food there because of someone I can't stand.
It looks heavy. Give it to me. I'll carry it for you.
What was that about? Is something really going on between them?
I'm home.
Dong Sook is home.
- Mr Lee. - My gosh!
Dad! When did you come back?
I've been so worried about you.
I called you and sent you so many texts, but you never got back to me.
I'm back safe and sound, so all is good now, right?
Yes. I'm so glad that you're back.
- Thanks so much for coming back. - I'm glad, too.
We would've rushed home if we had known that you're back.
Thank you for making such a big decision.
I'm so happy to have Sam Do back at the shop.
I called the fried chicken place, and they said you weren't there.
Where have you been?
It's none of your business.
Gosh, seriously. This woman...
Mr Park. What brings you here by the way?
Me?
How can I do nothing when my future father-in-law is back?
I had to come meet him, of course.
Father-in-law?
How can you make such a rash remark?
What are you talking about?
I like that he's so straightforward.
Oh, boy.
What is that in your hand?
I went shopping with Dong Sook.
I got this 300-dollar dress for myself.
I also bought this 100-dollar scarf for myself.
And I got this 2,000-dollar designer purse, too.
2,000 dollars? Are you out of your mind?
You always do whatever you want.
I've decided to do whatever I want from now on like you.
You're honestly being so ridiculous.
I guess you're doing this because I booked vasectomy secretly.
You can't do this, though.
Let's sit down and talk since the topic has come up already.
I don't want to talk to you. Get lost.
What?
Do you want me to say it again?
Get lost.
- Mr Park. - Yes.
I'll say this again.
Please don't visit my place without my permission.
As you know, my future mother-in-law invited me today.
It's not like we're married.
It's uncomfortable to hear you call my parents your in-laws.
Marriage? We'll soon get married anyway.
What are you talking about?
When did I ever say I wanted a proposal from you?
"Proposal"?
Were you expecting that from me?
What's with women and their obsession with proposals?
- That's not what I meant. - I understand.
Just give me some time.
I'll put a lot of money into it and surprise you.
You just wait. Got it?
- Hey, Mum. - Hello.
You're coming home late.
- I work night shifts. - I see.
Let's see here. You've been working hard.
How about I give you some allowance?
No, thanks. I'll pass.
In this case, you just say thank you and accept the money.
Here you go.
Hands.
Hold out your hands.
Here you go.
On top of that, here's one more.
You thought I was done, right?
There's another one.
Let's make it 30 dollars.
- Thank you. - Sure.
Buy yourself something nice.
Dong Sook.
Now that I took out my wallet, I'll give you some allowance, too.
I'm good.
It's fine. This is nothing. Here you go.
What's wrong?
- Is it too much? - Yes.
It's way too much.
I can't accept this kind of money without having a heart attack.
Dong Sook.
She's even thrifty.
I like that.
She's quite the opposite to how she looks.
She has every right to be my wife...
You scared me!
- What is it? - 50 dollars? Is that it?
Are you sure you own buildings? You're lying, aren't you?
Hey.
Do you know how much wastepaper you need to recycle for 50 dollars?
There's a reason why you're still living on rent at that age.
Am I not allowed to live on rent? Are you trying to start a fight?
Here we go again.
Go ahead. Hit me.
This should make some pocket change. Go on. Hit me.
- What did you say? - You're pathetic.
Hitting other people takes money, too.
People who live on rent like you...
can't afford to go around punching other people. Got it?
Why you little...
I won't forget this.
Mr Lee and Ms Choi, I'll be going now.
I'll give you a ride.
We're going the same direction. Tae Yang said he'd walk me home.
All right, then. Have a safe trip.
- Are you done now? - Yes.
- Let's go, then. - Okay.
Where's Yun Shil?
- She just left. - Why did she go so early?
I packed all the side dishes and bulgogi for her to take home.
Give it to me.
- I'll deliver them to her. - You will?
Thanks.
I think...
I'll have to quit my job.
Why? Did something happen?
Mr Min found out...
about me and Ji Yun.
But all you wanted to do was...
prove your worth regardless of your relationship with her.
Don't rush into any decisions.
The thing is,
I thought I got the job because I was worth it.
But Mr Min knew of our relationship in the first place and hired me.
- What? - I think he wanted to play with us.
He enjoyed watching our reaction...
as he planned everything behind our backs.
What a jerk.
I should have known.
I should have known he's a wicked man...
when he switched our suits.
I know I'm desperate,
but I can't continue working there knowing his intentions.
Does Ji Yun know about this?
I heard this from her.
She's still not going to break up with him?
She said she was grateful...
for him not leaving her despite knowing everything.
She's not in her right mind, either.
I noticed that she's changed a lot when I saw her earlier today.
I'm having a hard time trying to understand everything.
I'm confused.
Yun Shil.
It's me, Dong Jin.
My mum asked me dearly...
to deliver you this food.
Open up.
Is she sleeping already?
Gosh.
Hello? Open up, already.
It's me, Dong Jin.
Isn't she too old to go to bed this early?
Goodness.
Goodnight.
Sweet dreams.
- What are you doing here? - Oh, gosh.
What?
Oh, I...
My mum got me to send you these.
She packed some food for you.
Well, I didn't want to come.
I'm really tired.
I asked her if I could give you this tomorrow,
but she kept insisting that I give you this today.
You know how stubborn she can get.
Right. Good work today.
- Let's go out drinking some time. - Sure, Dong Jin.
I'll see you tomorrow, Yun Shil.
I almost took the food with me.
I forget things these days.
I'll really go now.
Don't be wandering around so late.
Are you okay?
I'm fine. It's nothing.
I'll go now.
What's going on with him?
Mr Lee's been acting strange today.
I think...
he has a crush on you.
Who does?
Dong Jin, of course.
That's nonsense.
Why would he have a crush on someone like me?
That's impossible.
I think I'm right about this.
What are you talking about?
I'm certain.
Dong Jin has a crush on you.
Ms Min?
What are you doing here?
I've been waiting for you.
Why would you wait for me?
What do you think you're doing?
- I marked you. - What?
I marked you as mine.
Kang Tae Yang is mine now.
I'm not going to let anyone else take you away from me.
Ms Min.
Why are you being so unreasonable?
Are you mocking me?
Why are you so twisted?
I'm not mocking you.
I'm telling you that I love you.
I already told you.
I don't feel the same way about you.
But if you keep doing this,
it makes me think that you're mocking me.
I've never loved anyone like this...
in my life.
I fell for you when I first laid my eyes on you.
I constantly thought about you and missed you.
I don't care if you think I'm shallow and have no self-esteem.
When you love someone with all of your heart,
things like self-esteem don't matter.
- Ms Min. - My name is Hyo Won.
Hyo Won.
Hyo Won, I get that...
you're the purest person I've ever met.
But that's about it. I don't have any more feelings.
I see.
I guess I'm really not your type.
I get it. I'm not some stalker.
I won't continue to do this if you say so.
I'm sorry about everything.
I'm sorry.
You should be.
You should be sorry, Tae Yang.
Do you know why?
From now on, no other woman will ever love you the way I loved you.
I'm going.
I'll get you a cab.
Stop being kind to me.
If you keep doing this,
I might not be able to forget you.
I'll go now.
You're going to quit working at the tailor shop?
Now that there's Dong Jin...
and Sam Do, it's about time I step down.
Are you sure we can leave the tailor shop up to those kids?
Fresh eggs belong in a new basket.
They'll figure it out on their own.
But you spent your whole life doing needlework.
What are you intending to do all day without suits?
I'll go to nice places and enjoy good food with you.
I'm going to spend the rest of my life...
not as the tailor of Wolgyesu Tailor Shop,
but as Choi Gok Ji's husband.
You've grown up after your little deviation.
Stay by my side for a long time, Gok Ji.
What's gotten into you today?
Let me do one last thing.
Gosh. That's gross.
Thank you.
I'm always grateful and sorry.
I'm certain.
Dong Jin has a crush on you.
No way.
That's impossible.
That's nonsense.
I doubt it.
Here.
Na Yun Shil, You've gone out of your mind.
No, no. There's no way. No, no. It can't be.
Wake up, Na Yun Shil.
Know your place.
(Wolgyesu Tailor Shop)
You got here early.
Are you sick? You don't look so good.
I didn't get any sleep last night.
Why not?
I had some things on my mind.
- Do you want some coffee? - I'll do it.
No, I got it.
Are those pictures from yesterday?
What are these? These are all pictures of me.
It's 2 to 2 to 1, right?
I didn't say you could see them.
I'm sorry.
Hold on.
Never mind. It's nothing.
Wait.
I need to ask you...
I need to ask you something just in case.
Please don't take me wrong.
I'm just worried, that's all.
I know I'm wrong, but I'm just asking to make sure.
I know this is ridiculous, but I'm just asking.
By any chance, do you...
happen to like me?
(The Gentlemen of Wolgyesu Tailor Shop)
How can she say something like that so directly?
She's unbelievable.
He got really upset.
He looked me at me like I'm crazy.
You've grown up after your little deviation.
Do you want to run away from home one more time?
Why doesn't Sam Do want a baby?
Maybe he still hasn't forgotten about Young Eun.
How do you know Young Eun?
- I have a job offer, Jun. - Did you say, "trot"?
This is your opportunity to start a new life.
I got the wrong idea since you were so nice to me.
Why did I do that? Am I actually in love with her?