(The following content may not be suitable for viewers under 15.)
(Viewer discretion is advised.)
It's 2 to 2 to 1, right?
(Episode 23)
You can't go through those without my permission.
Sorry.
Hold on.
I want to ask you something, just in case.
I'm just worried, that's all.
I know this is ridiculous, but I'm just asking.
By any chance,
do you...
happen to like me?
- Oh, no. - I don't believe this.
How could you say something like that so brazenly?
How can you say that so nonchalantly?
I don't know. I think I lost my mind for a few seconds.
Pretend you didn't hear that.
How can I do that when I heard it so clearly?
Is something wrong with you?
I think so. You might be right.
I think I lost my mind for a while.
I didn't ask because I had an ulterior motive.
I just saw that you'd taken a whole load of photos of me.
I was just curious.
I know I was wrong, but I wanted to be sure.
I'm really sorry.
Were you very surprised?
If I were you in your shoes, I would have been taken aback, too.
Like I told you earlier, I didn't get much sleep last night.
I think that caused my brain to go a bit haywire.
If I don't get enough sleep,
everything in my head gets jumbled up,
and I can't do anything properly the next day.
What are you talking about?
Shall I get you a cold drink to help you cool off?
No, it's fine.
No, leave it. I'll clean it up.
Okay.
What's wrong with me?
Why did I say such a thing?
How am I supposed to face him from now on?
How can she say something like that so directly?
She's unbelievable.
Why did I do that?
Do I really...
No, it can't be.
Walking down this street with you feels like a dream.
It does.
Walking down this street with you...
makes me feel like we went back in time.
You can't leave us ever again.
Stay with us forever.
Will you look who's here?
Mr Lee, you're back.
Hello. How have you been?
Where were you all this time?
The whole neighbourhood felt empty because you were gone.
I had some business to take care of.
Mr Lee.
I was so afraid I wouldn't get to see you before I died.
I'm glad you're back.
You've gotten even younger.
- Don't say that. - Thanks.
- Mr Lee! - Are you well?
Yes, I am.
Hello, Seul Gi. It's been a while.
Seul Gi recognised you from far away and wanted to say hi.
It really is you.
Did you miss me that much?
You have no idea how badly she wanted to see you.
- Will you come by every day? - Yes.
- Were you sick? - Welcome back.
- Visit us often. - Sure.
Mr Lee's back.
Mr Lee.
It's been a while. Are you well?
Yes. Yun Shil told me that you had come back.
You have no idea how pleased I was. Welcome back.
Thank you for taking care of my shop for me.
(Lee Man Sool)
It's just the same.
Nothing has changed.
Of course not.
The store belongs to you.
No. Wolgyesu Tailor Shop belongs to you all now.
It's not mine any more.
What do you mean, Sir?
New wine should be kept in new wine skins.
Old people like me should step aside in due time.
Just like how I inherited this store from my father,
I now found people I trust to take over.
I can now retire with a happy heart.
I can't let you do that.
I can't handle this store without your help.
I have a lot to learn.
You can't retire yet.
You proved your skill and worth at the competition.
Now that I'm old,
my eyes are dim and my hands are clumsy.
They even shake sometimes.
Sir.
Listen.
With your skill, you and Dong Jin can manage this store just fine.
You have Ms Geum to rely on, and you also have Yun Shil.
Dong Sook, wait.
I couldn't sleep a wink last night.
Why not?
I knew you'd regret it.
I told you not to buy it, but you said you only live once.
Now did you get your senses back?
I wasn't in my right mind yesterday.
Can I go back and ask for a refund?
What?
You took it with you to a restaurant and a club.
- You can't ask for a refund. - No, right?
That's just wrong.
Can you buy this bag off me?
I'll give you a 30-percent discount.
I can't afford to buy an expensive handbag like that.
I'm even thinking about selling the handbags I already have.
You're right.
I'm already short of money this month.
I spent all the money we had saved up before we moved here.
I might end up penniless at this rate.
Good morning, Dong Sook.
What are you doing here?
I brought you this. One of my tenants...
gave me a box of crabs, saying her parents sent them.
I brought them to give to your mother.
You could eat them yourself. Gifts make me feel uncomfortable.
Don't say things like that. That hurts me a lot, you know.
Yes, Dong Sook.
He brought them for you. Thank him and say you'll enjoy them.
I don't want to, but thanks.
It's heavy. I'll take it inside and greet your mother, as well.
She went to the sauna. I'll take it.
Okay.
Crabs are all good,
but do you know what Dong Sook likes the most in the whole world?
What Dong Sook likes the most in the whole world?
That's me, Park Dae Sub.
My goodness. You're such a funny man.
The thing Dong Sook likes the most in the whole world...
are expensive handbags like this.
- Expensive handbags? - Dong Sook...
wanted this handbag so much.
You'd earn a lot of brownie points if you bought it for her.
Dong Sook, get over here quick.
- What? - Come here.
Do you want this?
Sun Nyeo.
This is unbelievable.
Yes.
If you want to buy it, I'll give you a 20-percent discount.
It's yours for 1,600 dollars.
1,600 dollars?
1,600?
Let's do this.
There's a building in Yeongdeungpo that I've been eyeing.
Once I buy that building, I'll buy this for you.
- Wait until then, Dong Sook. - You're so cheap.
Bags don't cost a fortune. Why wait until you buy a building?
I save up dimes and quarters to make a dollar.
That's how hard I saved up to become a landlord.
Not that story again.
I'm going upstairs.
Why...
Dong Sook.
Can you spare me some time this evening?
- What for? - To show you my buildings.
Once you see the buildings I own,
you won't even want a truckload of those handbags.
What's... What's that you're hugging?
It's a handbag that Dong Sook wants.
If you want to buy it,
I'll give you a special 20-percent...
I know how strapped you are.
I'll give you 40 percent off the retail price.
Is this the handbag that Dong Sook wants?
Yes.
If you give this to her, you'll earn a load of brownie points.
The day you give this to Dong Sook,
Mr Park will be thrown out of the picture.
- Keep it for me. - What?
I'll buy it off you when I make a hit album.
I shouldn't have asked.
Don't sell it to anyone else. I'll buy it off you.
When will that be?
What should I do with you?
Here.
Okay.
- Mr Kang. - Jun.
- Do you want to work at a cabaret? - A cabaret?
Someone I know manages one, and he's looking for a singer.
You value your pride too much. You'd never sing at a cabaret.
- Forget I asked. - I'll do it.
I'll go anywhere that'll let me sing.
How about I start tonight?
Okay.
He used to say he wanted to make suits until the day he died.
I don't understand why he wants to retire.
He worked hard his whole life.
I think we should let him take a break.
What? Do you have something to say?
Not. It's nothing.
He looks really angry. What should I do?
Why did I ask such a stupid question?
What's wrong with you, Yun Shil?
I'm really, really sorry about earlier.
I know how incredulous it sounded, but please forget about it.
What if the text makes him angrier?
No.
It's better to send it than not to.
(Send)
No. He might find it more infuriating.
What should I do?
- Do you want some coffee? - Oh, no.
What's wrong? Did something bad happen?
No, it's nothing.
- Just a moment. - But...
What got into her?
What an odd case.
I'm really, really sorry about earlier.
I know how incredulous it sounded, but please forget about it.
(Wolgyesu Tailor Shop)
Welcome to...
Mr Moravia.
I didn't know you'd come here.
Well, your tailor shop has the best suits I've seen in Korea.
And I know I'll regret it if I don't get some suits while I'm here.
So, I decided to stop by before I leave the country.
You want a suit from here?
Make me two.
I'm going to show them to my colleagues in Milan.
I'll keep one for myself...
and give one to the company as a sample.
What did he say?
He wants you to make him a suit.
Me?
That would be an honour.
Here you go.
15.
19-and-a-half.
24-and-a-half.
15.
I know you.
You're the rat who stole my jacket.
Thank you very much. I will send you the suit when it's done.
I'm looking forward to it.
Likewise. Have a good trip, and I hope to see you again.
Me too.
Thank you.
Gianni went to Dong Jin's store?
What for?
What? To get a suit made?
Okay.
Fill me in when you get here.
Nothing's working out.
I saw you at the competition, and it looked like you worked for...
Wolgyesu and not Meesa.
How do you know Dong Jin?
We're close. We're sworn brothers.
He's lost his mind.
I want to ask you something.
You hired me specifically for a reason.
- Is that reason... - Choi Ji Yun.
Why else would we cross paths?
I wanted to keep an eye on you.
I wanted to see who she'd been blindly in love with...
and if there were residual feelings I should be concerned about.
I wanted to clear that up.
You used me, then.
In a way, yes.
I will resign.
I tendered my resignation to Ms Min.
I don't think you're in any position to put your pride first.
I'm not quitting out of pride.
It's because I see this company has no future.
- What? - You hire staff...
out of curiosity about your girlfriend's exes,
and you steal a competitor's clothes during a competition.
I won't work for a corrupt CEO with no vision whatsoever.
How dare you.
Good bye.
Kang Tae Yang.
You came in freely, but you can't leave on your own terms.
You dared to make the first move?
I won't let you go so easily.
What do you think you're doing?
- I marked you. - What?
I marked you as mine.
Kang Tae Yang is mine now.
I'm not going to let anyone else take you away from me.
Hyo Won, I get that you're...
the purest person I've ever met.
But that's about it.
I don't have any more feelings.
What a jerk.
Is she crying?
What about?
I think something's wrong.
Is something wrong?
It's Ms Min. She won't stop crying.
Oh, dear.
Ms Min.
What is it?
Why are you crying in front of your staff?
Who said I was crying?
Don't get the wrong idea, people. My eyes are sore.
- They hurt bad. - Okay.
- Okay. - Okay.
You should know what I'm crying about.
Now you comfort me?
(Sample Request)
- What is it? - A sample request form.
I have to send them to suppliers and relevant departments.
I requested 10 of each.
(Min Hyo Won)
I'll take it to the CEO.
What a horrible eye infection.
I'm sure it's not an infection. Did she get dumped?
- Maybe. It looks serious. - It does.
Come in.
You wanted to see all the papers I sign.
- Here's my sample request form. - Let me see.
(Kang Tae Yang, TF Team)
Leave it here.
Why's your make-up a mess? Were you crying?
No. Mind your own business.
She's in a rotten mood.
(Sample Request)
Kang Tae Yang. I'm spending a fortune because of you.
Hello, Madam Ko.
Is Choi Ji Yun here?
Yes. She's getting her hair done.
You didn't tell her that I was coming, right?
Of course not. You told me to keep my mouth shut.
Okay.
Let's have a look.
Take a seat.
Some tea, Madam?
Yes, I'll have some rooibos.
Sure.
Hello.
Hi.
- Hello. - Hi.
Do you have a specific style in mind?
No. Just fix it a little bit.
Sure.
That's hot.
My goodness. I'm really sorry.
I don't think it touched your skin, though.
Are you calling me a liar?
- No. - It's hot if I say it is.
Give me a mirror.
Yes, Miss.
What if I end up with a scar?
Can't you be more careful?
I didn't touch...
I apologise. I'll give you free hair treatment to make up for it.
That's not the problem.
I tie my hair up often.
What if I end up with a scar on my neck?
I'm sorry. I'll be more careful from now on.
You even singed my hair last time.
You do nothing right.
Da Jeong's...
one of the better ones here.
She's pretty good at her job and serves her clients well.
Manager.
- Yes, Miss? - Get me another stylist.
I can't trust her with my hair.
I understand.
Go to the shampoo room.
Yes, Ma'am.
Someone has a nasty temper for a young lady.
Are you talking about me?
What the...
- Hello? - Madam Ko.
It's me, Bok Sun Nyeo.
Who's Bok Sun Nyeo?
Have you forgotten my name already?
I'm Bae Sam Do's wife.
Why are you calling me?
Hello, Madam Ko.
What business do you have with me?
I promised you that I'd bring you some kimchi,
but life got in the way and I forgot about it.
You seemed to like my Korean lettuce kimchi,
so I brought you some as they're perfectly ripe.
Is everything okay?
Something happened recently.
What happened?
Mr Lee came home last night.
- Did he? - Yes.
Also, my husband won the most prestigious award...
at the Bespoke Suit Tailoring Competition,
so we all celebrated last night.
Where was Mr Lee and what was he up to all this while?
He travelled the country...
and made free suits for people who couldn't afford one.
He goes out of his way to make his life harder.
What's that handbag?
This isn't the real reason I came to see you, but...
What is it?
I bought it at a department store yesterday.
Could you buy this off me?
I'll give you a 10-percent discount.
Why should I buy yours?
I swear that I only used it for one day.
I practically hugged it when I walked,
so there are no scratches.
No thanks. I don't even like the brand.
Then I'll give you a 20-percent discount.
Are you trying to bargain with me?
Of all the people I know,
you're the only one deserving of this handbag.
Could you please help me out?
It's not even my style.
Why did you buy a bag you won't even use?
I bought it out of spite after getting into a fight with Sam Do.
I can't afford this, and it doesn't even suit me.
I tried to live beyond my means, and I'm paying for it.
What was the fight about?
That is unbelievable.
How could he get such an operation without your consent?
My point exactly.
I got so angry that I saw red.
But why doesn't he want to have children?
He said it's because...
I can't give up despite my age, and I get stressed over it.
He said it's for my sake.
Wait.
Does he still miss Young Eun?
Who's Young Eun?
His first love.
His what? He had a first love?
Of course. Why wouldn't he, with his looks and build?
He told me that I was his first love.
No way.
He brought her to the tailor shop a few times a long time ago...
and introduced her to Mr Lee and me.
Who is that witch?
You startled me.
So who is that witch?
They grew up together in the same orphanage.
She was pretty and nice.
She used to smile a lot, too.
Where is that witch now?
Do you have to call her like that?
Where is that woman now?
How would I know?
I think I heard that she moved to Seattle after she got married.
Goodness.
Should I not have brought it up?
Well... It wasn't anything serious.
I'm sure it was just puppy love.
Don't tell Sam Do...
that I told you this, okay?
Oh, that's right. I'll buy this purse from you,
so don't tell Sam Do.
Just pretend that you didn't hear anything.
How much do you want for the purse?
- 2,000... - 2,000?
2,300 dollars.
I'm home.
People at the shop told me that you left a while ago.
Where have you been?
I had to take care of something. Have a seat.
What is this?
What are these rings for?
I thought about it...
and realised that I have never given you a ring.
When we got married, I couldn't afford it.
And since then, we've been preoccupied with running the shop...
and raising our kids while trying to make ends meet.
Honey.
I appreciate everything you've done, and I'm sorry that it's so late.
I got two rings for you...
to make up for keeping you waiting for so long.
Try them on.
Oh, my! They fit perfectly.
I've lived with you for long enough to know.
It looks like your little deviation away from home...
has matured you a lot.
I can't even recognise my hand with these rings on.
It looks like it belongs to a woman from a very wealthy family.
Are you that happy?
Of course I'm happy.
You've never given me a ring before.
I'm sorry. I should've been more affectionate.
How about you leave again?
What?
You gave me two rings this time. If you leave again,
you might come back with a gold necklace.
You silly.
- Would you like a cup of tea? - No, thanks.
I just came to get a glass of water.
I was just kidding earlier.
I just said it as a joke, but you took it so seriously.
Your reaction got me all flustered.
You don't need to worry about it at all.
Why is he being like that? Doesn't he know that I'm embarrassed?
Can't he just pretend to believe that it was a joke?
Gosh, this is stressing me out.
I mean, it's Italy's top suit brand.
I'm making a suit for the head designer there.
It's like teaching a fish how to swim.
Don't think like that.
You could have something Italian craftsmen don't have.
No. I think I should ask Mr Lee to make this suit.
What if I make a mistake and ruin our shop's name globally?
Gianni fell in love with your suit at the competition.
Don't worry too much and just put your skills to use.
- Hey, Yun Shil. - Yes, Master.
I wrote down the fabrics and materials I need on this order form.
Can you go to the fabric market and get them for me?
It'll be a very expensive suit.
I'd like you to feel the fabrics and check everything in person.
- Sure. - Dong Jin, you should go with her.
Just take a taxi, Yun Shil.
I have to take care of something urgently.
I'm going to the market.
Okay. See you later.
Well,
I know I said that I was joking earlier,
but I actually wasn't.
You've been so nice to me,
so I got the wrong idea.
People can get wrong ideas at times, you know.
I apologised to you in person as well as via text.
Do you have to make me feel embarrassed like this?
I should've been...
more thoughtful.
- Pardon me? - I was just worried as a co-worker.
That's why I treated you like that.
I guess my acts of kindness made you get the wrong idea.
I'm sorry for giving you the wrong impression.
I'll be careful from now on.
You don't need to apologise.
I talked nonsense to you like a fool.
I'm sorry.
Yes, I did the right thing.
I can't have her think that I'm leading her on.
What are you doing here?
I was waiting for you.
Why were you waiting for me?
You keep crying at work...
and skipping meals. I feel like it's my fault, so I got worried.
I thought I made it clear.
I may cling onto you again if you're nice to me.
I'm going to erase all memories of that day.
You should forget about it, too.
How can I forget?
It was my first kiss.
First kiss?
It wasn't your first kiss, was it?
Of course...
it wasn't.
See? I knew it.
Then how many girls have you kissed? Where am I on your list?
That's such an inappropriate question.
Second?
Or...
Third?
No? You can't count with the fingers of both hands?
Enough.
It's my loss. My poor lips.
I better get going now.
Where do you think you're going?
Take responsibility for what you've done, you jerk!
Are you all right?
- What's wrong? - I think I hurt my back.
Gosh, what should I do?
- I can't get up. - Really?
Ouch.
Please be gentle.
Hold on a second.
- Why? - Just a second. I'm in pain.
We're here. Get off.
I can't get up by myself. Help me get up.
What's wrong?
Ouch.
I can't get up.
Why not? You were fine when you were walking out of the hospital.
I was okay earlier because it was right after I got a shot,
but it's hurting again now.
What's that look? I fell because of you. How can you be so mean?
I'm not trying to be mean.
What do you want me to do, then?
- Carry me. - I beg your pardon?
Carry me to my room.
Ms Min.
I can't even get up. What am I supposed to do?
Shall I stay in the car all night?
Well...
Ms Min, what happened?
Please open the door.
Okay.
Is it Hyo Won or Hyo Sang?
It's Ms Min.
But some guy is carrying her.
A guy is carrying her? What do you mean?
Hello.
What happened to her?
What did you do to Hyo Won?
Mr Kang didn't do anything wrong.
I accidentally fell in the parking lot.
I fell on my behind and hurt my back a little.
- What? - I took her to a hospital.
The doctor said that it's not a serious injury.
She just needs a few physiotherapy sessions, so please don't worry.
Tae Yang. You haven't been to our place before, right?
My room is upstairs.
Sorry.
My gosh.
What is that girl thinking?
Gosh!
- Goodness. - Are you all right, Madam?
Leave me alone.
Thanks. Am I too heavy?
No, it was fine.
You don't look fine at all.
You're sweating so much. Gosh.
Halt!
You two.
What were you just doing?
We weren't doing anything. He just put me in bed.
Thanks for today.
I would've had to call the ambulance if you weren't there.
Are you actually injured?
Yes, I told you. Here, look.
The doctor even gave me medication.
Ouch, my back...
I'm in pain.
I should get going now.
What are you doing? Follow him.
Why should I?
He took me to the hospital and carried me. You'll just let him go?
It's dinnertime. You should offer him food.
You want me to ask him to stay for food?
You made galbitang this morning.
Fix a meal with that along with some grilled fish.
What is wrong with you?
Go catch him before he leaves.
Go on. Hurry up!
All right. I'm going.
Hurry up.
Have a seat.
- Help yourself. - It's okay. I'll just eat at home.
If I let you go without feeding you, Hyo Won, that brat...
I mean, my daughter will lose it.
No, I mean,
she will be very angry at me.
Why are you chuckling?
I think Ms Min takes after you.
That's what people say.
I used to be pretty like her when I was young.
You're still beautiful.
You know how to butter up the elders.
I mean it.
Eat up.
- Aren't you going to eat? - Not now.
I'm going to eat with my son when he gets home later.
Don't worry about me.
Thank you. It looks delicious.
To be honest, Hyo Won...
is way too much for you to handle.
Just being smart isn't enough to get married into a rich family.
It's nothing to be proud of, so I don't like to talk about it openly,
but people know about it anyway.
My older daughter married a guy from a normal family...
but ended up getting divorced.
Love couldn't conquer the difference in status and class.
So I suggest that you come to your senses...
and give up on dating Hyo Won.
I'm not interested in Ms Min.
You're not interested in my daughter? Why not?
This may sound rude, but she's not my type.
So you have nothing to worry about.
My gosh.
Well, I'm relieved to hear that.
But what's wrong with my daughter? Why is she not your type?
From her looks to her academic background,
she's certainly an amazing catch.
She is,
but what you're concerned about will not happen. Please don't worry.
All right.
He can be quite manly.
Shall I fix dinner for you?
No, it's okay.
Try this, too.
- Do we have a guest? - Yes.
Some guy carried Hyo Won home.
Someone carried her home? Who is the guy?
He's having dinner with Madam Ko in the kitchen now.
I see. You must like tteokgalbi.
Did Hyo Won get a boyfriend?
I think he was one of the models at the fashion show.
Who's Young Eun?
His first love.
His what? He had a first love?
He brought her to the tailor shop a few times a long time ago...
and introduced her to Mr Lee and me.
What a liar.
He has been lying to me that I'm his first love.
What is this smell? Are you going to burn all the chicken?
Gosh, I'm sorry. I was distracted.
Why are you getting home so late? I'm starving.
It's not like I was out playing.
- What about dinner? - Just eat this.
What are you talking about?
You can't even cook dinner for your husband who worked hard all day?
How can you tell me to just eat fried chicken?
I also worked hard all day.
Fix dinner for yourself if you want something else.
Are you really going to be like this?
It's up to me to decide whether I'm going to be like this or not.
Gosh, I'm so sick of this.
Sure, you're sick of me.
It's autumn now, so you must also miss your first love.
What are you talking about?
That little...
- Ms Bok. It's me, Da Jeong. - Yes, come in.
Here. This registered mail came for you earlier today,
and Grandma signed it for you. She asked me to give it to you.
Oh, I see. Thanks.
You're welcome. Have a restful evening.
All right. Good night.
I guess it's from the bank.
(Notice of Acceleration)
"Notice of Acceleration"?
"Certification of contents"?
(Total Amount Owed: 56,300 Dollars)
What is going on?
What are you doing?
What is this?
What's this?
Why are you asking me?
It looks like you agreed to guarantee someone's debt.
This is... I think I agreed to be a guarantor when my friend, Yong Suk,
from the orphanage was starting a business about 10 years ago.
Just a second. Where's Yong Suk's number?
The number you have dialled does not exist. Please check...
The number does not exist. What is going on?
What did I tell you?
I told you that you should never guarantee anyone's debt.
Hold on a second. This guy, Yong Suk,
would never eat up my money and disappear. I'll try to find him.
Come to your senses already.
We always had issues when you did this in the past.
We always ended up having to clear all the debts.
We lost our store,
and we're going to lose all of our money now.
When will we save enough to buy a home and a car?
Will we ever get to live like other people?
I'll just pay it off.
It's over 50,000 dollars. How will you pay it off?
We even got a notice of acceleration. If we can't pay it,
there will be seizure tickets all over the place.
You'll become a credit delinquent. What are you going to do?
That's for me to worry about. Mind your own business.
How can you say it like that?
- Am I a stranger to you? - I wish you were.
- What did you say? - You're always like this.
Nothing matters to you besides money and babies, right?
Gosh.
What are you doing?
Don't craw back in here before you get that money back.
- Are you kicking me out right now? - Yes, I am.
You should learn a lesson on the value of money.
Don't come back until you have that 50,000 dollars.
Okay.
I won't come back even if you beg, so don't worry.
You should run back to your first love, Young Eun.
Young Eun?
How do you know Young Eun?
You horrible man.
Get out of my face!
What's going on out there?
What's that suitcase for?
I'm sorry for making a fuss, Mr Lee and Ms Choi.
Where is Sam Do going?
I kicked him out.
- You did what? - What?
He guaranteed someone's debt without telling me again.
We received a letter of demand from the bank.
- What? - I'm sick of it.
I'm done cleaning up after his mess.
I can't do it any more.
I've had enough.
But still, how can you kick him out at this time of the night?
He'll figure it out on his own. I'll go back upstairs.
First it's you, and now it's Sam Do.
What should we do about him?
My goodness.
You said that I should leave you first
You said you only wanted me to see your pretty moments
You told me to leave you there
- Susanna - Stop right there.
- But this is the good part. - It's an opening ceremony.
You'll scare off every customer if you sing such a sad song.
We don't want you to sing a sad song.
Can't you sing anything cheerful? A trot song, perhaps?
Trot?
But I'm a rock ballad singer.
What? Who sings rock at a cabaret?
- The song needs to be exciting. - Come on.
- Sing us some trot songs. - What?
I think you've got the wrong person.
I don't sing trot songs. I'm a rocker.
- A rocker. - Hey, come on.
They really want to hear you sing.
Come on and sing us a trot song.
I'll pass. No matter how desperate I may be,
I can't just throw away my rock spirit.
I'm sorry.
Jun.
- Jun. - Don't come out.
Come on.
Dong Sook.
- Get in. - Are we...
going to eat at that diner again?
I can't take you to the same place again.
Today, I'll be giving you a tour around the two buildings...
I own in Jongno.
After that, we'll go to Gwangjang Market, and I'll buy you...
bindaetteok and gimbap.
Bindaetteok and gimbap?
Are they not to your liking?
They're quite popular at the market.
Fine. I know a nice snack bar next to that place.
Let's go there. They have more than 30 menus.
I tried all of them, and jjolmyeon is the best.
- If you order a large size, they... - Fine. Let's go.
- Okay. - Going somewhere, Dong Sook?
You do know that I own two buildings in Jongno, right?
I'll be showing her my buildings.
After that, we'll have dinner together.
- Shall we? - Let's go.
What a nice car.
A tour around buildings and a dinner date.
Dong Sook is getting what she deserves.
When will I ever get a car like that and give Dong Sook a ride?
- Excuse me. - Yes?
Can we turn on the heater?
- Are you cold? - Yes.
I've been coming down with a cold since the afternoon.
Oh, my. What are you doing?
You're being gross.
What do you mean?
I was just making you warm since you said you're cold.
Why would you do that? Just turn the heater on.
What are you talking about?
We don't produce any oil in this country.
You want me to turn the heater on and waste my gas away?
I'm a building owner.
If I turned the heater on whenever I wanted to,
I wouldn't have become what I am today.
You're ridiculous.
Why bother driving a car, then? You could just walk.
I love a woman who thinks like that.
Dong Sook.
You have all the requirements to be the wife of a building owner.
We're so perfect for each other.
(Wolgyesu Tailor Shop)
It looks like everyone took off except for Mr Lee.
- I can't do this. - What are you doing here?
- Be quiet. - Why are you acting so surprised?
What are you doing?
- What are you doing here? - Tomorrow's your birthday.
I came to see you.
That's not what's important right now.
- Let's go talk somewhere else. - Where are we going?
Let's go.
Here you go.
Do you know what kind of position you put me in?
What are you talking about?
You told me that Mr Lee has a crush on me.
- I did. - So I asked him in the morning...
and made a fool of myself.
You asked him that directly?
- Yes. - How could you do that?
He must've been embarrassed.
It wasn't like that. He got really upset.
He looked at me like I was some crazy woman.
That's not possible.
Of course it is.
He didn't even make eye contact with me today.
Why did you ask him that, anyway?
I was worried that he actually might have a crush on me.
Why would you be worried?
Someone like him shouldn't...
Well, I know it's not possible,
but if he does actually like me,
that would be terrible.
How is that terrible?
I'm not well educated nor do I have a wealthy background.
I also have Gi Pyo.
Technically speaking, you and him have nothing going on.
You have every right to see someone you like.
Don't think you're not a match for Dong Jin.
Stop saying things like that.
You made things get awkward between me and him.
He thinks I'm silly a woman.
I guess she decided to go home right away.
Dong Jin.
What brings you here?
I stopped by when I saw the lights on.
You did? Take a seat.
- Do you want some tea? - I just had some with Yun Shil.
Yun Shil scolded me during the entire time.
The thing is,
I told her something I shouldn't have.
It's my fault, not hers. Please go easy on her.
What are you talking about?
To be honest, I'm the one who told her that...
you might have a crush on her.
Why would you think that?
It's not like I have a clear reason,
but that's just what I thought based on my observations.
Was I mistaken?
Yun Shil is a good person.
It's true that I have good feelings for her.
But I'm not sure if those feelings are what you said they could be.
She's a good person.
But I think it's more like a feeling of sympathy...
for everything she's going through.
That's not what it looked like to me.
To be honest, I don't know what I'm feeling right now.
I'm trying to ask myself that.
So until I do find an answer, don't tell Yun Shil about it.
Can you keep the promise?
She already has enough worries. I don't want to bother her.
I understand.
Sam Do. What's all that?
This? I got kicked out.
- What? - What?
My goodness. This needs ironing.
I know how you must be feeling,
but you can't kick out the man of the family.
The two of you should join forces at times of hardship.
This is the third time...
he threw away money for guaranteeing someone's debt.
It'd be easier to make a cow understand...
than to get through to him.
I understand why you're upset,
but he might get really angry and never come back.
I don't care.
I have to get some sleep. Please take Ms Choi and leave.
He always gets used by other people.
I have to teach him a lesson once and for all.
Oh, my head.
I was just worried as a co-worker. That's why I treated you like that.
I guess my acts of kindness made you get the wrong idea.
I'm sorry for giving you the wrong impression.
I'll be careful from now on.
Why am I crying? Silly me.
Is that you, Yun Shil?
You didn't have breakfast yet, right?
Mum made seaweed soup for your birthday today.
You should come over before you go to work.
Don't refuse.
Mum made it just for you, so stop by for some, okay?
Okay. I'll see you later.
Is it Yun Shil's birthday today?
Yes. Mum made seaweed soup and breakfast for her.
Mum didn't want to leave her all alone on her birthday.
I see.
Hello.
Hi.
Ms Choi asked me to come and have some seaweed soup.
I heard that it's your birthday today.
Happy Birthday.
Wait.
People make mistakes and misunderstand from time to time.
Have you never made mistakes...
in your life?
What are you trying to say?
I know you're baffled and upset...
because of what I said to you,
but how can you change your attitude completely overnight?
Does it hurt your pride that much...
to be mistaken for...
having a crush on me?
- It's not like that. - Why did you buy me those shoes?
Why did you follow me to the temple?
Why did you bring me medicine and porridge when I was sick?
Why did you fix my sink?
Why did you walk me home,
worry about me and say nice things to me?
It's...
I'm trying to figure out why I did all those things.
You can hurt people's feelings with unintended kindness.
What are you talking about?
You're a well-educated and well-off man,
so I guess you took pity in me because I looked pathetic to you.
But you can't blame me for getting the wrong impression.
It's not like that.
To be honest,
I'm relieved.
About what?
I'm relieved that someone like you doesn't have interest in me.
Do you know how worried I was in case you actually did like me?
Is me liking you...
a worrying matter?
It's a good thing for someone to like someone else.
Why do you have to be worried?
It's my fault for getting the wrong idea,
but you're also responsible for giving the wrong impression.
Let's call it even.
That's all what I wanted to say.
I'll get going now.
Do you have any idea how confused I am with myself?
Call it even, my foot.
We agreed on each other's faults.
This is a done deal.
(The Gentlemen of Wolgyesu Tailor Shop)
Watch yourself. Just because the goalkeeper is missing...
doesn't mean you can play around with the ball.
- You must be in love. - What?
How low do you have to get to like someone like her?
Is this the best you can do? Do you know how much damage...
you caused to my company?
What happened? Is this because of the 30,000 dollars?
What's this, Mr Lee?
This won't be enough, but it'll help.
Everyone makes mistakes.
My acts of kindness weren't out of sympathy or pity.
I gave it a lot of thought. and I think I...