(The following content may not be suitable for viewers under 15.)
(Viewer discretion is advised.)
I'll completely forget about what you said to me yesterday.
You should do the same thing.
(Episode 26)
Is that how you really feel?
I'm asking you a question. Is that how you really feel?
Yes. That's how I feel.
Yun Shil.
I'm grateful that you like me when I lack so much,
but please stop here.
Do you not like me?
Or did I do something to upset you?
It's not that.
You know the situation I'm in.
I'm in no position to like someone else.
Hong Gi Pyo? Is it about him?
Let me make this clear.
Whomever you date,
even if it's someone other than me, Hong Gi Pyo can never be...
an obstacle.
I may be out of line,
but legally and emotionally speaking,
you are not his wife in any way.
Do you understand?
You'll need time to think...
just like I did.
I was too rash.
I won't force...
my emotions on you or rush you.
And I won't hate or blame you...
for not feeling...
the same way as I do.
Take all the time you need to think,
and tell me when you're sure.
I'll respect your decision.
Even if...
it's not the answer I want,
I won't stop...
liking you and...
wanting to protect you.
I should go.
Move. Get out of my way.
How did you find me here?
I said you can't get away from me.
- Look here. - Don't treat me like a stranger.
Call me by my name.
I'll find a job and pay you back...
for helping out my dad.
Will you please leave me alone?
Do you think I donated an organ for cash?
It's not cash I want. I want you.
I told you that...
I'm not interested in you.
Try to become interested instead of trying to run away!
Don't you see how I feel?
I don't know what I'll do if you keep running away.
I can't guarantee what'll happen to you.
You're here early.
Good morning.
I don't know for sure if it's the motor or the pump that needs fixing.
Tomorrow at the quickest?
I'll freeze to death tonight.
Can't you come today?
Give me a call.
- My goodness. - Did your boiler break down?
Yun Shil's boiler hasn't been working since last night.
Did she sleep in a cold room last night?
Her room was freezing cold this morning.
I need to get it fixed as soon as possible.
Hi, Seok Jun.
Can you put me in touch with...
a subcontractor that manufactures boilers?
No. A friend's boiler broke down yesterday,
and it needs fixing.
Yes.
Okay, thanks.
I'll text you the number to call.
See you soon.
Do you want tea?
No thanks.
I guess he's very upset.
I always wondered what your place looked like.
This is what it looks like.
I see.
You like cup noodles.
You need to go.
Only men can stay here. Women aren't allowed.
I could get kicked out.
Okay, okay.
This is insane.
Oh, no.
- I'm really sorry. - Why did you look in there?
What on earth happened?
Why did you leave home?
While waiting for you yesterday, I saw a notice saying...
there was an empty room, so I rented it.
- Why? - To be close to you.
But why...
- What about work? - I quit.
Why?
I like you, and I'm on your side.
I can't work for a company that fired an innocent man.
Stop being silly and go back home.
I paid three months' rent in advance.
I can't let the money go to waste.
- Who is it? - Can I come in?
What now?
- Is this yours? - Yes, it is.
It was hanging on the line, and it looked like yours.
Oh, so that's where my clothes were at.
Haven't you had breakfast yet?
I should get something to eat.
My mum sent me some ox bone soup. Do you want some?
No, but thanks for the offer.
- See you. - Bye.
I'm hungry.
Buy me food.
(Lunch available)
You can eat the egg.
Come on.
You eat it.
You always ate here alone,
so I thought you weren't dating.
But you have a beautiful girlfriend.
Thanks for the compliment, Ma'am.
I haven't seen you before.
Do you live near here?
I live with him.
I thought you two looked alike.
Are you newlyweds?
- We're more like... - Yes, we are.
We got married yesterday.
What are you doing?
Didn't you go on your honeymoon?
We need to save up.
We'll go on our honeymoon some other time.
Too bad.
But it's good to work hard while you're still young.
The good times will come.
What are you doing? Why did you tell such a lie?
It's not a lie. It's called role-playing.
What if people talk about us?
You're so shy and timid.
I'll take full responsibility.
I will marry you.
Here. I like your attitude,
so this is on me.
Thank you, Ma'am.
Chew nice and slowly, my darling.
- Ms Min. - See?
I got you free bulgogi.
There you go.
(Mum)
Eat all you want, my darling.
You're so cute.
There is no answer.
She's ignoring my calls.
Where on earth is she?
He's my first love.
I can't give up so easily.
I have to muster up my courage.
That's it. That's where she is.
She's with Tae Yang.
- Have you heard from Hyo Won? - Get me Tae Yang's address.
- What for? - I think...
she's with him.
I swear that...
he kidnapped her.
Mum.
She left voluntarily. That's not kidnapping.
He's manipulating her.
Get me his address.
You must have his resume!
Mr Lee.
We spent this much on fabrics this month.
We have to pay it by by today.
Can you approve it?
Sure. I'll wire the money later.
Do you have something to say?
No, I don't have anything particular to say.
I'm just concerned that you might be angry because of me.
I told you that...
I won't force my emotions on you.
I don't want to rush you, either.
I will take a step back.
Take all the time you need to think and decide what you want.
I'll respect your decision.
Ouch!
- What is it? - What's wrong?
- Are you hurt? - No, I'm fine.
That was close. You should be more careful.
Sorry.
Two people made online reservations for tomorrow afternoon.
Already?
Yes, it's working better than I thought.
Hello?
Is this Mr Lee Dong Jin from Wolgyesu Tailor Shop?
Yes, I'm Lee Dong Jin.
I'm reporter Park So Yeon with Jeil Daily News.
I would like to write an article on you and your store,
since you won the recent tailoring competition.
An article?
"Wolgyesu Tailor Shop".
Is the door stuck?
What are you doing?
The door seems to be stuck.
The entrance is over here.
Hang on.
If it isn't the landlord from Jongno.
I'm here to buy a suit from my brother-in-law.
What business does a nightclub singer have here?
"A nightclub singer"?
The sworn brothers of this nightclub singer...
offered to make me a bespoke suit, and that is why I am here.
Wait, "offered"? Do you mean for free?
Of course.
My brother-in-law doesn't know how to run a business.
No business does well if they give away too many freebies.
What are you mumbling about?
Me first.
He's a snake and a cheapskate.
I would just love to punch him.
Hello, my brother-in-law.
Brother-in-law?
- Why are you here? - Why else?
I'm here to boost your sales.
The store looked huge from the outside,
but it's actually pretty tiny.
What's the floor space?
Sam Do, I'm here.
You cut your hair.
Brother-in-law.
I'd rather you not call me that.
Why not? Everyone knows it's a truth and a fact...
that I will marry Dong Sook soon.
As someone who's lived longer and is therefore wiser,
let me give you some advice on life.
You shouldn't give things to people for free.
That's the quickest way to go bankrupt.
Tae Pyung modelled for one of our suits at the tailoring competition,
and the free suit is our way of thanking him.
Is it? Okay, then, make sure...
you make it quick with the cheapest materials and fabrics.
Don't waste effort on a non-profit case.
What style would you like, Sir?
This is a secret, but in a few days time,
I will propose to Dong Sook.
You'll propose to her?
It's a suit for that occasion.
I want my masculinity and my sexiness...
to stand out and create a synergy...
and make an explosion of attractiveness.
That's the kind of neat style I want.
I've been a tailor for 30 years,
and you're the first person to want a neat style where masculinity...
and sexiness creates a synergy that makes an explosion.
You don't seem confident.
That's fine. I shouldn't have come here in the first place.
What if I don't like what you make?
Please watch your manners.
He won the tailoring competition. He's a master craftsman.
A master craftsman?
I thought that's what people call bakers and chefs.
Are there master tailors, as well?
You may have a few buildings, but you really lack class.
I left out the most important detail.
How much do you think a suit like that would cost?
That depends on the fabrics you choose.
I know that, but you must have an average or an estimate.
How much is that?
This much.
How many zeroes?
(1,500 dollars)
This is...
How inflated is this price?
I can get a suit for 300 dollars at any market.
This is five times that.
Sam Do's suit is a work of art.
Don't compare it to what they sell at markets.
They still shouldn't charge me this much.
Are you trying to bleed me dry for just one suit?
How could you say such a thing?
You need to make a profit, I get that.
Give me a family member discount. I'm not paying this much.
Don't expect me to pay full price when we know each other.
- Go. - What?
I don't want to waste my suit on someone...
as ignorant and crass as you, so get out.
What did you just say? I'm ignorant and what?
Brother-in-law, why did you hire someone like him?
Get out of here before I beat you up and toss you out!
Get up and get lost before he punches you out the window!
What did you say?
Why do you always grab me by the collar?
- Get lost! - You, too?
- Let go! - Get out.
- Calm down. - What's wrong with you?
- Sam Do. - Do you have a bat?
- Relax. - You ruffians!
You scoundrels!
Just a moment.
- I'm coming. - Where to?
Wherever it is you're going.
It's not a place I can take you.
Where are you going that I can't come along?
Did you meet another old lady while you were away,
and are you visiting her every day?
Don't be silly.
If not, I can come with you.
I'll take you with me when the time comes, so don't nag.
See you later.
Where on earth does he go that he won't let me join him?
This is so suspicious.
Do you feel the raised dots here?
Yes.
Braille consists of six raised dots.
Here, 1, 2, 3...
and 4, 5, 6.
That's 2 columns and 3 rows, a total of six dots.
I see.
Do you feel these?
- The six dots. - Yes.
Good. Now, feel this line over here.
Find the odd one out in this line.
There's one that's missing. It's the 4th dot.
You found it already?
Your fingertips are really sensitive.
You'll learn braille in no time.
Practise a bit on your own.
Okay.
We all come across a trial in our life.
I believe a gentleman is a man who doesn't whine...
when he is faced with an ordeal.
I dreamed of being such a gentleman while I made suits.
It is time for me to overcome my weakness, pain...
and discomfort and be strong.
That is the belief I lived with for as long as I was a tailor.
I got a call that the loan I applied for was approved.
- Can I see some ID? - Sure.
- Here you go. - Thank you.
Of the amount you applied for, the loan we can give you...
is 10,000 dollars.
Thank you.
Fill in this form and the pledge.
- We'll wire it right away. - Thanks.
- Honey. - That's 40,000 dollars.
It's for you.
It's not for free. I expect you to pay me back.
Honey.
Who did you order so much for?
For me, who else?
I wanted to snack each time I passed by,
but I didn't just so I could save up.
Someone I know spent 50,000 dollars in one day.
I can't believe I stopped myself from buying...
a few dollars' worth of snacks just to save up.
It's so unfair,
so I'm going to eat today.
Slow down.
Drink some water.
It's all my fault.
You were the breadwinner, and even when I had nothing,
I co-signed a loan.
I'm really sorry.
How could you say you'll use separate rooms if you're sorry?
Yesterday, I got so angry that I just...
To be honest, I was embarrassed and out of excuses.
I was actually angry with myself,
and I ended up venting it on you.
I'll take it all back and move in.
I'll use the same room with you, too.
Do whatever you want.
I don't care.
I'll sign a contract saying I'll never co-sign loans again.
And...
I'll do my best with our homework.
Do you mean that?
I do.
If you leave home or retaliate again,
- it's really over. - You bet.
Can I eat something else? I can't stand pork liver.
It's good for men.
You need to eat well so you can do your homework.
- Open up. - It stinks.
Open your mouth.
Now chew.
Tae Pyung came by the store earlier.
He invited us...
to visit his workplace.
- At the cabaret? - Yes.
He suggested I bring you along to drink, dance...
and get rid of some stress, so I said no.
- What for? - You wouldn't like...
a place like that.
Well, of course...
I don't enjoy watching drunk men and women...
cling to each other and dance,
but Leather Jacket finally found a decent job after a while.
Let's cheer him on.
Do you want to go to a cabaret?
I won't be alone. You'll be there with me.
Let's see how other people have fun.
Shall we do that?
I'll come by around the time you get off work.
(Bespoke Suits for Department Store Customers)
Come and have a snack.
All the food here cost exactly 50,000 dollars. I hope you enjoy it.
Why did you buy all this for?
I got a bank loan,
and my wife chipped in to pay off the debt.
I bought this on the way back.
Did you make up with Sun Nyeo?
- Something like that. - Well done.
I ate more than enough, so this is for you.
- I need to wash my hands. - Okay.
Let's see.
- Here. - Thanks.
Here.
I'll use these.
Hello?
Yes, I'm Na Yun Shil.
You'll come over to fix the boiler now?
Okay.
I'll be there on time.
- Someone's coming by? - Yes.
That's such a relief.
I was worried you'd sleep in a freezing cold room.
- How did he get your number? - What?
I didn't give it to him.
Maybe you forgot you did.
Do you mind if I go home for a bit?
Someone's coming over to fix my boiler.
Go home, then. Do you know about boilers, though?
Dong Jin, why don't you go with her?
They'll be experts.
They'll know what to do.
I'm working on a proposal right now.
- Can you manage? - What?
Sure, of course.
I won't be long.
- See you. - Eat some of this.
I will when I get back.
- Eat up. - Okay.
(Wolgyesu Tailor Shop)
Why couldn't he come with me?
Yun Shil.
What's wrong with you?
Do you expect him to be nice...
after what you said?
I need to get a grip.
She should dress for the weather.
No wonder she's sick.
- Hi, Seok Jun. - They called your friend.
I just heard about it.
They sent their best technician, so don't worry.
Thanks a lot.
The motor broke down, so the control box has no power.
I think the condenser's broken, too.
Does it require a lot of work?
Not much,
but I don't have the parts, so I can't fix it today.
I'll have to fix it tomorrow.
Tomorrow?
What now?
You can't sleep without heating.
No, don't do that. The room's small,
but sleep with me in my room.
Okay. Come back to the store for now.
Can't they fix it today?
The man doesn't have the parts he needs.
She'll have to sleep with me.
Hello, Ms Choi.
- Your boiler's out of order? - Yes.
It's old and worn down.
Come over to my place after work.
I can't do that. It's fine.
It's not fine.
I'm weak and tired and won't repeat myself.
You can sleep here, so come by after work.
I will.
Thank you.
Hey.
Why did you take my juice?
"My juice"?
Yes, I was about to drink it...
when you took it from me.
You're really thick-skinned.
You drank two bottles of my juice already.
What kind of nonsense is this?
Are you drunk?
You're unbelievable. Why is this your juice?
- Is your name written on it? - Yes, it is.
"Young Hee". It means bright and cheerful.
This situation isn't bright or cheerful at all.
My gosh.
I didn't see it.
- Are you new here? - Yes.
You can't take other peoples' food.
I could make a big deal out of this. Shall I call the police?
I didn't know it was yours.
I thought the manager stocked the fridge.
I thought we pay when we leave, like in a hotel.
Like in a hotel?
Look around. Do you think we eat brunch here?
Looks like a weirdo just moved in.
A weirdo?
Don't swear. I said I made a mistake.
"Weirdo" isn't a swear word. Shall I really swear?
What's going on?
I drank some juice, not knowing it was hers,
and she called me a weirdo...
and glared at me with eyes like this.
She said it was an innocent mistake.
You shouldn't have sworn.
Manager, look. Who's older, me or her?
Look at what she's doing, and we just met.
I pay part of your salary every month.
Say something. Who's older?
This is a gosiwon, not a hotel.
You can't eat whatever's in the fridge.
I didn't know the rules.
They're posted on the kitchen wall.
Didn't you read them?
You shouldn't be here.
Pack up and go home.
I told you already.
I paid for three months in advance so I can't go home.
I'll give you the money. Go home.
Tae Yang.
(Mum)
(Peace Gosiwon)
Are you sure that this is the place?
Yes. This is where she is, Madam.
Come with me. Let's drag her out of this place.
Do not let her get away.
Yes, Madam.
This brat...
I shall teach you a serious lesson today.
Hey, Min Hyo Won!
Mum, how did you know that I'm here?
What do you think? My quick wits got me to where I am now.
Finding out where you are is a piece of cake!
This brat. This little...
Hey!
Open this.
Are you really going to be like this?
Mr Kim, why are you just standing there? Come help me open this!
Yes, Madam.
Hey, let go!
Let's see who wins, you wench.
Hey.
What are you doing now?
- How have you been? - How do you think I have been?
Open this now. I'll call the police if you don't.
We absolutely cannot let her in. What are you doing? Help me.
That little... Stop right there, you brat!
Mr Kim, go get her!
Yes, Madam.
Go away!
- Gosh! - What is going on?
You lured Hyo Won into moving out of home, didn't you?
No, I didn't.
You punk. You stay right here.
So? Did you get it fixed?
Yes, it's fixed perfectly.
Is it okay?
Yes, it's fine.
I'm glad.
They're the highest heels I've ever seen in my whole life.
They're probably bad for your knees. Are your knees all right?
- Just a second, please. - What is it?
What's he doing with my coffee?
It looked too hot, so I asked them for ice cubes.
Well, it's good now.
I'm glad to hear that.
This must be how you approached my daughter.
- I beg your pardon? - Didn't you cater...
to all of her needs like this to seduce that naive girl?
You got the wrong idea. I've never had such intention with her.
Then are you saying that she's feeling that way alone?
I'm not interested in Ms Min that way.
You really didn't talk her into moving out of home?
I almost fainted when I saw her at the residence this morning.
So you had no idea?
Not at all. Please believe me.
That girl has lost her mind.
I'll be sure to send her home before the end of today,
so please don't worry and wait for her at home.
- Do you really mean it? - Yes, I do.
If you lay even one finger on my daughter,
I'll make sure that you're doomed.
What you're worried about will not happen.
Then I'll leave it in your hands...
and wait for her at home.
Okay.
Are you all right?
I'm fine.
It's probably not my place to say this, but I'm just worried.
You should consider wearing heels that are about 5cm lower.
Know your place. How dare you lecture me.
I'm not lecturing you. I'm just worried.
You're talking back again. It's rude.
I'm sorry.
My gosh.
I was wondering whom Ms Min takes after.
She's just like her mum.
I'm sorry for inconveniencing you.
You're not inconveniencing us at all.
You're like family to us.
That's right. Make yourself at home here.
Yun Shil, shall we sleep together in the room my mum and I share?
- Shall I? - It's too small for three people.
I'll just sleep in Mum and Dad's room.
You can sleep in my room.
Your room?
Yes.
I want to sleep beside Mum and Dad.
Oh, my. How long has it been?
I can't even remember the last time you slept beside me.
Look at you smiling from ear to ear. Are you that happy?
Of course I'm happy.
Dad, aren't you jealous?
Mum loves Dong Jin more than you.
What's there to be jealous about?
It's normal for women to be more infatuated with younger men.
By the way, are you not seeing Mr Park for dinner today?
He pestered me about meeting up, but I said no.
Why did you say no?
The more I get to know him, the more obnoxious I think he is.
What's wrong with him? Why do you think he's obnoxious?
He makes so much noise when he eats,
and I hate how he touches everything on the table with his chopsticks.
I hate it so much.
When he talks, he licks his lips like a pervert.
Also, I guess he wears trousers that are too tight. When he walks,
he keeps touching the front, which turns me off.
And I don't know why he shudders whenever any money issue comes up.
You're just too spoiled.
Stop complaining and set a date for us to meet his parents next week.
I don't want that.
Stop pushing ahead with it, Honey. You should listen to Dong Sook.
Dad is right, Mum. He sure seems like a handful.
Everyone has flaws.
All married couples understand each other's flaws...
and help each other. That's what marriage is.
I'm really fine alone. Dong Jin should get married first.
What? What are you talking about all of a sudden, Dong Sook?
Don't even worry about Dong Jin.
Women are lining up to have their daughters set up with him.
Seriously, Grandma?
Of course. Your uncle is such a great catch.
Many smart young ladies from good families want to meet him.
Stop teasing me, Mum.
Gosh, this place is huge. I've never been to a place like this.
Me, neither.
- Let's just leave. - Why? No.
We came all the way here. Why do you want to leave already?
We have to cheer for Jun when he performs.
All right. Then let's just stay for one performance of his.
Okay.
What are you doing now?
What? What was I doing?
What would you like for drinks and food?
Are five beers and a fruit platter enough for the minimum spend?
Yes. Certainly, Ma'am.
- We'll get that, then. - Sure. I'll be right back.
Honey, have you been here before by any chance?
- No. - Then how do you know...
what the minimum spend for the table is?
Jun told me. I spoke to him on the phone earlier today.
Jun told you?
Yes.
Next up is the former prince of rock ballads...
who made a surprising comeback as a trot singer.
Let's welcome Tae Pyung to the stage.
Please give him a big round of applause.
Tae Pyung, Tae Pyung!
Go,Tae Pyung!
Hello, ladies and gentlemen. I'm the intellectual, sexy...
and charismatic singer who is now known...
as the gentleman of trot music, Tae Pyung. Nice to meet you.
I hope all of you enjoy your night.
Did you see him doing this?
The last farewell on the two-lined bridge
Even the wind that brushes my skin
- Breaks my heart - He's really good, isn't he?
He's not half bad.
- Why can't I stop you? - Let's take a picture.
I'm just standing here
All I can do is cry
I can't cross the bridge
- That's all I can think - Look over here.
I can't take my foot off to cross the bridge
Shall we dance?
- I look back - For just one song, then.
And I look at your face
I feel stupid for not holding on to you
Where did she go?
At the end of the two-lined bridge
We called out
- each other's names - Would you dance with me next?
Okay.
- We're too - I'd like to dance with you next.
Far apart
I can't hear you
I wish the bridge breaks down
So I won't be able to cross
My heart is in pain
Our love
Is not meant to be
Go, Leather Jacket. Encore!
Sam Do.
Hey, Leather Jacket.
Way to go.
You have the voice, the body and the face for it.
You've got the whole package.
I should bring Dong Jin and Tae Yang next time.
Thank you, Sam Do. That really makes me feel good.
You did good.
Why is Sun Nyeo...
taking so long in the bathroom?
She must be constipated.
She didn't go to the bathroom.
Can you guess where she is? Oh, she's over there.
She's a natural.
I didn't know she was such a good dancer.
Look at her moves.
Has she gone out of her mind?
This is not looking good.
- Thank you. - You promised me that...
you'll let me have the honour next time.
I'm going first.
I'm sorry, but I came with someone. This will have to do for today.
Don't be like that.
You promised that you'd hold my hands.
Come on.
- What? - Get over here.
Honey!
Are your hands some kind of a bus strap?
You let this man and that man hold your hands.
I'm sorry.
I was going to dance for just one song,
but I haven't danced for years.
I guess I got carried away.
You said it was your first time at a cabaret.
When we sold chicken at the Central Market,
I went with other shop owners...
on our off-days to have some fun.
And you lied to me saying it was your first time?
You would've never known if I contained myself.
Those people went crazy over me and didn't let go of me.
Shut it.
If I catch you going there again, I won't let it slip like this time.
Are you being jealous?
Nonsense.
Was it that shocking to see all those men begging me to...
hold their hands?
Not a chance.
Do you want me to hold your hands?
- Shall we dance? - I'll pass.
Follow my lead.
Go, 1, 2, 3, 4.
I said I'm fine.
Social dancing...
is good for blood circulation, your heart and lungs.
It's good for relieving stress.
I know that you were under tremendous amount of stress lately.
A little dance will make it all go away.
Are you sure?
How does it go exactly?
I'll teach you.
Do as I show you.
- Give me your hand. - My hand?
Yes, your hand. There you go.
Now, let's go, 1, 2, 3, 4.
Go, 1, 2, 3, 4.
You're pretty good. Are you sure this is your first time?
Am I really that good?
Go, 1, 2, 3, 4.
- You're home late. - Yes.
I had to fill in for my senior.
Thanks for the food yesterday.
It didn't mean anything. Yesterday, we had a party without you.
- I just wanted you to have a taste. - I see.
I'm just very grateful that you still care about...
someone like me.
- Next week is the family meeting. - A family meeting?
Mr Park's father and my family will be meeting together.
When the parents come to an agreement,
the marriage will take place in no time.
Don't you have anything to say to me?
How could I say anything to you?
I'm feeling a bit tired. I have to go inside.
Dong Sook.
Yes, Sung Jun?
Do you want some baked sweet potatoes?
I bought some on my way home. It's still hot.
You should have some.
I don't want any. I didn't ask for this.
I even kept it under my coat to keep it from getting cold.
You should eat it when it's hot.
Do you need something?
Not really. She's taking quite a long time to do the dishes.
Yun Shil is washing all the rusty pots and pans.
Do you have something to say to Yun Shil?
No, I don't.
Why does she always go out of her way?
Why is she doing that? She should get more sleep.
I wonder if my mum cleaned this room.
Gosh.
I made your bed.
You should get some sleep. You look tired.
I'm sorry for bothering you.
I don't mind sleeping on an electric mat at home.
Since you were here before,
you know where my room is, right?
What?
I do.
Get some sleep.
He wasn't lying when said he studied hard. Look at all these books.
There are a lot of books in different languages.
He looks way different from how he looks now.
He was a handsome little boy.
He looks like a cute little chick.
Why does he still have his wedding pictures when he got divorced?
Give me a big smile.
Gosh.
I've been doing this for 30 years now.
But I've never seen a couple looking this uneasy.
Can the bride stand up for me?
There you go.
Do you hate marrying me that much?
Try putting on a smile.
I'm trying.
You should try, too.
I don't know.
I'm trying, too, but it's not working.
I guess we're meant for each other.
Neither of us has a good poker face.
I'll take the picture now. In 1, 2.
I must be getting old,
seeing that I'm thinking of the past.
Come on out.
Hurry.
The door.
I don't want to go home.
I made a promise with Ms Choi.
You should go back if you don't want her to think I'm a liar.
Then promise me one thing.
- What? - Don't ignore my calls.
You have to answer my calls when and wherever you are.
Fine.
I'll answer your calls. Can you go inside now?
There's one other thing.
Stop calling me Ms Min from now on.
Call me by my name.
You're awfully demanding for someone being asked to go back home.
We don't even work together.
It's weird how you keep calling me "Ms Min".
I don't think I can do that.
Unless I'm really close with someone,
I can't call a person by their first name.
Okay, fine.
Give it a try, then.
I'll do it later.
Call my name.
Come on.
Okay.
Can you look over there for a second?
Hyo Won.
My name sounds so pretty when you say it.
It's getting late. You should go inside.
Let's talk later.
Get back inside right now!
Why do you have to embarrass me?
Drive safely, Honey.
What are you doing at my house?
I'm on my way back after taking Ms Min home.
Why are you approaching my sister?
Is this your way of getting back at me for stealing your girlfriend?
You're using her, aren't you?
I'm not low like you.
I don't play with other people's feelings.
Why you little...
I'll let you off the hook because you were once my boss.
But I hope you watch your behaviour next time.
I thought you were going to start family with that Tae Yang boy.
Why did you come back home?
I wanted to do that,
but my Tae Yang is very up-right.
He kept refusing, so I had no choice.
"My Tae Yang"?
Do you have any idea what you put me through?
I'm not going to make the same mistake as you.
- What? - I'm going to marry someone I love.
I'm not going to pick money over love.
Is that any way of talking to your mother?
You witch.
How dare you! You little brat.
Calm down, Mum.
- What did you say about me? - What's wrong?
- Let go of me. Let go! - Take it easy, Mum.
- Let me go! - We should leave.
I'm not low like you.
I don't play with other people's feelings.
Arrogant prick.
Hey, Ji Yun.
Did everything work out with your sister?
What? Oh, it did.
Can I ask you what it was about?
It's nothing serious.
There was a small incident at home.
You said she also works at Meesa Apparel, right?
I'm worried that she won't like me.
My friends said that...
sister-in-laws can be worse than mother-in-laws.
My sister is a simple person. You don't have to worry about her.
What are you doing out? It's cold.
What about you? Why are you out?
I couldn't sleep thinking about this and that.
Is my room uncomfortable?
No. It's not that.
It's not your first time sleeping there. What's wrong?
Back then, I passed out from drinking too much.
It was a mistake.
Please forget about it.
Here you go.
You don't want to catch a cold.
Thank you.
Are you not sleeping because of what I said to you?
It's not entirely about that.
I won't tell you to make any quick decisions.
I want you to give some thought...
on how you really think about me.
I've already...
failed in a relationship once.
I didn't want to rush into decisions this time.
I thought a lot before I said what I said.
So now,
it's your turn to think.
Promise me that you will.
Okay.
I will.
It's snowing.
It's the first snow of this year.
It is.
It looks like...
I do many things for the first time with you.
Seeing the first snow,
having my first night-out at that temple...
and confessing my love for the first time.
I didn't say that to pressure you.
Were you never...
in a relationship before?
There were times when I had feelings for someone,
but you were the first person...
I ever confessed my feelings to.
My life has been a one-way road so far.
Do you think I'm lying?
No.
It's not that.
The truth is,
it was my first time, too.
It was my first time hearing a proper love confession.
It's settled, then.
We're clumsy because we're both new at this.
So let's understand each other.
Okay?
(The Gentlemen of Wolgyesu Tailor Shop)
Mr Min and his girlfriend just arrived.
That sly woman is your girlfriend?
Why are those two women Hyo Sang's mother and sister?
Why is this happening to me?
- Did you buy a lottery ticket? - A lottery ticket?
- What's this? - It's a prenuptial agreement.
Let me know if you want to add something.
Should someone as imperfect as me...
be allowed to have feelings for Mr Lee?
Don't think about anything else other than your own happiness.
What are you two doing over there?