(The following content may not be suitable for viewers under 15.)
(Viewer discretion is advised.)SUBBED BY VIU/SA143
(Episode 27)SUBBED BY VIU/SA143
There were times when I had feelings for someone,
but you were the first person...
I ever confessed my feelings to.
My life has been a one-way road so far.
Do you think I'm lying?
No. It's not that.
The truth is, it was my first time, too.
It was my first time hearing a proper love confession.
It's settled, then.
We're clumsy because we're both new at this.
So let's understand each other, okay?
Is it okay for someone like me, who has so many flaws...
to like someone like him?
What if I'm too greedy and it doesn't work out in the end?
I often think about it,
but whenever I see his face,
my heart pounds and I feel butterflies.
And I don't mind about it at all.
Is it really okay for me to like Mr Lee?
Yun Shil has an innocence...
that I lost long ago.
Seeing you, Yun Shil...
is now a source of pleasure and happiness.
I want to provide you with shoulders you can lean on...
and a warm heart to envelop you.
Don't think of anything else but your happiness, Yun Shil.
I will be with you forever.
It's so cold outside.
I think it snowed last night.
Just a bit. It's all melted now.
You're helpless.
Did you dance enough to hurt your knees?
I'm old. My joints aren't the same.
I can't believe that I'm sticking...
pain relief patches on my dancer wife.
We lost all the money we got from selling the store.
What should we live off now?
I wish we got a windfall.
- Sorry. It's all my fault. - I'm glad you know.
How about...
I do the housework while you rest?
What should I do? Cook breakfast?
No. Do the laundry. There's a whole load waiting.
Okay.
He has a conscience, though.
He offered to do the housework for once.
What's this?
A lottery ticket?
Did you buy a lottery ticket?
What?
I forgot about that.
Check the numbers. Maybe we got lucky.
Dream on, lady.
Let's see. Which week was this for?
- Okay, 6, 7. - 6, 7.
- 18. - 18.
- 23. - 23. My goodness.
- Honey. - What is it? Was it correct?
I think we might win the first place.
Are you kidding me?
I'm not, see for yourself.
We got 6, 7, 18, 23?
What's the next number?
Let's see. It's 32.
- 32? - Is it 32?
- It's 32. - Did we actually win?
- What will you do if we win? - Me? I don't know.
I should pay off my debt first.
I will... I'll buy a house first.
With a huge garden.
I'll plant trees and flowers, and get a dog.
Okay.
- Read the next number. - What?
Hang on. I'm so nervous I can't see properly.
Hurry up.
It's 40.
- 40? - 40.
Did we win third place?
What?
Wait, there's a bonus number.
The bonus number's...
41.
Okay, 41.
- We won! - We won?
We won. We won!
Let me see.
- My goodness. - We really got it!
What's this noise?
Come over here.
What's going on?
Sun Nyeo won the lottery. Second place.
- Second place? - The pig dream I had...
was about this, not a baby.
How much does the second-place winner get?
Even after all the tax,
it's about 20,000 dollars.
Am I dreaming? Pinch me so I can check.
It's not a dream.
I guess there's always a way out.
I was so upset about the debt you got us into.
We got a windfall after all.
I can't believe this happened to someone I know.
Congratulations.
I bought a lottery ticket, too...
and I can't find it anywhere. I should look for it.
My goodness.
Wait.
This is my ticket.
What are you talking about? Why is this yours?
I wrote the word "peace" on the back of the ticket.
You're mistaken. I wrote that.
You wrote the word "peace"?
- Yes. - Why?
Because I wanted to.
Honey, he's wrong, isn't he?
You bought this, right?
I did.
That is my handwriting.
This is just insane.
Call out the numbers, then.
The numbers? Sure.
They're 6, 7, 18, 23, 32, 41.
- Correct. - That's because...
6 and 7 are the date of my debut, June 7.
18 is for January 8, the birthday of my late dad.
23 is for February 3, the birthday of my late mum.
32 is the number of my house in New York.
And finally...
42 is my age. Okay?
It makes sense.
I don't care.
That ticket is mine.
I know money changes people,
but this is wrong.
Why is it wrong?
That ticket is mine.
Time out, people.
Let's have a test.
- A test? - A test?
Listen up.
The person who can write the word written on the back...
is the owner of the ticket, okay?
Begin.
Oh, silly me.
What did I write on the back?
"Peace", in English.
That's it. I wrote "peace".
Is that it?
This stands for "personal computer".
It's "peace".
I see.
I got a bit distracted.
P...
S?
IS?
I think this is yours, Tae Pyung.
Where did you find this?
I found it on the ground while I was...
doing community service, so I picked it up.
I didn't throw it away. I dropped it.
Whether you threw it away or dropped it...
Anyway,
finders are keepers.
- Come back. - Sun Nyeo.
You really can't do this.
Where are you going? Don't do this!
- Sun Nyeo! - I just can't believe this.
Sun Nyeo!
You're up early, Sir.
Come back, Sun Nyeo.
Good morning, Sir.
Sun Nyeo!
I'll sweep the yard later. Leave it.
What's all the fuss about?
Well...
I'll tell you later.
What's going on?
Where did this woman get to?
I don't know.
She just disappeared.
She's really fast.
Banks close on weekends...
so she can't claim the money.
I'll make her...
return the ticket.
I know you're in a tough spot,
but I bought that ticket as a last resort.
- It's my final ray of hope. - I know.
Whatever people say, it's yours.
- Don't worry. - Thanks.
She'll be back soon. Let's wait inside.
Okay.
My feet are freezing.
You're wrong.
It belongs to whoever has it.
Where should I hide it?
Sam Do will find it if he strip-searches me.
Should I bury it under a tree?
Wait.
Is Yun Shil still asleep?
I guess she was tired.
I checked on her and she was fast asleep.
Should I have woken her for breakfast?
Sleep is the best medicine when you are tired.
It's her day off. Let her sleep in.
Will you stay at home, Uncle?
Yes. I have a book to read.
- See you later, then. - Have a nice day.
There is food on the table...
for when Yun Shil wakes up.
Tell her to heat the soup and have some rice.
I will.
- Let's go. - Bye, Uncle.
- Bye. - Bye.
- Take care. - Bye.
Is she catching up on a week's worth of sleep?
It's nearly 11am.
She's still fast asleep.
Where am I?
Oh my goodness.
What time is it?
Is everyone out?
Ms Choi. Dong Sook.
- Are you up? - Sorry.
I don't usually wake up this late,
but I slept late last night.
Did everyone go out?
My parents went to a wedding...
and Dong Sook and Da Jeong went to work.
I see.
Go and freshen up. I'm setting the table.
You don't have to.
I'll eat something at home.
I waited for you to get up.
You didn't have to.
Wash your face first.
There's sleep in both your eyes.
That was lame.
The yolk broke.
Too bad.
Let's succeed this time.
Not again.
Frying eggs is harder than I thought.
It's so difficult.
Let's do this.
And then...
Did I do it this time?
I did it.
It's a success.
This is a perfect fried egg.
What's all this?
Sit.
Did you cook all this?
My mother set out the table.
I fried this egg, though.
What do you think?
Isn't it the perfect shape?
It's hard to fry both sides without bursting the yolk.
You must be a good cook.
If you want to taste...
a perfectly shaped fried egg,
just say you'll marry me.
I'll make them for free every day.
I'm not trying to put pressure on you.
- Eat before the soup gets cold. - Okay.
Eat the fried egg.
- It's fine. You eat it. - I had two already.
To be honest,
I ate the two fried eggs that I'd ruined.
I only bared succeeded on cooking this.
Why did you try so hard?
I will eat anything.
I don't like it...
when you say things like "anything"...
or "something".
I want you to be treasured,
looked after and treated with respect.
That's it.
That's where I'll start.
I never thought that...
I was a person worth treasuring.
You're the first to tell me that.
So you don't like it?
Good. Eat up.
Okay.
Let's go inside.
Just a moment.
I need to take some deep breaths.
My mum and sister aren't too tough to deal with.
- Don't worry. - Okay.
Give me two minutes.
You tortured me half to death...
and you seem so relaxed.
You brat.
- What is it now? - "What is it now?"
I know that love blinds you,
but how dare you run off at night.
Don't you care about your family? Is Tae Yang all you care about?
You and Hyo Sang will do fine without me,
but my Tae Yang knows no one else in Seoul.
"My Tae Yang"?
I should shave your head and kick you out.
What should I do with you?
- Kick me out. - What?
I paid three months' rent in advance so I have a place to stay.
I have a regular restaurant nearby, too.
I have no worries.
Why you little...
You're too stupid to be my daughter.
I can't believe I carried you for 10 months.
- Are you going somewhere? - No.
Why are you dressed up...
like someone going to a party?
Your son and his girlfriend just arrived.
Okay.
You dressed up to meet Hyo Sang's girlfriend.
Will you let them get married?
No way. I'll tear them apart.
Be nice.
He likes her. Case closed.
You idiot.
Do you think it's that simple?
Get changed and come downstairs.
Why should I get changed?
We need to crush her on the first day.
What's wrong with her now?
- Wear this. - You're so childish.
Okay. Fine.
You can relax. It's just a meal.
Okay.
Mum.
We're here.
I see that. Welcome.
Hello.
Hello. I'm Choi Ji Yun.
That's not the problem.
I put my hair up often. What if I ended up with a scar?
You have quite a temper for someone your age.
Are you talking about me?
What was that about?
What a small world.
I apologise.
I had an important taping that day and I was nervous.
It's understandable.
- What are you talking about? - You don't need to know, son.
It's a female topic.
My goodness.
Thank you.
It doesn't smell nice.
My younger sister, Min Hyo Won.
Wait, your girlfriend's that evil witch?
I mean, is that her?
Are you okay?
- What was that for? - What do you mean?
You tripped me up for no reason.
Shouldn't you apologise?
I didn't trip you up.
You didn't look where you were going.
Watch it.
What? What are you doing?
Don't tick off someone who's trying to be calm, okay?
How dare you?
Let go. Let go of me.
We meet again.
I'm pleased to see you.
Are you pleased?
I really don't think you should be.
Do you know each other?
I'll explain later.
Let's eat first.
There's no way you're marrying my brother.
Are you okay?
She can't eat if you two keep staring at her.
Don't mind us. Eat in peace.
Thank you.
Why are you two so dressed up?
- We aren't. - We aren't.
You're both dressed like you're going to a ball.
I'm here for the job interview.
Just a moment. I'll tell the manager.
- Hello. - Hi.
Have you worked in a restaurant before?
Not at a hamburger joint, but I did serve pizzas once.
Can I use the bathroom?
Of course you can.
Use the one upstairs.
Okay.
Where are you going?
To get my phone from my room.
I won't be long.
Why are they his mother and sister?
Nothing's working out.
I feel sick.
Why can't I open the door?
Can you open the door for me?
I didn't bring my phone.
Let me out.
- Is anyone there? - You need a lesson.
How do you know Ji Yun?
I met her at the salon a few times, then at a bar.
Why are you sulking?
Don't you like her?
- Of course not. - Of course not.
What's taking her so long?
Maybe she needed to take a dump.
Taking a dump the day she meets us?
She's a tough one.
It takes a lot of guts for a woman to take a dump...
at her boyfriend's house on her first visit, right, Mum?
Right.
I'll check on her.
You'll only embarrass her.
I'll go.
Let me out. Is anyone there?
Hyo Sang.
What's this?
Did you do this?
Did you?
Why?
I have nothing and I hate it, so I'm all twisted inside.
What kind of woman am I?
You have nothing and hate it, so you're all twisted inside.
- Me? - Yes, you.
How dare you?
Hey.
Get out here.
You witch.
I'll let you off today because I'm drunk.
You'll pay for this next time.
You caught me at a bad time. I was upset over a personal issue.
I went too far.
I apologise. I'm sorry.
How odd. That apology didn't feel sincere at all.
Your brother told me a lot about you.
I was curious.
Can we get over the past...
and act like sisters from now on?
We'll see.
What a brat.
Choi Ji Yun.
There's no way you'll become my sister-in-law.
I don't want to be your family.
So,
your parents died in a car accident when you were young?
Yes. My uncle raised me until I finished high school.
That must have been tough.
I dreamed of getting married...
and living with my in-laws as one big happy family.
Also, with many children.
This is how thoughtful she is.
Ma'am.
What do you want?
The upstairs toilet is clogged.
Can you do something?
It was fine just this morning.
I only washed my hands.
For that long?
You took over 20 minutes.
That's because...
- the door got stuck. - It's fine.
I didn't mean to embarrass you.
It's okay.
Strange things happen. Such is life.
It's seriously clogged.
We need to call a plumber, Madam Ko.
Hyo Joo is home.
My older sister.
Hello, I'm Choi Ji Yun.
- Hyo Sang's girlfriend? - Yes.
I'm practically a guest here.
Don't try to look good for me.
Don't get scared.
Of all the people here, I think that...
you're the normal one.
What was that about?
That brat.
Now that we're divorced,
I should forget our wedding anniversary.
I don't miss being married.
Min Hyo Joo.
You're so pathetic.
Let's see...
- Let me do the dishes. - It's fine.
I'll do it. You make some coffee instead.
Can you really do the dishes?
What do you think of me?
I fried the perfect egg.
Okay.
Was something wrong with lunch?
Why did you suddenly feel dizzy?
I feel fine now.
The spell only lasted a while.
Let's see a doctor tomorrow.
Don't worry about me.
I'll be fine after a nap.
Here you go.
Let me do the dishes...
- while you drink your coffee. - It's fine.
I just want one sip.
Feed me a sip.
Come on.
What are you two doing?
You're back early.
Your father didn't feel well,
so we didn't stay long.
What are you doing?
Yun Shil said she couldn't stay for too long,
so I was doing the dishes.
She offered to do the washing up...
but I was bored and wanted a go.
You said you had to go.
What?
Right.
I'm sorry, Ms Choi. I should have helped out.
If you have to go, you are okay to leave.
Thank you. I'll get going then.
Take the gloves off.
- I'm almost done. - Take them off.
I'll change and do the rest.
Okay.
It wouldn't be the case,
but what if someone got the wrong idea...
and spread rumours?
Don't be silly.
What kind of rumours?
Yun Shil's...
husband and mother-in-law are the worst kind of people.
What if you get into trouble...
just for getting involved with them?
You shouldn't do anything that will give people ideas.
Why won't you answer?
- I understand. - That goes for her, too.
Even though we're close and we treat her like family,
how dare she make you do the dishes when she ate?
- She went out of line. - Stop it, Mum.
I said I'd do the dishes.
Watch how you act around her at work.
Don't give people a reason to gossip.
Did what my mum say upset you?
What she said is true, though.
She treated me like one of her own.
If she finds out that we like each other,
she'd feel so betrayed.
That was a wake-up call.
This is between you and me.
Anyone else is of no consequence.
No. You mean a lot to me,
but so does the rest of your family.
I can't lose them all...
over you.
Yun Shil.
It didn't make sense from the beginning.
I had lost my mind for a while.
What's wrong is wrong and isn't meant to work out.
Don't say that.
I don't know how someone like you...
ended up liking someone like me.
You said you liked me...
and I felt grateful.
I was fascinated, too.
To be honest, I think I got a bit too excited.
I'm easily swayed.
When you said you liked me,
I got confused.
Are you saying...
you aren't attracted to me at all?
Well.
That would be a lie.
But...
I thought about that.
It wasn't a rational attraction.
You were so good to me,
and I felt a debt of gratitude.
Do you mean that?
I was a bit confused until a while ago,
but now everything's clear.
Sorry.
Hello?
You finally picked up.
I got the parts for your broken boiler.
Are you at home?
I will be back in 10 minutes.
Yes.
I'll be right there.
The boiler engineer is coming to my place.
I have to go.
Bye.
We haven't even begun...
and she's running away already?
I replaced the faulty parts and cleaned the burner, too.
Thank you.
Sign this, please.
(Repair Form)
It says that Lee Dong Jin requested the repair.
Yes. Mr Lee is a friend of...
the CEO of one of our clients.
So our CEO ordered that we make you our first priority.
I see.
Yun Shil, you did the right thing.
But why do the tears keep falling?
Hi, Tae Yang.
Why are you coming back so late?
Your future wife came long ago.
My future wife?
Don't play dumb.
How did you hide such a pretty girlfriend all this time?
You really should be examined.
- What are you talking about? - Go to the dining room.
It's totally a feast.
Hold on.
Party people!
- I'll take more. - Here you go.
Thank you.
She is so sweet.
- Enjoy. - Thank you.
Me, too.
So good.
I hope you like it.
It melts in my mouth.
Is this Korean beef?
Of course, it's Korean beef.
You're Tae Yang's friends. Of course, I got Korean beef.
You are the best wife, you know that?
I envy Tae Yang so much.
Thank you for the compliment.
Please take good care of him.
- Don't fight. Get along, okay? - Okay.
What's going on?
Hi.
I was serving your friends some food.
Sit down and eat.
So why are you...
- Sit down and eat. - Here.
Here you go.
I'm so jealous.
What did you do...
to deserve such a pretty and kindhearted girlfriend?
If I had a girlfriend who took such good care of me,
I'd pass the civil service entrance exam in one try.
In light of that, let's give Hyo Won an applause.
- Applause. - Applause!
You're the best.
Thank you for complimenting me.
Do you want some more?
Let's talk.
Look. He held her hand.
- What are you doing? - I'm so jealous.
You can't do this without even asking me.
I wanted to surprise you.
You're surprised and totally moved, right?
Why did you bring that food?
It was a bribe for your neighbours to be good to you.
What did you just say?
They say I'm the perfect wife.
Everyone envies you a lot.
Please stop doing this, Ms Min.
Don't call me "Ms Min".
You promised to call me "Hyo Won".
- When did I... - In exchange for going home,
one, you won't ignore my calls.
Two. Don't call me "Ms Min".
You agreed to call me "Hyo Won".
- That was... - You said it...
just to get me to go home?
Then I'll run away again.
Are you threatening me?
Fine. I get it, so stop.
Look there.
Hyo Won.
Hearing you say my name makes me so happy.
What will become of me if you do this?
What do you mean?
Every guy in your building envies you.
Where did the food come from?
My brother brought his girlfriend home,
so we made a lot of food.
I brought some to share.
Do you know the announcer Choi Ji Yun, too?
- What? - My brother's girlfriend...
is an announcer at KBC.
She's so annoying.
I'm sure my brother hit on her first,
but I'm sure she liked him for his money.
Women know other women.
Let's hurry inside and eat.
This is this season's latest.
We have a wide range.
I like the design. I'll take one of the outfit you're wearing.
This? What a great choice.
This is the hottest design of this season.
Come this way. I'll ring you up.
Dong Sook. Dong Sook.
Why are there so many customers here today?
We're promoting the newest designs.
Really?
I'd like to buy you everything here.
but then you'll have nothing to do,
so I'll refrain myself.
He's so full of it.
Dong Sook, take a look at this.
- What's this? - This? It's a prenup.
It's what Hollywood stars sign before they get married.
This is that.
Why are you giving it to me?
I thought we should tie all loose ends before the parents meet.
Look through it and let me know if you have any edits or additions.
Here.
(Prenuptial Agreement)
Section one.
The husband, Park Dae Sub, will control all financial matters.
Section two.
Park Dae Sub will provide 2,000 dollars a month...
for living expenses...
and will negotiate every December.
Section three. If you give me a son, you'll get 100,000 dollars.
If a daughter, nothing.
Section four. Park Dae Sub has no obligations to support...
Lee Dong Sook's daughter Kim Da Jung...
and therefore, she will not live with us.
Section five. If caught lying,
you will be fined 1,000 dollars.
If caught cheating, not only will the parties get a divorce,
the cheater must pay a penalty of 20,000 dollars.
Section six.
Each will financially support their families from what they earn.
Neither party may ask the other for money.
Section Seven. In case of divorce, you will not request...
a division of assets!
P.S. If the wife, Lee Dong Sook...
doesn't make her husband, Park Dae Sub breakfast,
she will pay a penalty of six dollars.
That is all.
What do you think? You should settle these matters early on,
so you don't fight after marriage.
See? If I cry and whine...
after something happens, saying I knew it would happen,
it would be too late.
- Look, Dae Sub. - Yes?
I have no desire to marry you,
especially if I have to do this, so dream on.
You must not be used to the Hollywood way yet.
All the rich families in Korea do this, too.
I don't care what rich people do. Get it out of my sight.
You're so annoying.
She's a pro.
She's good at playing hard to get. She's a good negotiator.
Well, if it is for Dong Sook,
I should make some changes for her, but what? It's perfect.
Anyway. Dong Sook.
I'll be back. Okay.
Press one to leave a message.
Hey you, Bok Sun Nyeo!
Don't live like that.
I know you like money,
but how could you say someone else's lottery ticket was yours?
Stop humiliating your husband and come home right now.
I'm very angry. That is all.
Did you hear from her?
She turned off her phone, so I left a voicemail.
I need to get at least that money...
to stand tall in front of Dong Sook.
I know. You should have been more careful.
Why did you drop it in front of Sun Nyeo?
That's like dropping a fish in front of a cat.
When I think about that, I want to stab my stupid hands and feet.
But Sam Do.
Didn't you say she's working at a chicken place
- Yes. - Where is it?
I don't know. I only know that she's working at a chicken place.
It's nicely fried, so please enjoy.
Oh my gosh.
What are you doing here?
What do you mean? Why else?
Who knew there were so many chicken places here?
We went to every chicken place.
Stop playing hide-and-seek, and give me my lottery ticket.
Why is that yours? It's mine.
Stop being unreasonable and give it to him.
Then let's split fairly, okay?
I bought it with my money. Why should I split it with you?
Then I'll give you the money for the ticket. Let's split it.
Are you kidding me? You're making no sense.
Fine. I'll give you 10 percent of it. Deal?
Hold on.
I need to think.
Darn it.
Where is she going now?
- Stop! - No.
Stop right there.
You!
Stop it!
Stop.
You lied about your knees, right?
Why do you run so well, Ma'am?
I know. She should be a track star.
She's like a squirrel.
Hand it over while we're being nice.
Fine, I will.
You are so annoying.
Darn it!
Why you...
Wait!
I've got you.
Let go. Let go! Let go!
Shut it and hand it over.
Finders are keepers.
If I hadn't picked it up, it would have been thrown out.
How does it belong to you?
The person who bought the ticket owns it.
I can't accept it.
Hey. This is embarrassing, so let's take her first.
- What happened? - Don't get me started.
She had us running all day.
- What is it? - I came second in a lottery.
- You did? - Yes.
But as luck would have it,
I dropped that lottery ticket by mistake...
and she picked it up.
She claims that the finder is the owner...
and won't give it back.
That's not right.
How is it yours?
It belongs to the person who bought it.
That's what I'm saying.
Let's not waste our energy...
and hand it over. Now.
There are morals in gambling.
How could you try to claim it all?
I'll give you 20 percent of it. Deal?
- Deal. - Good.
Give me my ticket.
Okay.
It's not there.
- Where did I put it? - What are you saying?
Stop playing around. What do you mean?
I'm sure I put it here.
If you put it there, it should be there.
- Look carefully. - It's not here.
Are you trying to be tricky?
I am not.
- I'm sure I put It here. - Let me see.
Put your arms up.
- She really doesn't have it. - She's not lying.
That's strange.
- I can't remember where I put it. - Calm down.
Take your time and think slowly.
Did you hide it in your socks like I do with money?
It's not there.
I've been forgetful lately.
Even if you have been...
I mean, please think about it again.
- Tree. - What?
I must have buried it under the tree.
- Tree? - Tree?
- Here. - Light.
- Here? - There.
Darn it.
What are we doing in the middle of the night?
I know.
Thank goodness it was the second place. Imagine if it were first.
She would have gone to overseas.
Darn it.
Where are you? Please.
My hands hurt so much.
I don't think it's here.
Are you sure you buried it here?
I think so,
but I can't remember.
You buried it with your own hands. How do you not remember?
I know.
I must have been too upset earlier.
I just can't remember.
- Maybe it's at home. - No.
She hasn't been home yet all day.
If it isn't under the tree,
it means it's on her body.
- What... - No
We checked every single pocket.
Sun Nyeo.
Look into my eyes.
Take off your sneakers.
- Why? - Go ahead.
Did you find it? Did you?
(Lottery Ticket)
Yes.
I found it.
When did I put it there?
Congratulations.
Thank you.
Did you forget or did you pretend to forget?
I really didn't remember.
Where's your head?
You said finders must keep it.
I found it, so it's mine. Okay?
Okay.
Congratulations.
Here.
Why are you giving it to me?
I must pay you back first.
You can take your time.
I'll work hard for the rest and pay you.
Thank you.
If I don't win the lottery, why did I see a pig in my dream?
It was a meaningless dream.
So it went in circles and finally went to Dong Sook.
Congratulations.
Thanks.
- How do you feel, Father? - I'm fine.
I'm fine now, but your mum keeps treating me like a patient.
You are not fine.
I thought you'd faint during the wedding.
I was simply light-headed.
It's nothing.
Whatever happens tomorrow,
you're going to see the doctor with me.
Got it?
I'll take him.
- Go with me - Okay.
Don't disregard what I said this afternoon.
Come on, Mother.
I didn't say for no reason.
You shouldn't let other people talk about you.
I just told you in advance so that you can be careful.
If you want to taste...
a perfectly shaped fried egg,
just say you'll marry me.
I'll make them for free every day.
I don't think...
I'll ever eat a fried egg again.
You've been okay for a while. what's with the wines?
It's time for dinner.
Hold on.
It's your wedding anniversary.
Who cares? We're divorced.
I forgot that a long time ago.
If you forgot,
why do you still wear the wedding ring?
It isn't too late. Beg him to forgive...
and ask him to start over.
What did I do? Why should I beg?
I feel like...
you regret it.
That's nonsense.
Forget it then.
Earlier,
- that girl you brought. - Ji Yun?
When I first saw her, she reminded me...
of when I saw your mum for the first time.
- What do you mean? - Her eyes are full of ambition.
She's a lot like your mum.
What is she talking about?
- Were you with her until now? - Yes.
She told me basically what happened.
It's just a misunderstanding.
Don't be prejudiced.
Be nice to her.
I can't be related to...
a pooper like her.
You little brat.
How dare you pick on her already?
- That hurts. - I know you're behind it!
- Do you have proof? - I don't need proof.
It's obvious.
I heard you locked her in the bathroom, too.
She's a little tattle tale.
If she marries him, she'll manipulate and tear us apart.
Why did you lock her in?
I couldn't stand her.
How low-class.
Anyway, I'm absolutely against letting her into our family.
Hyo Won, don't say a word now.
I agree with her.
What for?
What? She's not my type.
Why not?
Hyo Joo says she reminds her of you when you were young.
That psycho... How do we resemble each other?
You're blind.
How dare?
(Wolgyesu Tailor Shop)
I'm at the tailor shop. Let's talk.
I'll until you come.
Is that Yun Shil?
What...
Why are you here?
I have something for you.
I'm at the tailor shop. Let's talk.
I'll until you come.
You need to be cool-headed.
You need to be strong.
He said he'd wait until I go over.
What if he waits all night?
Do you even know what day today is?
I guess not.
Why? Is it a special day?
It's our wedding anniversary.
You're right.
How long have we been divorced that you forgot our anniversary?
It's meaningless to both of us now.
There's no need to remember.
That's true.
I came to return this.
I didn't think of the ring.
You don't need to return it,
but I'll take it if it'll make you more comfortable.
(Wolgyesu Tailor Shop)
He must still be waiting.
What's this? He told me to come.
You've changed a lot.
I should change.
The people and place have changed.
It would be strange if I didn't change.
When I saw you at the competition,
I saw smiles and expressions...
that I had never seen before.
You looked like a stranger.
I questioned if it was the same man I had slept in the same bed with.
You must be happy.
When I think about it,
I was caught up with success, not the actual work.
But lately, I'm learning that work itself is enjoyable.
Is that all?
Of course, that's probably not all.
If you're done, why don't you go?
- What? - I have an important plan.
Okay. Sure.
Sorry for dropping in without calling.
It's late, but congratulations...
on becoming the director of the arts foundation.
It's just for a position.
Still, it'll help psychologically to work,
rather than being locked up. I feel much better.
Get home safely.
Okay. I will.
Someone kept sneaking peeks from behind the bushes.
Where did she go?
So this is where you were hiding.
I didn't mean to eavesdrop.
It was a coincidence.
You say you like me, so why were you with her?
Are you crying because that upsets you?
I'm not crying because I'm upset.
I don't know.
I just keep crying.
I don't know what's wrong with me.
What do I do? What do I do?
Do you want to know why?
It's because...
you like me.
(The Gentlemen of Wolgyesu Tailor Shop)
Have we divorced 5 years ago or 10 years ago?
I saw a lucky pig in my dream but Leather Jacket benefited.
I'll be direct.
Do you want to date me?
I don't get it.
I don't understand why you're so into me.
It's strange.
I must find out where he goes every day.
What's wrong with him? Is he sick?
Give me your hand.
I'm worried and scared that it'll be tough for Dong Jin.
Can we really do this?