(The following content may not be suitable for viewers under 15.)
(Viewer discretion is advised.)
What do I do?
Do you want to know why?
It's because...
you like me.
Thank you for liking me.
(Wolgyesu Tailor Shop)
(Episode 28)
Here.
Hey, Yun Shil.
Yes? I'm listening.
What are you looking at?
Did you put some sweets on the ceiling?
I did not.
You're so two-faced.
What?
You could have just told me that you liked me.
You told me only after I found out.
You played hard to get.
I'm not that kind of person.
I was afraid I'd get you into trouble, Mr Lee
That's the only reason I was unable to tell you how I felt.
We hugged each other, so stop calling me Mr Lee
What should I call you, then?
Dear Dong Jin.
Go on. Say it.
Dear...
I'll just call you Dong Jin.
Okay, that is not bad, too.
By the way,
is it really okay for us to do this?
- If you, Mr Lee... - Dong Jin.
I'm worried and scared that it'll be tough for you.
I'm just worried about it.
You shouldn't cause harm or hurt...
to the person you like.
It's true that we're facing a lot of obstacles.
We can overcome them one by one.
As long as what we feel for each other doesn't change,
it's not a problem. We can overcome anything.
Okay?
Well done for plucking up the courage.
Forget about everything and get some sleep.
I will, Mr...
You, too.
You're a fast learner.
You're obedient, too.
- Go on inside. - Okay.
See you.
Yun Shil.
What?
I don't want to go home like this.
Shall we kiss each other?
What if someone overheard?
You are so silly. I have to go.
Try not to trip up.
(Mr Lee)
Don't I look good from behind?
Can't she see this?
Whatever.
That was embarrassing.
That was really embarrassing.
Still, I'm the man and I should be in charge.
I can't stand it.
Dong Jin.
Hi.
- Why are you here? - Tae Pyung won the lottery...
and he's treating us all.
What do you mean he won the lottery?
Why are you out here?
- Sam Do. - Yes?
Did he really win the lottery?
Yes, it's crazy.
We should all congratulate him.
Come inside.
Okay.
- Congratulations. - Cheers.
I would like to make a short speech.
I don't believe that what happened is a mere coincidence.
Tae Pyung insisted on singing rock music only,
but after much thought, he decided to sing trot songs...
at a cabaret just to make ends meet.
The universe saw that he wanted something so badly...
and sent him some good energy. After that, he collected them...
and that turned into this huge reward.
That is what I believe.
I agree. This stroke of luck wasn't a coincidence.
Congratulations, Jun.
Thank you, Dong Sook.
- Congratulations. - Thanks.
You should say something.
I briefly lost my mind early this morning...
and I am very embarrassed and sorry.
I would like to sincerely apologise from the bottom of my heart.
- I should bow to you. - What for?
If you hadn't found my lottery ticket,
it could have ended up in the trash.
Thank you, Sun Nyeo. I owe you forever.
Are you serious?
Please accept my bow of gratitude.
I guess this is what my piggy dream meant.
I think we should keep the lively atmosphere...
by listening to a song by our beloved singer, Tae Pyung.
I'll sing 10 songs for you people.
Okay, then.
Next on the stage is trot superstar Tae Pyung who just got back from...
his hit Southeast Asia tour.
Applause.
Everyone
Everyone will get lucky one day
I am back and I have a dream
Sadness and pain can stay away from me
Do not cry,
do not cry, do not cry.
There's nothing you can't do if you try hard enough
Everyone will get lucky one day
I wasn't this emotional...
when I won the Best New Artist Award...
in 2000.
So much happened to me over the years.
Thank you, everyone.
I love you all.
Gosh. Why are you crying, Dong Sook?
I don't know. Tears just keep coming out.
My goodness.
Are we gathered here for a funeral or what?
Why is everyone crying on this happy day?
I know, right? It looks like you and I should...
lift up everyone's spirit.
Gosh, seriously.
Why are you... Okay.
- Between the sky and the earth - Between the sky and the earth
This is exciting!
- Came down the flower rain - Came down the flower rain
- After passing - After passing
- A forest in a valley - A forest in a valley
- We met for the first time - We met for the first time
- Then one day - Then one day
Then one day
- The fairy left - The fairy left
- Rising high up in the sky - Rising high up in the sky
- She left everything behind - I haven't seen this in a while.
It's not like we got divorced 5 or 10 years ago.
It has only been a few months. How can he forget our anniversary?
What a jerk.
Did you meet up with Dong Jin?
My quick wits got me to where I am now.
Pour me a glass, too.
- What did Dong Jin say? - He doesn't even remember.
That jerk.
He forgot your anniversary already?
He's changed so much in a few months.
I think he's seeing someone now.
No way.
He's cold and cautious.
He can't be seeing someone already.
No, I'm getting a weird feeling.
He didn't seem...
to have even an ounce of regret about what happened.
What about you?
Do you regret getting divorced?
What are you talking about?
Why would I regret it? What's there to regret about?
Tell me if you have any regrets.
I'll try talking to him in person.
Don't do anything useless.
I might go crazy.
Goodness gracious. You're being ridiculous.
You can't find someone like Dong Jin.
You signed those divorce papers too thoughtlessly.
- Hello? - It's me, Hyo Won.
What is this about? This video call is making me uncomfortable.
- I'm going to hang up. - If you hang up,
I'll run away from home again.
You're using that to threaten me every single time.
What were you doing?
I just took a shower.
- Then what will you do from now on? - I'm going to put on my skin toner.
- Go ahead and do it. - Sorry?
I wanted to know how you'd apply your toner.
So don't mind me and go ahead.
Why are you curious about such random things?
Come on.
Tae Yang, you look cool even when you're doing that.
You can be a model for skincare products.
We're good now, right? Bye.
Hold on!
What now?
What are you going to do now?
I'm going to do a few push-ups before going to bed.
- Have a good night, then. - That's perfect.
I'll give you a countdown and say, "Start."
- All right, one... - What are you doing now?
Start now.
Hey.
I won't bug you after this.
Just do this for me as one last favour. Please?
For goodness' sake.
This is the last time.
All right. One...
Two.
Three.
Four.
20, 21.
22.
What's this sound?
23.
24.
Keep it up. You're almost there.
All right. 25.
26.
What are you two doing right now?
My goodness.
Hey, Kang Tae Yang.
Why on earth are you topless right now?
He's working out. Don't interrupt him.
26.
You're seriously a piece of work.
I guess you're trying to seduce my daughter with your muscles.
- Are you a gigolo or what? - Pardon me?
Why are you being so rude to him?
My goodness.
You said you are not interested in my daughter.
How dare you get topless in front of her? You little...
Why are you saying that he's topless? Look.
He's clearly wearing a top.
- Look! - I'm angry, so just hang up!
See you later, Tae Yang.
Good night.
He's wearing a top. Because of you, I couldn't watch...
I'm so scatterbrained right now.
Gosh, I fell for Ms Min's trick again.
For some strange reason, I always end up doing what she asks for.
What brings you here this late?
You said you're working late today, so I thought I should stop by.
I see. I was just about to call you.
Have a seat. Let's sit down.
I'm seriously so upset...
because of your mother and Hyo Won.
I don't even know how I got into that situation with them.
They hate me, don't they?
They'll open up to you soon.
Don't worry too much.
I'm actually more worried about Hyo Won.
I hear you. I'm more worried about her, as well.
Speaking of which,
can you think of a way for me to get closer to her?
I'm not sure. The situation has gotten pretty awkward.
What's up, Dong Sook?
Why are you giving this to me?
Release your album first.
I don't need that money urgently.
No, I don't need this. Take it back.
Don't be stubborn. Just listen to me.
Stop performing at clubs and cabarets.
- Release an album with this and... - If I want to release a new album,
I'm going to do it on my own.
I won't get help from other people.
- Jun. - I've been regretting a lot.
If I didn't get help from you back then,
we didn't need to become this distant.
I tried to rely on others to take the easy way and ruined everything.
Whether I succeed or not, I won't depend on others any more.
I'll figure it out on my own.
Just a second.
- Hello? - Hey, Dong Sook. It's me.
Why are you calling again?
Dong Sook, you remember...
the prenuptial agreement, right?
I revised it. Check this out.
You know that the living allowance was 2,000 dollars, right?
I increased it to 2,500 dollars.
Also, it said you won't get anything if you give birth to a girl, right?
50,000 dollars!
I increased it from 0 to 50,000 dollars.
You must remember Section six about your family, too.
I'm going to give them 300 dollars every month.
I made these revisions.
You know what? This means...
that I made all the compromises I could.
Don't make any compromises.
- Pardon me? - I won't be signing that agreement,
so you don't need to make compromises.
What's wrong with her?
Should I have increased it to 2,700 dollars?
Did you and Mr Park have a fight?
I'll be direct.
If you say that you want to date me now,
I'd definitely be interested.
Do you want to date me?
Winning the lottery for 20,000 dollars doesn't change anything.
I'm still...
a no-name singer who performs at clubs and cabarets.
I don't want to see you having worries about money like I do.
That's the last thing I can do for you.
You're a coward.
You're such a coward.
What's the matter, Mum?
Did you have a fight with Tae Pyung?
I'm so upset, Da Jeong.
Why are you crying?
It was all for nothing.
I saw a lucky pig in my dream but Leather Jacket benefited.
It's good that someone got lucky.
You'll be blessed.
Let's hope so.
Honey.
What?
Did you really forget that...
you'd put the ticket in the sole of your shoe?
Did you lie?
I did not. I really forgot about it.
How could you forget where you hid something?
I just did.
How could you forget something like that?
You stressed me out so much over the past few weeks...
that I almost lost my mind.
So stop causing trouble.
What are you doing?
I was getting my bedsheets out.
What about you?
I just got back from a party at Sam Do's.
Is he celebrating something?
No, Tae Pyung is.
He won the second prize in the lottery.
Did he really?
Yes. So we gathered for a drink to congratulate him.
That's great news.
He'd had a hard time after he got conned.
He did. I'm happy for him.
I'm envious. He must be so pleased.
You won the lottery, too.
When?
You won me, Lee Dong Jin. I'm a lottery ticket, too.
You're telling lame jokes again.
- Do you want a hug? - What?
If you want a hug, just say so.
Don't beat around the bush and complain about my jokes.
I don't think we should talk any more.
- I'm hanging up. - Just a moment.
We have a date at 2am. See you in my dreams.
I'll hug you then.
I really have to go. See you tomorrow.
No one ever reacted to my jokes as warmly as she does.
What are you doing here?
I was waiting to take you to work.
I said I'd walk with Ms Geum.
Are you ready, Yun Shil?
Is she still sleeping?
(Vibrate)
- Hello? - Are you ready for work?
I'm waiting outside the gate.
I got up late. You can go ahead.
Okay, then.
Why was she whispering?
Is there something wrong with her phone?
Let's go the other way.
Give me your hand.
I waited for you a while and my hands are cold.
What if someone sees us?
There's no one here.
Do you want to brag that we're holding hands?
- No. - It's too obvious if we walk apart.
Stay close and natural.
- Should I? - Come here.
See? It's much better this way.
I feel uncomfortable. Can we not hold hands?
I'll carry you if you keep complaining.
Okay, then. I'll keep quiet. Let's just walk.
Honey.
Where are you going?
You said Dong Jin would take you to see a doctor.
I have to go somewhere before my appointment.
Where are you going?
To meet some friends.
Which friends?
It's not like you to keep prying.
I think it's strange that you leave home...
at the same time every day when you don't go to the store any more.
Nothing's strange. I'm going for a walk.
See you later.
Is he going somewhere?
He goes out every day right after breakfast.
- I'm going to follow him. - Wait.
You'll catch a cold if you don't wear a coat.
Something's off.
I need to find out where he goes every day.
Stay at home. I'll follow him.
You will?
I'll give you a call.
See you.
I'm sure he's hiding something from me.
- Like what? - I don't know yet.
What's wrong?
Is he sick?
(Community Centre for the Blind)
A community centre for the blind?
Why is he going inside?
Today, you will learn how to write in braille.
- Okay. - Okay.
This is called a stylus...
and you use it to write braille.
Hold it like this and press down to punch holes.
Hang on.
What's he doing in there?
Excuse me.
Those people in there. What are they doing?
They're learning braille.
Braille?
It's a class to help those...
who became or will become blind.
People who will become blind?
Yes.
- Hello? - It's me.
I called because you aren't here yet.
I'm not able to talk to you right now.
Let's talk when I get to work.
Is he losing his sight? How is that possible?
You did very well today.
Get home safely. See you next week.
Master Bae.
What are you doing here?
That's what I'd like to ask you.
You left home...
to take some time to settle things down for your condition.
I had no idea even if I called myself as your best pupil.
I'm sorry.
Don't be.
We all grow old and sick. It's part of life.
I never strayed from my road...
during my life as a tailor.
That makes me a happy man.
- Master. - Many people have died...
but I'm still here, alive and well.
I have a trustworthy pupil like you,
and my son inherited the business so my ancestors will be proud.
What could beat that?
You were alone.
You must have felt so lost.
My heart breaks for you.
I think this is a huge gift.
I was given a chance to sort things out...
and as you can see,
I was given time to get used to what will come next.
From now on...
I will take better care of you.
I was too indifferent.
I'm okay at the moment.
I will tell my wife and Dong Jin when the time is right.
Keep it from them until then.
Dong Jin came across a report from the hospital,
so he knows my condition.
Master...
This is our new menu. Please give it a try.
This soy sauce dressing...
is handed down in the family from the mother of my grandmother.
Addition to that, I mixed it with a special sauce of mine.
- How do you like it? - It's good.
Thank you.
I heard your chicken is tremendous.
What brings you here?
We are coming back from the bank.
How does it feel to be filthy rich?
It's all because of you.
Here.
- What is it? - It's your share of the money.
It's not that much, but I want you to have it.
Forget it. If Sam Do finds out about this, he'll scold me.
It's really not much.
- It's what Sung Jun wants. - That's right.
When my second album comes out and sweeps the charts,
I'll pay you back again. So just keep this one.
This isn't what I had in mind when I gave you the lottery ticket.
I'll work hard...
and pay back the rest of your money.
Is that all you have to say to me?
Fine.
Pay back properly with interest.
Dong Sook. You're here.
Here you go.
- What's this? - It's the prenuptial agreement.
The corrected version.
I said I'm not interested. Stop doing this.
Dong Sook, I know what has been bothering you.
I talked to my lawyer and corrected them all.
All you need to do now is put your stamp on it.
- Why don't you read it? - What are you talking about?
Dong Sook, you shouldn't do things like that so carelessly.
What? It's none of your business.
Mind your own business and get lost.
I said I don't want to marry you with or without this agreement.
Dong Sook, I'll take a look.
"Prenuptial Agreement"
"The husband, Park Dae Sub, will control all financial matters."
"Park Dae Sub has no obligations to support...
"Lee Dong Sook's daughter Kim Da Jung."
"In case of divorce, you will not request a division of assets."
What kind of contract is this?
Give it back.
And stay out of this.
You don't even deserve someone like Dong Sook.
How dare you propose something like this to her?
And you call yourself a man?
You're irritating me. You have been bothering me.
Just what exactly is your relationship with Dong Sook?
Why do you have to interrupt everything I do?
Let go of me before you hurt yourself.
Okay. I did. So what?
How dare you use violence on him?
- Take that. - What was that, Dong Sook?
- Why are you doing this? - I'll knock some sense into you.
- Why are you doing this? - You won't learn any other way.
"Prenuptial Agreement"? It's more like "Slavery Agreement".
I didn't let her go so she could be treated like this.
- Oh, gosh. It hurts. - Don't you ever come see Dong Sook.
That will be the last day of your life.
What are you two trying to do on me?
Get lost before I really hurt you.
I'll go. I'm going.
But one day, you'll regret this.
My head.
Are you okay, Dong Sook?
I...
Did you mean what you just said?
Let's talk later.
What's going on?
Why are you taking a step back? You should've proposed to me.
Why didn't you tell me?
Tell you what?
That Mr Lee is sick.
I was just at the community centre for the blind.
He wanted to...
keep it a secret for a while.
But you should have told me.
He said he'd tell you himself.
I'm sorry.
I can't even stay standing up.
Then...
What happens now?
For the time being,
we should do as he says.
He's a very composed man.
When he's ready, he'll tell everyone else.
Why can't I stop crying?
My dad is a strong person.
He took it very well.
Let's just see how it goes for the time being.
If he does lose his vision...
and can't be without someone by his side,
then we should help him.
- Hello? - It's me, Ms Choi.
I've been waiting for your call.
Did you look into where this old man goes everyday?
I saw him playing go at a go club.
- He plays go? - Yes.
He plays money games with his friends, too.
When he's hungry, he orders jjajangmyeon, too.
Then he should've told me that. Why would he keep it a secret?
He's been...
working all his life.
He must have not wanted you to think that he's idle.
That's not true.
So Ms Choi...
Don't worry at all.
Okay. I won't.
- Thank you. - Goodbye, Ms Choi.
Why would I think like that?
You sacrificed you entire life working for family.
What's so wrong about playing go?
What a stubborn man he is.
Gosh.
- Are you really not going to work? - Why would I? I quit.
Why would you quit your job for someone like Tae Yang?
It's not entirely about him.
Do you know what they call me at the office?
Princess Loner.
Princess Loner? What does it mean?
It means I don't have any friends.
How dare they?
Who would call my daughter like that?
- Who said that? - Calm down.
Why do you think I got that nickname?
It's because I'm not social and don't have capabilities.
Let's be honest. I didn't get there by myself.
The other employees don't think of me as a head of department.
I think so, too.
- Hyo Won. - I never liked my job anyway.
I wasn't cut out for it, too.
- So stop expecting so much from me. - You mean to tell me...
that you will keep seeing Kang Tae Yang...
while being unemployed?
I mean, marriage is the same as being employed.
Get a grip, you fool.
That hurt.
If you're not going to work there, you have to go study abroad.
- What are you talking about? - If you say yes,
- I'll let you to date him. - What?
What?
This is the burger and coke you ordered. Thank you.
Can you take my order?
Of course.
How did you know I was here?
I know a person or two in your building.
- What about your job? - I told you.
I handed in my resignation.
- What on earth are you doing? - What?
I'll have bulgogi burger and coffee.
Make that an americano, please.
Bulgogi burger and coffee, coming right up.
Thank you.
Honey.
All the best!
Welcome.
(Tony Burger)
Thank you.
She's been sitting there all day.
She's even sleeping now.
Shouldn't we do something about this?
Ma'am?
You should leave if you're done with your food.
I'm not done yet.
I can eat some more.
But you had so much already.
I can still eat. No problem at all.
Can you take my order?
Stop eating. You might get sick.
It's totally fine.
I normally eat like a glutton.
Which one shall I get?
I'll get a chicken burger. I'd like some orange juice, too.
Here you go.
I can do it.
Honey.
Why are you still here?
I wanted to go home with you, so I've been waiting for you.
What on earth are you doing here all day?
I saw you working...
and had a filling meal, too. It was a pretty good day...
What's wrong?
Did I eat too much?
I think I have indigestion.
You kept eating. I knew this would happen.
I feel like throwing up.
Try to hold it. You cannot... Don't throw up, okay?
This way. Let's go.
Thank you.
Are you feeling all right?
Good work, Sam Do.
This one looks even better than the one you made for the competition.
I agree, Master.
The higher placement of the notched lapel makes it look very stylish.
Definitely. This suit certainly looks different from other ones.
It does. I'm sure Gianni will love it, too.
You think so? Then shall we send it via express courier tomorrow?
Yes. I'll take care of it as soon as I get to work tomorrow.
Great. Let's call it a day, then.
- Dong Jin. - Yes.
I'm feeling a little down. Do you want to go for soju with me?
I'm actually meeting up with my university friends this evening.
Really? Okay, then.
Yun Shil, let's grab food together before we head home.
My husband is away on a business trip.
I'm supposed to meet up with Tae Yang for dinner.
Really?
Then I should just go home and eat the leftover food.
What are you guys doing? You should get ready to leave.
- Right. - Yes, Master.
- Have you been waiting long? - No, I just got here.
Here. Give me your hand.
It's so cold.
There we go.
It looks like Sam Do has a lot on his mind because of my dad.
So it's just a matter of time before your family finds out.
I'm worried.
If Ms Choi finds out about it, she'll be so shocked.
We'll get through it. We'll console and support each other.
I'm worried that I might be adding to your stress.
This is our very first date.
Let's try to talk about hopeful and happy things, okay?
All right.
Since it's our first date, I paid special attention to plan it.
First, we'll have Italian food accompanied by wine for dinner.
Then we'll have some tea at a place with a great night view.
And we'll end the night by watching a film together. What do you think?
Do you want to do all of those things in one night?
As you know, I'm quite capable. Don't you worry.
We don't need to do fancy things.
Let's just go for a bowl of warm noodles.
Gosh, you're so not romantic.
Have you forgotten how special today is? It's...
our first day together as a couple.
We eat those noodles every day. It's not special enough for today.
You don't need to do anything. I'll take care of everything.
Don't worry and just come with me.
Wait, where are we going now?
The first destination.
We're going to have Italian food with wine for dinner.
This is my place.
Yes. We're going to have Italian food and wine...
right here at your place.
The ingredients are already here.
Let's see.
The salad and pasta. Okay.
- Open the door for me. - Sorry?
Okay.
By the way, is this the only apron you have?
Can I give you a hand with anything?
No, don't worry.
Just relax and chill in your room.
I'll chop the onions for you at least.
Gosh, I'll take care of everything. Just go inside and rest.
I have so much to do.
I think I smell something burning.
Isn't it the meat on the frying pan?
Goodness, I said I got this. Don't you worry. Just go inside.
Don't come out.
I must not burn it.
What should I do next? Right. The spaghetti.
Yes.
Dinner is ready. Come out.
Okay.
Did you make all these by yourself, Mr Lee...
I mean Dong Jin. Did you really make all of these dishes?
I didn't have enough time to put 100 percent of my skills,
but it won't taste bad.
I'm impressed.
Have a seat.
All right. Let's start with the wine.
- Sure. - Here.
We have to use these mugs because you don't have any wine glasses.
How is it?
It's good.
There aren't that many dishes, but I hope you enjoy everything.
Okay. Thank you.
What's wrong? Does it taste bad?
I think the steak is burnt.
That's weird. I let just the outside burn slightly to give it a taste.
Gosh, why is it so burnt?
It's okay. I prefer well done.
No, no. Don't eat the steak. Try this spaghetti instead, okay?
Hold on a second. Let me try it first.
The noodles are all soggy.
It's all right. I like soggy noodles.
Do you have any instant noodles by any chance?
I'm really good at making instant noodles.
What's all this?
I made a little mistake earlier,
but I guarantee that you won't be disappointed now.
I prepared so much for this.
I said we're going to watch a film. Do you remember?
Are we going to watch a film here?
That's right. We'll watch a film.
Right here.
My gosh!
It's my favourite film, but I'm not sure if you'll like it or not.
I love this film, too.
Gosh, I'm so relieved. This is a success, then.
You're 10 times prettier...
than Julia Roberts.
No way.
I'm serious.
I don't tell lies.
By the way, I think you look like that male character.
I do?
I guess our eyes look similar.
But don't you think...
my eyes are prettier?
When I was at school,
they called me Pretty Eyes.
Gosh, you made me shiver.
Pull up the blanket, then.
Gosh. Look at me.
- What do you think? - No.
What about now?
- Wait. - How is it?
I told you.
I'm home, Honey.
Don't talk to me. I have to focus right now.
What's all this?
If Leather Jacket came in second, I can come in first.
What?
I gave it some thought.
I can't just hand over my dream of a lifetime...
to Leather Jacket.
My lucky dream is still valid.
Look at these.
How much do these cost?
If I win the first prize, this will look like pocket change.
You never stop surprising me.
- Okay. - What was that?
It's the method I invented.
Coming up with different series of numbers is hard.
You're so smart when it comes to things like this.
Okay.
- Are those your numbers? - Yes.
Is anyone in there?
- Is nobody in here? - Who's that?
Lee Dong Sook.
Where is Lee Dong Sook?
Come out here, Lee Dong Sook.
- That sounds like Mr Park. - Lee Dong Sook.
What on earth does he think he's doing?
Lee Dong Sook.
Come out here!
There you are.
Oh my goodness.
Gosh.
What brings you here without any notice?
Hello, mother-in-law.
I came here to tell you something.
Who are you calling a mother-in-law?
Hey.
What did I do so wrong?
I can't wrap my head around it.
What's going on?
I think you are drunk.
If you have something to say, come back when you're sober.
No.
I have to do this now...
in front of everyone.
What are you waiting for? Come inside.
What's wrong with that guy?
Did you two have a fight?
He's a lunatic.
My gosh.
Right.
Do you know what this is?
This is the diamond ring...
I got for Dong Sook.
My goodness. It should be two-carat at least.
That's right. It is two-carat diamond.
My goodness.
I didn't do something like this when I got married for the first time.
I made a big decision...
to get this for Dong Sook.
Why did you two fight?
We didn't.
I just got...
beaten up by them.
Dong Sook and that nightclub singer who lives upstairs.
Look at this.
This is what they did to me.
Why would you do that?
He deserved it.
I deserved it?
My gosh.
Look what I've got.
All I asked for was her seal on this agreement.
That's when they started beating me up.
What's this?
- "Prenuptial Agreement"? - Let me see.
"Section one."
"The husband, Park Dae Sub, will control all financial matters."
"Section two."
"Park Dae Sub will provide 2,500 dollars a month for living..."
"expenses and will negotiate every December."
"Section three."
"If you give me a son, you'll get 100,000 dollars."
'If a daughter, 50,000 dollars."
"Section four."
"Park Dae Sub has no obligations to support Lee Dong Sook's..."
"daughter Kim Da Jung and therefore,"
- "she will not live with us." - What?
How is that possible?
I can't leave Da Jeong behind just to get married.
Why are you crying?
It's not like I raised her.
Why would I be obligated...
to support a 20-year-old adult?
She's an adult now.
She should take care of herself.
So you're saying...
you'll marry my daughter,
but will treat my granddaughter like a complete stranger?
We wouldn't be complete strangers, but think about it.
What about when she decides to get married later?
I'll have to pay for the wedding and everything.
That will be a lot of money.
Why would I want something like that?
You disgraceful jerk.
Get out of my house!
Mr Lee. Calm down.
You're right, Dad.
Don't let someone like that get on your nerves.
They say you never know the true human nature of someone.
I misjudged you by a mile.
- Go. Go home. - I'm not done yet.
You know what?
- Go home. - Wait, hold on.
- Let's talk outside. - Give me one second.
I can't leave with that ring.
- Come here. - Fine.
- Gosh. - Get out of here.
We'll take care of him.
Don't you worry, Mr Lee and Ms Choi.
I'm sorry, Dad.
Mum.
It's not your fault.
I should have never forced you to get married to him.
You'll feel better since you took the pills.
Does it hurt a lot?
I'm feeling better now.
Your tummy is too small to take all that food.
You shouldn't eat so recklessly.
I did it because I was sorry.
My brother fired you, so you had to start working part-time.
I was sorry about that.
I felt like I needed to help you.
You had 5 hamburgers and 3 drinks in one sitting...
to boost our sales?
You're so clueless.
I don't understand.
What?
Someone like you...
should have rich and handsome men lined up for you.
I don't understand why you want me so badly.
I thought it was because you're dumb.
What did you say?
But you're not like that when it comes to other things.
Or maybe,
you're looking for an easy target who won't abandon you...
after being heartbroken after a breakup.
You're not easy.
If I put in half as much effort as I did to you to other guys,
they would be all over me by now.
Why are you doing this to me, then?
You move my heart.
You...
move my heart.
I know I'll look stupid.
I know you won't understand.
But I don't want to be smart and calculative...
when I'm with you.
I don't want to be like that.
I want to show you who I really am.
I just want to follow my heart...
without considering the consequences.
I have faith that...
you will accept me one day...
as who I really am.
Hyo Won.
I don't know if you heard,
but my mum...
is a second wife.
She kicked out my dad's sick wife for his money...
and took her spot.
She was shunned by everyone ever since then.
I didn't show it,
but it was hard for me, too.
Kids teased me and bullied me...
when I was in school.
The mum of a guy I met a few times when I was in college...
called to tell me to leave him because she didn't want...
her son to date the daughter of a mistress.
Really? That's horrible.
I know.
But things like that happened.
I pretended to be okay,
but I always felt intimidated.
I was always concerned what others thought about me.
That's why I found it hard to make friends.
But...
strangely enough, when I'm with you,
I let my guard down.
I trust you...
and I think you'll understand however stupidly I act.
It's not my fault that my mum's a mistress.
It's not your fault that you're poor.
That's why...
your conditions are of no concern to me.
We all lack something...
and if that's money, then that's actually a relief.
I thought you were thoughtless.
You actually had a lot to think about.
Am I a goldfish? To have no thoughts?
That stank.
I'm beginning to feel much better.
You can't burp like that in public. You are a goldfish.
Did you call me a goldfish?
What's that?
I didn't say anything.
You called me a goldfish. I heard it loud and clear.
I'm not a goldfish.
What else are you?
Carry me.
I can't carry you.
My tummy's hurting again.
Is it really?
- Are you happy now? - Yes.
- Is your tummy okay? - Yes.
- Are you sure? - Yes.
Good, then.
How was our first date?
I'll never forget it forever.
Mr Pretty Eyes.
I should go. It's getting cold.
I'll walk you to the door.
It was cold while watching a film. Go inside and warm up.
- But still. - Go inside.
Walk safely back.
Bye, then.
Mr Pretty Eyes is out.
Who's here?
What's the boss doing here so late at night?
I'm leaving after seeing Yun Shil.
What are you all doing here so late at night?
Us?
Our boss sent us.
I thought I warned you.
Stay away from his wife.
You threaten and scare people.
I know that's your thing, but it won't work with me.
What did you say?
One more thing.
Stay away from Yun Shil.
If you keep bothering a powerless young lady, I will make you pay.
Are you actually challenging us?
That's enough.
This is above our pay-grade.
Let's talk to the boss.
Hello.
Why aren't you at work? Are you sick?
I'll come in a bit late. I have something to take care of.
What's that?
It's nothing, really. I'll tell you later.
Bye.
(Prison)
Hello there. You came sooner than I thought.
I'm Lee Dong Jin.
I wanted to meet you.
(The Gentlemen of Wolgyesu Tailor Shop)
Are you dating?
Your expression changed recently.
How could you turn your back on me like this?
I gave up everything for you.
What happened?
You can't step a foot out of your room without my permission.
This is illegal, Mum. I'll call the police.
She hasn't called me once today. Is something wrong?
I'm afraid you'll get hurt.
Both happiness and fear come from heart.
So, focus on the happiness only.