(The following content may not be suitable for viewers under 15.)
(Viewer discretion is advised.)
(Episode 29)
I heard from the boys.
You must think you can play with...
that naive girl and have fun while I'm in here,
but if you do,
you're dead.
I know you have been forcing the relationship onto her.
Please let Yun Shil go now.
I didn't force anything.
Yun Shil and I are married.
That wedding was never completed,
and your marriage is not registered.
And most importantly,
you did not gain her love.
You know Yun Shil did not...
considered you as her husband...
even though she decided to marry you.
Don't give me that.
If you keep this up, I won't forgive you.
I can make sure you never walk again.
Look,
if I was afraid of your threats, I wouldn't be here.
You punk.
I...
love Yun Shil...
and I came here because I want to take responsibility for that love.
Please don't let your boys make Yun Shil miserable...
any more.
Please.
Making someone miserable and threatening...
isn't love. It's violence.
You should watch your words.
Do you think I'll be in here forever?
I'll get out in a few months.
How dare you run your mouth? How will you deal with the consequences?
Nothing will change...
even if you are released.
You don't know me very well.
I, Hong Gi Pyo,
shouldn't be taken so lightly.
I may kill you guys very secretly.
Do you think you can make Yun Shil happy?
She chose you...
in order to repay you.
Nothing will be left...
in that kind of relationship if the debt is repaid.
That's enough.
Get out of my sight.
And let me warn you again.
I'm not a moron who will let someone steal his wife.
Let me repeat. Yun Shil is not your wife.
Stop being stubborn.
You might think of me as a dead person because I'm in here,
but I have nothing else to lose.
That means I have nothing to fear...
and nothing to hold me back.
Do you understand?
I knew Yun Shil since she was young, so I know her very well.
She can never betray me.
- Hello? - It's me.
The line is busy.
Please leave a message...
Even if every woman out there changes, I never thought you would.
How long have I been in here? A year? 10 years?
How could you do this to me?
What do you mean?
That guy, the owner or something...
- just came to see me. - What?
How is someone having an affair with another man's wife so arrogant?
I'm just speechless.
Make some sort of an excuse.
What's going on?
- I'm sorry. - Sorry?
Are you apologising?
Are you saying you like him, too?
Is that how I should interpret?
Yes.
- That's what... - Hey!
Quiet.
How could you do this to me? You ingrate.
I made so many sacrifices for you.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry I couldn't keep my promise,
- but there was nothing I could do. - What?
It may sound irresponsible,
but I didn't want...
to get married.
How many couples get married because they're madly in love?
Everyone gets married like us and then they grow on each other.
You were lonely because I wasn't there,
and you fell for that jerk's ploys because you're naive.
But to be blunt,
why would someone like him love a girl like you?
He's just having fun. He'll discard you once he's done.
Why don't you see that, you idiot?
Even if that were to happen,
I won't regret it.
You have completely lost your mind.
I'm sorry.
That's all I can say.
If you thought an apology would cut it,
you were gravely mistaken.
Do you think I'll leave you guys alone?
I'm Hong Gi Pyo!
The day I'm released,
I'll set fire to the tailor shop and make sure...
Lee Dong Jin will never walks again. Got it?
I'll keep it brief.
I'll be getting out soon.
Don't do anything you'll regret later.
I wonder if Tae Pyung's suit is ready.
Yun Shil.
Why are you so jumpy?
I'm sorry.
Is something wrong?
What?
No, nothing.
But what did you say?
I wondered if Tae Pyung's suit was ready.
If you're done sewing it, I wanted to iron it and finish it.
Yes, it's almost done.
I'll finish sewing the buttonholes on the sleeves and give it to you.
- Okay. - Okay.
What's with her?
She's as pale as a ghost.
What's this place? Why does she come here early in the morning?
What's this? Is Tae Yang...
working here?
- What are you doing here so early? - What else?
I came to have a morning burger.
Will you eat again, after suffering like that yesterday?
That's why I didn't have breakfast and came straight here.
And at lunchtime, people...
I mean my friends are coming.
I'll raise your sales even more than yesterday.
You don't need to raise our sales, so please leave.
What? You can't kick out a customer.
I'll tell the store manager.
Please take my order.
One bulgogi burger, french fries, a cola,
a burrito and a shrimp ring.
Will you eat all of that?
Your stomach will burst.
Its okay. I'm going to stay here all day long.
All day?
I have to wait until you get off work.
Actually,
should I get a job here, too?
Should I work with you?
Forget it. Just eat your burger.
Welcome.
What are you doing?
Those punks are having fun dating.
This is serious.
Hi, son.
Why are you letting Hyo Won do whatever she wants?
What?
- Hyo Won? - Yes, Hyo Won.
Why are you letting a clueless little kid does as she pleases?
- What now? - Hyo Won...
went to see Tae Yang early in the morning.
I thought she was sleeping.
Where is Tae Yang?
He's working at a burger joint.
- What? - Do you want a loser...
who can't get a real job as your son-in-law?
He's too poor...
to afford his own place and lives in a hostel.
- He's not good enough for Hyo Won. - Not a chance.
I'm sure that Tae Yang, that punk,
is after Hyo Won for her money.
I asked him flat out,
and he said he isn't interested in her.
Seriously. You are so naive.
Did you believe him?
- It couldn't be. - No, it definitely cannot be!
Make sure she can't see Tae Yang again.
Seriously.
(Wolgyesu Tailor Shop)
Why are you standing outside in the cold?
What happened?
Why did you go see Gi Pyo without talking to me first?
Did he call?
He seemed very angry.
He's really scary when he's angry.
You never know what he'll do.
He's trying to scare you.
Don't think too seriously about it.
I know what he's like.
Once he loses his temper, he's capable of doing anything.
Calm down. Let's talk inside.
Listen to what I'm about to say.
Both happiness and fear come from heart.
I learned that during the few months I've been back here.
That's why in these situations,
your heart is the most important.
You want to be happy, don't you?
I do.
Then think only about that.
Everything else is what you must overcome, not fear.
Whether it's Gi Pyo or my family,
you can overcome it with me.
You understand what I mean, don't you?
I do.
That's why I went.
I wanted to handle the matter with Gi Pyo first.
- Still. - People like that...
specialise in intimidating others.
They aren't scary. They just scare you to fear them.
Those people fear people who don't get scared and confront them.
I'm not afraid of Gi Pyo at all.
So you have no reason to fear him either.
He doesn't listen to others.
I'm more afraid that you'll get hurt.
I told you.
People like that are meaner to weak people.
Of course, he'll threaten like crazy at first,
but he'll get worn out and leave.
I guarantee it.
Do you really think so?
Do you know why they call people like that "gangsters"?
Because they don't have the guts, so they need to travel in a gang.
If you aren't afraid and face them with confidence,
they will fear you instead.
Do you really think so?
Trust me.
I bought some baked sweet potatoes.
Sorry. Sorry.
What should we do?
It's okay. I'll talk to him.
My goodness.
I didn't see wrong just now, did I?
No, you didn't.
How long has it been?
It hasn't been long.
Before, it was just interest.
We got close recently.
I can't believe I missed it.
I did notice there was something going on between you two,
but I didn't know it had progressed this much already.
I gave it serious thoughts before making my decision.
I'd appreciate your support.
Of course. I'm always on your side.
But once the family finds out, especially your mother,
it may be a problem. Will you be okay?
I'll have to face it. Mother likes Yun Shil, too.
Naturally, Yun Shil is the purest person you'll find,
and your mother acknowledges that.
But I think it'll be a different story when it comes to you.
First, I need to take care of Gi Pyo.
I'll tell her afterward.
Please help me.
Sure, of course.
But Dong Jin,
to be honest,
I'd like to tell you to stop if you can.
Yun Shil's husband...
I mean, Gi Pyo is one thing.
There are so many mountains to climb.
I can't do that.
I'll make sure nothing will worry you.
Okay.
- Aren't you eating? - What?
No. I'm not hungry.
What are Mr Lee and Master talking about so seriously?
Is something wrong with the shop?
What? You met that man?
Yes. I just came back from visiting him at the prison.
You are determined this time.
Hi guys.
Please keep it a secret for now, especially from him.
Why did you stop talking as soon as I walked in?
What do you mean? We were just talking about the shop
Okay. I'll go up, then.
I'll let you two talk.
Dong Jin, you're dating, aren't you?
What do you mean?
I mean, you look completely different recently.
You used to always look angry and anxious.
See? Now, there's a sparkle in your eyes...
and just look at you.
You seem moody and emotional.
Yun Shil looks different lately, too.
Goodness.
People always said my eyes sparkled so much.
They called me "Mr Pretty Eyes".
My eyes started to sparkle when I was three.
They were always like that.
You started dating when you were three?
I was born this way. I had no choice.
I'm going up.
Okay, go up, Mr Pretty Eyes.
He is naiver than I thought.
I took a guess,
and he pretty much admitted to dating Yun Shil.
He did well in school, but he is...
very naive.
But you can't tell anyone, okay?
Okay.
But that couple won't have it easy either.
Worry about yourself.
What's going on with Dong Sook?
Mr Park has made his exit,
so you should march forward.
You should propose and strike with confidence.
I want to do that,
but then I wonder if I could take care a woman for live,
I feel very worried and scared.
Speaking of which, how did you propose to Sun Nyeo?
Don't ask.
It's painful.
I used so much blood to write this,
that I'm too dizzy to even sit straight.
So let's make it quick.
Is this blood?
Not red ink?
Don't you see this?
Take that off.
Why should I do that?
I barely stopped the bleeding.
If this is really written in your blood,
I'll marry you.
But if it's a lie,
you're out from this moment on.
I... I really did write it.
This is your blood, is that it?
There's no wound.
All you ever do is lie.
How dare a young kid talk about writing in blood?
It must have healed already.
My skin regenerates quickly, so it healed already.
I did write that with my blood.
At first, you lied that you were studying Korean literature at Ehwa.
Now, you lie that red ink is your blood?
What's in your head? Why do you always tell lies?
They were white lies.
That's how much I love you. That's why I did it.
This is not a white lie. It's a red lie.
So get out right now.
I won't take a step until you say...
you'll marry me.
Are you threatening me?
I'm not threatening you. I'm loving you.
Fine. Then I'll go.
Go after we're done talking.
What more is there to say?
And to be honest, you're not my type.
I like the puppy type.
But you're the cheetah type.
And I can't stand people who are pushy like you.
Then why did you kiss me under the street light...
a few days ago?
That's because I was too drunk and...
Anyway, I apologised.
You stole my lips and try to make it up with an apology?
Stole your lips? You stole my lips.
You were much more aggressive.
- You thief. - Why are you hitting me?
You thief.
- That hurts. - Thief.
- You thief. - Stop hitting me.
Freeze!
Why you...
You punk. What are you doing to Sun Nyeo?
Who are you? Why are you grabbing me like this?
Us? We're Sun Nyeo's cousins.
Cousins?
- How did you find me? - How dare you date?
You're just a kid.
- Did you call your cousins? - No, I did not.
Our aunt has been stressed out because of that girl,
so we followed her. Is that a problem?
- No. - You spent a night together, too?
No.
We didn't do anything weird. Nothing at all.
We drank and slept holding hands.
Do you expect me to believe that?
What are you going to do?
You ruined her future, so you should take responsibility.
Take responsibility? How?
What do you mean? How else?
You have to marry her.
Marry her?
See?
We're destined for each other.
I should have resisted, even if they beat me to death.
Whenever I think of that day, I want to stab myself.
I had no idea you had such a sad story.
Anyway, that was me.
Good luck.
You look great with the suit.
Hello.
- I'm looking for a jacket. - A jacket?
How about these?
I'll take this one.
- This one? - Yes.
This is your size, too.
This will keep you warm all winter long.
Please ring this up.
- Please come this way. - Thank you.
Who is that?
What is it now?
- What is that? - Take a look.
It's a total of 367 dollars.
It's 367.
Canned coffee, 60 cents. Soup, 6 dollars.
This is the total cost...
from while we were dating.
I was being nice...
and split it right down the middle.
As you can see,
I didn't add on a penny.
I can't believe this.
Wait.
Hold on. I have change.
Just give me 400.
Then...
it's 33, right?
Here's 30, and 3...
Here you are.
Give it to me.
Come to my house later.
I don't have enough cash.
Fine. I will.
Money matters should be resolved accurately,
so I'll wait until you get off work...
and wait...
by your house.
I've never met someone like that in my entire life.
Seriously.
Enjoy.
I'll take your order.
- Do you... - Have...
- A girlfriend... - Right now?
Sorry?
I'd like to get to know you better.
- Give me your number. - Give me your number.
Those little brats.
A girlfriend?
I do have a girlfriend.
He is totally my type.
I'm so sad.
You almost made me cry.
Just now. You said,
"I do have a girlfriend."
Why did that almost make you cry?
Weren't you talking about me?
No.
I lied, so that they would...
leave me alone.
- Really? - Really.
I was happy for nothing.
Welcome...
"Welcome"?
What?
Do you work here?
How did you find me?
- Did you follow me? - You're acting like a fool.
How could I not?
Hello.
You say you're not interested in her,
but you take off your shirt and show her your naked body...
and call her out to meet.
A man should stand by his word!
He didn't call me out.
- I came because I wanted to. - Shut it, brat!
I'm warning you.
You'll regret it if you don't leave my daughter alone!
I told you Tae Yang did nothing wrong!
Shut it!
If you see my daughter again,
I really won't forgive you!
Let's go!
- Let's go! - Tae Yang.
My bag. My bag.
- Let's go. - Tae Yang, I'll see you tomorrow.
She should have gone when I told her to.
She'll probably get in trouble at home.
My goodness.
That hurts!
How could you like someone who can't get a job...
and has to work at a burger joint?
And whose fault is that?
What will I do with you?
Do you know how worried your brother is?
Tell him to worry about himself.
Tae Yang is 100 times better...
than that witch Ji Yun.
Why you...
I'll make myself clear.
That witch Ji Yun will never become my sister-in-law.
How did he fall for that evil witch, anyway?
Ms Min Hyo Won. Just worry about yourself.
- Don't worry about him. - That hurts!
From this moment on, you cannot step foot...
outside of this house without my permission.
- Got it? - What?
- You can't do that. - Yes, I can.
- Darn it. - Go upstairs.
Our tailor shop...
is entering a department store?
Yes. It hasn't been finalised yet.
I wanted to get your opinions before submitting...
the proposal to the department store.
I'm all for it, of course.
Our tailor shop will become national and become huge.
That's true, but could this small crew...
meet their demands?
That concerns me as well.
So I suggest we control the volume...
by taking only advance requests...
and in-person requests.
We can hire more workers...
or collaborate with my father's mentees who are...
spread around the country.
Yun Shil, why aren't you saying anything?
Why is she so deep in thought?
- Yun Shil. - Oh my gosh.
You startled me.
- Why are you so jumpy? - I'm sorry.
My mind was elsewhere.
- Master. - Yes?
I'll take Yun Shil with me to research the department stores.
Okay. We need to do that...
in order to prepare the proposal anyway.
- Go ahead. - Okay.
- Get ready to go out. - Sorry?
Okay.
Weren't we going to the department store?
We're playing hooky.
Hooky?
You look stressed out,
so I want to take you somewhere to get some air.
You must be busy with the shop.
It's okay. Let's go back.
What do you think?
Isn't the ocean air clearing your head?
Yes. I feel like I can breathe again.
Thank you.
See? Aren't you glad you listened to me?
Give me your hand.
When I'm with you, I become more courageous...
and even feel stronger.
I guess you don't.
Don't you trust me at all?
It's not that.
I'm sorry.
We aren't alone. We have each other.
Let's share our burdens...
and double our joys, okay?
I know you're upset because I met Gi Pyo without telling you,
but I thought that was right.
For us to date in secret...
is like admitting that our love is forbidden.
So I want to...
tell my parents right away.
Give me a little more time.
I need to prepare myself.
Okay.
- I have... - By the way.
- What did Master Bae say? - Well...
He said he'd back us up, of course.
Was he upset that we hadn't told him sooner?
Dating at work is always like that.
Sam Do's good-hearted enough to understand.
He said he will support us, so don't worry.
I got you a...
I think Leather Jacket noticed something.
My goodness.
- Did something happen? - It's nothing.
Wait right there.
What is it? Did you drop something?
I got it.
What is it?
It's nothing. All is well.
You're drenched. Are you okay?
Yes.
I think I'm...
not okay.
My dear.
My goodness. My husband isn't that small,
but you're way too tall.
Thanks for lending me his trousers.
I'll return them as soon as my clothes dry.
Don't you worry. Come and eat.
The food's ready.
- Okay. - Thank you.
Just a moment.
What are you doing, taking a photo of this?
Tracksuit bottoms suit you well.
You look good. Very good.
That's impossible. Delete those.
I won't. I'll look at them whenever I feel down.
This is pathetic. I meant to draw a heart in the sand...
and put the necklace around her neck.
I just ruined my chances.
I'm freezing.
Why won't you eat?
I think I'm catching a cold. I lost my appetite.
Then eat the fish for its flavour.
That was lame.
I feel even worse now.
You feed me, then.
I had to battle the waves and all that...
drained me of my energy.
Don't be silly. You didn't battle anything.
You just splashed a few times.
That's not all I did. How could you put it like that?
Whose fault is it that I have a cold?
- Is it my fault? - Of course it is.
- Why? - It was your...
Don't ask. You don't need to know.
Anyway, feed me some food.
- Me? - Yes.
It melts in my mouth because you fed it to me.
Give me some soup.
You're so childish.
I'm serious.
I feel really unwell right now.
Okay, okay.
That tastes good.
You two look like a mummy bird feeding a baby bird.
It's so cute.
What are you doing? Don't starve your baby bird.
What do you want?
An oyster.
An oyster?
Here you go.
Here comes your oyster.
Here's your oyster.
- Is it good? - Yes.
- A shrimp next. - A shrimp?
(Shellfish Story)
What's that?
I felt bad that we had a good meal...
so I bought some fish and shrimp.
For your mum and dad.
You didn't have to.
Those are the shoes we bought last time.
Yes. What do you think?
They suit you.
Let's see...
Now we look like a real couple.
Just a moment.
Great.
Now that we're wearing the same shoes,
let's go back to the beach.
What for?
To do what I didn't get to do.
What do you mean?
You know, draw a huge heart in the sand...
and run after each other yelling, "Catch me if you can."
What every couple does at the beach.
Did you look it up online?
Why... Yes.
You said you caught a cold. Let's just go home.
We came all the way here. I can't just go home like this.
We should get back before Ms Choi prepares dinner.
When can I give her this, then?
- Let's go before it gets dark. - Okay.
This was so boring.
- Welcome home. - Hello.
- I heard you play Go. - What?
Sam Do told me that...
you go to play Go.
You didn't have to hide that.
You worked for us all your life.
No one will complain you for having a new hobby.
Thank you.
What's this?
Sweet red bean jelly?
With chestnuts, your favourite.
Did you buy these for me?
I bought them to make you smile,
because I like seeing your lovely smile.
Did you meet a little bird on the way home?
I quite like the new song you're singing.
Gok Ji.
I hope we can live for a long, long time.
I'd like you to stay with me for many years, in good health.
Here you go.
It's a new menu.
It's cooked in a special sauce, so it's salty...
but also sweet, so have a go.
What do you think?
- It's tasty. - Great.
Enjoy your meal.
(Dried fish shop)
Hi, Dried Fish. It's been a while. How have you been?
How are things over there?
Sun Nyeo, try not to be too shocked.
Is something wrong?
A few days ago, the oil store lady...
disappeared in the night.
What do you mean she disappeared in the night?
Where's our money?
It was my turn next month.
Taxi.
(Available)
Seoul Station, please.
I have to go to Daejeon.
Hurry, please.
Okay.
Silly me.
My head hurts.
B. B minor. Okay.
If you say that you want to date me now,
I'd definitely be interested.
Do you want to date me?
Mr Park has made his exit,
so you should march forward.
You should propose and strike with confidence.
Even if we do rush things,
if we get married,
I have to find a place...
with two rooms for us to live in.
I can't propose to her without any plan.
What will you do, Tae Pyung?
Is my phone on vibrate?
It's not.
No missed calls?
She hasn't called me once today.
Is something wrong?
We have until she finishes her shower.
Hurry up.
- It's all done. - Good.
- Thank you. - Bye.
What...
is that?
Did you just lock my room?
You're grounded.
First you took my phone, now I'm grounded?
Sorry.
I have no choice.
Come back. Ma'am! Mr Kim!
Get her! Don't let her get out!
Get out of my way.
If we do, we'll get fired this time.
She's about to lock me up.
Don't you feel sorry for me?
Mum.
Please let me go.
You can't go anywhere in that.
Take her to her room.
- Yes, Madam. - Yes, Madam.
This is a crime, Mum.
I'll call the police.
Do whatever you want.
Open the door.
Until you promise you will break up with Kang Tae Yang,
I won't let you out.
That will never happen. Dream on.
Okay, then. I'll never unlock the padlock.
I'll serve your dinner on a tray.
Mum.
- Open the door. - Shut your mouth.
Should you really be locking up a grown woman?
- Stay out of it. - Let her marry whoever she likes.
Or she'll regret like me.
You brat.
Would you say that if she were your real sister?
I wonder.
All I have to do is watch and enjoy.
Have fun.
What a jerk.
I'm back, Sir.
Hello.
You did a good job today.
- Where's Ms Choi? - She is preparing for dinner.
Good.
Do you have any difficulty reading the paper?
Not yet. I can manage.
Good.
These are vitamins that are good for your eyesight.
Take two of them each day.
Thank you.
Seeing you read the paper...
makes me cry.
Hello.
Where's Dong Jin?
He's...
meeting a client.
- Is he late? - Yes.
He hasn't called yet.
He should be home for dinner.
About...
Yun Shil.
She works so hard and so well.
She does the work of three people.
She's sweet and skilled.
She's nicer than most girls.
She is.
At first she and Dong Jin got off on the wrong foot,
but now they get along so well.
Everything's great.
It would be so nice...
if she were your daughter-in-law.
Don't be silly.
What are you saying?
- Hello. - Hi.
Hello.
Did you meet our client?
- What? - Client.
Yes.
It worked out just fine.
Here.
Yun Shil bought it for you.
- Yun Shil? - Yes.
She saw them at a market and thought they looked fresh.
She bought it for you.
She should've kept it for herself.
Shall we have soup stew?
I'd like that.
I was just...
talking to them about Yun Shil.
What? What about?
I said she is a hard worker.
It was just nonsense. Don't bother.
Okay.
It's meant to be a secret.
I didn't say anything.
Oh my.
They're as fresh as if they came straight from the sea.
Let me see.
Hello, Ms Choi.
Dong Jin just brought home the fish.
It's not much. I hope you enjoy it.
We will, thanks to you.
Where did you find such fresh fish?
A distant relative...
sent them to me.
- Dong Jin said you bought them. - What?
Did a relative send these?
Yes. See...
A distant relative bought them at a market...
and sent them to me,
- and I gave it to you. - That's so complicated.
Thank you anyway.
You're welcome. Have a good night.
Why...
do I feel so scared?
I should have gave her...
on the beach in the sunset.
I totally ruined my plan.
Goodness.
Who's this??
What are you doing here?
Call Dong Sook for me.
Call her yourself.
Isn't it over between you?
It may be, but we have a deal to settle.
Call her for me.
A deal? What deal?
What could it be?
The money I spent on our dates.
We decided to split it.
Go get her.
You are amazing.
How could you think of halving the cost of your dates?
That's why I'm a landlord.
I'm more powerful than a deity.
I just can't stand you any more.
Is she not home yet?
Listen.
I need to bill you as well,
but I won't ask for it as I'm too pity for you.
- What bill? - Think.
You bashed my head in a few days ago.
I bought an ointment and bandages.
I was going to bill you,
but decided that you couldn't afford to pay up. Okay?
Mister.
- Hello, Da Jeong. - If you left my mum over me,
you don't have to.
I'll live here with my grandma and grandpa.
How thoughtful.
You're way more thoughtful than your mum.
Let's get this out in the open.
You and I aren't related at all...
and we dislike each other.
Your mum is weird.
Why does she want her grown daughter to move in with us?
That's like one plus one for me.
How dare you say something like that.
Why do you always grab my collar?
Calm down.
Da Jeong, go on inside.
Don't worry. Just go on inside.
Marrying Dong Sook makes Da Jeong your daughter.
How dare you hurt her like that?
Jerks like you need to be taught a lesson.
Are you addicted to grabbing people by the throat?
Don't you dare touch my face or my body.
If you do again, I'll sue you.
If you truly love someone,
you must accept the person as they are.
You didn't love Dong Sook.
You are a pathetic singer. No wonder you sing about love.
Trashy landlords like you have no right...
to love someone like Dong Sook, okay?
My goodness.
You're such a joke. Crawl back to your building!
By the way, where is she?
Why isn't she back yet?
We're told never to trust anyone,
but how could she do this to us?
Almost everyone in the market lent her money.
She took that and all the money we lent her.
She planned this for a long time.
We lost our rent deposit...
and now the money I lent her.
We're really dirt poor now.
What should I do now?
Hello?
Where are you?
Me?
Where am I?
I must have taken a wrong turn.
What are you talking about?
I was so deep in thought. I got off the bus at the wrong stop.
Where am I?
What were you thinking about?
I wonder myself.
I think I got off a stop too soon.
I'll take another bus. I won't be long.
Why do you sound so upset? Is something wrong?
Why would there be?
I'll get right on the next bus.
I guess this is how he felt...
when he found out he owed 50,000 dollars.
I had no idea...
and gave him a hard time.
Where's the nearest bus stop?
Open the door right now.
Promise me you'll leave Tae Yang.
- Then I'll let you out. - I can't do that.
Then you'll have to stay in there for the next 10 days.
Maybe even a whole month, okay?
Even if you lock me up for a whole year,
I won't break up with him.
I can't believe you're such a romantic.
Hyo Sang and Choi Ji Yun are here.
Without even calling ahead?
We have a visitor, so stay quiet. Okay?
I'll jump out my window if you don't let me out.
Do whatever you want.
Give me back my phone, then.
I want to hear Tae Yang's voice. Please?
Mum.
Hello, Mother.
What are you doing here?
I invited her over for dinner.
We should meet at a restaurant. Why to bring her here?
I was trying to think of a way to get close to you...
and Hyo Sang suggested that we should eat together often.
I know it's rude, but here I am.
Is Hyo Won out?
What?
Yes.
She's out.
I'll help set the table.
Did Hyo Won go to see Tae Yang?
I locked her up.
You did what?
I had a padlock put on her door to lock her up.
I know she's a bit mad and all,
but you should talk to her, not lock her up.
She's in no state of mind to do as she's told.
Tae Yang is causing trouble for so many of us.
It's not my fault that my mum's a mistress.
It's not your fault that you're poor.
That's why your conditions are of...
no concern to me.
We all lack something...
and if that's money, then that's actually a relief.
What's wrong with me?
(Kang Tae Yang)
(Lee Chang Hee, Kang Tae Yang)
What's all this?
Isn't it beautiful?
Your girlfriend came by and stocked the fridge.
Who, Hyo Won?
As a fellow man, I'm so envious.
Where did you find an angel like her?
The quality of the food is incredible.
There's tteokgalbi, expensive fish, salted fish roe and abalone.
Those are special dishes.
Tae Yang, can I have some?
Sure you can.
Really? Thanks.
Is something wrong?
Why didn't she call?
Where are you going?
For some fresh air. I feel stuffy.
Don't you have a cold?
I'll just walk around the block. It won't be long.
Okay.
It's not like he has a wife to keep him company.
The winter nights must be so long and lonesome.
Hello?
- Are you in bed? - Not yet.
I'm on my way to your place.
What for?
To give you something.
What?
I just passed the junction.
I'll be there in three minutes.
The road looks different at night.
Is it this alley?
Or that one?
It's this one.
It's me.
Is he here already?
Hang on.
What brings you here at this hour?
What's this?
Open it.
This is...
I wanted to hang this...
around your neck on the beach while the sun was setting,
but I dropped it into the sea. So my plans were ruined.
There are two rings.
One is yours and one is mine.
Once we have taken care of...
all the problems we're faced with,
let's put wear them together with a happy heart.
- Dong Jin... - Until then,
please take care of them.
Can you do that?
It suits you.
It's lovely.
Thank you.
You can't cry over something like this.
This is nothing.
Thank you is...
all I can say.
That goes for me, too.
Thank you.
Thank you for...
appearing before me.
See,
I have a bit of a cold.
If I kiss you now, you might catch it.
It's okay.
What?
I have a pretty strong immune system.
I don't catch colds easily.
I see. That's a relief.
Then...
Your eyes.
I think I lost out.
- What do you mean? - If I'd known you wanted a kiss...
enough to be willing to catch a cold,
I'd have kissed you sooner.
What do you mean?
You kissed me first.
I paused to ask you a question.
If you're okay with catching a cold.
I don't remember.
You're unbelievable.
Do you really not remember that?
- Did you have to embarrass me? - Why did you hit me?
- You can't mention such things. - Okay, I won't.
- Don't hit me. - You hit me first.
Stop it.
What are you doing?
(We thank Choi Sung Kook for his special appearance.)
(The Gentlemen of Wolgyesu Tailor Shop)
Did she find out already? Can you handle it?
About Dong Jin. We should find him a wife.
Why is life so hard?
Why does nothing work out?
Really? Young Eun's back?
I guess Sung Jun really loves you, Mum.
- What? - Do you want to marry him?
- What are you doing here? - Did you let Hyo Eun out?
Let's go to community service centre right now.
Please let me go now.