(The following content may not be suitable for viewers under 15.)
(Viewer discretion is advised.)
(Episode 3)
Are you okay?
You're the CEO.
What? Is it you again?
You aren't ignoring me this time.
Do you remember me?
Is this a joke?
Why did you follow me here? Are you a stalker?
Me? A stalker? No way.
I'm not like that.
Why did you follow me, then?
I didn't follow you. I was just taking care of...
You're the one who showed up while I was taking care of business.
An adult should know better than to urinate in public.
Where are your manners?
It wasn't in public.
My mother-in-law works at this vineyard.
What are you doing here anyway?
Are you a pervert?
A what?
I came here for a company dinner.
I came to eat some kind of fish...
Forget about it. What a rotten day.
Grape stains never come out.
Gosh, where do you think you're touching?
By the way,
don't you know Hong Gi Pyo?
I said I don't.
Why do you keep saying that?
You're the CEO of Meesa Apparel.
I'm not.
How many times must I tell you that I'm not?
Mr CEO.
Where are you?
- Mr CEO.
-  Darn it.
Mr CEO.
Why are you hiding?
- What about you?
-  Mr CEO.
Should I not?
- Mr CEO.
-  Sit still.
Mr CEO.
You are the CEO.
- Meesa Apparel CEO Min Hyo Sang.
-  Mr CEO.
I'm not. That's not who I am.
Where in the world is he?
Oh, no.
Wait.
Don't just leave.
You might as well help me out.
I have a feeling you could get Gi Pyo out.
There's a misunderstanding.
I don't know that name.
- Will you let go of me?
-  Oh, no.
Could you help me get up?
Gosh, grape stains are hard to get out.
Wait. Sir.
Good riddance.
Sir. Come back!
Hey! Come back!
Something bad happens whenever I meet her.
Gosh, what a mess.
This shirt's ruined.
Look at this mess.
My goodness gracious.
What happened?
You crushed some perfectly fine grapes.
What should I do with these? It's such a waste.
Are you here to help me or ruin me?
Why are you always causing trouble?
I'm really sorry.
- Lead the way.
-  What?
We can't let someone get away with ruining our grapes.
We have to get compensated.
He didn't ruin them on purpose.
He just lost his balance and fell.
What is wrong with you? What kind of attitude is that?
Your husband's in jail, and he needs our support.
We have to salvage and sell whatever we can.
I would love to know what you're thinking.
I wasn't like you the last time Gi Pyo was in jail.
Was he in jail before?
Is this not his first time?
Stop talking nonsense.
Just lead the way.
Come along.
- I couldn't find him.
-  Did he get lost?
Sir.
- My goodness.
-  Sir.
What happened to you?
I lost my balance and fell. I'm fine, though.
You don't look fine.
- Miss Kim, your handkerchief.
-  My handkerchief.
Really, it's fine.
You need to wipe that off.
You look like a drenched mouse.
You there.
Is that him?
You can't just disappear after crushing...
someone's prized grapes.
You look like a gentleman.
I was going to report you for destroying my crops,
but then I got curious.
I wanted to see the face of the shameless fool...
who had the guts to run off after doing this.
- That's why I'm here.
-  Mother.
You're such a softie. Be quiet.
Look here, lady.
Don't talk to him like that.
Do you even know who this gentleman is?
- Who is he?
-  Let me introduce him.
This is Meesa Logistics' CEO, Lee Dong Jin.
Aren't you Min Hyo Sang?
Mr Min's the CEO at our head office in Seoul.
Mr Lee here is the CEO of Meesa Logistics.
That means you must have a lot of money.
That's 10 boxes at 20 dollars per box.
So you owe me 200 dollars.
How is this worth...
Okay. Fine.
We don't take credit cards. It's cash only.
Sorry.
If you're short on cash, I can lend you some.
- 30 dollars, please.
-  Sure.
Here you go.
Sorry. It wasn't my idea. I'm really sorry.
I'm so sorry. I really am.
- He isn't in.
-  Oh, dear.
Do you think he's ill?
I hope not.
His wife is here.
- Hello.
-  Hello.
Is your husband sick?
He isn't.
Why hasn't he come to work then?
I haven't seen him in days.
He had some family business to take care of.
He went to his hometown.
My goodness, I had no idea.
I thought he had fallen ill.
I was so worried.
Do you know when he will be back?
I don't know.
It'll take him some time to sort everything out.
Just a moment.
I brought these for your husband.
I didn't pick them up from the street.
They're from my back garden.
They're clean and fresh. Cook your husband something.
How do you know that...
he likes courgettes?
You might not know, but your husband...
is like family to us now.
He cares for my daughter like she's his own granddaughter.
He's like a dad to me.
(Closed for a while)
Your food is here.
My gosh. You didn't have to come all the way here.
I could come home for lunch.
You missed lunch because you had to go out on business.
I made kalguksu...
with fresh clams and courgettes, your favourite.
Eat up before it gets cold.
It smells delicious.
Try the soup first.
I worked so hard all day that I can't even hold a spoon.
Could you feed me?
You become more like a child as you get older.
What if people see?
It's just us. Who is there to look? Come on. Feed me your kalguksu.
My goodness.
Open wide.
That's good.
It tastes better because you're feeding me.
Your comments are getting cornier, too.
I'm getting goosebumps.
Do you like me that much?
Will you stop it?
You can't stop liking me, can you?
Stop being silly and eat up. My goodness.
Here you go.
That is so good.
I hope he's eating well.
Stop making me worry and come back home.
I'll chop up some courgettes...
and make you kalguksu.
Hey.
Excuse me.
What's he thinking about?
Sir, wake up. The chicken's burnt.
Oh, dear. Was it in for that long?
It turned black in a blink of an eye.
You're so witty.
If you could spare me a few minutes, I'll fry up a fresh young chicken.
Sure, go ahead.
You must work out in your free time.
Look at your muscles.
I do, a bit.
You have a lovely set of biceps and triceps.
They're like a horse's thighs.
You must work out yourself if you can tell them apart.
I've been going to the gym for over 10 years.
Oh, I see. That must be it.
I could tell you know a few things about muscles.
If only my husband had muscles like yours.
Would you mind if I touched them?
What?
That's a bit...
Just a slight touch.
Let me compare it with my husband's.
Quickly, then.
This here is the bicep.
This is the real deal.
And to the back here is the triceps.
They say it looks like the horse's thigh.
My finger won't even go in. You're so...
Who are you?
- What are you doing to my husband?
-  Honey.
You can't assault our customers. She'll lose her hair.
Ouch, ouch.
Take your chicken and leave.
Don't ruin the market's friendly atmosphere...
by groping my husband's arm.
Let go! I didn't grope anything!
I just wanted to compare it to my husband's arm!
She didn't grope me. I taught her about muscles.
Don't you lie to me.
Let go before I call my husband!
Okay. Get your husband over here.
I will grope his muscles instead...
and maybe even crush them if I can.
That really hurts!
(Traditional patbingsu)
She's so violent and ignorant.
She's always getting into fights.
Everyone saw her.
What an embarrassment.
I can't stand it.
I've had enough.
That's so cold.
Oh, dear.
(Mr Lee)
The phone has been turned off. Please leave a message.
To record, press one.
Why won't you pick up? Where are you? What are you up to?
Can you at least leave a message to say you're okay?
If you're angry or upset, go home and talk it over.
I'll wait for your call.
You're possessed by a fighter's ghost.
What woman doesn't care about shame or reputation?
You assault someone at least twice a week.
I told you to sell chicken, not flirt with customers.
Why did you start all this by showing her your muscles?
Get help before it's too late.
Why? Am I bleeding?
I don't think so.
Go to a mental hospital. Your jealousy is just too much.
- What?
-  See?
This is why two people who are similar should get married.
You married me out of greed.
That's why you're always anxious.
You're chronically and habitually delusional.
I'm married to a man who looks so perfect.
I must've done something heroic in my previous lifetime.
Sun Nyeo, could you grant your great husband one wish?
You know that I'm...
I'm very sensitive and artistic.
Do I really have to spend my life...
chopping up and frying pieces of chicken in a market?
Not again.
Don't even talk about suits.
Mr Lee left home. He disappeared.
- Why is that your business?
-  Why do you think he left?
He inherited the store, and he has no one to leave it to.
He can't bear the thought of closing it himself.
Mr Lee practically saved my life. He's like a father to me.
He put me through high school and got me a job.
He did what my biological father didn't.
Could you please let me take over his store?
This is your final warning.
If you go back to making suits,
it really is over between us.
I'll divorce you.
Divorce?
Should I just go for it?
We called it in three days ago. Why hasn't anything happened?
We're doing our best. Give us a bit more time.
The FBI and CSI people...
find criminals just like that with very little evidence.
Why are you so slow?
We're... What's the word?
We preserved the scene and there are clues everywhere.
What's the problem?
You watched a little too much TV.
What?
All I do is look at you.
(Miseong Supermarket)
All I do is wait for the right time
I'm always whispering sweet nothings.
And yet I can't.
Say that I love you.
- I just stand in the alley
-  My goodness.
- Who's that?
-  As I miss you.
It's Sung Jun.
My heart just aches.
For your love.
What should I do?
We're running in circles.
Time is passing us by.
First, he sang at a wedding.
Now, he's promoting a supermarket.
How did he end up like this?
Oh, dear. It's raining.
My heart just aches.
For your love.
What should I do? It's raining.
What should I do?
My goodness.
I was a fan since I was a teenager.
"Susanna's Handkerchief" is still my favourite song.
I can't believe I'm sharing an umbrella with a fan.
It's like a scene from a romance novel.
When do you get off work?
I think I can wrap things up soon.
Why don't you come back to my store to dry up...
and have some tea?
That's so nice of you. Is your business nearby?
Yes.
What do you do?
You could say that I'm into contents distribution.
Contents distribution?
Contents distribution was an exaggeration.
All she does is rent comic books.
Sung Jun.
I made you ramyeon that's so good, you won't notice a murder happen.
My goodness. It'd be wrong of me to eat this here.
I'm not that rude. Don't mind me.
I haven't seen you in so long.
I don't mind serving you instant noodles.
I think...
you are slightly older than I am.
You keep talking to me like I'm older.
I don't know how to react.
Is there something wrong with my makeup?
I'm not that old.
I'm a year younger than you.
How rude of me.
My apologies.
It's fine. It happens.
Don't feel pressured...
and help yourself.
Okay.
I don't want to be rude, so I'll just have a taste.
Maybe it's because you're a singer, but you have strong lungs.
That was cooked perfectly.
Have some kimchi, too.
The kimchi turned red in anger...
because I was eating only the noodles.
You haven't lost your sense of humour, either.
"Red in anger". You're so funny.
So you like these types of jokes.
(Dong Sook's Comic Book Store)
What is this?
- Thank you for the noodles.
-  No way.
I didn't cook you noodles to make money off of you.
I know.
I...
I know how you feel, Dong Sook.
But I hate taking things for free. It goes against my principles.
I was famous for refusing sponsors when I was active as a singer.
Yes, but...
still,
I can't take money from you.
Rather than money,
why don't you sign some autographs for our clients?
What autographs?
Shall I?
Thank you.
Everyone.
Attention please.
Today, the famous rock ballad singer,
Sung Jun, is here with us today.
He says he will give five lucky people an autograph...
on a first-come-first-served basis,
so please line up.
It's only the first five.
Mr Kim, don't you want an autograph?
I'm fine.
What about you, Mr Park?
These days, I guess everyone call themselves a singer.
Min Soo, isn't it your dream to become a singer?
You should get an autograph from an experienced singer.
How lame.
- You rude little...
-  I have a gig, so I need to go.
- Thank you for the noodles.
-  But...
Sung Jun. Sung Jun.
Sung Jun!
Sung Jun! Sung Jun!
What do I do? That must have hurt his ego.
Why were they being so difficult? Just take the free autograph.
Those punks are useless.
How humiliating.
What a disgrace.
I will never forget this insult.
They said we could turn our misfortunes into our advantage.
I'll call and then...
(Two Grand)
I'll put an end to this.
(Traditional Chicken for Sale)
What? What now?
What do you mean, "what now?" When will you pay for my guitar?
I have nothing to say,
- so talk to my wife. Wait.
-  You coward.
I have nothing to say to your wife, so don't you dare put her on.
Yes, hello.
We were just about to forget, and you call again.
I fixed it perfectly with glue.
What did you call to complain about this time?
Look, mister!
Are you listening? Hey!
This is not my day.
I'm so humiliated.
He didn't do it on purpose.
It was an accident.
You went too far, taking 200 dollars...
for the grapes.
It's not like we need to throw them out.
If we make grape juice like this, we don't take a loss at all.
You're such a softy.
How many times do I have to tell you?
We need to earn as much as possible...
to send your husband some money when he's in jail.
I'm telling you, it's not easy taking care of someone in jail.
Goodness.
Also, let me make this clear just in case.
You may not gone through with the wedding,
but you promised to wed and exchanged rings,
so you and Gi Pyo are a married couple, okay?
So don't get any funny ideas and wait like a good little girl,
and prepare yourself to be a good wife.
Why aren't you responding?
Yes, Mother.
I've never worked at a convenience store before.
It's your rare day off. Why didn't you rest at home?
I like helping you like this.
It's not helping at all, so please leave.
- Hello?
-  Is this Kang Tae Yang?
Yes, it is. Who is this?
This is the HR office at Meesa Apparel.
You passed...
the written application stage for the open recruitment,
so I wanted to let you know.
Om September 5 at 1pm,
come to Meesa headquarters for your interview.
I really passed?
You didn't call the wrong number, did you?
- Is it really Kang Tae Yang?
-  Yes, it is.
We will text you the details for the interview.
Tae Yang, you just got a job, didn't you?
Which company is it? Where?
I passed the written application stage, that's all.
That's awesome!
I heard it's impossible to pass even the application stage.
You're awesome.
It's nothing. Stop freaking out.
It is not nothing.
You need to look good for the interview,
- so I'll cut your hair.
-  No thanks.
Tae Yang, do you want to watch a movie with me?
I'll treat you to a movie and dinner since I got paid today.
I watch movies and eat only with my girlfriend.
Do you mean the announcer, Choi Ji Yun?
You know well.
She's a regular at our salon,
and she's so arrogant and stubborn.
She complains about the shampoo scent, the water temperature...
and all sorts of ridiculous things that drives the staff crazy.
Da Jeong. Watch what you say. You don't even know her.
Women know women the best.
Don't come by if you're going to say things like that.
You'll regret it when she betrays you and breaks your heart!
He's so stupid.
He has no taste in girls.
- Let's eat.
-  Okay.
- Here. Cheers.
-  Cheers.
- Cheers.
- Thank you.
-  Hi, Dong Sook.
Has Dad called yet?
Did you go to the police?
No. I'm out of town, so I can't today.
I'll go tomorrow.
How's Mother doing?
Okay. I'll see you tomorrow.
Anyway, my uncle is the mayor of this town,
so he went...
to the grape orchard owner's son's wedding,
and he said the police came barging in during the ceremony...
and that it was a huge mess.
- That means they never got married.
-  That's right.
I heard the groom used to be part of a gang.
Did he start a gang fight or something?
No. That son had the galls to take Meesa suits...
and change the labels and sell them.
- That jerk.
-  What? Really?
What do you mean? What are you talking about?
Look here!
Hey, lady.
Where's your husband?
- Why do you ask?
-  Your husband...
changed the labels on Meesa suits and sold them in the market,
and that's why he's in jail, right?
I don't know any of that.
Of course, you do.
- Were you in on it?
-  What?
Did you and your husband work together to commit the crime?
What are you talking about?
If not, why did you come into my office...
and ask for Min Hyo Sang?
What about you? Why were you in someone else's office?
Don't change the subject and answer my question.
Why must I do that?
And why are you being rude to me?
I'm busy, so move.
What are you doing?
Hi, Mr Kang. It's me.
Our company filed a suit recently against someone taking our suits...
and selling them under a different label. Find out its status for me.
- Great work today.
-  Thanks.
- You too.
-  Let's go eat.
What should we get?
Are you just getting off work?
Who is he? Is he your boyfriend?
Really? You had a boyfriend?
He isn't my boyfriend. He's just a friend from college.
What brings you here?
I wanted to grab dinner with you.
You should've called first. What if we missed each other?
I'm going to go first. I'll see you tomorrow.
- Good night.
-  I'll see you another time.
- Okay.
-  Sure.
Why do you keep showing up without calling?
I kept calling, but you didn't pick up.
Do you think I'm still a trainee? I'm an announcer now.
I sometimes don't even have time to eat with broadcasts and meetings.
Must you run right over to complain just because I don't pick up?
I'm sorry for showing up unannounced,
but I'm not here to fight, so let's stop.
Is that a new watch?
It's a fake.
I saw it in Dongdaemun when I went for a shoot.
It's cheap.
It's late, but happy birthday.
What is it?
It took me a while to pick it. I hope you like it.
I'm sorry, but I can't accept that.
- What do you mean?
-  A ring...
is too burdensome. Sorry.
Are you saying I am burdensome to you now?
No, that's not it.
If not, just take it. I won't force you to wear it.
I said no.
Are you okay? Are you hurt?
My watch.
I scratched it. Oh, no.
I'll buy you a new one.
Do you know how much this costs? Someone like you can't afford it.
Someone like me?
You said it's cheap.
You said you bought it from Dongdaemun.
I didn't tell you the truth to spare your pride,
but you can't afford this even if you save up for 10 years.
You can never buy me a new one.
Does that ring cost even 100 dollars?
You got a cash advance in order to buy that, didn't you?
I'm going to get a job soon.
I got a call saying that I passed the written application stage.
Is there any guarantee...
that you'll pass the interview?
Ji Yun.
Once you pay off your school loans, send your mother money...
and pay your rent, how much would you have left?
What's wrong with you?
When I look at you, I'm reminded of when I ate...
at the convenience store to save just a few cents.
It's so pathetic that it's suffocating.
So leave me alone.
Please, I beg you.
(Yun Shil)
Are you in Seoul?
No, I'm still in Anseong.
There's so much to do, so I am helping Mother. I'll go tomorrow.
Did you give Ji Yun her gift?
- Not yet.
-  Why not?
You haven't seen her yet?
What? Well...
She must be busy. I'll give it to her another time.
Why do you sound so down?
Is something wrong?
I just feel deflated.
Yun Shil.
I hear there's a watch that I can't buy even if I save up for 10 years.
That's so unfair.
If I can't buy a stupid watch...
after saving for 10 years,
something is wrong with this world, don't you think?
What are you talking about?
Yun Shil! Where are you?
My mother-in-law is looking for me. I'll call you later.
I'm coming!
I hear this part-time job pays well.
The medical testing?
I made 700 dollars after four days last month.
- 700 dollars?
-  Give them a call.
I need to do this.
700 dollars? Wow.
A new drug test?
The world has changed.
People don't like your style of music any more.
Find another path.
I...
am Sung Jun.
I won Best New Artist in the music awards in the year 2000.
I'm Sung Jun!
I will show them.
I'll make my come-back as a singer...
and silence those jerks who disrespected me.
You guys...
are all dead.
Just wait.
Ma'am, may I have more soup?
- Don't you want an autograph?
-  I'm fine.
These days, I guess everyone call themselves a singer.
How lame.
Sung Jun! Sung Jun!
Poor Sung Jun.
Go to sleep already.
I have to leave early for work tomorrow.
Okay.
So find a good shaman.
If I can find out where he is,
I will pray, make sacrifices and do whatever it takes.
Who is that?
Okay. Call me.
Who is it?
I called my sister to find me a good shaman.
Come on, now.
How could you believe in superstitions like that?
You annoying brat.
Why are you hitting me?
Who cares if it's just a superstition?
We need to do everything possible...
to find your father.
I went to the police...
and called everywhere he could've gone.
I've done my best, too.
Did he get possessed or something? What happened?
How could he disappear overnight?
What is going on?
That's it.
- What?
-  We made a mistake...
on the tombstone for Uncle who passed away this spring.
What?
We made a mistake on the tombstone, so the ghosts must be angry.
Why else would your father leave home? Why?
Hold on.
Wait. Hold on.
What are you doing?
I can't just sit here.
I'll go to Uncle's wife...
and tell her to fix the tombstone.
Come on.
Do you realise what time it is?
Get your head on straight.
Who cares about the time?
We don't know where your father is or what he's doing.
It's past 10pm.
Sleep for now, and I'll go with you tomorrow. Okay?
What am I supposed to do?
What are you doing?
You should be happy I'm sleeping in the same room.
Are you still angry?
I said I was sorry.
You humiliated me in front of everyone. An apology doesn't cut it.
I didn't humiliate you. You can argue at times...
You're supposed to argue with your mouth.
But you used your hands and fists.
You're lucky she didn't file charges against you.
Do you think I'd just take it if she did?
She was groping my husband's arms.
- She deserved it.
-  Why do I bother?
- My goodness.
-  My gosh.
My life stinks.
Are you really going to sleep separately?
Don't touch me.
Come on, now.
I'm not in the mood.
You're never in the mood.
Come on, Sam Do.
Get off of me! What's wrong with you?
I have no idea where Mr Lee is or what he's doing.
How dare you try to seduce me? You're despicable.
To be blunt,
are you his son or something?
His children aren't doing anything.
Why are you so upset?
I told you. He is just like a father to me.
So please,
can't I run the tailor shop at least until he returns?
The store's about to close. Please.
I warned you...
never to mention the tailor shop again!
- My goodness.
-  Sun Nyeo.
Sun Nyeo. Sun Nyeo. I'll be good.
Stop it!
My gosh.
What should I do about the tailor shop?
My gosh. It reeks of alcohol.
You drank until you were plastered, and you're drinking more?
Can't you live without alcohol?
Maybe you should get tested for alcoholism.
What if I'm alcoholic?
Was stealing Dad's fortune not enough?
- You plan to pocket mine, as well?
-  What?
Why do I bother talking with a drunkard? I should stop.
Did you visit your in-laws?
I heard your father-in-law ran away from home.
You're the only daughter-in-law. You should do your duty.
My duty?
It's so awkward hearing you say that.
You should think about your husband.
He must feel bad toward his mum and sister about living here anyway.
If the only daughter-in-law doesn't care about his family,
how would he look?
Shouldn't you...
be the one to go visit my in-laws?
I heard you used to work...
at my father-in-law's shop before you got married.
You brought the clients tea and did the laundry.
But then again, I did hear you were quick-thinking even then.
According to my mother-in-law.
And? Did your mother-in-law say anything else?
Why? Do you share a secret with my in-laws or something?
What secret?
You look scared.
Did you steal money or something?
You should know how to hold your liquor. You're a mess.
That viper.
- Is she drinking again?
-  Yes.
She's completed plastered.
Why did her father-in-law leave home?
That's the thing. They don't know.
How could they not know? Are you saying he left for no reason?
I don't know. Da Jeong doesn't seem to want to talk about it, either.
What gotten into him? He's not like this.
Dong Jin.
Why do you look like that?
Dong Jin. Are you doing physical labour at the factory?
No, I'm not.
Where's Hyo Joo?
She's in the kitchen.
How long are you going to lock him up in the factory?
When will you call him up to headquarters?
He barely just left. We can't call him back up already.
You're terrible.
I won't be your daughter any more. Remove me from the family registry.
I wondered why you weren't bringing that up.
You evil stepmother!
You fool.
If I'm the evil stepmother, you're the evil stepsister.
Really?
Why are you hitting me? You're so annoying.
Did you call my mother?
I said to at least call her if you weren't going to visit.
Do you expect me to be a good daughter-in-law in this situation?
And what situation is that?
Like you don't know?
Everything will be back to normal, so get your act together.
What do you mean?
Do you mean...
- you can become CEO again?
-  Of course.
Do you mean it? You're not just saying it, are you?
Do I look that reckless to you?
- No.
-  So please...
stop drinking.
What is it?
How did things change that you're so confident?
Hyo Sang and Mother will have to give in.
- Really? Do you mean it?
-  Yes.
Thank you. Thank you, Honey.
What are you doing, Mum?
- I think Dong Jin caught on.
-  Caught onto what?
Mr Park. Did you look into what I asked?
Yes. Just as you said,
Hong Gi Pyo was the one responsible for selling under fake labels.
Send me all the documents on the matter.
And check...
how the legal department is doing with the lawsuit.
Yes, Sir. I'll call you back.
If Hong Gi Pyo tells the truth,
things would be resolved smoothly.
Hey, lady.
You should respond when someone talks to you. Hey.
What the...
You're the guy from yesterday.
What? Are you here to buy more grapes?
No, that's not it.
Granny, where's your daughter-in-law who was working here yesterday?
Granny?
- Do I look that old to you?
-  Pardon?
I'm sorry.
Where's your daughter-in-law?
Why do you care?
Your son is Hong Gi Pyo, correct?
It's because I think I can help your son in jail.
- You'll help my son?
-  Yes.
So where is your daughter-in-law?
- Enjoy.
-  Thank you.
(Sweet Grapes for Sale)
I meant to go up yesterday, but it was too busy at the orchard.
Don't worry about us and take your time.
The shop is closed, so there's nothing to do anyway.
Mr Lee hasn't called, has he?
You'll be the first person I call if I hear from him.
Don't worry too much.
He'll come back after clearing his head.
The more time passes,
I feel more and more nervous.
Don't be so weak.
And don't skip your meals just because you don't have an appetite.
Okay.
Okay. I'll see you tonight.
(Sweet Grapes for Sale)
Hello!
A box of grapes sweeter than sugar is only 18 dollars!
Hello...
What now?
I need to check something, so come with me.
To where?
I checked the documents back at my office,
and Hong Gi Pyo, your husband, seems to be a victim, as well.
What do you mean?
I can't tell you anything yet.
Let's go see your husband first.
I need to ask him a few things first.
Why would I trust you enough to go with you?
I'm trying to help your husband.
- Still. I can't go now.
-  Why not?
My mother-in-law said not to budge until I sell everything here.
I can't move until I sell every box of grapes.
This is insane.
How many boxes are there?
20 boxes.
How much is that?
(18 dollars per box)
What?
It was 20 dollars yesterday. Why is it 18 dollars today?
- Did you scam me yesterday?
-  I don't know anything.
I just did as my mother-in-law said.
What a joke.
Load them.
- All 20 boxes?
-  Yes, all of them.
What will you do with them all?
That's my problem. Let's go to Hong Gi Pyo.
We don't take credit cards.
I know. Cash only. Here.
I have no time. Let's go.
Has your husband told you about Chief Director Min Hyo Sang...
I mean, CEO Min Hyo Sang?
Why do you ask?
Tell me anything you know about why he was arrested and...
why he's in jail.
You were so rude yesterday and accused me of being a criminal.
Are you interviewing me today?
I'm sorry about yesterday.
Everything was going wrong, and it was also hot and annoying.
I apologise. I'm sorry.
I wasn't any better, either.
Do you really not know anything?
It's because I think Hong Gi Pyo may have been framed.
If we can clear up the misunderstanding,
I may be able to help him get out of jail.
Did your husband ever tell you anything about being framed?
At first, he said he was framed,
but he denied it later.
Can you really help him get out of jail?
If you cooperate.
Gi Pyo.
Who's he?
He came to help you,
so answer everything he asks.
Why would he help me?
Who are you?
You sold Meesa Apparel's products under fake labels.
I know Min Hyo Sang is involved, so tell me the truth.
That's the only way I can help you.
What are you talking about?
Min Hyo Sang? Who's that?
What are you saying? You know Mr Min Hyo Sang well.
He's his brother-in-law.
Tell me the truth, so that we can claim extenuating circumstances...
I don't know what you're talking about.
I've never heard the name Min Hyo Sang before,
so stop bugging me and please leave.
I don't know what deal you made with my brother-in-law, but...
I said I don't know any Min Hyo Sang, so get lost!
Lower your voice, or this visitation is over.
Stop your gibberish and get lost.
You shouldn't trust my brother-in-law too much.
If you change your mind, tell your wife to contact me.
What's wrong with you?
He said he'd help you get out.
You fool. Can't you tell? He's a bad man.
He lied to you so that he could attack me and Mr Min.
Why? For what?
I'm not sure.
But don't talk to him if he comes back, okay?
Then is everything he said true?
Why did you do that?
I...
Stay out of it.
Wait one year, and I'll let you live comfortably.
Don't worry. You trust me, right?
And if he bugs you again, report him the police. Okay?
Maybe it's going to rain. My surgical spot is aching.
Does it hurt a lot?
It'll get better with some rest.
I need to go in and rest. Give my mum my regards.
I'm done here.
Get in.
I'll drive you to the orchard, so get in.
Have you no shame?
Who? Me?
How could you not apologise after lying to me?
What lie did I tell you?
At first, you acted like Min Hyo Sang, the CEO,
and now, you lied that you'd help Gi Pyo get out.
I never said I was Min Hyo Sang.
You're the one who mistook me.
As for your husband, he has to tell the truth for me to help.
What can I do when he lies and just gets upset?
Wait a second. Why are you speaking rudely again?
You can be rude too if you want.
Do you think I can't?
Anyway, don't show your face again!
I'll report you to the police.
What's his problem?
Hyo Sang definitely made him do it.
(Sam Do)
Hi, Sam Do.
I've been thinking about it for the past few days,
and I think Mr Lee left home because of the tailor shop.
The tailor shop?
He left home because he was hurt and heartbroken...
that there's no one to pass the shop down to.
That's what it said in his letter, too.
He said to close the shop while he's away.
- That's true.
-  Dong Jin.
- Can you really not do it?
-  Do what?
The tailor shop. Are you really not interested in running it?
Come on. How could I run the shop?
Why not? You've seen enough.
That was a long time ago. There's no way.
You really won't take over the shop?
No. I really won't.
Then I guess I'm the only one.
With whom are you whispering?
Fine. Bye.
Whom were you talking to?
I talked to the woman who touched my biceps. So what?
What?
I called Dong Jin to talk about Mr Lee. Happy?
You scared me.
I know I said it already, but you have serious paranoia.
You need to get treated.
Forget it. I'll just live with it.
Why do I have to put up with it when I did nothing wrong?
You did nothing wrong?
You stole my heart completely.
Bae Sam Do, you must serve a life sentence.
I'm speechless.
Look how cute.
I almost forgot about you. Why are you back?
Bae Sam Do, you destroyed my guitar. You...
must serve a life sentence.
What are you doing?
Are you okay?
Stop it.
I came to participate in the new drug study.
What is your name?
Kang Tae Yang.
Do you see the beds over there?
Go to the one with your name on it and wait.
Okay.
Do we get paid as soon as the study is over?
If everything goes well, it'll be deposited within a week.
Thank you.
(Kang Tae Yang)
(Clothing Inventory and Returns Report)
Hong Gi Pyo changed many of the labels...
for the old items with labels from the new releases.
The pure dollar amount makes it unlikely that he did it alone.
How is the lawsuit going?
As soon as Min Hyo Sang was inaugurated as CEO,
there were orders that his office would handle the lawsuit,
so the legal department was unable to proceed.
Hello, Mother.
I just got to Seoul. I'm on the local bus headed home now.
There are some grapes missing. It's your doing, isn't it?
I told you I was taking some to give to the tailor shop adults.
I told you to take the ones I put aside to make juice.
I didn't tell you to take the ones for sale.
You softy.
Do you know how much each box costs?
Then dock it from my pay for the past two days.
Are you giving your mother-in-law an attitude?
I'm only kidding.
The next stop is Wolgyesu Tailor Shop.
Mother, I'll talk to you again soon.
I have to get off the bus. Bye.
Sir, this is my stop.
(Wolgyesu Tailor Shop)
(Closed for a while)
We closed for just one day, and there's dust everywhere.
Mr Lee would've yelled at us all if he were here.
(Closed for a while)
- It's me, Mum.
-  Where are you?
I'm nearby. I'll be there in five minutes.
Dong Sook.
Put the soup pot on the stove. Dong Jin's almost here.
- Drive safely.
-  I will.
Is the store open?
Why would it be? Your dad's away.
We'll keep it shut for a while.
Okay. See you soon.
(Wolgyesu Tailor Shop)
Where are you, Mr Lee?
Don't let dust gather.
Come back soon.
Who are you?
Thief!
What? You're the thief.
(The Gentlemen of Wolgyesu Tailor Shop)
Say hello. This is Dong Jin, my brother.
The jerk. Scumbag.
Na Yun Shil works at the workshop.
Why did you hire such a troublemaker?
Let's not meet each other even by chance.
I wouldn't even dream of it.
Call a real estate agency. I'll sell the store.
You made the right call.
Who would come to an old store like this?
The store's up for sale?
I gave it my all, but I can't do it any longer.
Are you sick? Should I call for help?
Get out here, Sam Do! Where are you, Bae Sam Do?