(The following content may not be suitable...)
(for viewers under 15.)
(Episode 30)
This is it.
Don't hit me.
You hit me first.
Stop it.
What are you doing?
What a cheek!
Isn't it not enough for you to date outside?
How dare you bring a man into your house?
My son is having such a hard time now.
And you're flirting with a man.
How dare you!
Please calm down.
Let go of me.
If you want to say something, just say it.
Let go of me, you jerk.
You seemed suspicious when you visited my vineyard.
You two were having an affair since then, right?
This jerk seduced you, didn't he?
Did you just call me jerk? Please watch your mouth.
My precious son got into such a trouble because of you.
You deserve to be called a jerk.
I'm so angry that I want to bury you alive.
Please stop, Mother.
How dare you stab me and Gi Pyo in the back...
with such an innocent face?
Blast it!
I don't understand...
why you're treating Yun Shil this way.
My daughter-in-law is having an affair with another man.
Shouldn't I say something to her?
You should go to the jail.
For the record, Yun Shil is not your daughter-in-law.
You're deluding yourself.
Why isn't she my daughter-in-law?
She had a wedding ceremony with my son.
That wedding ceremony was not completed.
Also, they are legally not married.
Stop being unreasonable.
Are you trying to teach me right now?
You're having an affair with my daughter-in-law.
How dare you try to teach me?
Please stop, Mother.
Let's go inside and talk with me.
You stay right there.
You wait and see, you junk.
That jerk.
Please go home before you face a rough ride.
How can I leave you here and go home?
I'll be fine. Although she talks like that,
she's not really a bad person.
I'll wait here, then.
I wouldn't be comfortable with that. Please go home.
Then call me if something happens. I'll be here right away.
All right. I'll call you later.
The world is come to an end.
How can you do this?
Your husband is having a hard time in a cold prison cell.
How can you, as his wife,
have an affair with another man?
Don't you feel pity for your husband?
I was going to marry him...
not because I loved him.
- What? - Half of the reason was fear...
and the rest was to repay the debt.
And things brought me to this far.
I'm sorry to say this, but as you heard a while ago...
I didn't complete the wedding with your son,
and neither did I register the marriage.
Please let me go now.
Stop that nonsense!
Mother, you're a woman, too. As a woman...
please understand how I feel.
Now I want to...
set everything in order.
Is Gi Pyo a baggage or a garbage to you?
What do you want to clear up?
Don't you remember what Gi Pyo has done to you and your dad?
Are you going to discard him because you've got what you want?
If hitting me can make your anger go away,
hit me as much as you want to.
You're so shameless.
Are you the same Yun Shil that I know?
Ms Choi brought me fish stew and it tastes amazing.
Have a seat.
Ta-da!
Why don't you eat? Here.
Is something wrong?
Why is life so hard, honey?
Why? What happened?
The oil store lady fled.
What did you say?
You mean the store at the market?
What do you mean she fled?
- She ran away with my money. - What?
Remember the money we lost because you stood surety for your friend?
I was waiting to get my money to pay for it.
Why is everything so messed up?
That's why you looked so out of it.
They say that you shouldn't trust anyone.
How can she do this to me?
I heard almost everyone at the market...
got his or her money stolen by her.
The entire market has been turned upside down.
Gosh, they say you can never know what people are really thinking.
How can she do that to us?
What should we do, Honey?
All we have is the rent deposit now.
I mean, we're not young any more.
We don't even own a house.
What if we grow old like this?
Let's be positive.
It could have been worse.
If we were still selling fried chicken at the market,
she could have taken so much more than just that money.
You're right.
I really want to save money, but things keep happening.
Things just keep on happening.
When will we be able to save up enough money...
to buy a house and a car?
When will we be able to live like other people?
We have to remember that both you and I have...
never done any harm and have managed to be self-sufficient.
We have no kids,
but the two of us have been happy enough.
Also, I promise you that I'll focus and work very hard from now on.
You sound mature for a change.
And let's be honest.
You at least have a handsome husband.
On that note,
shall we do homework after dinner?
Deal.
You naughty woman.
All right, let's eat.
Come on.
Let's power up for homework.
But...
can we do homework first?
I should have gotten numerous texts from her by now.
It's weird that she's been quiet all day.
Did she get sick from eating too many burgers?
- Or... - Tae Yang, I'll be back tomorrow!
Did her mum scold her harshly?
I'm worried about you...
because I saw you leaving like that earlier.
Your mum didn't hit you, did she?
Look at this kid.
(Kang Tae Yang. Your mum didn't hit you, did she?)
My mum...
would never be violent with anyone.
She's a wonderful person with a kind heart.
I'm relieved.
Be honest with me.
What do you think of my mum?
This may sound discourteous,
but I think she's very cute.
Don't you think she looks scary and mean?
She can be a little intimidating,
but I think she's very cute and lovely.
You're buttering her up to win her over, aren't you?
I'm not good at flattery.
You know what? I think you'd be so lovely...
if you age like your mum.
Gosh, I didn't know I was that lovely.
You sound fine, so I'll get back to studying.
Study hard.
All the best!
My goodness.
What am I doing right now?
(Study hard. All the best!)
Mum, why are you texting in the middle of dinner?
- Who is it? - What?
Well...
My friend who's been living abroad for a long time is in Korea now.
I got a little chatty because I'm so happy that she's back.
Mother, all the side dishes are so delicious.
You must be an amazing cook.
You saw my housekeeper making everything.
Don't butter me up like that.
Gosh, that's not what she means.
She's just being polite.
I guess Hyo Won is staying out late today.
It would have been good if she could eat with us.
She's not out.
She's locked up in her room.
She's locked up?
Are you saying she's confined?
Although I'm very brave,
I don't think I can jump from here.
I miss Tae Yang.
Mum took my phone. I don't have my laptop, either.
I have no way of getting in touch with him.
My goodness.
Darn it.
To be honest with you,
I didn't like you from the first time.
You're too tall...
and skinny.
You look miserable and unhappy.
I couldn't stand you.
But what can I do? Gi Pyo likes you.
He kept saying that he has to marry you.
No parents can win against their children, so I had to allow him.
How dare you...
cheat on my son?
Please don't talk like that.
I didn't cheat on him.
Gi Pyo and I aren't actually married.
Shut it!
You cheated on your husband.
How can you have the audacity to talk back to me?
Goodness.
Listen to me carefully.
I gave birth to Gi Pyo myself,
but I sometimes wonder if he's really my son...
because he can be very spiteful.
What are you going to do now?
When he's out of jail,
who knows what he'll do to you for cheating on him?
That's enough. Please stop.
Listen. My son will kill you.
You're so dead now.
Gosh, I'm getting drunk.
- Hello? - It's me.
I thought I should call you so that you won't worry.
Thanks. How is she?
She drank...
and just fell asleep.
- Was everything okay? - Of course.
I'm still worried, though.
- I'll come over now. - No, it's okay.
It's getting late. I'll see you tomorrow.
I'm fine,
- so you don't need to worry. - I have to see you...
to stop worrying.
I think she went to see Gi Pyo...
and heard about it from him.
She's angry,
but I can understand her.
All of this must be hard for you.
It is,
but it's better than my expectation.
It's probably...
because you're by my side.
Thanks for saying that.
And thanks a lot for mustering up your courage.
I should be the one thanking you.
Knowing how complicated...
and tough the process would be,
you still decided to love me.
Thank you so much.
You had a long day.
You should go to bed early.
Sweet dreams.
What's this?
I want you to smile.
When you worry too much,
that makes me feel sorrier.
You don't have to be sorry.
We're walking together, heading toward the same direction.
Did Sung Jun really say that to Mr Park?
He did.
"If you truly love someone,"
"you must accept the person as they are."
"Trashy landlords like you have no right..."
"to love someone like Dong Sook, okay?"
My goodness.
That touches my heart.
I was touched myself, too.
I guess Sung Jun really loves you, Mum.
What's wrong, Mum?
Go to bed, Da Jeong. I'll be right back.
What are you doing here in this cold weather, Dong Sook?
I was waiting for you.
What's the matter?
Why don't you propose to me?
- What? - You love me, don't you?
I...
love you.
Then why don't you confess your love...
and propose to me?
It's because...
I have nothing.
Think about it.
If we are to get married and live with Da Jeong,
we need to rent a two-bedroom house.
We can live in my house.
Da Jeong will have her room as she has now.
I can be with you in your room.
I don't have a regular income. What about our living expenses?
I can make a living.
We won't live in luxury,
but we won't go without food.
I appreciate that, Dong Sook. But...
even though I can't rent a splendid place...
to nicely propose as others do,
I should at least give you a decent ring.
You do have many rings on your fingers.
Just take one off and give it to me.
Please put this ring on my finger yourself.
Dong Sook.
Now...
kiss me.
Kiss you?
Shall I kiss you first?
No.
No, you should not.
Thank you.
It was such a romantic and nice propose.
What's wrong?
Do you regret proposing me?
It's not like that.
It's because I'm moved.
Why do you...
love a man like me?
I don't deserve you.
I'm so thankful and happy that...
I want to cry, Dong Sook.
Thank you for taking the initiative.
I appreciate that you did as I asked you to.
Please have some fruit, Mother.
All right.
A stranger would think that you're my daughter-in-law.
Don't you think you're overdoing it?
I'm trying hard to win your favour.
Don't you like it?
It's not that I don't like it, but I feel awkward.
It's just your second visit to my house,
and you're acting like you've been living here for 20 years.
It's actually somewhat creepy.
I'll be careful next time, Mother.
How can you say "Mother" so unreservedly?
it's nice to see...
two beauties here together.
Thank you for the fruit.
I think Mother doesn't like me.
She doesn't easily become acquainted with people.
But once she gets intimate,
she's nice and kind.
By the way, why is Hyo Won locked up in her room?
Well... Wait a minute.
I need to talk on the phone and check some documents. Wait here.
Hello?
Yes.
Open the door. Open the door!
Wait a minute.
- Who is it there? - It's Choi Ji Yun.
Choi Ji Yun? A pooper?
What is pooper doing here?
I have the key with me.
Shall I just go back?
Wait a second.
Please open the door.
I'm asking you.
All right.
How did you come here?
I visited for dinner,
and I came up here after hearing that you're locked up.
I was worried about you, too.
What happened?
I'm dating someone recently,
but Mum and my brother don't like him.
Why?
Because he's poor and he isn't from a good family.
Is that why you're locked up...
so that you can't meet him?
That's right.
I can't believe it.
I know. I can't believe either.
I'm embarrassed to say this...
but Mum is so egoistic. She's a dictator.
If you marry my brother, Mum will be hard on you.
Would you agree if I marry your brother?
I was always worried that you don't like me.
As I'm in debt to you today, I won't disagree.
Thank you.
Make sure to keep it a secret that I opened the door today.
Sure. Don't worry about it.
Are you going out to meet him?
Mother will get furious if she knows.
I'll just see him and come back right away.
You are nice today.
Let's get along well from now on.
Just see him and come back soon, all right?
Don't tell anyone that I opened the door.
Don't worry.
Things are getting better than I expected.
One obstacle removed.
I should go home now.
Really? I'll take you home.
Mum! Ji Yun is leaving.
Okay. I can't leave my room now as I took the shower just now.
- Get home safely. - Thank you, Mother.
I'm come by again soon.
No one welcomes you here.
I think he sort of looks...
like the English teacher whom I had a crush on in school.
In terms of looks, he is exactly my type.
Who is it?
Darling!
What brings you here?
I came to see you because I missed you so much.
Now that I'm hearing your voice,
I finally feel like I can breathe.
Didn't you have dinner yet?
- I didn't even have lunch. - Why?
It's a long story.
Get me...
something to eat first,
my darling.
You look like you have been starving all day.
Eat slowly.
I haven't had any food since eating the burgers in the morning.
Why? Did something happen?
Actually, my mum...
No one is home.
Is everyone away or something?
My mum is abroad on a trip,
and my brother is away for work.
Our housekeeper is visiting her family in the countryside.
I see.
So I am...
going to sleep at hostel today.
- At hostel? - I told you.
I already paid for three months up front.
Still, you have a home...
It's way too scary to be alone at home.
What if a burglar breaks in?
It's safe there.
Well, that is true.
I'm so glad that I have rented a room there as my second home.
It was such a clever thing to do.
I have such wise foresight.
Wait, hold on.
Guys are not allowed in here.
Don't be so square.
The manager will turn a blind eye because we're best friends now.
When did you two become best friends?
We've gotten close since the orange juice incident.
What do you think of my room?
Isn't it so cute?
I've lived here for a long time,
but I've never seen a decorated room like this.
It suits you.
Thanks for the compliment.
Have a good night, then.
Wait.
I've never slept away from home before.
I don't think I'll be able to fall asleep.
So?
Put me...
to sleep before you go.
Where are you going? I'm not done talking.
I don't want to fall for your tricks again.
It's simple, so you don't need to worry.
It's simple?
Sing a lullaby for me.
Forget it.
I really don't think I can fall asleep alone.
I've never slept away from home before,
so I'm a little nervous.
I won't be able to sleep if I miss the time I usually fall asleep.
I'll end up staying up all night.
If I can't fall asleep, I might go to your room...
and bug you all night long.
Pardon me?
So please...
sing a lullaby for me, okay?
Then I'll be able to sleep very well.
Goodness, that's such a weird favour to ask.
Please?
I'll sing it just once, okay?
I'm so sleepy right now.
I'll probably fall asleep before you even finish singing.
Close your eyes.
Sweet dreams, my baby
In the garden and on the hills
The birds and lambkins
Are all asleep, too
The moon is guarding you
It's sending silver and golden bells
Your way tonight
Sweet dreams, my baby
Are you asleep, Hyo Won?
What did I just do?
Good night.
You might think of me as a dead person because I'm in here,
but I have nothing else to lose.
That means I have nothing to fear...
and nothing to hold me back. Do you understand?
You should be in bed. Why are you drinking at this late hour?
Nothing. I couldn't fall asleep.
- So I wanted to have a glass. - Why can't you sleep?
- Is something bothering you? - No.
I guess I'm not sleepy now.
You should meet a nice girl soon.
I want you to have cute children and live happily with your family.
I'm sorry, Mum. I feel like I let you down.
What are you talking about?
I'm so proud of you, and I rely on you a lot.
You didn't let me down at all.
- Mum. - What is it?
Do you have something to tell me?
No. I just want to wish you a good night.
What was that about?
We should find a nice girl for him as soon as possible.
What are you talking about?
I'm talking about Dong Jin.
He's drinking alone in the kitchen.
- Dong Jin is drinking alone? - Yes.
He's trying not to show it because he doesn't want to worry us,
but he must be so lonely to be single at that age.
When will I be able to stop worrying about my children?
I must say,
it's much better than making our children...
worry about us.
Parents who are able to worry about their children are lucky.
You're right.
But still...
It'll be hard to find a woman as wonderful as his ex-wife.
It's all over. There's no point in talking about it now.
It's pointless.
It just came out because I'm upset.
What are you doing, taking a photo of this?
I just found the happiness. I can't give it up.
I will focus on myself.
It's okay to do that now.
Why did you gather us so early in the morning?
Say what you need to.
I was cooking breakfast.
What is it, Dong Sook?
I want to get married.
- Get married? - Get married?
- With whom? - With whom?
Are you saying you want to marry him?
Yes, Mum. I want your permission.
Don't accept the bow.
I know I have many shortcomings...
and that you don't approve of me.
That's why I considered moving away for Dong Sook's sake,
but I decided love can overcome it all.
Allow me to marry Dong Sook, Father, Mother.
Please. Sung Jun and I are meant to be.
You are not. Don't say such nonsense.
I'll never ever allow you as her husband.
Mum.
Of all the men in the world...
you chose one who can't even support himself.
You got divorced twice. Are you aiming for a third time?
Please calm down.
I have nothing more to hear.
Da Jeong, help me up, will you?
- Sure, Grandma. - My legs went weak.
- Get up slowly. - My goodness.
Dad, you might not know,
but Sung Jun won Best the Newcomer at a year-end award ceremony.
At the 2000 KBC Gayo Festival.
I know that.
You do?
I'm not as close-minded as you may think.
Do you mean you give your approval, Mr Lee?
There's no reason to refuse them if they love each other.
- Dad. - However...
I can't let you get married...
just because I approve when my wife doesn't.
You two need to work together...
and convince her.
Thank you, Dad.
Thank you, Sir. I mean Father.
Is that a new ring?
Yes.
Sung Jun put it on my finger last night when he proposed.
It's one of his.
The proposal was a bit hurried.
I did with one of my rings.
How could you be so inconsiderate?
How dare you propose to my sister without even getting her a ring?
Dong Sook, are you happy being treated like that?
I told him to give me one of his rings.
Why should we waste our hard-earned money?
We don't have much.
I'll earn a fortune and within two years...
I'll buy her a ring with a diamond the size of a teardrop.
You're all talk.
Dear brother-in-law.
I'm not your brother-in-law, okay?
Ddong Jin.
I believe you're in no position to threaten me.
I'm actually thinking of...
barging into that room to tell your mum everything.
- Like what? - Like what?
Now that I thought about it, proposing with your own ring...
could actually be quite meaningful.
Right? I'm glad you get it.
I have to go and get ready for work.
Dong Jin gave in easier than I expected.
I know. I expected him to throw a tantrum.
Men have a way of communicating.
Now we just have to persuade your mum.
Congratulations, Leather Jacket.
Everything's going smoothly since I'm wearing a suit you made.
I feel good about this.
Are you happy? Your wish came true.
That's what.
It's her third time.
- Sorry. - My bad.
Why are you waiting out here in the cold?
You should have texted me.
I just got here. How about her?
She drank a lot last night and is still asleep.
I made some soup and set the table for her.
Did you have a hard time?
I'm not alone any more.
It was hard, but bearable.
Based on her reaction last night, I don't think she'll just go back.
She might do something unexpected, so let's brace ourselves.
Okay.
I today will be long and tough.
Let's take a long roundabout route so we can...
walk in the morning sun and recharge ourselves.
Give me your hand.
By the way, how is your cold?
It's fine.
Good. I was worried.
I'm fine, but I was worried...
you'd end up getting sick because of me.
I told you that I have a hardy immune system.
That sounds like you want me to kiss you again.
Shall we? To kill time?
Stop it. You're being gross.
You managed fine last night. Come here.
Stop teasing me or I'll never kiss you again.
What? I can't let that happen. Fine, no kissing.
My hand is getting sweaty. Wait.
What if someone saw that?
Who cares? We aren't strangers.
We're a couple in love.
Why do you hesitate when you always do in the end?
Don't say that.
Your kiss chased all the blues away.
Were you very upset last night?
Because of what Gi Pyo's mum said?
It would be a lie to say I wasn't,
but don't worry about it. We expected something like this.
I wondered if it's right for me...
to keep you close...
at the expense of you being insulted.
But I decided to focus on myself from now on.
I'd feel terribly down if we break up...
and I'm happy when we're together.
So I won't think about anything else.
That's the best thing I've heard from you.
Putting yourself first is the best thing...
you can do for me.
Do you get what I mean?
You became so brave in just one night.
My lips have amazing powers.
What? Why do you always end up talking about lips?
Lips? Shall we kiss while we're on the topic?
Stop being silly. Let's go.
Out of all these lottery tickets...
only three were the winners worth five dollars each.
I was never one to be lucky.
What was the pig dream about, then?
My neck is so stiff.
Gosh, I need a massage.
What did Ms Choi say?
I kneeled down for three straight hours...
and she didn't even flinch.
My legs hurt.
My goodness.
What are you doing?
Dong Sook, you have therapeutic hands.
Your touch made the numbness go away.
- Are you serious? - Yes.
Dong Sook, you are the pharmacy of my life.
How did you keep your feelings for so long?
I'll leave you two alone.
I'll go to work.
Bye, Seon Nyeo.
Can you clean up for me?
- You got nothing? - Nothing.
Dong Sook.
What if your mother never approves?
She'll change her mind after a few days.
She was against my first...
and second marriage at first,
but in the end she went, "I don't care any more. Suit yourselves."
That's what she said.
Gosh, I shouldn't have said that.
After all, this is your first time.
It's fine.
I'm very experienced in this.
Leave everything to me.
I'll take care of it.
Okay.
(Oh Young Eun Bakery)
Oh Young Eun Bakery?
Is that a new bakery?
Why does it have to be, "Young Eun"?
My mum's name is Oh Young Eun.
I see.
Your mum's name is Oh Young Eun?
- How old are you? - I'm five.
I see.
My mum's baking is amazing.
- Pay us a visit, okay? - Okay.
What a bright little boy.
I wish I had a son like that.
A year-end get-together?
Time does fly.
I've lost track of time with so many things going on.
I am busy,
but I'll try to make time.
After all, we're alumni of the same orphanage.
Young Eun is coming, too.
Who? Young Eun?
- Oh Young Eun? - Yes.
She's been living in Seattle until she came back a few months ago.
Are you serious?
Young Eun is in Korea?
Honey, I'm home.
Right. Okay.
I'll be there no matter what.
I'll see you then. Okay.
- What was that about? - What?
There's a year-end get-together for my orphanage.
I see.
By the way, where is everyone?
They went to have lunch,
but my stomach wasn't feeling very well.
- What are you doing here? - What do you mean?
Shouldn't you be working at the fried-chicken place?
Oh, dear me.
I was lost in my thoughts and ended up coming here.
Get it together, woman.
I will.
I'm not myself any more after losing that money.
Yun Shil?
Where are you, Yun Shil?
What brings you here, Ma'am?
- Who's that? - What?
That's the person who almost became Yun Shil's mother-in-law.
I see.
Why would I be here except to see Yun Shil?
- Where is she, by the way? - She's on lunch break.
There they are.
You little scoundrel.
How dare you seduce...
my daughter-in-law?
Let go of me.
I won't.
You brought pain to my son.
I won't let you go until you get what you deserve.
You promised you wouldn't be like this. Please stop.
Let go of him.
Are you...
taking his side in front of your mother-in-law?
- Let go. - Gosh.
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
I'll call the police if you keep this up.
Police, my foot.
Okay. Call them.
I'll make sure they take you away for stealing my son's wife.
- Call the police. - Ma'am.
You shouldn't be doing this at our tailor shop.
Let's talk about it outside.
I didn't know this was a tailor shop.
I thought this was a dating spot for all I know.
You call yourself a CEO when you...
have an affair with someone else's wife?
You're a thief.
Calm down, Ma'am.
I think there's been a misunderstanding.
What are you talking about?
You think Mr Lee is in love with Yun Shil?
That's not the case. Not a chance in the world.
It's true.
It is?
Dong Jin and Yun Shil are...
- Oh, my. - I'll make this short.
Follow me to the Community Service Centre.
Let's go register the marriage.
If you do that, I'll forget about all this.
Please stop this.
Haven't you done enough?
So please stop.
Are you crazy?
How dare you talk to your mother-in-law like that?
Why am I your daughter-in-law?
- What? - I told you.
I'm not related to Gi Pyo in any way.
The fear and despair almost made me marry him,
but the wedding ceremony didn't even get completed.
- Speaking legally, - Shut your mouth.
Don't you remember what Gi Pyo did to you and your father?
He even cut himself open for you.
And this is how you repay him?
I didn't ask him for that.
That had nothing to do with my will.
That was his decision and did alone.
So...
are you saying...
you have no use for him...
now that you have his kidney?
You darn witch.
What do you think you're doing?
Yun Shil.
Where are you running off to?
She has to go register the marriage at the Community Service Centre.
Where is she going?
What are you doing?
All of Yun Shil's points are valid.
Why do you keep on persisting?
That's what I mean.
I hate people like you...
who think raising their voice will give them what they want.
You're one to talk.
She's not even your legal daughter-in-law.
Haven't you bothered her enough?
Go back to where you came from...
if you've had enough fun.
Stop making them suffer.
That's right.
Your son and Yun Shil were never meant to be.
Do you get that?
Are you ganging up on me?
- Do you want to fight? - Is that a challenge?
Stop it.
Wait, Hold on.
Gosh.
- Honey. - Don't stop me.
- Gosh. - Relax your fists, Honey.
- Ms Geum. - Bring it on.
Stop it, everyone.
Are you okay?
(Wolgyesu Tailor Shop)
I can't stand this situation...
where I have to be this blunt.
I'm a horrible person, aren't I?
It's just that...
you've been holding on to those emotions until now.
It's not your fault.
But still...
There are certain people who try to take advantage of you...
if you be nice to them.
I've been through it, too.
If that's the case,
you have to be strong. You did good.
I know it was hard on you saying those things.
Let's get some fresh air.
(Wolgyesu Tailor Shop)
Did you sleep okay? How are you feeling?
Much better.
Your shoulder must be hurting.
I couldn't move by the slightest for half an hour.
My shoulder's cramped.
Really?
Don't do that. It's just a cramp.
You can just heal me with your cute gesture.
What? My goodness.
Your jokes are lame.
I never fail to impress you.
No way.
My shoulder really hurts.
Please do some cute gestures for me.
- Just once. - I can't.
Please. Just once.
Good morning, Tae Yang.
You can't keep coming here. We could both be evicted.
I told you I'm best friends with the managers here.
You don't have to worry about that.
My goodness.
I think this place is the perfect place for me.
I slept so well last night.
When I woke up it was morning.
At home, I wake up at least twice during the night.
I guess that's a relief.
When does your mum come back from her trip?
Her trip?
Well, she'll be back in about 10 days.
That's quite a long trip.
Will you be here for that long?
Of course.
Hi, Tae Joon, what is it?
What? Mum?
Okay, I'll leave shortly. Don't worry and go to class.
Okay.
Did something happen to your mum?
She hurt her knee and had surgery a while ago.
She lost her footing and fell down.
- Where are you going? - To see your mum.
Wait. You, too?
I'll get my car keys. See you in the parking lot.
I don't think she should visit my home.
Why are you still in bed?
It's time for breakfast.
Promise me that you'll forget all about Tae Yang...
and start going back to work.
Then I'll get rid of the padlock. Okay?
You little brat.
Goodness me. What's this?
Where on earth...
Hang on.
Ma'am.
Ma'am!
Yes, Madam Ko?
Did you unlock Hyo Eun's door?
No.
Why would I do that knowing what you'd do to me?
Then how did she get out?
Hang on.
This is mine.
Where did I put her phone?
(Hyo Won)
What is she doing with someone else's phone?
- What? - Why are you answering his phone?
Tae Yang went to get coffee. What do you want?
What? Then were you two...
together all night?
Of course.
Have you lost your mind?
What on earth are you up to?
Come home right now.
What for? To get locked up again?
If you were me, would you come home?
I won't lock you up. Come home right away.
I can't come back today. I'm off to meet Tae Yang's mum.
Why are you meeting his mum?
She scared me.
You met Tae Yang.
So I have to meet his mum, too.
I have to go.
Oh my goodness.
(Block calls and messages)
Thank you.
I'm never truly awake until I have my morning coffee.
I can go by bus. Why don't you...
Let's get going. Don't make your mum wait.
She might get the wrong idea when she sees you.
I'll say I'm your friend from college. Will that work?
Don't say anything silly.
I won't, okay?
Let's go.
Darling, let's go.
My son told me to see Mr Min Hyo Sang.
You can't if you don't have an appointment.
Then tell him I'm Hong Gi Pyo's mum.
The mum of the man who's doing time...
instead of him wants to see him.
What does that mean?
- I don't know. She's weird. - Let go of me.
- Don't do this. - You can't go in.
Why not? Let go of me, will you?
- Why are you so stubborn? - Come with us.
Let go. I said let me go.
What's going on?
Why is it so noisy?
Nothing much, Ms Min.
She insists on seeing Mr Min without an appointment.
I'm Hyo Sang's older sister.
You seem to have something to say. Will you talk to me?
Are you Mr Min's older sister?
You wanted to see my brother.
If you talk to me, I'll relay the message.
My son told me to speak to Mr Min in person.
You're his older sister and family, so I'll tell you instead.
My son told me to ask Mr Min...
to get him paroled as soon as possible.
Get him paroled?
This is too embarrassing to say,
but while my son is doing time in prison...
my daughter-in-law had an affair.
There's a place called Wolgyesu Tailor Shop.
My daughter-in-law works there.
She's dating her boss.
My son's half-dead with despair.
Did you just say Wolgyesu Tailor Shop?
Yes.
Wolgyesu Tailor Shop.
The one in Hyoja-dong?
Yes, in Hyoja-dong.
Your mum asked me to...
find this woman a job.
Her name is Na Yun Shil.
- What? - She talented and has...
a very important role.
I wouldn't swap her with anyone from Meesa Apparel.
This is unbelievable.
(Wolgyesu Tailor Shop)
(The Gentlemen of Wolgyesu Tailor Shop)
Are you really going to be like this?
Do you not have moral standards?
I had no idea the two were in such a relationship.
When did it begin?
- What if she gets pregnant? - Stop!
Shouldn't we call the police?
Marriage isn't a child's play.
It will take time. Have some patience.
What do you mean, "future daughter-in-law"?
Am I just a casual boyfriend to you then?
What are you doing at my house?
I can really make it work this time.
Let's start all over again.