BK
(Episode 32)
BioskopKeren
I think I can...
forget about the past...
and start with you.
And...
I think I can love again.
Thank you.
Thank you, Tae Yang. Thank you so much.
I tried hard to win your heart...
but you didn't seem to budge.
I pretended I wasn't, but I was really worried.
Thanks for telling me what's on your mind.
No, thank you.
Thank you, Hyo Won.
Compared to you,
I don't have a lot to offer.
As you have seen, I'm not from a rich family, either.
In some way,
it'll be a bad bargain for you.
Love isn't a business.
Who cares about loss or gain in love?
I've always been horrible at math.
So I hate doing calculations.
I never used to study math even as a student, and I'm older now.
I shouldn't have to do math just because I'm dating you, should I?
Things are so simple with you.
Isn't that why you fell for me?
That's right.
- How much longer do we have to go? - We're almost there, Ma'am.
- Yes, Hyo Sang. - Where are you, Mum?
I was reading, and I just realised that you aren't home.
I'm...
going to Kang Tae Yang's house.
What? The gosiwon?
No, I'm going to his parents' place.
Why are you going there?
When I spoke to Hyo Won on the phone earlier,
she said that she was going there to meet his mum.
I had forgotten about it.
So you're actually going there at this late hour?
Hold on a second. How did you even find the address?
My quick wits got me to where I am now.
Gathering that much intel isn't even a problem.
Anyway, I must say that Hyo Won is such a troublemaker.
Whom does she take after? She has such bad taste in men.
Look who's talking.
What did I do?
It's not like Ji Yun is any better.
What's wrong with Ji Yun?
She's sly, and she thinks about her interests and gains first.
I know exactly what kind of girl she is.
Why do you think so negatively of her?
Gosh, cut it out. Your sister is giving me enough headache.
Let's talk about her some other time.
- Let's hurry. - Yes, Ma'am.
Kang Tae Yang.
Min Hyo Won.
You two.
I'll teach you a serious lesson today.
If we start over...
I can do better this time.
I mean it.
I want to start over with you.
Start over with me?
Are you kidding?
I can't believe that he's seeing someone like her.
I'll be sure to make everything go back to the way it should be.
Hello.
Ms Choi will worry about you. Shouldn't you go home early?
I can certainly enjoy a glass of drink on a day like today.
Excuse me. We'd like a bottle of soju and...
What do you want to eat?
Chicken feet.
Do you eat chicken feet?
Of course. It's so delicious.
We'll get one serving of chicken feet and rolled omelette.
Sure.
Gosh, you can eat chicken feet. You're so tough.
I told you.
I'm going to be brave.
Today was another long and hard day.
Thanks for being patient and sticking it out.
I should thank you.
Gi Pyo's mum insulted you...
and made harsh remarks about you, but you didn't even get upset.
To be honest, I'm so grateful for everything you've done for me,
and it also made me realise how mature and thoughtful you are.
I got so worked up when I saw that person earlier...
and whined at you.
You totally did. You still have a lot of growing up to do.
I do.
It's no fun if you just admit it like that.
It's true, though.
The situation isn't the greatest for both of us now,
so let's make sure to ask and check with each other,
and talk things through at all times.
At the very least, we shouldn't misunderstand each other.
Letting your imagination run wild and jumping to conclusions alone...
is such a foolish thing to do.
I'm hungry. Let's eat.
okay.
Wait.
Try this.
It's so chewy and tasty.
I'm not a picky eater, but I can't...
eat that. You go ahead.
Come on. Just give it a try.
No, thanks.
Gosh, just try it.
- Here. Try it. - Goodness.
Chew it well.
Goodness, you two are having so much fun.
You're feeding each other.
I was wondering who the sweet couple was.
It's you and Mr Lee.
What a lovely sight.
We're just having a drink. Please do not bother us.
Don't mind them. Let's eat.
We warned you, but it doesn't look like you got the message.
Should I talk some sense into you?
Yun Shil.
You're being too reckless for your own good.
Gi Pyo's mum is fuming mad right now.
How can you have a drink with the guy you're having an affair with...
at this late hour?
I clearly warned you guys not to bother us.
Gosh, I'm so scared.
You warned us?
Your ways...
might have worked with Yun Shil, but not with me.
- Don't make me repeat myself. - What's this jerk saying?
It's all right. Don't be afraid.
Put your hands off her, you punk!
Who do you think you are?
Let him go.
Ms, please call the police!
These guys are using violence towards an innocent man.
Now that you've fallen for a man, you don't realise the situation.
I won't suffer as I used to before, okay?
You...
shouldn't come and threaten me again.
If you do, I'll send you to the jail.
She's totally out of her mind.
Gi Pyo told us to lie low for a while.
Let's call it a day.
Let's go.
Are you all right?
I'm fine.
It was embarrassing as people were watching us, right? I'm sorry.
That's what those guys want.
If you avoid them for embarrassment and worry about rumours,
they'll come for you again.
As I told you before,
if they are tough on you, we should be tough on them, too.
In fact,
as I see how you reacted,
I don't think I should worry about you.
I had nothing to be scared of when you were with me.
You are brave...
and daring in expressing your love.
I really like you.
How can you make a joke in this situation?
For some time,
they might visit you and bully you.
If you get upset and distressed each time,
you're fooled by their trick.
So we should face it like it's nothing.
I get it.
What happened to your button?
It must have come off.
Shall I take this shirt off?
No.
I can put on the button while you have your shirt on.
All done.
Thank you.
Thank you for enduring today,
and thank you for putting on the button.
What I can do for you...
are just those kinds of things.
Those are enough for me.
Don't even think that you're sorry for me.
I'm overly happy to
be together with you,
Yun Shil.
Tell me straight.
When did you start loving me?
I was not in a situation to love somebody.
I was not sure at first...
then I became falling for you.
Since you are so bright and innocent,
you washed away the wounds and darkness inside me.
After then...
I realised that you are not just an innocent person,
but you overcame your own wounds.
That's how I got to trust you.
I'm happy to hear that.
I thought, when I'm with you...
I could smile and overcome...
any difficult situation.
What a big compliment it is!
Thank you.
You are the only one who can see the real me.
By the way, Hyo Won,
I haven't told you one thing.
What is it?
In fact,
I was concerned whether I should tell you this...
before I confess my love to you.
Is it a serious matter?
In a degree, yes.
Do you have to say that today?
If I say it later, it might be misleading.
I don't want to hear it.
Today is...
a happy day as you confessed your love to me.
I don't want to break the mood.
We can talk about a serious matter later.
Do you agree?
All right.
Min Hyo Won!
What a devious girl!
How did you know I'm here, Mum?
I've lived by my wits.
You're playing in the palm of my hand.
Didn't you say that Madam Ko is on a trip abroad?
Well,
Actually, I lied a little bit because...
I wanted to be with you.
You shouldn't have lied.
You sly girl.
Stay right there.
Today, it's the end for both of us.
- Gosh. - You devious girl.
Why are you doing this? You're scaring me.
You are someone who can be scared...
and you run away from home?
I ran away because you locked me in.
Were you locked in?
She locked me in my room on the second floor.
Did you really do that?
What could I do?
I couldn't break her legs or shave her head.
Locking her in her room was the only thing I could do.
Still that was too much.
How can you lock in your daughter?
Wait until I get my hands on you, sly girl!
Today,
you're dead!
Hey!
You devious girl.
My goodness.
You sky girl.
Watch your steps.
Mum!
Madam Ko!
Are you all right?
Are you laughing?
You fell down yourself. Why are you taking it out to me?
Be quiet. I don't care, you sly girl!
What's wrong?
I guess when I fell down...
I strained my back.
I do have a weak back.
I'll carry you on my back.
- I've never been on someone's back. - Excuse me.
It's not your first time.
After the year-end party last year,
you were so drunk that you came home on Mr Kim's back.
Shut up, you rascal.
I'm worried that I'm heavy.
I'm worried that you're too light.
It's natural that you fall down running with such high heels on.
Why do you keep wearing them when I advise you to wear low heels?
How can you nag me?
I wouldn't have come here at this hour if it were not you.
My goodness.
By the way...
what's this sound?
Splashing.
Is this the sound of the waves?
Haven't you been to the sea before?
It's the sound of the waves.
It's so romantic.
Maybe it's because I'm here at a night sea.
The sound of the waves seems to be louder.
I've never felt this before.
Shall we get closer to the sea?
Splashing.
The sound of the waves is so romantic.
Tae Yang must be tired. You should go back home now.
Are you tired?
No, I'm fine.
Then let's go near to the sea.
I want to hear them more closely.
What am I supposed to do?
I love the sound of the waves.
Mum, are you here to admire the ocean?
No, I'm here to drag you home.
Oh gosh, my back. Let's go.
Where were you until this late hour?
Where is she?
She was worried about upsetting you, so she left before dinner.
I do understand how you feel,
but she has changed a lot.
She's totally different from how she used to be.
She said that she divorced you out of anger...
but has been deeply regretting her decision.
She realised that you were the only one on her side...
and that she should have been more thoughtful.
It's all in the past. Let's not talk about it, Mum.
It'd be much better for him to go back to his ex-wife...
than finding someone new to be with.
I must have made you uneasy,
but I felt comfortable and warm as if I have...
finally come home after being away for a long time.
Both of your parents...
are such wonderful people. Why did I break their hearts?
Why couldn't I trust you and be there for you?
I regret everything and wish I did things differently.
Gosh, what a coincidence.
I mean, Seoul is a big city.
How can she move to this neighbourhood?
Young Eun...
looked exactly like before. Will she recognise me?
Gosh, I should pump up...
- Are you working out or what? - My gosh.
No. I haven't been able to work out recently,
so I was just checking to see if my muscles have shrunk.
Move over.
Stop checking your muscles...
and pay attention to your wife.
Ask me if anything is bothering me...
or whether I'm feeling well or not.
You're so healthy.
What are you talking about? I have many health issues.
That's why having a chilled and positive attitude is important.
You get so worked up over the littlest things...
and lose your temper. That's why your head...
Hold on.
- Honey. - What is it?
I asked you to dry clean this navy suit. Why is it here?
Is it? I forgot. I'll drop it off tomorrow.
Gosh, how can you forget to do that?
Well, you have many suits.
Just wear anything. Why are you being so picky?
Gosh, this suit...
It suits me the best. It fits me so well.
I was going to wear it tomorrow. Goodness.
Why? Are you going somewhere special tomorrow?
What? No, why do you ask?
Then why do you have to wear that navy suit?
Well... We might have some...
VIP customers coming to the shop tomorrow, so I wanted to wear it.
I'm tired.
Turn off the light. I'm going to sleep.
All right.
I'm exhausted.
I can't believe I met Young Eun again.
Am I dreaming?
Why are you here? It's cold outside.
I was waiting for you.
You made it through another day, Jun.
You also worked all day long...
and took care of your mum. Good job.
How's Ms Choi doing by the way?
She's all right.
She must really hate me.
Don't be discouraged. You have to just face it and be direct with her.
Okay. I won't get discouraged.
Dad and Mum, Jun is home from work.
I'm home, Ms Choi and Mr Lee!
What's wrong with him?
Why is he reporting to us that he's back from work?
Is he trying to act like our son-in-law or what?
Just leave him.
You must be tired. Go get some rest.
Thank you, Mr Lee.
Ms Choi. I hope you have a good night, too.
Why does he even care?
Stop giving them a hard time and just approve of him now.
If you think about it, he's more than what we can ask for.
He has never been married before,
whereas Dong Sook has been divorced twice.
She also has Da Jeong, too.
It's not easy for a bachelor to marry a divorcee.
I think he's broad-minded.
This soup is delicious.
Ta-da.
I'll debone this for you.
Is Da Jeong not back from work yet?
She called me from the bus stop earlier.
Where are you going in the middle of dinner?
I'm going to wait for her outside.
It's late now. What if something happens to her?
Her co-worker also lives in the area, so you don't need to worry.
Even so, it's dangerous to walk around this late.
- I'm home. - Hey, Da Jeong.
There you are.
- Mum. - Hi.
You're home safe and sound.
What?
Jun has been worried about you...
because it can be dangerous at night.
Thank you.
Welcome home. Have you had dinner yet?
We had so many customers today.
I just ate some bread and milk.
That's not enough. You have to eat a proper meal.
I'll bring rice and soup for you. You should eat a little bit.
Gosh, the fish is well grilled.
I'm really okay.
Jun can be so sweet.
Here it comes.
- All right. - Eat up.
- Thank you. - No problem.
- Here. Eat this. - Okay.
- Jun. You, too. - This is so good.
The fish tastes perfect.
Tae Yang.
You kidnapped Hyo Won on purpose, didn't you?
I didn't kidnap her.
That's not true at all.
Then why did you ignore my calls?
I called you so many times.
You called me?
I didn't get any calls from you.
I marked every phone number you can call from...
as spam.
Sorry?
Aren't I so meticulous?
Gosh, that brat.
Why on earth did you guys come here?
Tae Yang's mum hurt her leg, so he had to visit her.
Are you...
Are you her daughter-in-law?
What does his mum's injury have to do with you?
I'm sorry.
I couldn't keep the promise I made to you.
I told you not to worry because I'm not interested in Hyo Won,
but I have fallen for her.
Gosh, I'm in pain.
- What did you just say? - A little while ago,
Tae Yang told me that he has feelings for me, too.
You jerk.
You told me not to worry saying that you're not interested.
How can you stab me in the back like this?
You jerk. You must have planned all of this from the get-go.
Stop talking to him disrespectfully.
Mother will hear you.
Why are you swearing?
- Mother? - Tae Yang's mum.
I can't believe you two.
Leave us alone for a moment.
I want to have a word with Hyo Won.
You're not...
going to hit her, right?
Who do you think I am?
I'm not a violent person.
Call me if something happens.
I'll be waiting outside.
Be honest with me.
How far did you go with him?
How far...
did you go with Kang Tae Yang?
We went all the way.
You went all the way?
How can you be so shameless?
How can you say that in front of your mother?
You were the one who asked me.
You're so shameless.
So allow us to see each other.
Now,
- there's no going back. - My goodness.
Oh, my gosh.
Do you have...
any idea...
how I raised you?
Do you know how cautious I was?
How can you fall in love...
with someone from lowly background? You darn wench.
My goodness.
Gosh.
Quiet down. She'll hear you.
I can't live like this.
- My goodness. - What's going on in there?
It's nothing. Don't worry about it, Mother.
I can hear her crying.
My mom is just a very emotional person.
Don't mind her at all.
Hey, Ji Yun.
- I'm calling with worries. - About what?
About Hyo Won.
Did she return home?
Not yet.
- Oh, gosh. - Why did you have to...
go out of your way and worsen the situation?
I was just trying to looking out for Hyo Won.
That man Hyo Won is seeing...
Is he that bad?
The two seemed to be mad in love.
Can you persuade your mother?
I'm a bit tired right now.
Let's talk later.
Okay. Goodnight.
If she finds out that that man is Kang Tae Yang,
she'll definitely pass out.
Yes, Mr Hwang.
Can you make some time for me tomorrow?
I want you to go somewhere with me.
Mr Hwang, the lawyer?
Welcome home, Honey.
Hello.
The way she called him "honey" sounded so natural.
Aren't they strangers now after the divorce?
Shouldn't she be disallowed to call him, "honey"?
"Honey", my foot.
(Mr Pretty Eyes)
Hey, Honey.
I must be out of my mind.
Did you just...
call me, "honey"?
No. I can explain.
I was thinking about something and...
You must have really wanted to call me, "honey".
Should we just get married...
after my sister's wedding?
That's not what I meant.
My mind was somewhere else just now.
Were you thinking about us getting married?
Gosh. It was a mistake.
Can you just forget about it?
I can't just forget about something I heard with my own ears.
Honey.
You're grossing me out.
Look at you being all shy.
I know you want me to call you that.
It's not like that.
I read on the Internet that...
many dating couples call each other that these days.
From now on,
you've been promoted from Ms Shiny Eyes to Honey.
Forget it.
Let's hang up if you're going to keep talking nonsense.
Fine. Goodnight, then.
- Honey. - Gosh.
Please...
Please get a grip, Na Yun Shil.
How could you call him that?
I should have gone back home even at the late hour.
It's too late now.
And you said your back was hurting.
I can't sleep.
By the way, what is that awful smell?
It's the fermented soybean lump.
I like the savory smell.
Does your love for Kang Tae Yang...
make this smell savory to you?
The power of love is astonishing.
By the way,
what do you like about Kang Tae Yang so much?
What did you like about Dad?
Well...
It's hard to answer, right?
Ever since I was young,
I grew up hearing bad things about you.
- That you married him for money. - How dare they say such a thing?
- Who said that? - Nobody says that in your face.
They'd say it behind your back.
And I didn't need them to say so. I could just see from their faces.
So?
So...
I thought...
I'd find myself true love,
have a happy relationship...
and get married.
But...
Everyone I met was interested in either my background...
or they rejected me talking ill of you.
It's not like I can stop being your daughter...
and I can't stop being the youngest daughter of Meesa Apparel, too.
I've always wanted...
someone who can see me...
as who I am.
And that person is Kang Tae Yang?
Yes. I knew he could do that from the start.
When I got to know him better,
he was even better than what I was looking for.
I can count on him...
to find what I've been looking for...
in my whole life.
You've only known him for a short while.
I just want you...
to stop being so negative...
and see him as who he really is.
I thought you were just an immature troublemaker.
Looks like I was wrong.
It's chilly out there.
Wait a minute.
Where are my shoes?
What are you doing right now?
I noticed that you and Hyo Won's shoes have gotten dirty,
so I washed and dried them.
- Where's your mother? - She's sleeping in the other room.
She spoke ill of me for being senseless, didn't she?
No, she's not the kind of person to speak ill of anyone.
What? Then what about me?
Are you saying that I'm that kind of person?
That is in no way of what I meant.
Are you hungry?
I haven't eaten at all today worrying about Hyo Won.
I'm famished.
Do you want me to cook you up something?
You?
I don't know whether you'll like it or not.
That's so good.
What is this called?
It's salted rockfish soup, a winter specialty.
The soup tastes delicious.
Well,
your mum is a very good cook.
The fish melts in my mouth.
It's so tasty.
Would you like some?
What?
Just one shot, then.
That was just amazing.
Hyo Won drank half the vat earlier today.
That crazy brat.
Can you give me just one more shot?
The alcohol's warming me up and I feel much better.
Just one more shot.
Thank you for cooking breakfast.
Let's eat, everyone.
- Thank you. - Thank you.
You're welcome.
You started already.
What are you doing here?
I invited him to join us for breakfast.
Honey.
I'll get his soup and rice.
- Okay. - Have a seat, Jun.
Thanks.
You all seem to think that ganging up against me...
will make me give in.
I'm not a pushover.
- Here you go. - Thanks.
Let's eat.
- Okay. - Okay.
Thanks for the food.
The egg roll looks very appetising.
Thank you, Father.
Would you like some bean sprouts?
He saved you from embarrassment so take the hint and stop it.
Can't you be nice to him while he's eating?
He might have indigestion.
Sorry.
It's okay. You can take the call.
I don't know this number.
Hello?
Are you Sung Jun who won KBC's Best Rookie of the Year Award...
back in 2000?
Yes, I'm that Sung Jun.
I'm Kim Bong Soo, the producer of "Music Stage".
I called to ask you to come on our show.
KBC's "Music Stage"?
Don't you have to be really famous to appear on that show?
I heard you went from singing ballads to trot songs...
and thought your old fans would like to see how you're doing.
We'll tape the show next Thursday. Are you free?
Thursday?
Yes, I'm free, of course I'm free.
Yes, Sir, I understand.
I'll see you, then. Thank you.
Who was that?
They want me to appear on KBC's "Music Stage".
That was the producer of the show.
"Music Stage"?
You have to be quite good to be on that show.
Come on, Mum.
Jun won the Best Rookie of the Year Award at KBC's...
year-end award ceremony in 2000.
Did you actually...
win an award, then?
It's true, Mum.
Tae Pyung was a really famous singer at one time.
If Dong Jin says so, then it must be true.
I thought you were just a poor musician.
I guess I was wrong.
He's in a slump, but he'll rise again soon.
You don't have to worry.
Dong Jin.
- Thanks a lot. - For what?
For siding with me at breakfast.
I wasn't taking sides. I just told the truth.
I'll never forget what you did.
If your mum disapproves of you and Yun Shil,
then I'll take a stand and...
Will you watch your tongue? We're right outside the gate.
You're right, sorry. I'll be careful next time.
Ddong Jin, it seems that...
your ex-wife isn't over you yet.
You need to make things very clear to everyone involved.
One small mistake...
could end up in you hurting Yun Shil badly.
You're in no position to give me dating advice.
Focus on your own relationship.
That sounded like you mean we're family now.
That was nothing. I'm off to work.
Bye.
Have a nice day.
If Ddong Jin takes my side,
then his mum is practically in the bag.
This is it.
Sung Tae Pyung's life is about to get much better.
May the force of the universe be with me always.
This is a bit to garish.
This looks gentlemanly, but too stern.
I can't make up my mind.
Honey, help me out.
Which of these ties should I wear?
Wear whichever one you want. Why do you care how you look?
We might get a VIP client today.
I want to look well-dressed.
I like this gentlemanly one.
This one? Okay.
- Are you wearing cologne? - What?
Yes, in case the suit smells...
because you didn't have it dry-cleaned.
Why didn't you just wear another suit? You're so particular.
Are you going to work already?
Yes. We got a huge pre-order so I have to go in early.
I'll walk you out.
What for?
What? Don't you want to walk me to work?
Did I say that? Don't get imaginative.
Come on out.
She just ruined it.
What if we meet Young Eun?
Why are you walking so slowly?
Why don't you go ahead? I'll...
I'll take a slow stroll while I enjoy the view.
What's there to see? We take this route every day.
Even if we do,
the view can be different each morning.
I want to take a slow walk.
You've been acting strangely.
How so?
You snuck out last night.
And now you're walking a few steps behind me.
Did you...
vouch for another loan?
Is that what you think?
If I ever help someone take out a loan, I'll change my surname.
I'll never do that again.
That was just a small test.
I'm glad it's not that.
You go this way.
I'll go that way.
- What for? - The view...
I didn't sleep well last night and I feel a bit woozy.
I want to cool my head by breathing in the cold air.
Okay, you do that, then. See you at home.
Have a nice... Bye.
See you.
(Oh Young Eun Bakery)
I guess she's not here yet.
The bath in the early morning...
and gussying up all went to nothing.
Maybe I'll come back during lunchtime.
(Oh Young Eun Bakery)
Did you sleep well, Honey?
- What was that? - What was what?
- You called me that first. - That was...
It was a mistake.
So please forget it.
I was really happy to hear that.
I couldn't get any sleep because I was so embarrassed.
Why would you be embarrassed?
I didn't want you to think of me who desperately wants to marry you.
Don't worry about that.
I'm the one who desperately wants to get married.
I'm way more desperate than you.
After we're done overcoming the obstacles ahead of us,
I'd like to marry you.
I'd like to have a daughter who looks just like you...
and a son who has my pretty eyes.
I want to have a normal life...
just like everyone else.
Do you agree with me, Honey?
- Stop calling me that. - Fine.
We're going to be late. Let's hurry.
It comes automatically now.
Stop teasing me.
I won't.
Oh, no.
What happened here?
It must have been Gi Pyo people's doing.
They must be holding grudges from last night.
Good morning.
What on earth happened here?
We just got here, too.
What kind of scoundrels would do something like this?
Let's clean up the broken glass first.
Let's change the suits on the mannequins.
Okay. I'll call the glass shop.
Don't do anything. You might hurt yourself.
I'm sure this is Gi Pyo people's doing.
I'm sure of it.
Yes.
It's an urgent matter. Please come at once.
Okay. Thank you.
The glass shop sent people here just now.
I think we should install...
security cameras inside and outside of the shop.
That'd be good.
I'm curious to know the jerks behind this.
I cleaned up the broken glass...
and changed all the mannequins.
Good job.
Darn hooligans.
Why would they do this to us?
We should consider ourselves lucky that the damages weren't as severe.
He's right.
There are all kinds of people in this world.
Let's just forget about it.
We have to find the person responsible for this...
or something like this could happen again.
We'll install security cameras by the end of the day.
If this happens again, we'll report to the police.
Anyone there?
Yes?
Oh, my.
Please send your mother my regards.
She probably didn't even sleep very well...
with us sleeping in the bedroom.
You embarrassed me so much.
What would you be embarrassed about?
Did you forget how loud you cried?
What about your drinking habits?
What kind of impression do you think you left?
What drinking habits?
I only had two glasses of plum wine.
Was it...
that bad?
Nothing out of the ordinary except when you cried and sang.
Kang Tae Yang.
There you are.
Oh, gosh.
You little punk.
Why would you hit him? He didn't do anything.
Behave yourselves, both of you!
Are you okay? Is your nose bleeding?
I'm fine.
- Are you okay? - I'm fine.
It's all right.
Kang Tae Yang.
What have you done to Hyo Won?
Did you brainwash her?
How could you make her kick her only brother?
- You punched him first. - What did you say?
Stop it already!
Shut it!
Stay away from my sister while I'm still being nice.
Or else.
Who are you to tell him what to do?
Can you knock some sense into her, Mum?
Are you going to just let them be?
Kang Tae Yang.
Min Hyo Won.
You two.
I'll let you date for now.
- Ms Ko. - Mum?
What are you talking about?
It's not like all dating couples end up marrying.
They might break up mid-way.
So let's see how it goes.
Have you lost your mind?
You're supposed to break them up, not encourage them.
You're matching someone like him with Hyo Won?
If this is how you're going to be,
I'm not going to live here any longer.
I'm sick of everything.
Then...
You can date Choi Ji Yun.
Are you satisfied?
I have a conference meeting with Jeil Department Store.
Okay. Are our suits...
really going to be sold at the department store?
We'll have to see about that.
What's there to see? I'm sure you'll get it done.
I have to go to the bathroom.
I'll go check on how the glass replacement is going.
Go on, then.
If only my honey would just give me a kiss on the cheek,
I think the conference meeting will go very well.
They might hear us.
Who? We're the only ones here.
Good luck on your meeting.
I'm all charged up.
I'll be back.
This brings back memories of the times...
when you were the Deputy CEO of Meesa Apparel.
I'm no longer the Deputy CEO of Meesa Apparel.
I'm here to represent Wolgyesu Tailor Shop.
I appreciate you seeing me.
Take a seat.
We went over your proposal.
But everyday customers...
aren't very familiar with Bespoke Suits.
I wanted to hear your insights...
on how we're going to make profit.
Firstly,
we should diversify the suits according to the price range.
It should raise the brand awareness.
After we stabilize,
we'll work towards getting recognition as a premium brand...
targeting VIP customers.
That's my market strategy.
With Wolgyesu Tailor Shop being part of the department store,
it'll be a new paradigm...
of the composition of men's wear department.
It'll aid the department store with diversity...
and improvement in quality.
The sales of our newly launched outdoor brand is looking alarming.
We are still at the early stage of launching,
but the performance is below our expectations.
We're not doing good on consumer recognition either.
There hasn't been improvement shown in brand awareness.
The outdoor wear market...
was already a red ocean when we went into business.
We see that as the main cause of our failure.
We should adopt more aggressive marketing strategies...
to raise brand awareness.
It's somewhat too early to say,
but we might have to declare loss cut.
It's time for us to make a decision.
I mean...
Can you tell me...
what have the marking team been up to...
with all the promotional spending?
Is this the best you can do even with mobilizing...
Meesa Apparel's local distributors?
It might sound like an excuse,
but we weren't able to fully utilize our technology...
with outdoor wears' nature of...
having to be functional and efficient.
We overlooked the fact that...
the market adopted a trend of athleisure wears.
We see that as the main cause of our failure.
Is that all you're capable of?
All you do is make excuses.
Not a single one of you can come up with a countermeasure.
If you don't show me a result, in marketing or product development,
I'll fire all of you.
Consider yourself informed, okay?
I'm not saying this just to scare you.
Here's your order.
- Enjoy. - Thank you.
What should I have today?
I'll have a bulgogi burger and orange juice.
You don't need to increase our sales. Stay with your mother.
Fine. I'll stick around only for a bit.
There's a new menu. Do you want to try that?
Is it? Okay, I'll try that.
Whatever you recommend.
I'll help you pay for your order.
I didn't think my mum would give in so soon.
You have a way of moving a person's heart.
My mum must have fallen for your charms.
Do you think it's me she likes?
She gave in out of worry for you.
Let's talk later.
Hello.
(Pooper)
- Hello? - It's me, Min Hyo Won.
Hyo Won, are you back home?
Yes. I decided to come home this morning.
Your brother told me off for letting you out.
Thanks to you, Poop...
Thanks to you, Ji Yun, everything worked out.
My mum just gave her approval that I can date my boyfriend, too.
That's great. Congratulations.
Thank you. I'll treat you one day.
You, I, Hyo Sang and my boyfriend can have dinner together.
Work hard.
Hello.
The coat should come down to...
about here. What do you think?
I'd like that.
Ms Na, 145, please.
I took all your measurements.
Come downstairs to pick a design.
- Okay. - And let's have some tea, too.
Hello, this is Wolgyesu Tailor Shop.
Hello, there. I see you changed your number.
I won't talk to you. I'm hanging up.
Did you notice the broken window?
That was just a warning.
Next time we might blow up the whole shop...
or your boss might lose a limb or two.
Do you think I'm scared of your threats?
If you won't back down,
we'll have to go all the way.
Let's see how far you want to take this.
What was that about?
Was it from the jerk from prison?
I need to go out.
Where to?
I have to go somewhere urgently.
I'll tell Master Bae on the way out.
Okay.
What on earth is going on?
- Let's go inside. - Okay.
Hello, Mr Hong.
Who are you?
I'm Hwang Gyu Seok, a lawyer.
I'm Min Hyo Joo, Board President of Meesa Cultural Foundation.
(Min Hyo Joo)
Board President of Meesa Cultural Foundation?
Meesa Cultural Foundation...
You might know me as...
Lee Dong Jin's ex-wife.
Lee Dong Jin?
Yes.
We might be in the same boat.
I'd like to help you.
Don't you want to see your wife as soon as possible?
I'll help you.
You will get your wife back...
very soon.
I will do my best to get him paroled.
See what you can do.
I'll keep you informed.
Why are you here? Aren't you too good for me?
I'm sorry.
I should have come to tell you sooner.
To be honest, I lacked the courage to do so.
Please...
let me go.
What?
You know that...
I wasn't going to marry you out of love.
Do you want to pretend that nothing happened?
Do that for me.
Please.
I can't.
I'm locked up here...
and Lee Dong Jin's with you.
It's not a fair game.
I'll be getting out soon. Let's do this on equal footing.
What?
Did you think I'd be here forever?
Someone offered me help and it looks like...
I'll be out pretty soon.
That should make it a fair fight.
Did you see your husband?
Why are you here?
I'm here on business.
Looking after your husband who's behind bars...
while dating another man.
You must be so very busy.
I have no time for nonsense. I'd like to get going.
You dumped your husband...
to take someone else's.
What a horrid hobby.
Watch what you say.
How dare you talk to me that way?
(The Gentlemen of Wolgyesu Tailor Shop)
Where's Yun Shil.
Are you trying to kill my son?
How could you let her date Tae Yang?
What happened?
Become a lawyer. What about civil servant?
What announcement?
Let my mum marry Jun.
There's so much work to do. I have to stay late.
I told you to clip the roots and you took off the heads.
Are you sick, Father?
As much as you value your love, I do, too.
And I'll risk my life to protect it.