BioskopKeren
(Episode 33)
Did you see your husband?
Why are you here?
I'm here on business.
Looking after your husband who's behind bars...
while dating another man.
You must be very busy.
I have no time for nonsense. I'd like to get going.
You dumped your husband...
to take someone else's.
What a horrid hobby.
Watch what you say.
Who do you think you are?
Who do I think I am?
I have a right to say that as an ex-wife of Lee Dong Jin.
You are not his wife now.
You are his ex-wife.
I don't think you have the right to say that kind of words.
- What? - People have their own stories.
Don't stick your nose if you don't know what's going on here.
Lee Dong Jin is...
a much better person than those people like you.
Don't even think about him.
You are one of those girls...
who take advantage of men with compassion.
Those people like you make me sick.
You're pathetic.
I'm back.
You're back. How did it go?
I had a meeting with the chief director of product division.
It went better than I had expected.
You are amazing.
I never dreamed of selling our products in a department store.
Neither did I.
We have our own pattern making method.
I think we have a shot, but we must try our best though.
By the way, where is Na Yun Shil?
She rushed out of after receiving a call a while ago.
- A phone call? - Yun Shil said...
she should visit the prison.
- The prison? - Yes.
What is going on in your mind?
I replaced the broken windows...
and installed surveillance cameras.
You don't have to worry from now on.
Can I ask you where you have been?
I've been to Gi Pyo.
I asked him to let go of me...
and stop harassing us.
I thought I have to confront him...
and tell him what I think.
You must be tired after the visit in this cold weather.
I'm sorry. I didn't tell you before I go.
I'm fine with that.
I'm happy if you're comfortable after all.
Let's go inside and have some hot drink.
By the way,
I met her.
I mean Min Hyo Joo.
You met her in the prison?
This is Min Hyo Joo.
I met your son a while ago.
The lawyer said he will do his best.
I think Mr. Hong Gi Pyo will be free on parole.
Is that true? My goodness. I'm so thankful.
We'll never forget what you have done for us.
Thank you so much.
You can thank me when your son gets out.
By the way, about your daughter-in-law,
you should keep a close eye on her until Mr. Hong Gi Pyo gets out.
Am I in the wrong room?
What happened?
What's going on?
What are you doing here?
You should go to your new room.
New room? What do you mean?
- Your girlfriend. - What?
Your girlfriend moved your stuff to a VIP room.
She made an advance payment of 10 months.
My goodness. My girlfriend...
What am I talking?
Where is Hyo Won?
She invited all the guests here for a house warming,
I mean room warming.
Oh, my goodness.
Please help yourselves.
- Sure. - Thank you.
Also, please be friendly with Tae Yang.
- We'll surely do so. - Don't worry about that.
I've seen so many couples,
but you're the best girlfriend ever, Hyo Won.
You're the modern Shin Sa Im Dang.
I agree with you.
Let's applaud for...
Min Hyo Won, the modern Shin Sa Im Dang!
I know I'm in no way perfect,
but you think highly of me.
Thank you so much.
I'll try harder from now on.
Attention, everyone!
The owner of...
the VIP room has just arrived!
- Good luck. - Congratulations on your marriage.
- Honey. - What are you doing here?
The manager called to say the VIP room was empty,
so I signed the contract.
The room's huge,
has an en suite bathroom and an air conditioner.
This is paradise.
I'll move back to my old room.
- Why? - I know why you're doing this,
but you did so without discussing it with me.
That's like insulting the life I lived so far.
It can't be an insult.
That's nonsense.
I just...
tried to...
think of ways to make your life more comfortable.
I did this thinking you'd be really pleased.
If you keep doing this,
it'll make me look like I like you for your money.
No way.
Exactly.
Don't make me look bad.
Please don't.
I didn't think hard enough.
I'm sorry.
Thank you.
You're poor but strong.
You're proud and upright.
I picked a great guy.
Oh, no.
What's wrong?
What's all this?
I went to a department store...
and bought things for your mum.
Is that bad?
Would giving her this...
also insult the life you lived...
so far?
My mum farms and works by the sea.
She doesn't need such luxury goods.
These will keep her warm when she works outdoors.
Okay.
I'll return everything tomorrow.
Well...
If you feel bad,
shall we send her these?
Thank you.
Don't thank me.
I should thank you.
No. You acknowledged my efforts.
I was very impressed, you know.
I thought you'd be...
disappointed and leave me after seeing my house.
You got along with my mum...
and I appreciate that a lot.
I'm totally in love with your mum's home.
Eco-friendly houses like yours are all the rage now.
You're the first person...
to say that about my house.
Thank you.
Nothing's going as planned.
What's wrong this time?
Financiers are skeptical about...
Meesa Apparel's profits for this quarter.
The Finance Team's swamped.
Why did you even launch an outdoor line?
You should have focused on suits.
I need to show the shareholders that I'm better than Dong Jin!
All he does is sew clothes...
in a tiny store.
Why do you care about him?
His career as an entrepreneur is over.
You are right, but still...
Can't you think before you speak?
What it is now?
How could you let Hyo Won...
date Tae Yang?
- Are you senile? - What?
He's a scumbag.
Why do you think he's good enough for her?
He might be poor but he's a decent guy.
Both him and his mother...
are simple but upright.
Simple but upright?
He is well and truly duping you.
Why don't you see that?
Not all couples that date end up getting married.
They might date for a while and get sick of each other.
I'll tell you this again.
If Tae Yang and Hyo Won end up getting married,
consider me gone.
I'll cut ties with you all.
Are you...
- hiding something from me? - What?
You dislike Tae Yang a little too much.
Did something happen between you two that I don't know about?
As if.
I don't want to get involved with someone like him.
(Wolgyesu Tailor Shop)
Lee Dong Jin speaking.
I'm the VP of Jeil Department Store. We met earlier today.
- Hello, Sir. - I was hoping...
you could give a presentation to our executives.
When are you free?
I'm free any time.
Yes.
Okay. I'll see you, then.
- Was that the department store? - Yes.
He wants me to give a presentation to the executives.
If they want a presentation, doesn't that mean...
our chances are really good?
Let's do our best.
I'll have to stay late to work on the presentation.
You can go ahead.
Can I do anything to help?
Not right now. Help me later on.
I'll call when I'm done.
- Wait at home. - Okay.
Let's go home, then.
Sam Do, aren't you leaving?
You can go ahead.
- See you, Yun Shil. - See you tomorrow.
Aren't you going home?
Just a moment.
- Hello, honey. - When will you be home?
I want to cook some fish soup by the time you arrive home.
Oh dear, I feel terrible now.
I have so much work to do here.
I have to stay late.
I'd love to have fish soup.
Enjoy your meal.
I'll order some noodles. I'll see you later.
Bye.
- Are you going to stay late? - What?
Well...
Dong Jin.
Don't you think I need a haircut?
You got one not long ago.
I might look a bit younger...
if my hair's shorter.
I look nicer in brighter colours.
This tie is too dark and it makes me...
look old and cranky.
I think you look fine.
Do you have a bottle of cologne?
Cologne? No, I don't.
You said you'd work late.
Where are you sneaking off to?
I'll tell you later.
Bye.
Why is he so excited?
Who are you?
Why are you here?
Must you ask?
Do I need a reason to visit my daughter-in-law?
I waited for so long out here that I caught a cold.
Are you going to freeze me to death?
Open the door.
I told you before that...
I have nothing to do with Gi Pyo.
What?
Are you treating him like a stranger now that...
you have no use for him?
You witch.
You changed the lock...
so that I can't get in.
You have no reason to come by.
I do!
I need to watch my flirtatious daughter-in-law.
I'm going to...
hang around you until Gi Pyo gets out of prison.
- You can't do that. - What?
I'm sorry, but please leave.
Oh, my goodness.
I finished all the prep work so there's nothing to do...
on the farm. I don't need to be there.
This is kimchi.
This is dried radish greens.
If you stir fry this with soy sauce and perilla seeds,
Gi Pyo would finish a bowl of rice in the blink of an eye...
My poor Gi Pyo!
When I think about you eating cold rice,
my heart just breaks.
My poor Gi Pyo.
That's right. This is...
picked pepper...
and pickled garlic.
What are you doing?
Go back to Anseong.
I'll take you to the terminal.
You witch.
Didn't you hear what I said?
I came to live with you!
Why would I live with you? For what reason?
Oh, my goodness.
I rushed so much, I skipped lunch.
Make me dinner. I'm about to die of hunger.
Don't be mean to your mother-in-law.
Your husband is being released soon.
Someone up there must have known how wronged Gi Pyo was,
and gave him a helping hand.
Someone great has come to help us.
You must be tired from playing Go all day.
Go rest in the room.
All I do is eat and play. Why is that tiring?
- Honey. - Yes?
Do you want to go to a hot spring this weekend?
Why all of a sudden?
I couldn't enjoy the foliage last fall.
Let's soak in some hot water.
We can just go to a bathhouse. Why would we go so far?
Just take me to enjoy the cherry blossoms next spring.
Cherry blossoms.
I'm not sure. I don't know if I can.
What?
Okay. Let's do that.
- I'm going to work. - Okay.
Whatever.
Why does he keep reporting things like that?
Oh, my gosh.
I told you to clip the roots...
and you took off the heads.
Goodness. What a waste.
I'm sorry. I was thinking about something else.
I said to go to the room and rest. Why are you causing trouble?
I'll get some chilli paste.
Okay.
The water is overflowing. Wait.
Stay right there. My goodness.
Do you feel unwell?
No. I'm just a little dizzy all of a sudden.
I'll take you.
Thank you.
Okay. Take it slowly.
Do you get dizzy often?
I'm old, so it happens occasionally. Thanks.
I see. I get like that when I'm not feeling well, too.
- Tae Pyung. - Yes, Father.
Nothing in life is easy.
I'm sure it's more so...
- with relationships. - I see.
When I married my wife,
I had a very tough time because I was a poor tailor.
Don't be hurt and be strong.
Thank you. Hearing you say that...
makes me feel much better.
Please rest. I'll go now.
Okay. I need to lie down.
Here is the pillow.
I see. That's where it was.
(Oh Young Eun Bakery)
Young Eun.
Do you know who I am?
It's me, Sam Do.
Is that too boring?
Look who this is!
Aren't you Young Eun? Wang Young Eun?
No, Oh Young Eun!
My gosh. Long time no see.
What are you doing there?
Didn't you say you're working late?
Yes.
But my head hurt, so I left early.
I can just go in early tomorrow.
Why didn't you go home then?
I was too hungry so I wanted to have some bread.
What? You should go home and eat a proper meal,
not snack on pastries.
I bought two fresh fish at the market.
I'll cook up a nice and spicy stew with radish.
- Okay. - Let's go.
Why aren't you coming?
Okay.
Here.
It's good.
What is it? Does it taste bad?
No. The broth is nice.
Then why are you picking at it?
I don't have an appetite.
But honey.
Don't you ever wear dresses?
You'd look much prettier with a pretty shawl, too.
I stand in front of a fryer all day frying chicken.
Why would I wear a dress and a shawl?
Why are you complaining about my clothes?
I just think you'd look much more elegant and prettier...
if you dressed up a little, that's all.
Give me a bouquet of money.
I'll transform into the most sophisticated and elegant woman,
so much that the wealthy wives will cry when they see me.
You're making me lose my appetite.
Sorry. I didn't even realise.
How does a woman not know how to be bashful?
Why would I be bashful? We've slept in the same bed for years.
I'm not that fake.
That isn't about being fake, it's basic manners.
We're eating.
If you're so upset, you can fart, too. Then we'll be even.
Seriously. Just go to the bathroom.
It's okay.
From this angle, I can't tell whether the mannequin is you...
if you are the mannequin.
You're embarrassing me.
Did you say bye to my mum?
Of course. I did say bye,
but she wouldn't even make an eye contact.
She'll give in eventually. Why is she stalling so much?
Will she give in?
I told you not to worry. She has no hopes for me.
She went all in on Dong Jin.
She shouldn't go all in.
What do you mean?
What I mean is,
she'll probably be very picky...
when choosing a wife for Dong Jin later on.
Of course. She had a corporate heiress as a daughter-in-law.
She won't permit anyone just average.
You're right. It'll be a big pain.
Don't worry about Dong Jin.
He's always been smart about looking out for himself.
I'm worried about us.
What am I doing? You need to go to work.
Sorry.
It's okay.
I feel so secure, since your father is backing me up.
But is your father ill?
No. My dad's healthy. Why?
Nothing. It's just that he didn't look so well.
It's nothing. I was just asking.
I'll be late. I should go.
Wait. I'll come to your work after I finish.
It's okay. It's not a nice place. Don't come.
I'll see you at home.
See you later.
It's not like I come all the time. I haven't come in a while.
Must I cook for myself? Does that make you happy?
You wicked thing. You evil thing.
I saw Gi Pyo this afternoon.
- You went to visit him? - Yes.
I asked him to let me go.
You're determined to kill my son!
It's hard enough for him to even survive.
What stupid nonsense did you say to him?
It wasn't nonsense.
You're blinded by some guy,
that you disrespect your husband and mother-in-law.
You despicable, dirty witch!
I'll stick to you like glue...
and guard you...
like a hound until Gi Pyo gets out. Got it?
It's late, so you can sleep here,
but please leave in the morning.
Hey! Hey! Where are you going?
Why that...
That wicked thing.
I'm so angry.
That wicked little brat.
Darn it.
That's nice.
(Mr Pretty Eyes)
- Hello? - Hi. Did you eat yet?
I just ate. What about you?
I'm just having a burger.
Should I bring you some food?
- It's okay. I'm full now. - Oh, gosh.
I'll stop by on my way home.
- Make me instant noodles. - No.
- What? - You can't come over.
- Why not? - I'm going to sleep early.
Do you feel sick?
No, but I'm tired, so I want to rest.
Are you hiding someone at home?
Like who?
A young and handsome man?
- What was that? - Rest, then.
I'll call later.
Okay. You must be tired.
Don't stop by. Go straight home, okay?
Why does she keep saying not to come over?
Is she sick of me already?
She really has to leave tomorrow.
Don't be mean to your mother-in-law.
Your husband is being released soon.
Someone up there must have known how wronged Gi Pyo was,
and gave him a helping hand.
I'm sorry...
for creating trouble.
I know you did it for me.
That VIP room...
was nice and big,
and had its own shower...
and an air conditioner.
It was so nice.
Once I get a job and make money, I'll move into the VIP room.
Do you mean it?
Promise.
Hi, Mum.
Is Tae Yang with you?
- Naturally. - Let me talk to him.
My mum wants to talk to you.
- Hello, Ma'am. - What time is it?
Why are you keeping her out so late?
- It's only 8:30pm. - Okay.
Our curfew is 9pm,
so send her home right now.
Curfew is 9pm?
Since when did we have a curfew?
Starting today.
How could you set a 9pm curfew for your daughter...
- who just started dating? - Forget it, if you don't like it.
I'll just take back...
saying you to may date.
- Not that! - Then stick to your curfew.
We haven't even had dinner yet.
Then eat at home.
You'll save money, too.
Mum says to come over for dinner.
- No? - Tae Yang.
You don't want to eat with me?
No, we're coming right now.
My mum is so clueless.
I'm sorry.
It's okay. Let's hurry back before we miss your curfew.
Okay.
- Hello. - What have you been doing?
I stayed with him at his job...
and then we hung out in the gosiwon.
- Let's sit down and talk. - Yes, Ma'am.
How long will you work at the burger joint?
I think I'll have to work there until I get a full-time job.
Don't do that.
Return to the company.
I can't do that.
Why not?
Would you want to go back to the company that wrongfully fired you?
And Hyo Sang is still there.
Then let's draw a big picture.
Study for the bar exam.
I'll support you all the way.
The bar exam? Why...
That's the best way for raising your social status.
If you pass the bar exam,
I'll let you marry Hyo Won without complaint.
I'm so humiliated.
Don't you watch the news?
They're getting rid of the bar exam.
Really?
When?
Well,
I nap early evenings,
so I don't watch the news.
What about the Civil Service Exam?
- The Civil Service Exam? - Once you pass the exam...
and work at various important posts,
you can enter politics. What do you say?
I'm not interested in that field at all.
You don't like this or that. Then what?
You need a good job,
- so it'll be less embarrassing. - Mum!
- I'm still young, so... - You're not young any more.
You can't do part time jobs forever.
Just what...
- is your dream? - Mum, please!
Am I wrong?
Did I offend you?
No, Ma'am.
This is Min Hyo Sang. Come to the office right now.
I should go now.
But you didn't even have dinner.
Are you angry because of what I said?
I am definitely not. Everything you said was correct.
Then why are you suddenly leaving?
Our housekeeper is setting the dinner table.
I forgot I had dinner plans.
I'll come back another time. Please feed me, then.
Watch what you say, will you?
What did I say?
I'll walk you to the gate!
Was I a bit harsh?
So,
you grew to like my sister, with no ulterior motive.
Do you expect me to believe that?
I can't force you to believe me, but it's true.
Don't give me that rubbish.
You're trying to use Hyo Won...
to get revenge at me and Ji Yun!
Are you that closed-minded?
How many times did I tell you that wasn't it?
Hey.
If you're after money,
take this and get lost.
I'm sick of seeing you like this.
- Are you laughing? - In movies and on TV,
this usually comes from the girl's mother.
- The situation is amusing. - What is this punk babbling about?
Look here, Hyo Sang.
"Look here, Hyo Sang."
You must have lost your darn mind.
I am no longer an employee of this company,
so that's who I'll address you.
Just as your love is important,
my love is precious to me,
and I will risk my life to protect it if necessary.
Don't think you can buy love with a few dollars.
Love...
is precious and priceless.
How dare you lecture me?
Because you're the brother of my love.
I'll ignore what happened today.
Try being a quarter of the person Hyo Won is.
Hey, punk. Where are you doing?
We're not done talking!
If you act like this again,
I can't promise I'll be polite.
Let's forget this ever happened.
That arrogant punk.
- Why are you here again? - Ask your boyfriend.
Hi. You're here.
I saw Tae Yang on my way in.
What did you see him about?
We have a bit of a problem.
What is it?
It's nothing serious.
I felt bad that he was fired, so I tried to give him compensation,
but I guess it hurt his pride. He refused to take it.
I'm sorry...
for making you worry.
Why are you sleeping already?
Honey.
- Honey. - What?
You should wash up before going to sleep.
I'm too tired. I'm going to sleep.
Why do you sleep so much?
I wonder if the bakery is closed.
Where are you going?
(Oh Young Eun Bakery)
It's closed already.
It's Young Eun.
(Wolgyesu Tailor Shop)
Young Eun.
Isn't he heavy?
I'm fine,
but you must be tired.
I guess you fed him well. He's heavy.
What's his name?
Seung Woo. Han Seung Woo.
I see. Seung Woo.
He looks a lot like you when you were young.
His mouth, his eyes...
You haven't changed at all.
What do you mean? I'm an old man now.
But how did you end up moving into my neighbourhood?
Remember I used to visit the tailor shop with you?
I had fond memories there.
I didn't know Wolgyesu Tailor Shop would still be there.
You, too.
Your husband is the guy you were going to study abroad with, right?
Yes.
Tell him we should grab soju together sometime.
It's here.
I'll take him now.
It was good seeing you.
Me, too.
Come to my bakery sometime when you have time.
You like castella.
Okay.
- Good night. - Bye.
(Hyo Joo)
Hello?
Does something need to be up for me to call?
We were married once.
I don't understand why you're doing this.
I felt bad.
It's because I regret it.
I was a bad daughter-in-law to your parents.
I can't even begin, with respect to you.
I thought only of myself and never considered others.
I'm repenting.
I appreciate you saying that, but it's too late.
Give me another chance.
You know it's too late.
When I think about it,
I never tried my best with you.
I regret that so much.
I mean it.
That's why...
I want to do my best for you now.
Give me another chance.
Is that so hard?
Feelings can't be changed so easily.
You can't reheat feelings that cooled.
Is it because of Yun Shil?
Is that convict's wife that important to you?
Goodbye.
How degrading. How could you fall for a woman like that?
How could Lee Dong Jin, who was once my husband,
date a woman like that?
Lose your unfounded superiority complex.
You don't have right to treat her like that.
- What? - Also,
please maintain some of that pride that you talk about all the time.
Don't call me like this again.
- Honey. Dong Jin. - You seem drunk.
Stop drinking and go home.
Hello? Hello?
Jerk.
How could you do this to me?
It's me.
Did I wake you?
It's still early. I'm not sleeping yet.
Then I'll come up.
- What? - I'm out front.
Out front?
In front of my place?
- The burger wasn't enough. - No way.
I'm starving.
- Make me some instant noodles. - No.
I came all the way. Come on. I'll eat quickly and leave.
But my place is a pig sty. You can't come in.
It's okay.
You really can't.
I won't tease you. Don't worry. I'm coming up.
No! No!
I'm out of noodles.
What? I bought a lot last time.
I ate it all.
All of them? Alone?
Yes. Why don't we meet at the convenience down the street?
Then I'll wait here. Let's walk over together.
Well, but...
I just washed my hair,
so I need to dry it first.
I'll be right there,
so pour the water into the noodles and wait for me there.
You know I like soggy noodles, right?
You really like soggy noodles?
I do. Go on.
Okay. I'll go ahead, then. Come quickly.
Goodness.
What took you so long?
You must have been making yourself pretty to come see me.
What?
Yes. You're right.
I like it that you're admitting it.
You're out of breath. Have some water.
What's wrong with you? Is something wrong?
No. Nothing's wrong.
But hey,
do you eat instant noodles all the time instead of rice?
When did you finish all of that?
Yes, I know.
You can eat this today, but no more instant noodles for a while.
Okay?
Okay.
I'm worried now.
Will you only make me instant noodles after we get married?
Here. Eat first.
What's wrong?
I'm just thankful because you are so kind to me.
You're so attentive to me.
You shouldn't be moved with such a little thing.
You'll be all tears if I treat you better.
Have some water.
Go inside now. It's cold.
You should leave first.
I'll go inside after you leave.
You go inside first.
I feel relieved...
when I see you go in safely and turn on the light.
The light is on.
I was in a hurry getting out...
so I forgot to turn the light off.
You did miss me.
You hurried so much not to turn the light off.
Go inside.
I'll take you to the entrance.
You don't have to.
I can go myself. You should go.
I came all the way so far. I'd be sorry if I should leave now.
No, no.
I'm fine. It's so close.
You should go home now.
You were making that proposal all day.
You go first. I'll leave after you get home.
All right. Bye.
I was going to sleep just a moment.
Where is Sam Do?
Has he gone to the restroom? Honey!
Sam Do!
Where have you been?
What are you doing here? You were sleeping.
You were sleeping, too. Where have you been?
Me? Well...
I've been to the tailor shop.
You've been to the tailor shop at this hour?
Well, I had work to finish.
- Is that true? - It is. I have no place else to go.
What are you doing here in this cold weather?
Dong Jin,
are you coming from the tailor shop with Sam Do?
Pardon?
Oh, yes.
Then why are you coming separately?
I had to get an urgent phone call.
What's wrong? What happened?
It's nothing.
What are you doing? It's cold. Let's go in.
All right.
Thank you so much. You saved my life tonight.
Where have you been without telling your wife?
I'll explain later.
Oh, my.
How did she get in here?
Hyo Won.
Hyo Won, wake up.
You should hold yourself together.
What happened? Why did you come here?
I was afraid...
you might be upset because of Mum.
You said you have to be home by 9:00pm.
What are you going to do if ma'am finds out?
I checked her falling asleep and got out.
You must be upset a lot because of Mum.
She didn't say anything wrong.
Aren't you worried, Hyo Won?
- What do I worry? - What if...
I don't ever get a decent job and make a living with part time jobs?
Aren't you worried about that?
I...
trust you.
In such difficult circumstances,
you didn't give up...
and grew up to this well-mannered...
and nice person.
You can do anything if you have such capabilities.
I'll be by your side.
I'm really encouraged to hear you say so.
Get up now.
You should go home.
Can't I stay here tonight?
I don't want to go home.
You're not allowed to sleep out.
My friends' boyfriends always ask them to go on a overnight trip.
You're a strange man, Tae Yang.
I'm afraid...
you don't love me.
If you love someone,
you should try,
so that you keep it precious...
and people around you wish you luck.
Because you are the dearest and most precious person to me,
I want to cherish and protect you.
Do you understand?
Uncle.
What are you doing here in this cold weather?
I'm organising my thoughts...
before I make an important announcement.
An important announcement?
Please stay by my side when I say that.
Grandma always agrees to what you say, okay?
An important announcement?
What do you want to say...
to your grandparents at this hour?
I wonder.
What is your important announcement?
Grandma, Grandpa,
please allow Mum and Sung Joon get married.
I've never seen Mum happy as she is these days.
I'd also be happy...
if a man like Sung Joon is Dad.
Did Dong Sook asked you to say so?
It's not like that at all.
I'm telling you this from my heart.
I guess Da Jeong has been thinking about this enough, Mum.
I've been closely watching him.
He seems to be an innocent and responsible person.
What do you like...
about Sung Joon, Da Jeong?
It seems that...
he sincerely...
considers me as his family member,
like his own daughter.
Why don't we...
go to a church or a cathedral...
and get married now?
Then Mum would give up objecting.
That's not a good thing to do, Dong Sook.
That would just prove that...
I, Sung Tae Pyung, is...
a small-time busker.
I get it.
I said that since I was so upset.
I'll be brave as usual.
Father, Mother, we're home!
It must be Sung Joon.
Father, Mother, we're back from work.
- Good night. - Come in here.
Why are you all here?
What happened?
You are so childish.
You should thank Da Jeong.
- For what? - Da Jeong asked parents...
to allow you get married.
- Da Jeong. - Da Jeong.
Your mum decided to change her mind...
since she couldn't resist her granddaughter's appeal.
- Mum. - Mother.
This should be your last marriage.
Don't worry about that.
Sung Joon is my life-long mate.
It's my third time to hear that.
Stop that.
I'll make a deep bow to Father and Mother as a son-in-law to be.
Then...
I'll make a deep bow, too.
Thank you, Dad...
and Mum.
Thank you.
(Peace Gosiwon)
Can you drive?
Shall I drive if you're tired?
You have go to work early. You should get some sleep.
I'll be fine.
Call me when you get home.
Or I'll be worried.
It's so nice knowing that you get worried about me.
Are you wearing your seat belt?
Drive safely.
Is there something wrong with your car?
It won't start.
It won't start?
Is the battery flat?
It's out of power and it won't start.
Is the tank empty?
I need energy.
- Is that what you want. - Come on.
Fill me up.
What if someone sees?
Who is there to see us? Come on.
That's 30 percent.
Now I'm 50 percent full.
Isn't that enough to get you home?
Okay.
That's 100 percent.
I can go now.
Take care.
Tae Yang.
Yun Shil.
Who's the woman in the car?
- Did you see us? - Yes.
You two looked pretty close.
Are you...
Is she your girlfriend?
That's great. Congratulations.
I was worried that you were...
still moping over Ji Yun.
I'm glad. Good for you.
I have a problem, though.
I'll tell you on the way. I'll walk you home.
I can't go home.
Why can't you go home?
Hello, it's been a while.
Sorry to call you so late. I have to tell you something.
Sure. What is it?
Do you know where Yun Shil is?
She should be at home. I dropped her off a while ago.
She told me not to tell you in case you got worried,
but I thought you should know.
She's at the sauna on the main crossroads.
What is she doing at a sauna?
Gi Pyo's mother came over with a bag full of clothes.
She wants to stay with Yun Shil.
What?
Why is he calling so late?
- Hello, Dong Jin. - Where are you?
I was just about to go to sleep.
I'm outside your place. Can you come downstairs?
What for?
My mum told me to bring you some fresh kimchi.
I'm all ready for bed right now.
I can't come outside.
Do you mind leaving it by the door?
The kimchi will freeze. It's cold, so don't make me wait.
Okay, I'll be right there. Wait.
My goodness.
You don't live here.
How did you know that I was here?
Why does it matter how I found out?
Shouldn't you have called me when something like that happened?
Sorry. I didn't want you to worry.
We agreed not to tell lies.
- Yes, but... - What if I didn't know?
Were you going to live here?
Just for a while.
It's warm and I can take a hot shower whenever I want.
It's nicer than you think.
Come with me.
Where to?
You'll find out.
This is...
I can't let you stay at a 24-hour sauna.
I've never stayed at such an expensive hotel before.
I prefer the sauna.
This is for me.
For my peace of mind.
But still...
This place is too expensive.
First you lied and now you're insulting my efforts?
That's not what I mean.
I don't think I can sleep knowing that...
you're at a sauna.
Stay here for a while, for my sake.
If you find it too uncomfortable, talk to me, then.
Okay.
I'll stay here tonight.
Thanks. Let's go inside.
What's going on?
What are you doing here?
We have business here.
Do you?
What else can you do here but sleep?
Think whatever you want.
I wasn't wrong about you.
You have nothing to give but your body.
That's what you're like.
Watch your tongue.
Forget about it. Don't let it get to you.
You're drunk. Get home safely.
I will crush you both.
Hey, Lee Dong Jin!
(The Gentlemen of Wolgyesu Tailor Shop)
- She didn't come home? - Did you spend the night together?
This is unbelievable.
A commercial?
You want Tae Yang to be a model?
What nonsense is this?
I will catch you red-handed.
Take good care of Dong Sook and Da Jeong.
- Sung Tae Pyung. - Lee Dong Sook.
We promise to be happy.
Talk to Dong Jin for me.
He's seeing someone.
Dong Jin has a girlfriend?
Are you...