BioskopKeren
(Episode 34)
You spent too much on account of me.
Don't say that.
Nothing means more to me than you.
To me, you are...
most precious.
I'm way down the list.
I'd say I'm the fourth entry.
Thank you.
I'd only seen such rooms on TV.
I've never actually been inside a hotel before.
Did you see me put the card in the door?
You use this card to come in and turn on the lights.
If you ever have to go out, take this with you.
Don't leave without it.
Here you go.
Do you have to pay extra if I drink whatever is in the fridge?
Drink whatever you want.
I heard that you have to pay if you take something from the bar.
I paid for everything already.
You can eat what you want.
What?
Why did you pay in advance?
Who would eat all this?
Just eat what you want.
It would be a waste to leave stuff.
It's such a lovely room I doubt I'll be able to fall asleep.
Do you want me to stay and put you to sleep?
I was just kidding. I'll let you rest.
Wait.
Your ex-wife.
I think she still has feelings for you.
It's not that she misses me.
She can't stand being alone.
Forget everything she said.
I'm really leaving now.
I said I'm leaving.
You're so rude.
I paid for this lovely suite...
and you haven't thanked me.
You got the hint.
You're a smart Bucket Head.
Don't call me that. I almost forgot that nickname.
Okay. Goodnight.
What are you doing here?
We have business here.
Do you?
What else can you do here but sleep?
Think whatever you want.
I wasn't wrong about you.
You have nothing to give but your body.
That's what you're like.
Watch your tongue.
Forget about it. Don't let it get to you.
"Forget about it."
"Don't let it get to you."
That is unbelievable.
Take me to Hyoja-dong.
Not Pyeongchang-dong?
No. Take me to Hyoja-dong, please.
Okay.
It all worked out.
Let's see.
- We must pick a date. - Right.
- Rat, cow, tiger, rabbit... - Eight more come after that.
We already set the date. It's this Saturday.
This Saturday? What's with the rush?
Did you book a wedding hall already?
A friend of mine owns a café nearby.
I called him a while ago and rented the place for a day.
A café? Not a wedding hall?
Small weddings are trending these days.
It's all fine for you...
but it's Jun's first wedding. Don't you mind?
Why would I?
I have to buy a house, marry off Da Jeong...
and start saving up. I can't do what everyone else does.
We can invite our close friends and enjoy a lovely meal together.
He's grown up a lot.
- He has. - Mother.
It's me. Can you open the door?
Who's that?
It sounds like Hyo Joo.
You reek of alcohol.
Hello, Dong Sook.
What are you doing here?
I have something to tell your parents.
Father, Mother.
I'm here.
You had way too much to drink. You need to sober up.
If you came here so late at night...
it means you have important news.
What do you have to say?
Talk to Dong Jin for me.
What about?
He's seeing someone.
Dong Jin has a girlfriend?
If I must be brutally honest, they aren't actually dating.
She's using him.
Who is this woman?
It's someone you know.
You seem to know something.
Who is Dong Jin dating?
I didn't mean to say I know who she is.
I was trying to say that I was sure you'd know about it.
Why wouldn't you know about something like that?
What makes you think he's seeing someone?
My mum asked you a question.
I'm really sorry. Could you repeat the question?
Who is Dong Jin dating?
The woman he's dating is...
Gosh, the rice punch...
It's delicious. I want more.
Oh no!
I'm so sorry.
My bad.
Honey, wipe it up.
Shut her up, I mean wipe it up.
She's drenched.
What a mess.
She's so drunk she's about to pass out.
Dong Sook, help me take her inside.
I meant to help her.
She had too much to drink.
What a mess.
Someone should wipe the floor.
I meant to get some more punch and spilled hers.
- You're so careless. - I am.
Have some of mine.
Thanks.
Dong Jin will be furious when he finds out...
that we let Hyo Joo sleep over.
Hello?
It's me.
I can't believe you called me at this hour.
What's the occasion?
I didn't call because I wanted to.
Come over here and get your daughter.
Hyo Joo's over there?
She had too much to drink and passed out.
I thought she had more pride than to go over there.
She's in way too deep.
Come and get her.
It's too late to go over there.
Let her sleep with Dong Jin.
What kind of nonsense is that?
It'd be good...
to take this as an opportunity...
to help Hyo Joo and Dong Jin get back together.
What on earth are you talking about?
I think Hyo Joo...
still misses Dong Jin.
Let's just help the two of them...
get reunited.
If they reunite, it's their decision. But not like this.
Do whatever you want, then.
I'm tired, so I should go to bed now.
Hello? Hello?
What happened? Did Eun Sook hang up on you?
How dare she.
She's so rude. How can she hang up on me?
Hello?
Did I wake you up?
No.
- I was having a beer. - What?
You should have told me earlier if you wanted to drink.
I'm not drinking it because I want to.
It's free, you know. I don't want to waste it.
I see.
Liking freebies too much makes you go bald. Don't drink too much.
And don't open the door for anyone.
All right.
I'm not a kid.
In my eyes, you look like a three-year-old kid.
Don't drink too much and go to bed early.
Okay.
I'm home!
Dong Jin, come over to our room.
Okay, Dad.
She said she knows that she's at fault.
She kept apologising.
So you should also think about it again carefully.
She was your wife, you know.
It's not easy for two people to get married,
and completely ending the relationship is as hard.
It's already over, Dad.
We don't have any affection left for each other.
I don't think she feels that way.
I'm sure she's just saying it.
I should head over to my room.
Dong Jin.
By any chance,
are you seeing someone...
Never mind.
You must be tired. Wash up and go to bed.
Okay.
Do you think...
Dong Jin is seeing someone now as Hyo Joo said?
I don't know.
Let's not say anything to him...
and just observe the situation.
He's wise enough, and he can look after himself.
You literally insulted Tae Yang.
How can you drink the plum wine his mum made?
I never insulted him.
I just spoke the truth.
He'll figure out everything on his own,
so don't meddle in his business.
Is that why he is...
- working at the burger place? - Mum!
Madam Ko, Mr Min...
is here with the announcer, Choi Ji Yun.
- Put this away, please. - Yes, Ma'am.
Why did he bring her home at this late hour? What a nuisance.
Let Hyo Sang marry her.
You were dead against it until recently. What's gotten into you?
I want him to get married soon so that I can get married, too.
Goodness.
Mum.
Good to see you.
Have you been well?
Hello, Madam Ko.
What brings you here this late?
Hyo Sang and I went to a café for dessert...
and bought this delicious cake for you.
You should try it.
How do you expect me to eat cake at this hour?
You're so tactless.
My mum is on a diet all year long.
Gosh.
You have so much self-discipline.
I have huge respect for you.
Every time you open your mouth,
you butter me up like there's no tomorrow.
I'm not trying to butter you up.
I really mean it.
Mum,
spare me a second.
Have a seat.
I've been feeling this for a while now.
You're playing favourites.
You're nice to Tae Yang, and you even fixed dinner for him.
Why are you so cold to Ji Yun?
You try to embarrass her any chance you get.
She has a way with words because of her job as an announcer.
For some reason,
what she tells me doesn't sound sincere.
It just sounds like she's trying to flatter me.
You're judging her based on your biased viewpoint.
How did you and your boyfriend meet?
When he came to Meesa Apparel for a job interview,
I met him in the women's wash room.
In the women's wash room?
Yes. Some stuff happened.
So he was there for a job interview.
Does he work for Meesa Apparel now?
He used to work with me in the TF team,
but he resigned recently.
The TF team?
Do you want to see a photo of him?
- Sorry? Sure. - Just a second.
Ta-da!
Isn't he so handsome?
I... I think I forgot something at work.
I should get going now.
- Hello? - It's me, Ji Yun.
- What's up? - Meet me here now.
I'm at the café near the gosiwon.
I have no reason to meet you.
I'll wait until you come.
I didn't know that you were this vindictive and menacing.
- What are you talking about? - You got into Meesa Apparel...
to hover around me and even approached Hyo Sang's sister.
I can understand why you think that way,
but I didn't approach Hyo Won because of you.
My feelings for her have nothing to do with you.
Don't lie to my face.
You're being delusional, Ji Yun.
You don't mean anything to me any more.
I don't have time to do things just to get back at you,
so don't even worry...
and just go home.
Break up with her.
Break up with Hyo Won.
I like Hyo Sang,
so you dating his sister is just nonsense.
End it for me, please.
Are you telling me...
to give up on someone I love for your sake?
How can you think that you have the right to say such a thing?
- Tae Yang. - I love Hyo Won,
and I'll never break up with her.
So go ahead and break up with Mr Min if all of this bothers you.
How can you do this to me?
Why? Did you think...
that I'd always make sacrifices for you?
- Tae Yang. - I have changed.
So...
do not force me to comply with your unreasonable requests.
It won't work.
I cannot break up with Hyo Sang.
You're the one who will end up with a broken heart once again.
Hey, Hyo Won.
- What are you doing now? - Well...
I had to quickly meet up with someone I know. I just got in.
Why do you sound so down, though?
What do you mean?
You sound very upset.
- Did you have a fight with someone? - No, not at all.
Hyo Won.
Let's meet tomorrow. I have something to tell you.
Sure thing. You don't even need to ask me.
Tomorrow, the day after tomorrow and the day after that.
We'll meet every day, of course.
I'd love to stay right by your side 24 hours a day.
If you actually have to do that,
you'll get sick of me and run away.
Not a chance. That will never happen.
I should pester my mum to let my brother get married soon.
He has to go so that we can get married soon.
I want to marry you as soon as possible...
and have many babies with you.
I want our family to live happily.
What are you doing? Did you not hear what I just said?
"I also want an adorable daughter who looks just like you."
Shouldn't you be saying that?
Gosh, are you really not going to say anything?
I'd love to, of course.
It'll happen soon,
Honey.
I don't want Hyo Won to get hurt.
How should I tell her?
I'm just looking at you
I'm just waiting for an opening
- Sam Do. - Welcome to Wol...
Young Eun.
Nice to meet you.
I'm Han Gyu Sung and I study Business...
at the same college Young Eun goes to.
I heard a lot about you.
You must be her friend.
Yes. We met a few months ago...
through a mutual friend and we're dating now.
- Are you? - Young Eun said...
she wanted your permission and that's why we're here.
Please let me date Young Eun.
I'm in no position to do that.
I want to marry Young Eun and take her...
to America to study.
You'll marry her?
No, don't go, Young Eun.
What's he saying?
Don't go abroad, Young Eun.
Stay here with me in Korea.
Young Eun?
Is he dreaming of his first love?
How am I supposed to live without you?
You have Bok Sun Nyeo now.
Bok Sun Nyeo?
Don't go, Young Eun.
- Don't go. - Wake up!
Get a grip.
What do you think you're doing to someone who's asleep?
That's what I want to ask you.
What are you doing with Young Eun in your dream...
that makes you want to cry out?
Young Eun?
There's no way out.
I heard you loud and clear.
I have no recollection.
How could you call out your first love's name...
when your wife is sleeping right next to you?
Do you expect me to let you live?
- You misheard what I said. - I did not.
Hang on.
Have you been seeing Young Eun or Eun Young,
whatever the woman's called?
Now you're the one dreaming.
Why else would you dream of her and call her name?
Calm down, honey. Young Eun...
got married and went abroad with her husband.
I haven't met up with her...
or even seen her since then.
I haven't even talked to her.
- Is that true? - Of course it is.
This better not be a lie.
It's not.
Why did you dream of her?
Is she pretty?
Yes. I mean who?
The Young Eun or Eun Young woman.
Is she prettier than me?
If she were prettier, I'd have married her,
not you, wouldn't I?
I told you that...
you are my ideal woman. You're my dream woman.
You never said that.
Must I...
say things for it to be known?
A man speaks from the heart.
Don't you dare meet up with her even in your dreams, okay?
Okay.
Dream of me.
You bet I will.
Let's go back to sleep.
I'm sorry.
I was too drunk.
Do you want coffee?
No thanks.
What time...
did you come home last night?
Did you...
sleep with her?
It's none of your business.
Why isn't it?
I'm involved.
We're strangers now. It's over between us.
Not to me.
It's not over until I've had enough.
Stop being so stubborn.
I noticed that...
your mum doesn't seem to know yet.
Shall I tell her?
What happened to your pride?
Do you want to tattle now?
If she were to find out you're dating someone like her,
- she'd be so shocked. - I'll persuade her.
You shouldn't even care about these things.
You'll have to deal with Hong Gi Pyo first.
How do you know him?
I just happened to.
When he's released from prison...
that woman will abandon you.
- Get a grip. - You...
really have no clue.
Two people in love don't abandon each other.
You've never been in love, so you wouldn't know.
I don't want to ruin my morning by chatting with you.
You should go.
He's not in his right mind.
He's crazy.
Hyo Joo is home.
Your complexion changed overnight.
Did you have a good time with Dong Jin?
What do you mean?
You spend the night there.
I'm not as stuffed-up as you think.
It's okay to miss your ex-husband.
It wasn't like that.
You can't fool me.
Ms Choi called last night to tell me to pick you up.
I refused on purpose.
So you could have some fun.
Do you want me to meet up with her...
and see if she'll take you back?
You'll just make things even worse.
Leave me alone.
What?
Where are her manners?
You idiot.
Why did you go there and make a fool of yourself?
You're better than that.
I feel bad that she left without having any breakfast.
She had a lot to drink so her insides must be hurting.
Who? My sister-in-law?
Dong Sook, she isn't your sister-in-law.
Sorry. I'm so used to calling her that.
Don't let her in from now on.
Mum, we have an extra room, right?
Can Yun Shil stay there for a while?
Doesn't she have a place to stay?
She isn't able to go there at the moment.
What? Why not?
Gi Pyo's mum came over and insists on staying.
Yun Shil has nowhere to go.
What's that woman doing in Seoul?
She's trying to force Yun Shil to register the marriage.
Where is she staying right now?
At a 24-hour sauna, I think.
Oh dear.
Bring her over tonight.
It's terrible to have nowhere to go in the middle of winter.
You do that. I'll start cleaning the room after breakfast.
It'll be ready by tonight.
I have the morning off. I'll help you.
Sure.
- Did you sleep well? - Yes.
What's all this?
You said you already paid for everything in the fridge.
I'm taking what's left so I don't waste your money.
Why are you smiling?
I lied in case you wouldn't eat when you wanted to...
- just to save money. - What?
I can't believe you believed me.
I had no idea.
I stuffed myself with beer and noodles and snacks.
Is that why your face is so puffy?
- Really? - Yes. It looks like a balloon.
One small poke and it might even burst.
You're so mean.
You shouldn't deceive people.
It's fine if you enjoyed yourself. Consider it a fond memory.
Will you really take everything with you?
No.
No way.
You really packed everything.
You're greedier than you look.
You shouldn't leave behind what you paid for.
- This was here. - There's no end.
Her behaviour is so outrageous.
How can she occupy someone else's house and kick the owner out?
When I went upstairs this morning,
she even made a breakfast and ate it there.
It looked like she owns the house.
She's formidable.
What kind of person is she?
- Hello. - You're here.
I heard that you were kicked out of your house.
Well, that's what happened.
Then where did you sleep last night?
Dong Jin reserved a room in a hotel,
so I could sleep well.
- A hotel? - A hotel?
- It's not like what you think. - It's not like that.
Did I say something about that?
- I didn't say anything. - You didn't.
He didn't.
I just arranged a room at the hotel and went back home right away.
- What's wrong with that? - What he said is true.
All right, all right. No problem with that.
You slept in a hotel thanks to Dong Jin.
You enjoyed some luxury, Yun Shil.
By the way,
a hotel room must be very expensive.
You can't live there forever. What shall we do?
It might be little uncomfortable, but you can stay in my house.
I don't want to bother you.
I want you to stay with me,
but we can't do that as long as that woman is in the rooftop house.
Yun Shil!
Your mother-in-law is here.
What are you doing here?
I came to find my daughter-in-law who ran away.
- Why are you doing this to me? - I'm doing my job.
Excuse me, Ms.
This is not acceptable.
How can you occupy someone else's house and kick the owner out?
It's not someone else's house.
It's my son's house.
What nonsense!
How can you say that it's your son's house?
Yun Shil made a contract with me, and Yun Shil is paying the rent.
What belongs to my daughter-in-law also belongs to my son.
The money between spouses is not separable.
And you,
where did you stay last night?
Did you spend the night together?
It's none of your business whether we were together or not.
- What did you say? - You're disturbing the business.
Please leave the premise.
I won't leave here...
until Yun Shil...
registers the marriage with my son.
Do you understand?
Stop being ridiculous.
I told you I won't register the marriage with Gi Pyo.
All right.
We'll see who wins this game.
Hello, is this the police station?
This is Wolgyesu Tailor Shop.
What are you doing, you jerk?
I can't persuade you with my words.
I've no choice but to resort to the law.
What a cheeky fellow!
You seduced my daughter-in-law,
and now you even report me to the police?
I can't tolerate your behaviour any more.
If you keep entering my shop and disturbing my business,
You will have to pay for what you have done.
What did you say?
This is outrageous.
My goodness. You...
They are so vicious!
- Hello? - Mum, it's me.
Gi Pyo, my son!
How is Yun Shil doing?
She slept out last night.
She slept out?
She changed the door lock,
but I managed to go inside.
Then she yelled at me to go back to Anseong,
and went out of the house.
- How could she! - She has no feelings for you.
I guess she was with...
the president of that tailor shop,
the tall guy, last night.
I'll get both of them.
There are a lot of fish in the sea.
Gi Pyo,
- Let's put it behind us. - Mum!
Let's curse them and forget her.
You can find a better girl for you,
and make a new start.
Gi Pyo,
it's just between us,
but you didn't finish the wedding, and didn't register the marriage.
You're almost a stranger to Yun Shil.
There's no point to be obsessed with her.
I don't need any other girl except Yun Shil.
I'll go crazy if that punk takes Yun Shil from me.
All right, Gi Pyo.
I'll put everything back to the right place...
till you get out. Don't worry about it.
- Don't skip your meal, all right? - Mum.
Make sure you keep your eyes on her.
Don't miss anything.
Did you forget my nickname?
It's Anseong bulldog.
Sure. Talk to you later. Bye.
I don't know why he's so obsessed with...
a girl who doesn't like him.
What a fate.
My goodness.
Honey!
- What are you doing here? - You wanted to tell me something.
We'd better talk here than in the shop.
I see.
I almost forgot.
You should drink this.
- What's this? - It's oriental medicine for Mum.
It's very good for health.
Drink it, Tae Yang.
You shouldn't bring your mother's medicine here.
Mum takes other healthy stuff herself.
You should drink this,
and get healthier.
That's good.
How do you feel? Do you feel stronger?
I just had one, how can I feel that right now?
- Shall I give you one more? - No, it's enough.
Don't forget to take 1 pouch, 3 times a day.
I'm fine. Bring it back to your mother before she finds out.
Mum takes so many other things,
so she won't notice whether it's gone.
By the way,
What is the thing you wanted to tell me?
I have something to confess to you.
Something to confess to me?
I once told you,
I had met a girl before I met you.
Right.
Let me tell you something about her.
Are you going to see her again?
That's nonsense.
She has nothing to do with me.
You're the only girl for me now.
I swear.
I'm relieved.
Then what do you want to talk about her?
I feel like I'm deceiving you.
I think you must know who she is.
Don't say anything. I won't listen.
Please.
I don't want to know.
- Hyo Won. - It is what happened in the past.
Nothing good comes if I know who she is.
I'll compare myself with her,
and it will bother me.
Still I think you should know who she is.
Then Shall I tell you about the guy at the church I liked,
and the idol singer I liked when I was a high school girl?
It's different.
It's not different.
The past is the past.
I don't want to care about useless things.
I won't listen at all.
Wait a second.
- Hello. - May I talk to Kang Tae Yang.
I'm speaking.
This is producer Kim Min Su of ADTOWN, an advertisement agency.
An advertisement agency?
(Kim Min Su, Producer)
You modelled at the runway of Suit Tailoring Competition, right?
Yes, my acquaintance attended the competition,
so I modelled for amusement.
What's wrong?
I saw you at the satellite television.
You were impressive.
We're launching an advertisement.
I want to be a model for the paper advertisement.
My goodness.
Are you saying that Tae Yang will be a model?
He looks pure and innocent,
so I think he fits for the image of our new advertisement.
The advertiser also wants a model not well known to the public.
My goodness.
This is unbelievable.
It's unbelievable.
- It's unbelievable. - Hyo Won, Hyo Won.
I've never shot an advertisement before.
Don't feel pressured. We'll start with a paper advertisement first.
We'll pay you enough.
You'll pay me?
Sure. How can I ask you to work for nothing?
Then,
shall we talk about the guarantee?
Who is she?
Me? I'm Kang Tae Yang's manager and stylist.
I see.
Excuse me.
- Excuse me. - Coming, Madam Ko!
Well,
where is Doctor Oh's oriental medicine?
- Pardon? - It was in the kitchen yesterday.
Oh, that one.
Hoy Won took it...
said she would give to Tae Yang.
- What? - Mum, Mum, Mum!
You!
Hey,
where is Doctor Oh's oriental medicine?
I heard you gave it to Tae Yang.
- That's not important right now. - What?
Tae Yang will become a model.
What on earth are you talking about now?
Tae Yang will become a model?
He'll make his debut on magazines and newspapers.
- Are you serious? - Yes.
He'll sign the contract as soon as he gets off work...
and will get a camera test done.
So are you saying that he got picked up by an agency?
That's right. It's something like that.
Your future son-in-law will become a Korean wave star soon.
Korean wave star?
I'll give him all the support he needs...
and groom him into a global star.
Modelling for a mere advertisement won't make him a star.
Don't you think you're getting too ahead of yourself?
Whatever. I'm busy right now.
Why are you busy all of a sudden?
There are so many things I have to do to take care of Tae Yang.
I wanted to become a model when I was young.
If I was a little taller,
I would be enjoying worldwide fame right now.
I'm jealous of Tae Yang.
What an unexpected visit.
Why didn't you tell me anything?
I heard that Hyo Won...
is seeing Tae Yang.
How did you know?
Hyo Won told me when I was talking to her yesterday.
I couldn't get any sleep last night because my heart was racing so fast.
Don't worry.
Tae Yang and Hyo Won will not be able to get married.
Are you sure?
Have you ever seen me talking nonsense?
Their relationship will not work out.
I don't know why things keep getting complicated like this.
I'm really sorry, Hyo Sang.
So...
let's get married as soon as possible.
If that happens, they won't be able to do anything.
They'll just have to break up.
You guys are working so hard.
- Here. Have some tea. - Gosh, thank you.
Please have some tea.
How much longer will it take?
It's a small room, so it'll be done within an hour.
Please do a good job.
Of course.
She'll stay here only for a short while.
Why are you redoing the wallpaper as well as the floor?
It's a waste of money.
I want to make sure that the room is clean even if it's only for a day.
Redoing the wallpaper and floor doesn't cost as much as you think.
Gosh, this is such a hassle.
Look at all this dust.
Are you going to stay at the hotel again tonight?
I only stayed there last night because Mr Lee was worried.
I should sleep at the sauna today.
Gosh, you'll probably have to do this for a while. What a disaster.
I've never seen such a rude, nasty woman in my entire life.
Hello.
I'd like medicine for my headache.
Could you describe your headache for me?
I didn't get a good night sleep,
so my head is pounding, and it feels heavy.
Here you go.
I'll take this, too. It'll energise me.
Sure.
Shouldn't he be at work now? Where's he going all dressed up?
Honey...
I'm sorry.
Goodness.
Why does he care so much about his looks?
He has been acting suspicious lately.
Something is certainly fishy.
It almost looks like he's going on a blind date or something.
That man...
He's really acting suspiciously.
I'll make sure to catch him in action today.
Sun Nyeo is tailing you.
Stop. Do not turn around...
- and act natural. Walk slowly. - Okay.
Gosh, that bloke...
Where did he come from?
Sam Do, where are you going by the way?
I'll... I'll tell you later.
Okay. I think you should take a different route.
All right. Thanks, Tae Pyung.
Sam Do, are you cheating on Sun Nyeo?
No, not at all.
Let's talk about the details later.
You should go that way.
(Oh Young Eun Bakery)
What?
He got dressed up to the nines to come to a book store?
I must admit, he looks dashing.
I'll just sleep at the sauna today.
I felt like I was wearing an ill-fitting outfit...
the whole time I was in the hotel room.
I had trouble falling asleep, too.
All right. I knew you'd say that,
so I found a much better place for you to stay.
Gosh, it's really okay. I can sleep anywhere.
Goodness.
Just come with me.
You don't have to stay there if you don't like it.
- Really? - Yes.
I'm 100 percent sure that you'd like this place I'm about to show you.
Where is it?
You'll know when you see it. Let's go.
Why did you bring me here?
We have a room that's even better than a hotel room.
Come in.
Oh, watch your feet.
Do you like it?
How did you do this?
We used to use this room as a storage.
We just got the wallpaper and floor redone.
Nice, it's warm. Good.
- Dong Jin. - Don't worry.
My parents are also fine with you staying here.
Seriously?
We got this room ready in a rush, so it's not perfect,
but it'll be good enough to stay for a while.
Mr Lee, thank you so much.
Don't mention it. We're just letting you use the spare room.
I was actually quite worried about what to do.
Thank you very much.
You don't need to thank me.
Dong Jin is the one who cleaned mould off the walls...
and hired people to redo the wallpaper as well as the floor.
Ms Choi.
Thank you for your help.
Letting you use the extra room we have isn't a big deal.
- Yun Shil. - Yes.
You spend a lot of time with Dong Jin,
so you must know.
Pardon me? What do you mean?
Is Dong Jin...
seeing someone these days?
I'm not sure. I'm always focused on work, so I don't know if Dong...
I mean, I don't know anything about Mr Lee's private life.
Right. You probably don't know.
I think that he's seeing someone these days,
but he's keeping it all to himself, so I have no idea what's going on.
The tofu is slippery.
I'll help you, Mr Lee.
Thanks.
Yun Shil will make a good daughter-in-law.
Nonsense.
A lady like Yun Shil is hard to find.
She's diplomatic and loved by the elderly.
Shut your mouth and eat your food.
How can I eat with my mouth shut?
I need my mouth wide open to put food in it.
Just eat your food, Jun.
Okay.
How's the wedding preparation coming along?
What's there to prepare?
We'll just have a nice meal with our family.
Are you sure that's all you want?
Do you want me to find you a wedding hall?
There's no need to make a fuss.
Let's not make a hassle.
- Okay. - Okay.
Eat quickly.
Okay.
Do you need help?
Go back inside before Ms Choi sees you.
I think you'll be done faster if I help you.
You're going to give me a heart attack.
- Get out of here before she comes. - Fine.
I'll be waiting in your room. Don't make me wait too long.
I almost forgot.
- What's wrong with you? - Fine. I'm going.
Okay.
That should do it.
I'm so tired.
This moment where Dong Jin is resting on my lap...
feels like a story from a fairy tale.
I'm worried that...
this moment of happiness might fly away like the bluebird.
I am happy,
but at the same time, I'm not at ease.
There's no need to feel that way.
Our fairy tale...
will most definitely have a happy ending.
It's coming together nicely.
How much longer do I have to wait?
It's almost done. Don't come in.
It looks good.
I'd go to the wedding if it wasn't for the deadline for the coat.
I'll say.
It's too bad that you can't come.
Did you wash all the containers?
I did.
Thanks for doing this.
I should have tailored your wedding suit.
My eyesight's gotten worse.
I'm sorry about that.
Don't be.
I have you to thank for everything.
Please take good care of Dong Sook and Da Jeong.
Don't worry, Father.
I'll support the two ladies...
with all my heart and soul.
Thank you.
We should get going or we'll be late.
What about Sam Do and Dong Jin?
They left already.
They must be busy preparing things.
Let's go, Mr Lee and Ms Choi.
Okay.
What a handsome groom.
Please look after the house.
I will. Don't worry.
After you.
Wedding halls are nice, but a place like this...
would be nice, too.
Yes. It's much more cosy and romantic.
Should we get married in a place like this later on?
What is it? Do you not want to?
I do.
You just promised me that you'll marry me.
I guess that means...
I won't have to propose to you.
That's not right.
Do you want to make it official? Fine, then.
You're a greedy person.
I didn't mean it like that.
I get it. I'll do it.
The wedding ceremony will begin shortly.
Please be seated.
We will now begin...
the wedding ceremony between the groom, Sung Tae Pyung...
and the bride, Lee Dong Sook.
There will be a groom entrance.
Will the groom please come forward?
Now, there will be...
a bride entrance.
Please give her a big round of applause.
Will the bride please come forward?
Mister.
The groom and bride will now bow to each other.
Bow.
There will be a wedding pledge between the two.
I, Sung Tae Pyung,
take Lee Dong Sook as my wife.
I pledge to be a loving husband and love her consistently.
I will protect my wife...
and our daughter, Da Jeong, from hardship and suffering.
I pledge to be a reliable husband and father.
I, Lee Dong Sook,
take Sung Tae Pyung as my husband.
I pledge to be...
a wise wife who trusts and respects her husband.
- We pledge to our family... - We pledge to our family...
- and everyone who cares for us. - and everyone who cares for us.
- Sung Tae Pyung. - Lee Dong Sook.
We promise to be happy.
The father of Lee Dong Sook...
will recite the wedding announcement.
Sung Tae Pyung and Lee Dong Sook...
stand in front of us...
formed a family.
I'd like to represent...
everyone in this room...
and declare them...
husband and wife.
It's hard to open my eyes
It's taller than the mountain
The sky makes me feel pleasant
On a holiday morning
A phone call wakes me up
Where should we go
And what should we do today?
A gentle breeze
Blows on the window
I can feel love
I can feel love in the wind
In the world where I met you
I have no more wishes
Being wishful would be a sin
You scared me.
I've been your fan ever since I was at school.
It melts in my mouth.
To be honest, I'm touched.
You're the only person...
to have faith in me and encourage me.
I won't ever forget this...
until the moment I die.
You love me.
I do love you.
The reason I love you
The reason I dream
Is you
In this world I'm living in
During my whole life
Nothing will be better than you
On December
On one
Fine day
I love you, Dong Sook.
It's so cold.
What should I have for dinner today?
I hope Yun Shil comes home early today.
The bride will now throw the bouquet.
One, two, three.
Who wants to catch mine?
Nice.
I'll take the picture now.
Hyo Won.
What are you doing here, Ms Ko?
I heard you have a camera test today.
- Yes. - You're a model, after all.
We can't let you take the bus there.
- I'll give you a ride. - Pardon?
For now, my mum will be your road manager.
I'll be your stylist.
I'm just trying out for the job because it pays well.
All the Korean Wave stars and top celebrities...
started like this at first.
I'm nothing like a Korean Wave star.
I liked the impression you left when I first saw you.
I knew that I have a good eye for noticing people.
Didn't you say that his looks won't pay the bills?
Be quiet.
Wait.
We should get going before we're late.
Okay.
Get in, Honey.
I feel too uncomfortable right now.
There's no need to feel that way.
What about me?
You can sit in the front.
What is it?
You don't have to give me money.
It's not money.
What's this, Sam Do?
It's a love potion.
Isn't this what old people take when they go mountain climbing?
I'm still young to be taking these.
You can keep them.
I can tell that you need it.
Consider it an advice from a life coach.
I said it's fine. Have it your way, then.
Where are you going for honeymoon?
We're going to go for a drive in Yangpyeong...
and stay the night at a hotel.
Thanks for lending me your car.
Don't mention it. Drive safely.
Off you go.
You'll regret it later if you don't go on a honeymoon trip.
When we make lots of money,
we'll go on a trip along with all the family members.
Let's do that.
Where's your grandmother?
She went to the bathroom.
Why is the house so far from here?
They say you'll run into your worst enemy at the worst time and place.
Look who it is.
Go on.
- Drive safely. - I'm jealous.
Hold on.
Have a nice trip.
Stop right there.
What are you doing here?
Move aside. I have nothing to say to you.
I've been meaning to tell you of something.
(The Gentlemen of Wolgyesu Tailor Shop)
How can you do this to us on this wonderful day?
Don't you think this is too harsh?
We were to go through this at least once, so brace yourself.
I'm really sorry. I don't know what to say.
If we show her how sincere we are, she will eventually take our side.
Don't you have any special plans for Christmas Eve?
What are you doing? Why are you dressed like that?
Who is that? Surely, it's Sam Do.
Where do I know that lady from?
Don't you have anything to say? Are you not hiding anything from me?
I'm sorry?