Bioskopkeren
(Episode 35)
Why is the house so far from here?
They say you'll run into your worst enemy at the worst time and place.
Look who it is.
Go on.
- Drive safely. - I'm jealous.
Bye.
Hold on.
What are you doing here?
Move aside. I have nothing to say to you.
I've been meaning to tell you of something.
Do you remember me?
I'm afraid I don't. Who are you?
I'm Yun Shil's mother-in-law.
I saw you at her wedding.
I remember. How are you?
What brought you here?
You can talk to me.
Are you worried because I'm talking to your father?
Excuse me.
Don't make any trouble here.
- You can talk to me. - Let me go!
A father should know what his son does.
Is she talking about Dong Jin?
Ms Choi will be shocked if she comes out and see this.
Da Jeong, go and keep Ms Choi inside.
- What? - Hurry!
All right.
- Let's get her into the car first. - Sure.
What on earth is she talking about?
Well, father...
I can explain to you precisely.
Your son and my daughter-in-law are...
- You can talk to us. - Let me go!
- Get in the car, Dong Sook. - All right.
Let me go!
- Let me go! - All right.
What's going on?
Don't worry, Mr Lee. We'll take care of her.
We are leaving, Father.
Take care, Dad!
Tell me the truth.
What are you hiding from me?
Let me go. Are you crazy?
What are you doing?
You're kidnapping me.
It's not kidnapping.
Take her to the tailor shop, Tae Pyung.
All right.
By the way, what were you trying to tell Dad?
Your brother and my daughter-in-law are...
going out together.
What?
Dong Jin and Yun Shil?
I don't believe it.
I said the same thing just like you, Dong Sook.
But what she says is true.
What?
Stop the car now! I'll report to the police.
We're almost there. Wait for a minute.
Stop the car now! What are you doing?
Calm down, Ms. You might cause a car accident.
- What are you doing? - Stop the car.
- Let me go. - Stop her!
(Wolgyesu Tailor Shop)
How can you make such a trouble at other people's party?
That's too much.
My son Gi Pyo is having such a hard time at the prison.
I can't pull punches.
Mr Lee and Ms Choi are old and not healthy.
What if they collapse after listening to what you say?
it's not my fault. They should have controlled their son.
It's their fault.
I feel like I'm talking to a wall.
By the way, where does Yun Shil stay?
Is she living with that president guy or something?
How can you say that?
Both Dong Jin and Yun Shil are not such people.
Whatever.
What's his address?
I should meet his parents and have it out with them right away.
Who do you think you're talking to?
Would you tell me his address if you were me?
Let me tell you once again.
I won't just stand by and do nothing if you tell Mr Lee and Ms Choi.
My husband used to be good at fistfight.
Are you threatening me?
Yes, I am threatening you.
You'd better not do anything that you will regret later.
I'm tired.
Yun Shil, thank you for your effort making the food.
I didn't do much.
What are you talking about?
You got up early in the morning and made all the food.
I should go inside and take some rest.
Aren't you going inside?
You must be tired. You can take a rest first.
I have to talk to Dong Jun.
All right.
My goodness.
- I'll go inside, too. - Sure.
Dong Jin, let's talk in your room.
All right.
Don't worry.
What shall I do?
You were surprised, right?
It should be a lie if I say I'm not surprised.
I'm sorry I haven't told you first.
I was going to tell you after I sort things out.
Yun Shil is a good girl,
but I haven't thought her to be a family member.
I thought a lot before I made a decision, Dad.
You are a special child to your mum.
As you would expect, it won't be easy to get your mum's consent.
- I know. - Your situation is different...
from that of your sister's.
I understand.
I will take it seriously myself.
I'm sorry that I troubled you when you're not well.
Let's keep it a secret to your mum for now.
I can tell her only after I make a decision myself.
I agree with you.
Don't get me wrong.
I'm not saying that I don't like Yun Shil.
I'm saying that we should talk about this...
after thinking about it for enough time.
I understand.
Where's Gi Pyo's mother?
Well...
I managed to send her back.
I'm not sure how long she can keep quiet.
She asked where you're staying,
and whether you're living with Dong Jin.
- We had such a hard time. - I'm sorry.
You don't have to be sorry.
Where are Mr Lee and Dong Jin?
They are talking in his room.
I guess Mr Lee noticed.
I think he did.
It should happen anyway.
You should steel your heart.
I will.
It's me. Can I come in?
Sure, come in.
Is Mr Lee angry?
I think he's rather confused, not angry.
He said he would think it over.
He's not well.
I feel so sorry.
If we show him that we're sincere,
he will be on our side.
So, let's focus on ourselves. Okay?
By the way, you caught that bouquet.
It's bad luck if you don't get married in six months.
We should hurry.
It can't be common for...
a couple to catch the bouquet together.
It must be a lucky sign, so...
Don't waver.
Leave my mum to my dad.
Why won't you answer?
- I will. - At times like this...
we must work together.
Don't get distracted, okay?
Oh, right.
- Hello? - It's me, Tae Yang.
I left in a hurry that I didn't get to say bye.
I was worried because you left without eating.
Is something wrong?
No. I recently got a new part-time job and...
it's all the way in Gangnam.
Why do you sound downcast?
Is something wrong?
I can't tell you over the phone. Let's meet up one day.
Did you and Dong Jin argue?
No, we didn't.
Okay, then. I'll call you after work.
Bye.
- This is the current trend. - I see.
- He has to stand out. - Like that.
Hello. How are you?
Hyo Won.
Honey.
Why are you here?
- Hello. - Hello.
We were discussing today's shoot with the photographer.
- Pardon? - I've never seen...
such hands-on manager and stylist team.
A manager and stylist?
Why are you here?
I wanted to come alone but Mum insisted on tagging along.
I had no choice.
Sorry, Tae Yang.
You should be grateful I'm here.
If you have someone with my gravitas around,
they won't take you too lightly.
When you signed the contract...
I got you 300 dollars more, didn't I?
Of course I'm grateful for that.
Keep being grateful.
I'm not here because I'm free.
You're here because you were bored.
What did you say?
- Sorry. - Let's begin.
- Tae Yang, get your make-up done. - Okay.
I'll go and get my make-up done.
Don't worry about us. Go and get dolled up.
See you in a bit.
Don't slather too much make-up on him.
Make it look as natural as possible.
Kang star's appeal is his natural look.
"Kang star"?
People on TV...
say things like "so-and-so star".
You're helpless.
Will you just keep quiet?
Don't make things harder for him.
Making certain demands helps them decide what to do.
You used to work. Shouldn't you know the basics?
I guess...
this is why your staff ignored you.
Mum!
- Sorry. - Sorry.
Sorry.
I'm sorry.
Okay. I'm loving this.
This time...
I want you to hold your left hand at the back of your neck.
Okay, that's great. Please look at the camera.
That's it. Now look into the distance.
Good. Now look at the camera.
Give us a smile, to the camera.
Kang star.
Try to look more at ease.
You look way too stiff.
Loosen up a bit.
Smile with the corners of your mouth.
No, that looks fake.
Smile naturally, like you're greeting...
customers at the hamburger place.
"Welcome. What can I get for you?"
Yes, that's more like it.
Be quiet, Mum.
I got frustrated.
Let's continue.
Just a moment.
Your make-up needs fixing.
Hey.
Now you look pretty.
His make-up needed fixing. Sorry.
- Let's continue. - Kang star.
- Good luck. - Good luck.
Get the stool and put a foot on it.
That's it. That's perfect.
Put your leg on it and glare at the camera.
What is wrong with you?
You're so stiff. You look like a robot.
Do this.
Can't you even pose? Try harder.
No, that's not it.
Look at me.
Now you try.
Stretch.
Wait. Let me fix his make-up a bit more.
- Honey. - Stretch.
Hold this.
Get out of here!
- Us? - Us?
I can't get anything done.
If you don't get out of here, this shoot is cancelled.
- What did we do to upset him? - I don't know.
Get out of here!
Good luck, honey.
Get out!
My goodness.
Don't set foot out of this room.
I knew this would happen.
You aren't the photographer. You went too far.
Why did you keep retouching his make-up?
You aren't an expert.
Is this my fault?
Is it mine, then?
It's Hyo Sang.
Hello, son.
- Where are you? - Me?
I'm...
in town to meet a friend.
Which friend?
- Sook Ja. - Sook Ja flew in from Toronto.
Didn't she come by last month?
Is she back again?
Tell me the truth. You aren't with her, are you?
- Don't tell him. - Okay, son.
I'll see you at home.
Mum. Hello?
Hello? Mum?
Who is she with that she can't talk to me about?
Hang on. Is she with Tae Yang?
Does your mum spend time with him?
Yes, I think so.
She seems to like him.
That's impossible.
He lacks everything that your mum would like in a man.
That's exactly my point.
What does she and Hyo Won...
see in that jerk?
Why did you like him way back then?
Hyo Sang.
I'm sorry.
I got too excited.
Sorry if I upset you.
It's fine.
- Are you done? - I've had enough.
Have you lost your appetite?
I had too much rich food this afternoon.
- I think I feel bloated. - Do you want an antacid?
No thanks.
Where are you going? It's cold outside.
I want to get some fresh air.
Finish your meal and don't worry about me.
Does he feel unwell?
You didn't eat much. Have some warm rice water instead.
Thanks.
Thank you.
I'm sorry.
I feel bad that I became...
an ungrateful brat...
who took advantage of you.
You're not a brat.
You can't control who you fall in love with.
But then every human being...
has a position or opinion.
Let's take some time to think.
Okay.
Are you upset?
No. You're very right.
Don't take it the wrong way.
We treated you like you were our own,
but we never imagined you as Dong Jin's spouse.
We were taken off-guard.
Let's give it some time.
Yes, Sir.
Go on inside.
Okay.
It's cold out here, so don't stay out too long.
I won't.
Where are you off to?
I forgot that a customer said he'd come by for a fitting.
- What about dinner? - I'm not hungry.
I'll have some bread...
I'll have some cup noodles at the store if I feel hungry.
See you.
Wait.
You're too dressed up...
- for someone going to the store. - What?
Should I greet a customer in a tracksuit, then?
Stop nitpicking, okay?
There's no need to yell.
No tailor's wife should say what you said.
You lack the basic knowledge.
Okay, fine, go.
I might be late.
Don't wait up.
Why is he so clumsy? Does he have tremors?
He's been petty lately.
Must I eat alone?
That's so heavy.
Sam Do.
To the kitchen, right?
Yes.
- Can I do anything else for you? - No thanks.
Who is he, Mum?
He's an old friend from my childhood.
Say hello.
Hello.
I remember seeing you when you were asleep.
You haven't seen me yet.
No.
Shall we shake hands?
It must be great to have a son.
He's a young man.
I'll go inside to clean up.
You're great at drawing.
Who is that?
My dad.
Your dad?
Why did you draw a black ribbon?
That's his photo.
- What? - It's the photo...
we had at his funeral.
I don't think we should be at a motel on our honeymoon.
We'll only stay for one night and a hotel's too expensive.
We need to save up.
You're right, but we'll have only one honeymoon in lifetime.
This is not romantic at all.
Romance isn't good for anything.
We have to save up as much as we can.
We'll end up with nothing if we do what everyone else does.
I'm the one to blame.
Who cares if we stay at a hotel or a motel?
Anywhere I am with you is paradise to me.
How about you?
I feel the same.
Then stop grumbling and come inside.
I was up since dawn and the stress has drained me completely.
It's not the greatest of settings, but I'll serve you...
the best I can, Madam.
Just a moment.
Let's go inside.
Okay.
- There's no room? - There's no room?
We're full.
How can such a large motel not have one empty room?
Tomorrow's Christmas eve.
Did you expect us to have a room on a Friday evening?
What should we do?
Let's try another motel.
You can try, but you won't have any luck.
There is one VIP suite...
How much for a night in that suite?
300 dollars.
- 300 dollars? - 300 dollars?
That room's only free because someone cancelled...
at the last minute.
Forget it if you aren't interested.
Someone else will snap it up right away.
My goodness. This is daylight robbery.
Shouldn't we report him?
Let's go.
We'll call the police outside.
I can't believe he tried to overcharge us.
What kind of a motel charges 300 dollars for a night?
A Friday before Christmas eve is a peak holiday.
Even so, this is too much.
I saw another motel on the way here.
Let's try that one.
You wait here.
I'll ask if they have a room.
Okay.
Hello?
I was too curious to wait.
- Are you at the hotel? - What?
Of course we are.
- We just arrived. - What about dinner?
We went to a famous beef rib restaurant on the way.
We had a huge meal.
I'm glad to hear that. What is Tae Pyung doing?
Tae Pyung?
He went in to take a shower.
What happened to Dong Jin and Yun Shil?
I don't think Grandma knows.
Only Grandpa knows.
I still can't believe that Dong Jin and Yun Shil are in love.
Neither can I.
It looks like my dear mum's about to get the shock of her life.
I'll have to call you back.
Okay. Enjoy your honeymoon.
I will. Thanks.
How did it go?
They're full as well.
That's terrible.
Let's find another motel before it gets too late.
Shall we?
Take those off. I'll do it.
It's fine. I'm almost done.
You cooked since dawn today. You need to go and rest.
Get out before your mum sees us and starts another row.
She fell asleep already.
Give me those.
I really don't mind.
But I do.
I'll finish up. Go to your room and rest.
What are you doing?
You're up early.
I got thirsty. Maybe the dinner was salty for me.
What are you doing wearing rubber gloves?
Since Yun Shil must be tired making all the food from early morning,
I will do the dishes.
Take off the rubber gloves.
Men do kitchen work nowadays, Mum.
Don't talk rubbish.
Take off the gloves and give them to me.
I can do the dishes, Ms Choi.
What are you doing, Dong Jin? Go and do your own business.
All right, Mum.
I'm sorry, Ms Choi.
I will do it.
Even if Dong Jin says he will help you since he feels sorry,
you shouldn't let him do so, Yun Shil.
Until the present,
I haven't asked him to do any housework.
Then, how can you...
make my son wear the rubber gloves, Yun Shil?
I didn't ask him...
I'm sorry, Ms Choi.
You should be careful yourself if you want to stay in this house.
In the tailor shop,
you cannot help being friendly because of work.
You should draw a line in the house, though.
You should keep your private life and public life separate.
I'll keep that in mind.
I don't want Dong Jin...
to be gossiped because of useless misunderstanding.
I won't allow it even if it's concerned with you, Yun Shil.
Do you know what I mean?
I do.
- Mum is doing too much. - Wait.
A man should not intervene in women's matter.
You should be careful when you're with your mum.
I will.
I should have met his parents,
lay bare the truth and distinguish between right and wrong.
Damn it!
By the way, where is Yun Shil hiding?
- Hello? - This is Min Hyo Joo.
It's you. How have you been?
I called you to give you some good news.
Good news?
It seems that you can see your son by next month.
My goodness.
- Is that true? - Yes.
I talked to the lawyer a minute ago.
Are you saying that Gi Pyo...
will be released next month?
Yes. It's almost certain.
Thank you so much.
How can I repay you?
I don't need such words.
You should control your daughter-in-law instead.
She left home.
- What do you mean she left home? - After listening to what you said,
I made a decision and came to Seoul.
Then I found out that she ran left home.
Did she run away from home?
She must have moved in with that tailor shop owner.
She doesn't come home at all.
What?
You're back.
I'm tired.
You're home, Mother.
- You're here. - Where have you been until now?
I talked you on the phone that I would meet Sook Ja.
You met aunt Sook Ja of Toronto?
Sure.
Sure? I just talked aunt Sook Ja on the phone just now.
- What? - She's doing very well in Toronto.
My goodness.
Did I tell you that I was with Sook Ja?
I must be so old that I say wrong things.
I didn't meet Sook Ja. I met Sook Hee.
Maybe it's a menopausal symptom.
My mouth has a hard time keeping up with my brain.
Are you telling the truth?
What's wrong with you? What if I'm not telling the truth?
Stop it, Hyo Sang.
By the way,
what are you doing here?
Tomorrow is Christmas Eve.
I came to pay your respects.
I see.
What are you going to do tomorrow?
Ji Yun wants to see a movie.
We'll have a meal together and watch a movie.
It should be fun.
Can I join?
You're going too far.
Tomorrow is not just any day. It's Christmas eve.
You shouldn't join us tactlessly.
It was a joke.
You don't expect me to be that tactless, do you?
You're right.
It was just a joke, wasn't it?
I was worried that you might have meant it.
I don't think it's a bad idea...
that she joins us, Hyo Sang.
You're so weird.
- What? - I clearly said it was a joke.
I just...
Ji Yun was worried that you might be lonely.
- Why do you get angry? - No.
Stop it.
I'm so upset.
I said that because I care for her.
I don't know why she looks on me with a jaundiced eye.
She's not angry with you.
She's angry at me.
Do you want to spend Christmas Eve with Mum?
Does she have any special plan?
I don't know,
but it's our first Christmas Eve together.
How can we spend it with Mum? It will be a damp squib.
Why will it be a damp squib?
I can't let that happen.
We should have a romantic Christmas Eve...
just the two of us.
Would you go on an overnight skiing trip?
I don't know how to ski.
Then we can just go on an overnight trip to any place near.
I have a part time job.
We can leave after you're done with your part time job.
I will reserve a hotel room.
- A hotel room? - Let's...
spend our bridal night.
I thought you're innocent, but you're cheeky.
We can't stay out overnight, just the two of us.
I think you don't love me, Kang Tae Yang.
My friends' boyfriends...
pester them to go on a trip.
How can you reject when I ask you to go on a trip?
To trust each other,
we need to get know each other for enough time.
Before I set up conditions that I can love you responsibly,
I won't act hastily.
I promised that to Mother.
Since I'm confident that I will love you for a long time,
I don't want to rush about our relationship.
We can go on a trip anytime.
Instead, I will treat you big tomorrow.
I earned the greatest deal of money in my life today.
You'd better be prepared.
I will let you spend all the money you made today.
We should have a room-warming party.
A room-warming party?
Ta-da.
Let's have a nice room-warming party later,
and drink beer today.
Here we go.
Don't get upset about...
what my mum said.
I apologise instead.
She said what she had to say from her stance.
She objected my sister's marriage so much,
but she consented at the end.
So let's not be discouraged.
it's different from Dong Sook's case.
Both my sister and I are Mum's children.
When I saw my sister getting married today,
I envied her all the more.
When I get off from work every night, I can sit here,
talk about daily life and all with you while drinking beer.
It would be so nice.
It will be nice for us,
but what about Mr Lee and Ms Choi?
Every mum in the world...
feels happy when her child is happy.
It won't be easy.
If I were Ms Choi,
I won't just feel happy...
if I had a good and dear son like you.
Come to think of it,
you always end up talking about me.
Stop it. I'm very serious right now.
I know my mother better than you do.
She'll give us her blessing because she wants me to be happy.
Here.
It's almost 10. Where is he?
The person who have reached is currently unavailable.
What? Why is he not answering his phone?
(Wolgyesu Tailor Shop)
What? The lights are off.
(My Love Sam Do)
The person who have reached is currently unavailable.
He isn't at the shop and he isn't answering his phone.
Where is this punk?
Who is that?
I'm sure it's Sam Do.
Where have I seen her before?
What is he doing with her after lying about going to the shop?
Why those...
No.
I need to wait until I have conclusive evidence.
After he finally got his doctorate and a job at a university,
I thought things were finally going to pick up,
but he died in an accident one rainy day.
I must have no luck.
What do you mean?
He suffered in a foreign land, just studying,
and then died.
I thought you were doing well in the US,
but that happened.
While I was supporting my husband,
I learned how to bake in a community class.
That's why I opened a bakery once I returned to Korea.
I see.
I couldn't contact you,
but you were always in the corner of my heart.
That's why I opened a bakery in Hyoja-dong,
where I had memories with you.
I know I can't do much,
but I'll stop by the bakery often and look after Seung Woo, too.
Please come to the bakery with your wife.
I always wondered what she was like.
What?
Okay, sure.
We're here. Give him to me.
No, I'll take him in.
I haven't unpacked yet, so it's messy.
It's embarrassing.
Hey, what do you have to be embarrassed about?
When you were young,
you even peed in front of me.
That's right.
When I first got to the orphanage, I couldn't adjust and peed in bed...
every night and got in trouble.
The director made you go around asking for salt.
- Do you remember? - I do.
You always wore the winnowing basket...
and borrowed the salt for me.
That's right. I did.
That was funny.
He can't stop smiling.
That punk is definitely having an affair.
But where did I see her before?
My head.
(Motel)
What happened?
They don't have a room either.
Let's go back to the first motel...
You want to sleep in a 300-dollar room?
We have no choice.
I refuse to be cheated.
And even if we go,
there's no guarantee the room is available.
That's true.
Are you hungry?
Let's eat that.
(Eatery)
- Hello. - Hello.
That looks good.
How much this?
It's 6 dollars for 1, 12 dollars for 2.
We'll take two.
You want two?
We're on our honeymoon. We should splurge this much.
What? Is it a waste of money?
Of course, not. We'll take two.
Okay. Pick the ones you want.
Okay.
The bottom ones must be nervous. They're sweating.
What about that one on top?
The way it's hanging there, all shameless and arrogant,
annoys me. Let's eat it.
- Okay. - We'll take that one...
and the little one on the right.
- This one? - Yes.
Give us a lot of radish, too.
Okay. Just a minute.
That looks good.
Look at that.
It looks good.
I've never had such delicious chicken before.
Me neither. It melts in your mouth.
This is an emotional and happy feast.
Let's just...
eat this and go back home.
Go home?
What is there to a honeymoon?
I got to go on a drive with you all day long today.
That's enough for me.
Still, you'll regret it for years to come.
Why would I regret it?
We made memories that we will never ever forget.
Give me a minute.
Keep eating.
Why did you bring your guitar?
We may be out on the street because there are no motels available,
but It's our first night as a married couple.
We need to do something special.
Sir, may I sing a song?
That would be great.
Thank you.
"Susanna's Handkerchief", which brought us together.
Let me sing that for you.
When I looked at you, my blindingly beautiful you
I used to cry in quiet
Then, without saying a word
you would hand me a small handkerchief
One day, you asked me
To leave you before the end comes
You said you wanted me to see you only while you were beautiful
You said to leave you there
Susanna
I will stay
By your side
I won't let go of your hands
We will be
Happy together
I love you forever
Don't cry alone any more
Even if life separates us
Even if the world hates us
I will protect you
With every ounce of strength that I have
I love you
Susanna
I will stay
By your side
I won't let go of your hands
We will be
Happy together
I love you forever
Don't cry alone any more
Don't think too much, and go to sleep.
Worrying won't change anything.
Okay.
Let's be positive.
Who would have thought we'd be living...
under the same roof?
But we are living under the same roof,
and soon enough, we will be in the same room.
I don't want to go.
It's even harder to leave you since we're in the same house.
I feel like this room is 10km from my room.
Yun Shil.
May I just sleep here and go to my room...
- early in the morning? - What?
Don't be so gross.
What are you imagining?
I just wanted to sleep here.
Were you...
What improper thing were you imagining?
What do you mean? I did no such thing.
Just go to bed.
Okay. Good night.
What are you doing in there?
Yun Shil is kind and talented.
She's a great catch.
Yes, well,
she and Dong Jin weren't a good fit at first and fought,
but now, they are a great fit and get along well.
If you had a daughter-in-law like her,
you wouldn't have to worry.
Please stop Dong-jin.
From what?
He has a new woman.
Who is she?
You know her, too.
No way. It couldn't be.
What am I imagining?
Oh, my gosh. Who is this?
Good morning.
Why are you coming out from there?
Never mind. It's complicated.
Also, I think this is the medicine that you take.
Take it when you need it.
- Didn't you go on your honeymoon? - Well...
Wait.
Good morning to you, too.
Look who's here.
Good morning.
Why are you here? Didn't you go on your honeymoon?
Let's talk downstairs.
We were about to greet Mum and Dad anyway.
We're back.
Goodness, Dong Sook. You are so you.
Of all the place to skimp out.
You wanted to save on motel cost...
and came back without having your first night.
I never knew she was so determined.
The family grew, so we should tighten our belts.
Goodness. I'm so upset.
Anyway, welcome back.
Good times will come if you work hard.
Yes, Father.
Goodness. Goodness.
I'll do that.
It's okay.
I'll prepare breakfast.
Get ready for work.
I can do both without being late.
I'm too tired to talk, so don't talk to me and do as I say.
Okay. I will.
Yun Shil.
Yes?
Never mind.
Go and get ready for work.
Okay.
You must have worked late at the shop last night.
Yes.
I had to finish up a suit...
and some alterations.
I see.
- I'll see you. - Okay.
Wait until I catch you.
You're dead.
- Are you waiting for Yun Shil? - Yes, I am.
Hey.
If my wife asks you...
if I worked late last night, tell her I did.
What do you mean?
You've been acting suspicious lately.
What do you mean? There's a situation, that's all.
You know I can't lie.
- If you're doing something... - Hey, hey. It isn't like that.
Then why are you telling me to lie to her?
Hi. I'll go ahead. Take your time.
Let's go.
My daughter-in-law left home.
She must have moved in with that tailor shop owner.
She doesn't come home at all.
She wouldn't have. No way.
They wouldn't be living together.
- Mother. - Hello?
- Are you busy? - No, I'm not busy.
Then...
can you come to the house?
Right now?
Mother.
I hope you weren't busy.
Even if I am, I should come running if you want to see me.
I brought your favourite sweet potato cake.
Have it with Father later.
Thanks. Let's sit.
Okay.
How pretty.
Are you going out on a date with your boyfriend?
Of course. It's Christmas Eve.
I wish you a merry Christmas
Mum.
- What are you doing? - What?
What are you wearing?
Well.
I figured I shouldn't look old, if I'm hanging out with young kids.
So I dressed up a little.
A little?
- What do I do with you? - Hey.
We'll be late.
- Let's hurry. - Wait.
Are you really coming with us?
You said Tae Yang said the three of us should eat together.
Today is Christmas Eve.
That's why I have to tag along.
What if you get carried away...
and do something bad?
I need to stand guard.
We're heading out.
- See you later. - Yes, Ma'am.
- Merry Christmas. - Have fun.
This is insane.
Darn it.
Did you want to talk about something?
Just...
who is Dong Jin dating?
Sorry?
You know.
Who is she?
I have an inkling,
but I want to be sure.
Tell me.
Who is she?
She works...
at the tailor shop.
What?
I'm going to Jeil Department Store.
Okay.
Aren't you doing something special? It's Christmas Eve.
Of course, we are.
I'll be back before we close. Let's have dinner together.
- Okay. - I'll see you.
Okay.
Enjoy your meal.
Hello...
Mother.
Honey.
I'm sorry for surprising you.
Do you also...
find me embarrassing?
No, not at all.
Do you have to work more?
I'm almost done.
Okay.
I wanted to come alone. I'm sorry.
Both mother and daughter are so unpredictable.
I'm not that bad.
You better watch out, You better not cry
It looks great.
I was worried because I hadn't made a coat in a while,
but it came out nicely.
It looks warm.
(Wolgyesu Tailor Shop, Maestro)
The label is different.
Yes. Dong Jin and I discussed it and decided to create a new line.
We modified the traditional line...
and made it more natural and active.
We should make one for Mr Lee.
I didn't think of that. We should make one for him.
Hello?
Yun Shil?
Yes?
Come to the house right away.
I need to talk to you.
What...
Don't say anything to Dong Jin...
and come right now.
Okay. I'll come now.
Okay, here we are.
- What is this place? - A club.
- A club? - A club?
It's Christmas Eve. Let's have fun.
Tell me the truth.
You brought us here just to get rid of me, didn't you?
You rotten brat.
Tae Yang and I are going to play here for a while.
You should go home now.
We went singing with you and ate with you.
We did enough.
Don't be like that. Let's go somewhere else.
Mother, would you like to watch a movie?
There's a lot of new releases.
No.
I'm going clubbing, no matter what.
Okay. Let's go clubbing.
What?
It's my daughter's wish to go clubbing on Christmas Eve,
so I should go with her. Let's go!
Wait.
Can she actually get into the club?
I think your mother can.
Stop right there!
(Wolgyesu Tailor Shop)
It looked good.
I'm back.
Welcome back.
- Did it go well? - Yes.
Where did Yun Shil go?
She said something urgent came up and she had to leave. She just left.
- Something urgent? - Yes.
Ms Choi, I'm coming in.
Don't you have something to tell me?
Excuse me?
Aren't you hiding something from me?
I'm sorry.
Let's not waste our energy,
and end it here.
I want you...
to leave my house...
and the tailor shop.
What?
(The Gentlemen of Wolgyesu Tailor Shop)
This happened because of you.
Why did you have to leave home and create this mess?
Gi Pyo gets out next month.
I won't forgive you once I get out.
I'll make Dong Jin pay for everything.
What do we do now?
So this is how young people play. This is nice.
What did that punk Tae Yang do to my mum and Hyo Won?
Let's set a wedding date.
Where is he? Why is he screening my calls again?
What is it at this hour?
I will...