(The following content may not be suitable for viewers under 15.)
(Viewer discretion is advised.)
(Episode 36)
Leave Dong Jin alone,
Yun Shil.
Even though I treat you like my own daughter,
you shouldn't do this. I can't allow it.
I know I'm not good enough...
for Dong Jin.
Still, I beg you to accept me.
I'll do my best...
to Mr Lee, you, and Dong Jin. I promise you.
Even if you do your best, that won't solve the problem.
Let's say...
I accept you to see Dong Jin.
Can't you see what would happen next?
The moment Gi Pyo comes out of the prison,
he would harm Dong Jin.
And his mother would come...
to Dong Jin and harass him every day.
Bad rumors that I can't even say myself...
would spread out day by day.
What good would come to my son?
Dong Jin is meant to be a great man. You would just drag my son down.
He is as precious as my own life to me.
I can't blame you if you say I'm too greedy.
That's how I feel as a mum.
Ms Choi...
I'm begging you, Yun Shil.
Please leave my son...
without saying anything.
I hate myself saying all this to you,
but I can't help it.
Let's put an end to it.
I'm sorry.
Watch and Download App at Offical site HDFree.Se to support us
I saw Yun Shil running out of the house crying.
I called her to make her understood.
Don't just object her. Think about it carefully.
You should think about...
which decision could make Dong Jin happy.
To think about it,
a sweet and kind-hearted girl like Yun Shil...
is hard to find nowadays.
We have seen her in our own backyard so far.
This happened because of you.
It wouldn't have happened if you hadn't left home.
Then Dong Jin wouldn't have to work at the tailor shop,
and he would have never met Yun Shil.
Why did you have to leave home and create this mess?
I understand how much you're upset,
but don't be so pessimistic about it.
To meet a woman who gets along well with you, have children...
and live happily together, that's a good life.
You have lived your own life up to now.
What is a life about?
If you're going to keep saying those things, just leave home again.
- Honey. - I won't listen to you this time.
Don't even try to persuade me.
Don't you feel pity for Yun Shil?
Do you think I feel comfortable when I treat Yun Shil hard?
I feel pain as if I'm cutting off myself.
So you would better keep quiet this time.
Stop saying anything when you don't really know how I feel.
I want you...
to leave my house...
and the tailor shop.
(Wolgyesu Tailor Shop)
Leave Dong Jin alone, Yun Shil.
(Mr Pretty Eyes)
It's me.
Where are you? You promised to have dinner with me.
I had an urgent business to take care of.
I'm almost there.
(Wolgyesu Tailor Shop)
I'm sorry. You must have waited for a long time.
I was going to cancel the reservation at the restaurant.
What happened?
A friend from my hometown came to Seoul...
and wanted to meet me, so I met her.
I didn't know that.
I was worried that Hong Gi Pyo's mum might harass you again.
I'm sorry that I made you worry.
It's all right. If we leave now, we can make it to the restaurant.
Let's get going.
We don't have to have a fancy meal.
It's Christmas Eve.
Don't tell me to have noodles or instant noodles as usual.
Let's go now.
- It's been a long time, Mr. - It's been a long time.
I'll guide to your reserved table.
All right.
I'll do it.
I'll prepare the menu you reserved.
Thank you.
It's like what I saw in a drama or a movie.
Isn't it too expensive here?
It's a special day.
We can do those things that people in dramas do.
You don't have to do this.
I don't deserve this.
You deserve this.
You're the only precious jewel for me in the world.
I'm not a jewel.
I'm one of those stones scattered on the road.
Why are you being so humble today?
Are you pretending to be a good girl to get a present from Santa Claus?
I'm not a kid.
Eat slowly.
Thank you.
Have some wine.
You don't look to happy.
Did you argue with your friend?
No.
Then is something wrong?
We promised to discuss things...
if something goes wrong. You haven't forgotten, have you?
I haven't.
Do you want more wine?
- No. - Why not?
Are you afraid...
you'll get drunk and cause a scene?
I'll carry you home. Drink as much as you want.
I'd rather not today.
I think I'll get drunk too quickly.
There's a package for you.
Are you Ms Na Yun Shil?
Yes, I'm Na Yun Shil.
- This is for you. - What?
How did they know I'd be here?
I wonder how.
Open the box.
My goodness.
It's for you for being so good all through the year.
Dong Jin...
There's a package for you.
- Are you Ms Na Yun Shil? - Yes.
This is for you.
There's one more?
I said I'd make you feel like...
you're in a movie.
Open it up.
Oh, gosh.
Do you like it?
It's beautiful.
I'm glad you like it.
I think the last one just arrived.
I have something for Ms Na Yun Shil.
I heard that you shouldn't...
buy someone just one pair of shoes.
One pair means they'll run off.
Two pairs mean they'll come back.
I had no idea...
and bought you a pair of trainers.
It was really close.
I didn't get you anything.
You're right here.
You are a gift to me.
Thank you...
for coming to me.
There are cakes that are too pretty...
and too tasty to eat.
Welcome to Oh Young Eun Bakery.
You're so cute.
You're handsome and you're cute.
Go on inside...
and check out the cakes made with organic ingredients.
There aren't many left. Have a lovely Christmas.
Organic ingredients are good for you.
A family of three coming in.
Hello there. What a lovely couple you are.
Go and look around.
Welcome, welcome.
(Oh Young Eun Bakery)
(Fighter Chick)
Come and check out Oh Young Eun Bakery's cakes.
Come on inside.
There is no response. Please leave...
What is he doing and why won't he pick up?
The chicken's ready.
I'm coming.
Thanks.
Here's your order.
We ordered draught beer.
The chicken's ours.
Sorry.
I'm sorry about that. Enjoy the food.
- The braised mussels is ready. - Okay.
- Here is your braised mussels... - We didn't order that.
That's ours.
Sorry.
I'm so sorry.
It's Christmas and we're so busy. I got confused.
- Enjoy the food. - Thanks.
What's wrong with me?
Oh Young Eun Bakery's cakes are good for you.
Christmas cakes made with organic ingredients.
- Don't you feel cold? - Not at all.
- Have some hot chocolate. - I see.
Thanks.
This is lovely.
Thanks to you, our sales skyrocketed.
I didn't do anything.
Your cakes are pretty and delicious.
That's why they sell well.
Just a moment.
Hello?
Really?
Okay, I'll be right there.
- Is something urgent? - Yes.
A neighbour is watching Seung Woo and she thinks he has a fever.
You should go, then. I'll watch the store for you.
Sorry. I won't be long.
- Call me if you need help. - I will.
- Sorry. - I'd like to pay.
(Oh Young Eun Bakery)
I should get Mr Lee and Ms Choi a Christmas cake.
Hello and...
Santa's watching the store?
I'm here to buy a cake.
Sir, I mean, Santa.
Could you give me a discount?
Please?
You'll have to throw out whatever's left...
if you can't sell everything by today.
Can't you give me 20 percent off?
You're more like Scrooge than Santa Claus.
Be nice. It's Christmas.
He's too strict.
I'll take this one.
Were these made here?
You're good.
Do you need part-time help?
A salesperson should speak up.
How much is it?
Is it 23 dollars? Okay.
Here you go.
Can he not speak?
Have a nice day.
(Christmas Cakes Available)
That was so scary.
You look like a completely different person dressed up like that.
I feel awkward and weird.
You don't look awkward or weird at all.
You look stunning right now.
See? People are looking at you.
Aren't they looking at me because I look weird in this?
They're obviously looking at you because you look so gorgeous.
You make me proud.
Stop teasing me. You're making me blush.
I'm not teasing you.
I have to take a photo of you to remember this moment.
Gosh, forget it.
Don't be so difficult. Let me take one photo of you.
Come on.
Look at the camera.
Here we go. 1, 2.
Smile, please.
In 1, 2.
Mum, I'm sorry.
- For what? - Let's just go to a cinema.
No.
I'm going to have fun here.
I...
want to get in. Will there be a problem?
You're too beautiful.
Please go in.
Thank you.
Gosh, what a headache.
Mum!
Hold on a second.
As you can see, today is Christmas.
It's 20 dollars per person to get in.
I see. This is my first time to a place like this. Just a second.
Sure.
My gosh.
Hey, my goodness.
Is this how youngsters party these days?
This is awesome. I love it.
I'm so embarrassed because of you.
Mum, let's get out of here. Please?
We had to pay to get in. We got to get our money's worth.
Why do you want to leave already?
Are you embarrassed of me, too?
No, not at all.
"It's Raining Men"!
I'm going to go to the dance floor.
You two should have fun, too.
Yes!
Here I come!
Gosh. What should I do with her, seriously?
Just let her have fun.
Tae Yang...
Seeing her so excited is making me happy.
I'm so embarrassed.
What?
Nice!
Yes.
Yes, yes!
Yes. I did it again.
In 1, 2, 3. Go.
- In 1, 2, 3. - There.
Nice.
We should have just taken her to the cinema.
My heart keeps pounding since it's my first time to a place like this.
I guess your mum is fine.
Are you all right?
In 1, 2, 3!
Yes! Your head, please.
Hyo Won,
I'm having such a good time!
My goodness.
I'm going to beat everyone!
- I'm going to win. I'm going to... - Stop it.
Stop!
- We're here. - Hello.
Hello.
Where's mum? Is she already in bed?
Madam Ko tagged along on Miss Hyo Won's date.
What's the matter with my mum these days, seriously?
What does that mean?
Is she with Tae Yang right now?
- I wish you a merry Christmas - I wish you a merry Christmas
- I wish you a merry - Mum!
What are you wearing?
You little...
Let's...
go grab just one more drink.
I wish you a merry Christmas
You're quite drunk. I think you should get some rest now.
- I wish you - Hi.
Hi.
We should take her to her bed.
All right.
- I wish you a merry Christmas - Hey, let me do it.
I said I want to have another drink...
Mum, wake up.
I'll be right back.
- Seriously. - I wish you a merry
What is she keep saying?
Mum, are you in your right mind?
Have you lost your mind or what?
You can't go out dressed like that.
What if you run into people from work?
Be quiet, you brat.
You embarrassed me in front of Ji Yun.
She saw you dressed like this.
She'll probably think that our family is a big joke.
I give Ji Yun...
30 out of 100.
Tae Yang gets 90 out of 100.
What?
Gosh, I'm cold.
Goodness.
Do you really have to do this?
What do you mean?
You approached Hyo Won and even charmed her mum on purpose.
I had no idea that you could be this calculative and vindictive.
You probably think everyone is like you.
- What? - The word "approach"...
isn't appropriate to describe human relationships.
People exchange feelings...
and become close step by step with time.
Unlike you, most people don't abandon everything for their goals.
You have to open up to people and be yourself in relationships.
Are you lecturing me right now?
You're probably all full of yourself right now...
because Hyo Won likes you,
but you better come to your senses.
Do you think this family will allow you to marry her?
The women in this household drive me crazy.
Darling.
The two of you haven't officially met, right?
This is my brother's girlfriend, Announcer Choi Ji Yun.
This my boyfriend who is also my best friend...
and future husband, Kang Tae Yang.
Gosh, I'm in a foul mood right now.
As we have experienced with Dong Sook,
we can't have our way when it comes to our children.
Calm down.
That's what I'm saying.
They say that bad things happen all at once.
I was so stressed out over Dong Sook's marriage...
and now Dong Jin's giving me a hard time.
It depends on how you see it.
It could be better for Dong Jin...
to remarry and have kids...
than to live and die alone.
It depends on who he marries.
May we come in?
Are you sick, Mum?
Lunch didn't agree with her.
Should she see a doctor?
Or should I run to the pharmacy?
She'll be fine. She took some medicine.
Sun Nyeo bought you a cake.
Dad, come and have some.
No thanks. You go ahead.
Okay, then. Goodnight.
Goodnight.
Dong Jin was the smartest boy in his class...
and he always got good grades.
Why is he such a terrible judge when it comes to women?
He got that from me.
What?
I cracked a joke to make you laugh.
I can't believe you aren't bothered at all.
How could you make jokes at a time like this?
Mum, do you think Grandma...
found out about Uncle and Yun Shil?
Did you tell her?
No.
Then did Father tell her?
He said he wouldn't for a while.
Let's drink and be merry, then.
Lift your glass, Miss.
You can't call me that now.
Now you should...
call me by my name, Dad.
What?
Do you not want to be my dad?
It's not that.
I was so touched.
Thanks for calling me "dad".
Sure, Dad.
I lack in so many ways to be a deserving dad,
but I'll work hard...
and become a nice dad that you can be proud of.
Thank you, Jun.
Come on, you can't call him that any more.
You need to address him properly.
Should I?
Then...
- what should I call him? - "Honey."
"Honey"?
Honey.
Keep calling me that, honey.
I got goosebumps.
Shall we have a toast?
Shall we?
- Merry Christmas. - Merry Christmas.
Da Jeong.
Sing us a carol.
Yes, sing for us. 1, 2, 3, 4.
Dashing through the snow in a one horse open sleigh
O'er the fields we go laughing all the way
Bells on bob tails ring making spirits bright
What fun it is to laugh and sing a sleighing song tonight
- Dong Sook. - Jingle bells, jingle bells
Jingle all the way
Jingle, jingle, jingle, jingle, jingle.
Thank you for a great time.
Thanks to you...
I just had the best Christmas of my life.
So did I.
Go on inside. Here's the cake.
What about you?
Come and say hi to my parents.
subtitles ripped and synced by riri13
I'm a bit tired.
I'd like to get some rest.
You even bought a cake. Come and share it with us.
I had too much for dinner.
Come inside with me.
Show my parents how pretty you look.
I don't want to. I feel so awkward.
You don't have to.
Come inside.
I just love the sweater Da Jeong got me.
- I have great taste. - Hello.
- Hello. - Welcome home.
You look like a doll, Yun Shil.
You're adorable.
Thanks, Da Jeong.
Did he buy you all this?
Yes.
Are Mum and Dad in?
Yes. Mum's sick.
- Why? - Lunch didn't agree with her.
- Mum, Dad, I'm home. - I see that.
Yun Shil bought you a cake.
Can we come in?
Your mum just fell asleep. There's no need to come in.
Ms Choi must be sick because of me.
Hello.
Hi.
It's Christmas eve.
Were you very busy?
Yes. We get a lot of orders at the end of the year.
I see.
Orders, my foot.
Sam Do, just wait until I catch you at it.
I'll kill you.
What about dinner?
I had so many pastries that I'm full.
- Pastries? Where from? - What?
I was too busy to eat proper food.
You should eat a proper meal, not eat a few pastries.
I know.
I'm so tired. I'm off to shower.
(Oh Young Eun Bakery)
Why does he keep rubbish in his pocket?
(Draw pattern to unlock.)
What?
It used to be this one. Did he change the pattern?
Is it this?
(Wrong Pattern)
What about this?
No?
Is it this, then? No?
He's being clever this time.
I swear I saw her somewhere before.
I know her from somewhere but I can't remember where.
Where'd I see her?
What is wrong with me?
No, no.
Hello, Ji Yun.
Are you going somewhere?
To see Tae Yang.
Don't tell my brother.
He just left.
Mum followed us around all day and we didn't get any alone time.
Do you like my boyfriend?
Why?
Was he bad?
It's not that.
I was surprised. That's all.
Why?
I didn't think you'd like a man like him.
What's wrong with him?
I don't like talking about someone behind their back.
It's just between us.
I told you horrid things about my brother, too.
Regardless of everything else,
isn't it a huge problem that he's still jobless?
You can't choose which family you're born into,
but anyone can find a job if they try hard.
He prefers part-time jobs and that...
makes me think that...
he doesn't take his life or career too seriously.
If he can barely support himself, how could he...
care for you...
and be considered your equal as a spouse?
I'm just concerned.
I thought it was something serious.
- Tae Yang has a job. - What?
He just had a photoshoot.
He's a professional model now.
Is he a model?
Hey.
He's my boyfriend, not yours.
I'm so sorry.
A producer saw Tae Yang at the Tailoring Competition fashion show,
and he found Tae Yang's look attractive.
So Tae Yang took pictures for a paper advertisement few days ago.
- I can't believe it. - You'd better believe it.
Tae Yang will be a Korean Wave star soon.
It doesn't feel right.
I should have told Hyo Won about Ji Yun.
I can't focus.
I'd better take a shower.
I'm sending you a message as you might be sleeping now.
Good night.
By the way, you were so beautiful today.
Merry Christmas, Yun Shil.
Has she gone to bed already?
Where's Hyo Won?
She went out a little while ago.
Where did she go at this late hour?
She went to see Kang Tae Yang.
She said she couldn't have a decent date because of Mother.
She's totally crazy.
What on earth did Kang Tae Yang do...
to Mum and Hyo Won?
Something must be done. I should take an extreme measure.
Let's set a wedding date.
Hyo Sang.
If we do nothing about it, Kang Tae Yang and Hyo Won might...
make an outrageous announcement that they will get married.
I can imagine...
what will happen to us if that happens. Don't you think so?
All right.
Let's get married next month.
Goodness.
What's this?
What is this?
Who sent this?
(To Kang Tae Yang)
Ta-da!
My goodness.
Isn't this the best present for you?
What are you doing?
Mum totally ruined our date,
so I just couldn't stay at home.
Why?
Am I bothering you?
No, it's not like that.
All right, then.
Get me out of the box.
How did you get in?
The manager helped me.
All right.
My legs. Wait, hold me!
Please be quiet.
- Be quiet. - All right.
What are all these?
I brought Christmas presents for you.
This is a cushion with my picture on it.
This is a T-shirt,
this is a mug,
and a pair of socks.
Every present has your picture on it.
Of course. I want everything in your room...
to have my picture on it.
And the last one is the most ambitious work of mine.
Ta-da!
What's this?
Is this...
an underwear?
Isn't it cute?
Don't be embarrassed.
By the way,
I gave you all these presents.
Don't you have any present for me?
I'm sorry. I was going to get you something after work,
but you and Madam Ko came.
I'll prepare a present for you next Christmas.
All right. I'll let you slide this time.
Thank you.
Instead,
give me a kiss here.
All right.
One more time.
- One more time, please. - Stop it.
- Two more times. - I knew you would do this.
- Two more times. - Stop it.
- Stay still. - What are you doing?
Why do I have to stay still?
- One more time. - No, no.
I'll start my presentation for standing point proposal...
of Wolgyesu Tailor Shop to Jeil Department Store.
The Wolgyesu Tailor Shop is a bespoke suit brand...
that emphasizes tradition and honor in a suit.
Since 1917, we have succeeded the family business for 3 generations.
For nearly 100 years, we have kept the value...
and philosophy of Korean bespoke suit as a custom tailor.
Wolgyesu Tailor Shop has...
patterns, fabrics and portfolios for hundreds of suits.
We put continuous efforts for developing bespoke suits...
that customers want.
We are equipped to provide the perfect master suit.
We're designated as a Seoul future heritage in 2013,
and by winning the first prize in Bespoke Suit Tailoring Competition,
the name of Wolgyesu achieved recognition once again.
These suits are the samples from our shop.
You can take a look at them.
What are you doing here?
What am I doing here?
I came to see a runaway daughter-in-law.
Gi Pyo will...
be released next month.
You must be worried since you have done wrong to him.
Someone who knows Gi Pyo's innocence...
is going to pay bail for him.
You and that punk are in a trouble once Gi Pyo is released.
Are you ready for that?
I guess you lost your judgment as you've fallen for that punk.
Once Gi Pyo is released, he will break every bone...
in that punk's body.
Don't you know how Gi Pyo is when he's angry?
You should beg his pardon now.
That's the only way out for you.
You should leave now.
She has gotten so gutsy.
He told me to bring Yun Shil today.
He'll get mad at me again.
Gosh, I'm so stressed out.
Goodness.
Good morning, Yun Shil.
Did you come alone today?
Dong Jin went to the department store for the presentation.
Oh, right.
I forgot about it.
Is something going on?
Why do you look so spaced out?
Nothing's going on. I'm fine.
I'm going to get a glass of water before I get started.
Did something else happen?
What if Ms Choi found out?
It doesn't look like she knows yet.
What should I do now?
Thank you.
- I'll look forward to it. - Thank you.
(Jeil Department Store)
Hey, Dong Jin.
What brings you here?
I just had a meeting with them to discuss opening a store here.
I get that you won the competition, but you're being overly ambitious.
How can such a small brand get a store space at a department store?
That's none of your business.
Right. Having to be stuck at that tiny shop...
must be frustrating for you.
Don't be too discouraged even if it doesn't work out.
What about you?
Are you doing all right?
Everyone here told me...
that Meesa Apparel's numbers aren't as good as before.
Well, the CEO is visiting the store himself,
so the situation must be serious.
I heard that the outdoor brand you launched recently...
is not doing well.
A capable CEO isn't only focused on the growth of his business.
Risk management is equally important.
If you're struggling,
I'm more than happy to help you out as an adviser or consultant,
so get in touch with me anytime.
Who does he think he is? How dare he tries to lecture me?
Gosh, my blood is boiling.
Dong Sook.
What brings you here?
I came to see you.
I heard that you got married a few days ago.
Why didn't you tell me?
You and Dong Jin got divorced, so you're no longer our family.
Why would I get in touch with you?
It looks like you still resent me a lot.
I get it. I've been too set on doing things my way.
I'm sorry, Dong Sook.
What is this?
A wedding gift. I'm sorry that it's late.
That's crazy.
Dong Jin will get mad at me if I accept this.
I'm here, Dong Sook.
Hi.
You are with a customer.
Hello. Congratulations on your marriage.
We met briefly at our place a little while ago, right?
I'm Sung Tae Pyung.
I heard that you're a singer.
Well, yes.
I should invite you to our foundation's year-end party.
I'll pay you well.
Please come and sing for our VIP members.
So, is it for Meesa Cultural Foundation's VIP members?
Many famous people must be coming, then.
Of course.
He's so busy with TV shows...
and events these days.
You'll need to book him as soon as possible.
I'll contact thorough my employee.
Please come.
Okay. Well, it's...
- I'll see you around. - See you.
- Why did you say yes to that? - Why not?
We're on Dong Jin and Yun Shil's side.
I can't sing at an event hosted by his ex-wife's company.
I never said that I'm on Yun Shil's side.
- What? - Let's be honest.
Do you really think that she's good enough for Dong Jin?
Gosh, Dong Sook.
I do like Yun Shil,
but not as my future sister-in-law.
Gosh, I can't allow it.
She sounds just like her mum when she says things like that.
They say, "Like mother, like daughter."
I must survive one year.
(Wolgyesu Tailor Shop)
- Hello? - Hey, Young Eun. It's me.
Hey, Sam Do.
- How is Seung Woo? - He's a lot better.
He's at the kindergarten now.
Good. I was really worried about him.
- Are you at the shop now? - Yes.
I've been working all day. I just stepped out to call you.
- Have you had lunch yet? - Yes.
- Is the store busy? - It's all right.
You really boosted my numbers on Christmas Eve,
so I don't have to worry about this month.
I want to buy you a meal to thank you.
Don't worry about it.
I'll treat you to something delicious on your day off.
Bring Sun Nyeo, too.
Can I pay?
- Sam Do, I have to go. - Okay, let's talk later.
Honey!
What are you doing here? It's cold.
What brings you here at this hour?
I just finished my shift.
I started early this morning because of the group orders.
Oh, right.
You must be exhausted. You should go home and sleep.
- Honey. - Yes?
I'm feeling a little down.
Shall we go somewhere nice for coffee?
What are you talking about? I have to work.
Just for 30 minutes. Please?
You can have coffee at home. Why would you want to waste money?
Or do you want to come in? I'll make you a cup of coffee.
Gosh, you're so not romantic.
Forget it.
Bye.
What has gotten into her?
She's acting strange. Gosh, it's cold.
I hope you enjoy it.
- I will. - Goodbye.
Who is that?
See you again soon.
That's right.
I thought she looked familiar.
She's the owner of this bakery.
Gosh.
Hello.
Didn't you leave your wallet at my store the other day?
It's you, right?
Yes, it was me.
You have good memory.
If you're not busy,
you should come in for a cup of warm quince tea.
It's on me.
Shall I?
(Oh Young Eun Bakery)
How do Sam Do and that woman know each other?
She opened this bakery very recently,
so I'm sure they didn't just hit it off.
Thank you.
I guess you live around here.
Yes.
I recently moved back from Seattle.
I see.
Why did you decide to open a bakery in this neighbourhood?
My childhood friend...
used to work as a garment cutter at Wolgyesu Tailor Shop here.
I visited him a few times back in the days...
and had good memories about it.
That's why I decided to open my bakery here.
What?
Is she Sam Do's first love, Young Eun or whatever her name is?
My gosh.
- What's wrong? - What's the name of this bakery?
Oh Young Eun Bakery.
Is Oh Young Eun your name?
Yes. I'm Oh Young Eun.
Hello.
Just a minute, please.
Please try the samples.
That explains everything.
Bae Sam Do...
has finally met his first love again.
They met again.
Thank you for calling Wolgyesu Tailor Shop.
It's me, Yun Shil.
My mum was just here.
She said you didn't want to visit me with her.
We don't have to see each other any more.
I don't like what you just said.
Why won't we see each other?
You'll see me very often once I get out.
I'm warning you. I will make you pay once I get out.
I'll make Dong Jin pay for everything.
I'm not just saying this.
You know what I'm like.
I begged, didn't I? Just leave me alone.
I won't let you go until the day I die.
You are mine.
I won't lose you over my dead body.
See you next month.
(Wolgyesu Tailor Shop)
Hello?
Are you Kang Tae Yang's manager?
You dialed the wrong number.
No, you didn't. I am Kang Tae Yang's manager.
I'm Jeon Doo Yeon and I direct TV commercials.
I called to ask if I could cast Mr Kang.
In a commercial?
There you go. Here as well.
Kang star.
Why are you here, Mum?
You made it big.
Pardon?
Someone wants you...
in their commercial.
- A commercial? - A commercial?
Why are you doing this to me?
If you don't give in, I don't know how far I'll go.
No one knows what'll happen to you.
I might be in here, but I can see...
and hear everything you do and say.
I'm sorry.
That's all I can say.
If you thought you'd get off with an apology, you're mistaken.
The day I get out, I'll set fire to your shop...
and make sure that Dong Jin loses both his legs, okay?
It should end with me.
I can't put Dong Jin through this.
What are you doing at this hour?
Are you off work already?
I will...
break up with Dong Jin.
You were very right.
I'm not a good match for him.
I got too greedy.
I'm sorry, Yun Shil.
When you become a mother yourself,
you'll understand how I feel.
You treated me like I was your own.
I betrayed your favour.
Dong Jin's such a good guy that...
I was blinded for a while.
I'm sorry.
And...
thanks for understanding.
Ms Choi.
I need you to do something.
What's that?
Give me some time.
I need time to let go.
I won't take too long.
If you have made up your mind,
we can do that.
Thank you.
I'm sorry.
Blame me for everything.
(Wolgyesu Tailor Shop)
Why were you out for so long?
Sorry.
I went to get some fresh air and lost track of time.
Do you think you can take advantage of...
your relationship with the boss?
I don't.
I'm sorry, Sir.
Sam Do and Ms Geum left a short while ago.
How were things at the department store?
I got a favourable reaction.
I think we'll get some good news.
That's great.
You're so good at what you do.
Let's go home.
Just a moment.
What are you doing?
I'm going to ask Master Bae to teach me.
I want to practice with you as my model.
I have too great figure to be a model for free.
It's not for free. I'll cook you instant noodles.
Without an egg.
Okay.
I will take your measurements, then.
Dong Jin gave me so much.
I have nothing to give you in return.
The only thing I can do before I leave...
is to make you a suit.
That's all I can do.
Thank you for everything.
(Wolgyesu Tailor Shop)
(The Gentlemen of Wolgyesu Tailor Shop)
She said she'd leave?
You're odd. Is something wrong?
We set a date.
- A wedding? - You idiot.
Are you pregnant?
Why hasn't he called?
Is he with his first love?
She was spying on Young Eun? How did she find out?
Is something wrong? Why won't she pick up?
Do as I tell you...
and he'll treat you like a princess forever.
You're in a good mood. Is there good news to share?
The man who stole the heart of such a pretty woman...
must be the happiest man in the world.