(The following content may not be suitable for viewers under 15.)
(Viewer discretion is advised.)
(Episode 37)
Dramatorrent.com
(Date of fitting, Fabric code)
(Measurement)
(Name: Lee Dong Jin)
You melted my ice-cold heart...
and planted a tree called love in me, Dong Jin.
I am lack too much to be around you.
So, before I leave,
I'm making you a suit with threads of love.
Bespoke suits is a dying industry in Korea.
The ecosystem of tailor-made suits is completely destroyed.
My plan is...
to bring talented tailors who own small stores...
all over Korea to create a guild.
I will teach them our techniques and patterns...
to manufacture high-quality tailored suits.
A bespoke suit is made completely by hand.
We will accept reservations and visit VIP clients.
Those will be manufactured only at our main store.
Semi-tailored suits for the everyday consumer...
can be made by any tailor in our guild...
wherever he or she is located.
Where is Kang star? Why isn't he here?
Maybe he's busy.
Darling.
- Are you off work? - Yes.
Kang star.
Sit down.
Why won't you do the commercial?
Have you lost your mind?
You can't turn your back on a blessing.
I have an important exam that day.
An exam?
- What exam? - What is it for?
It's for my teaching licence.
A teaching licence?
Do you want to be a teacher?
Yes.
I'd been studying for years but I kept failing.
I took time off to interview for jobs,
but I want to try again.
I always wanted to be a teacher.
Teaching is great.
But don't you think it's a waste...
to give up on being a star?
Why did you do the photoshoot?
Because they offered a lot of money.
I plan to keep doing it when I have the time.
You have too little ambition for a man.
I have no ambition.
I want to live a simple life with Hyo Won...
and be happy and content.
Let him be. Let him do what he wants.
Did you want to be a teacher?
(Wolgyesu Tailor Shop)
(From Mr Pretty Eyes)
(I'm the happiest man...)
I'm the happiest man in the world...
as I stole the prettiest woman's heart.
- When did you come here? - I just got here.
It's so cold.
Please hold my hands. They're almost frozen.
I know you came here by car. Don't be such a crybaby.
I stayed outside for a while taking your picture.
Isn't it cold?
I think It's warm enough.
Can't you play along?
Where are Master Bae and Ms Geum?
They left a while ago.
You're the only one waiting for me.
I was waiting for fitting.
- Have you made the suit already? - Yes, I have.
But it took more than I expected because I had to make it after work.
Let me start your fitting, Mr.
Raise your arms and shoulders. Do you feel comfortable?
It's perfect.
What about your waistline? Do you feel all right?
It's a perfect fit.
How is the length of the jacket?
Let me see.
It reaches right to the hip.
Do you like the overall design?
I like it so much.
By the way, tailor.
The pants seem little short.
Oh, gosh. I'm sorry.
I'll mend it right away.
It's far more stylish than an Italian suit.
I thought you're only good at sewing,
but you're great at cutting, too.
You're flattering me too much.
It's wrinkled here.
No, it's not.
My ankles feel cold.
- The pants are so short. - No, they are not.
I'll mend them right away too.
(Wolgyesu Tailor Shop)
I didn't know that he could laugh so well.
I wonder why he didn't laugh when he was with me.
She said...
- she would leave? - Yes.
She promised me that she would leave without telling anyone.
Would she leave without asking for anything?
Yun Shil is not a bad person.
You should help me, Mother.
I have been thinking about my wrongdoings.
After a long thought, I realized...
that Father, Dong Jin and you will be my only family.
Please take me back, Mother.
I won't make a mistake again. I'll do my best.
Are you sure you will make Dong Jin happy?
Sure, Mother.
Will you be careful with your words, too?
I won't make the foolish mistake again.
I'm not such a fool, Mother. You know that.
All right, then.
I'll give it a try.
She said she would leave.
Why is she still around Dong Jin?
You're back, Madam Ko.
Yes.
How are you, Mum?
How are you, Mother?
- What are you doing here? - Aren't you happy to see me?
You visit my house too often.
I saw you here yesterday and the day before yesterday.
Why should I be glad to see you?
My goodness, Mum.
Why are you in such a bad mood today?
Please have a seat, Mum.
This way.
Do you guys...
- have anything in your mind? - Well...
We set our wedding date, Mum.
Who said you can set the date?
Are you...
pregnant?
- No, Mother. - My goodness, Mum.
An innocent girl like Ji Yun would never get pregnant before marriage.
We've been dating for a while...
and we got to know each other very well.
We don't need put it off further.
Did you push Hyo Sang for marriage?
It's not like that, Mother.
I will be more stable...
if I get married.
Then I can concentrate on the work in the company, Mum.
It's same for Ji Yun.
I'll support Hyo Sang very well.
As for Ji Yun,
she needs my support to thrive in the broadcasting business...
which is so competitive.
Isn't she going to quit her job after the marriage?
My goodness, Mum.
How can you say such an old-fashioned thing?
I'm not quitting my job, Mother.
My dream is to become Oprah Winfrey of Korea.
- Who's that? - My goodness, Mum.
She is a famous African-American...
female talk-show host in America.
- Oprah has curly hair. - Has she?
Well, I know her.
- Right. - Well,
you have such an over-sized ambition.
I'm confident I can do well at both ends, home and work.
Please give us your permission, Mum.
She should learn our family customs...
and get lessons for married life.
She has a lot to do. I say no.
If you hurry too much, something bad may happen.
What shall we do?
Don't worry.
I have an idea.
Ji Yun is too ambitious.
Tae Yang is too humble.
I wish they could be switched.
By the way,
what is Hyo Won doing with Kang Tae Yang without me?
Why is she calling? She's disturbing Tae Yang.
You must be tired. Get some more sleep.
What are you talking about? I was not sleeping.
I was watching you studying.
What is the mark around your mouth, then?
My goodness.
Just kidding.
Don't do that.
How is it going with your study?
Well,
so-so.
Do you think you can do better if I kiss you?
I'm fine.
Don't be shy.
I'll give my energy to you.
We're not supposed to do that.
That would distract me. I can't concentrate.
Why would it distract you?
Never mind. Let's get some fresh air outside.
All right.
- Please carry me on your back. - What?
Carry me to the hallway.
I'll be kicked out for demoralization.
It's a violation to be with you here.
Which is more important to you, me or the rules?
Don't say that way.
You seem to consider the rules more than me.
That's nonsense.
Then carry me on your back now.
My legs are numb that I can't walk.
My goodness.
Wait a minute.
Hurry up.
My phone. Got it.
Okay? Let's go.
Go.
- Let's go. - Go, go.
So...
We'll gather the tailors scattered all over Korea...
and create a guild.
- A guild? - Yes.
People don't order tailored suits,
so talented tailors turned to dry-cleaning or making alterations.
Some even changed jobs altogether.
I thought it's pity to waste such talent,
so if we can give them a chance to work again,
it would be great for us and for the industry.
You seem like someone from a different world.
What do you mean?
I started to wonder if...
I'm being too greedy.
If I can handle someone...
as great as you.
Things like that.
You tend to think too highly of me.
I'm not that great.
Don't overestimate me. It's stressful.
You are not laugh at my joke.
You're a bit odd today. Is something wrong?
Not at all.
I'm just tired and overworked.
Shall I massage you?
No thanks.
Turn around. I'll make you feel much better.
I can't believe you're massaging me.
What did I do to deserve this?
My parents will accept us soon.
You've known my mum for years.
She can't stand me being sad.
You make me feel warm.
Dong Jin.
My dear brother-in-law.
Brother-in-law?
She must be her sister.
I missed you so, so much.
I missed you so much...
but I didn't dare call you.
I thought of you a lot, too.
How do you know Hyo Won?
I meant to tell you, but I was too embarrassed to.
What?
Do you know my Tae Yang?
"My Tae Yang"?
She's my girlfriend.
- Your girlfriend? - Your girlfriend?
I've been hitting on him for ages...
and he finally gave in.
Who is this?
She's Dong Jin's girlfriend.
What?
What a small world.
I had no idea you two would end up together.
I still think it's a dream sometimes.
Have you two known each other for long?
We met when I started working at the tailor shop.
We haven't been dating for long.
I see.
You should eat. You like chicken.
- Here you go. - Thanks.
You like chicken, too.
Feed me.
I need to go to the ladies' room.
Excuse me.
I'll be back.
I didn't think you'd start dating so soon.
It just happened.
My sister isn't over you yet.
Do you not want to get back with her?
I don't at all.
My mum says Hyo Joo regrets what she did.
It's all in the past. There's no going back.
Your sister will meet someone worthy of her.
What do you like about her?
She's sweet and warmhearted.
And pretty as well.
It was good to see you.
Be nice to Hyo Won.
I will.
Call me if he ever upsets you.
I'll teach him a lesson.
Did you hear that?
This is a lot of pressure.
Let's meet up another time. Bye for now.
You two live in the same house, so you'll head off together.
We'll go ahead first.
Just a moment.
What do you mean you live in the same house?
Did you move in together already?
Now, now.
Let me go.
Dong Jin, this is too soon. You only just started dating.
Are you two living together already? Like a married couple?
Dong Jin.
Let me go, Tae Yang.
I need an answer. Dong Jin!
We should go, too.
Sure.
Did you feel uncomfortable around Hyo Won?
No. She's cheerful and honest.
She put me in a good mood.
She does that.
I'm glad and relieved that Tae Yang found himself...
such a cheerful and bright girlfriend.
Let's go home.
He should be home by now.
Why hasn't he called yet?
Is he with his first love?
The phone has been turned off. Please leave a message.
What, he turned his phone off?
What is he up to?
- Sam Do. - Will you...
leave with me?
Where will we go?
I will go wherever my wife isn't.
Can you really leave everything behind?
My life wasn't worth living until now.
Every day was worse than torture.
My wife picks a fight with me or someone else every day...
and we never got along.
I only lived because I could not die.
I feel so sorry for you.
I will be honest.
My body was with my wife...
but my heart was always with you.
When I saw you again...
I realised the lord was giving me a second chance.
Even if I must risk my life,
I swore to myself that I would not let this opportunity go.
If your wife finds out...
she will throw a fit.
If it's to spend just one day with you,
then I will have no regrets even if my wife beats me to death.
I am Bae Sam Do.
I am blinded and I fear nothing.
No!
No way.
Over my dead body.
I won't let them elope.
This is my new song.
Tell me what you think.
How long has it been since your last new song?
I'm so moved I want to cry.
This song...
portrays the love I have for you.
That's so romantic.
It's titled "My Brother Goes".
- That means me. - You?
I love the title.
My brother goes, goes, goes
He goes at full speed
He is coming to me
Dong Sook.
Do you smell something burning?
It's coming from the kitchen.
Something's burning.
What on earth is going on?
Don't, you'll burn your hands.
Let it cool.
She left in a hurry while cooking dinner.
Is something wrong?
She even left her phone.
What has gotten into her?
She's been really distracted recently.
Is Sam Do in trouble?
What is she doing here?
- You're called Seung Woo? - Yes.
Did you see a middle-aged man today?
What does he look like?
He's handsome and very muscly.
He makes suits.
He wasn't here today, then.
- I'll take two packs of castella. - Okay.
My husband loves castella.
Where is your husband?
Is he still at work?
I don't like to talk about my private life.
It looks like she lives alone with her son.
Is she divorced?
Did she move here to lure Sam Do?
(Oh Young Eun Bakery)
- Seung Woo. - Mr Tailor.
How are you today?
- Were you studying? - Yes.
Good. High-five.
- Hello. - Hello.
I just met friends from the orphanage.
They expected to see you...
and were so disappointed.
I needed to watch the store and Seung Woo.
- Are they all well? - Yes, they are.
Sam Do.
Can you do me a favour?
I want to meet your wife.
- My wife? - Yes.
We should say hi now that we're neighbours.
Your wife...
would be like a sister to me.
Right.
That's true,
but my wife is very...
Okay, I'll talk to her.
Tell me the truth.
What is Yun Shil like?
She's very nice and sweet.
It could be a facade.
We grew up together. She's practically my sister.
What you see is what you get.
She and Dong Jin can't be together.
What do you mean?
My sister isn't over Dong Jin yet.
No way.
My Yun Shil's the one for Dong Jin.
"My Yun Shil"?
I told you that we're practically brother and sister.
Even so,
how could you take her side instead of mine on this issue?
There are no sides.
There are.
I'm always on your side.
Be honest.
If Yun Shil and I were drowning, who would you save first?
That's such a stupid question.
You're refusing to answer.
Will you save Yun Shil first?
Let me think about it.
You need to think?
I guess I should save you first.
Will that do?
What's this?
It sounded so forced and insincere.
I was kidding.
How could you? You're so mean.
You should have said me right away.
How could you even hesitate?
- I said I was kidding. - You weren't. You meant it.
You don't love me truly.
I kept hitting on you...
and hassled you into giving in.
What are you talking about?
I fell for it!
I won't kiss you tonight!
Hyo Won, that's not fair.
I'll carry you.
Hyo Won. Hyo Won.
You got it wrong!
You're late.
The meeting at the department store ran late.
You must be tired. Go and get some rest.
You, too, Yun Shil.
Yes, Ms Choi. Have a good night.
Are you inside?
Yes, Sir.
Thanks.
Roasted chestnuts.
I saw it on the way back home and it reminded me of you.
Thank you. Did you just get home?
I met a few tailors...
I used to work with for a drink...
since it's the end of the year.
- Is the room warm? - Yes.
There's no need to feel...
anxious or uncomfortable.
Regardless of Dong Jin, you're like a daughter to me.
Thank you, Sir.
Give me more time.
I'll talk to my wife.
Okay.
Goodnight.
- Sleep well. - You, too.
If Mr Lee and Ms Choi...
were just a bit mean, then maybe I'd have pushed them.
I'd rather suffer alone.
I can't cause them any pain.
I'm home.
Hyo Won.
Why are you upset?
Did you and Tae Yang fight?
No.
I can tell you did.
Your forehead says...
"I just had a fight with Tae Yang."
What was it about?
- It's about Hyo Joo. - Hyo Joo?
Why do you have to fight with Kang Tae Yang because of Hyo Joo?
Tae Yang's friend from hometown and Dong Jin see each other.
What? Are you saying that Dong Jin has a woman?
Who is she? What does she do?
Tell me.
Have you had dinner, Mother?
I have.
Is everything all right?
Yes.
I was passing by the tailor shop today.
I saw them by chance.
She was still at the shop.
She asked some time to arrange things. I'm waiting her to leave.
She will keep her promise. Don't worry.
All right. I'll count on you and wait.
Good night, Mother.
Good night.
She's so carefree.
Hey, Hyo Joo.
I heard that Dong Jin has a woman.
Hyo Won saw them with her own eyes.
Dong Jin even introduced her to Hyo Won.
I know that. Don't make a fuss about it.
- Do you know that? - Yes.
Hyo Won said that woman works at the tailor shop.
Should I go to the tailor shop and teach her a lesson?
Don't show off your lack of dignity.
- What? - I told you before.
You shouldn't do anything for me.
I just...
thought you still have feeling for Dong Jin.
Will you be all right if Dong Jin marries...
the girl at the tailor shop?
That's nonsense.
What's wrong with him? He left like that and is not calling me.
How can he do this to me?
Sun Nyeo,
where have you been?
Why? What happened?
You should have turned off the gas. There might have been a fire.
I must have been out of my mind.
Fortunately, Sung Jun and I were at home.
Otherwise, there might have been a disaster.
I'm sorry. Something urgent came up.
Sun Nyeo, what's the matter?
It's nothing.
Sung Joon and I washed the pot and put in the dish closet.
Thank you, Dong Sook.
Thank you.
I'm tired. Let's go to bed.
All right.
There's something going on between Sam Do and Sun Nyeo.
Sam Do.
Did you have an argument with Sun Nyeo?
No, I didn't. Why?
Sun Nyeo doesn't look good.
She forgets things nowadays.
She forgot turning off the gas and went out a while ago,
and totally burned the pot.
What?
She's always been forgetful.
Good night.
- Go for it! - Great.
Why are you distracted?
I heard you burned the pot.
You're late.
Dong Jin said you left early in the evening.
Where have you been?
I told you I have year-end-party with orphanage friends.
Right. You did.
- Do you want to eat this? - No, I'm fine.
A new bakery called...
Oh Young Eun Bakery has opened at the intersection.
The bread from that shop tastes good.
Have you been there?
No, not yet.
You haven't been there.
I'll go and wash.
Yun Shil, are you in there?
Yun Shil.
Has she gone to the bathroom?
- Hello. - Where are you?
I thought you're in the bathroom, but you never came so I called.
I just came to the convenience store.
What made you go to the convenience store at this hour?
I had things to buy.
You should have told me. I could get them for you.
Never mind.
I'll go to the convenience store.
That's all right.
What's all right?
It's dangerous to go out at night by yourself.
It's an usual route.
I'll get some fresh air and go in.
Don't worry, okay?
Hello, Yun Shil.
What's going on?
(KBC anchor Choi Jin Yun...)
(marries CEO of Meesa Apparel, Min Hyo Sang late next month.)
My goodness.
Hello, Mum.
Have you seen the newspaper?
My secretary showed it to me a minute ago.
Which punk wrote this article?
That's what I'm saying. Who on earth is that?
As Ji Yun is such a popular anchor,
the reporters must have noticed what's going on.
There's nothing I can do.
What do you mean?
We're on the papers already.
What would people think if we don't get married?
CEO of Meesa Apparel has an issue in his private life, they can say.
Or, they can say that you were hard on her...
even before the marriage, and broke the marriage at the end.
Such rumors will spread out.
- Can you handle that, Mum? - Goodness.
Bring Choi Ji Yun home this evening.
Bingo.
I solve the matter at a single shot.
My goodness.
Stop.
Where are you going at this early hour?
Where else would I go except for meeting Tae Yang?
I heard you argued with him. Have you made up with him?
I'll go and make up with him now.
Wake up, girl!
It hurts, Mum. Why do you hit me?
Kang Tae Yang should say sorry first.
Why do you attempt to make up with him?
Does it matter who does it first?
You don't understand.
You should handle your man.
If you spoil him now,
you'll lose initiative to Kang Tae Yang.
You liked him...
- so you asked him out. - Yes.
You told him that you loved him before he did.
I did.
Then, what did Kang Tae Yang do first?
I don't know.
I think Kang Tae Yang should chase you around.
Why are you chasing around Kang Tae Yang?
Don't you have any kind of self-esteem?
Self-esteem doesn't matter when you love somebody.
My goodness.
Since you give up your initiative,
he's treating you in such a way.
- What do you mean? - Listen to me.
When you asked Kang Tae Yang whom he would rescue...
if you and his friend fell in water,
he couldn't answer, right?
Right.
So...
you should make yourself less available from today.
Keep that in mind that you're the leader...
and Kang Tae Yang is the follower.
Do you get it?
I get it.
(Darling, Honey, My Love)
It's Tae Yang.
You hurt me.
What did I tell you? Make yourself less available.
Don't respond to every attempt.
Are you saying that I shouldn't get the call when he calls me?
Trust me. I achieved everything with my wits.
If you take my advice,
you can be treated as a princess by Kang Tae Yang. Okay?
Okay.
Stop!
You shouldn't get the call.
(Darling, Honey, My Love)
Honey.
The phone has been turned off. Please leave a message.
Why is she not answering the call? Is something wrong?
I'm going to be late.
Good morning.
- Hi. - What's going on?
I wanted to clean before the new year.
I noticed on my way up,
and the windows were spotless, too.
- Did you work since morning? - Yes.
- Hello. - Hi.
Why did you come in first without telling me?
Sorry.
She came early in the morning and cleaned.
I wanted to clean everything out and start the new year fresh,
so I came in early.
I'm done cleaning, so I'll bring everyone some coffee.
Okay.
Did something good happen?
She's in a great mood.
Of course not.
She's cleaning because she's dying inside.
But...
is Hong Gi Pyo's mum still living on the second floor?
Of course.
I can't stand it every time I run into her.
She's a tough one.
- You like it two tea spoons, right? - Yes.
Thank you.
What's going on?
You seem different.
Is that a roundabout way of saying I'm pretty?
What was that?
That's right. I have something to show you.
(VIP Clients List of Wolgyesu Tailor Shop)
This is a list of orders...
made by our VIP clients.
You need to call them first,
ask how they're doing...
and call them to come in for tea when they have time.
They are the reason our tailor shop is still here today.
Okay.
These suits...
were never picked up by clients because of they move abroad,
forgot, or because their financial situations changed.
I see.
It isn't good if they pile up,
so Mr Lee used to give away...
them that are two years old to people who need them.
So you should...
filter out suits that are two years old, okay?
Why are you suddenly telling me to do it?
You should maintain the inventory and manage the clients...
in the new year.
What will you do?
I told you.
I'm going to learn tailoring for real now.
What a delinquent employee.
You make the boss do all the hard things.
I want to take it easy...
starting next year thanks to you. Is that a problem?
Okay. If it'll make life easier for you,
I can handle it.
- Thank you. - I'm the best, right?
You are.
There's a lot.
(Oh Young Eun Bakery)
What are you doing?
- Oh my gosh. - Why are you so jumpy?
It's nothing.
What are you peeking at?
Were you looking at her?
- How is she? - What do you mean?
From a man's perspective, is she attractive?
Let's see. She does seem to have an aura about her,
but she isn't my type.
Who is she, anyway?
- Oh Young Eun. - Oh Young Eun.
Who's Oh Young Eun?
You'll find out soon.
Oh Young Eun.
(Oh Young Eun Bakery)
She must be the owner.
What?
Sun Nyeo...
was peeking at Young Eun?
How did she know?
See? I knew it. I was right.
What is your relationship with that bakery woman?
Anne Shirley and Gilbert Blythe.
- She's my first love. - Anne Shirley and Gilbert Blythe.
First love?
We grew up together in the orphanage.
- So? - So what?
Are you saying you want to start something with her?
Are you insane? Start what?
Sure, my heart fluttered at first,
but what would I do now?
Be careful.
Don't get beat up by Sun Nyeo.
How did she find out?
Plus, she isn't the type to sit still.
That's right.
She wouldn't.
I'm so dead.
Darn it.
He talked so much about his first love,
that I expected a supermodel.
But she's not much different from me.
- What is it? - Well...
- Where are you? - Home. Why?
- Is everything okay? - Like what?
Nothing. As long as everything is okay. Bye.
Does she know about Young Eun and me or not?
You finished the tuxedo.
This needs to be delivered to Oh Young Eun Bakery,
I mean, Wedding Studio by 11. Would you bring it over?
Yes, Master.
(Wolgyesu Tailor Shop)
Let's go together.
It'll be quick by bus.
It's cold. Let's have lunch after we deliver this.
Okay.
How may we help you?
We're from Wolgyesu Tailor Shop. We brought Mr Hwang's tuxedo.
I see.
He just called and rescheduled the shoot because of an emergency.
How could they cancel after all the preparations were made?
This is so annoying.
We'll take their spot.
We're getting married soon, too.
What a good timing.
- Dong Jin. - We're going to take them anyway.
It would be nice to have them to look at now.
That's absurd.
Why is it absurd? Is that okay?
Yes, of course. Everything is already set up,
so you just have to change into a dress and tuxedo...
from our collection and we'll take the photos.
Wait. Where are you going?
Why would we take wedding photos?
We'll take them eventually. Let's do it now while we have time.
I'm glad I came.
You can't do this out of the blue.
Let's just go.
Let's take them now, and redo it if you don't like them.
What about her makeup?
As you can see, she is so beautiful,
she doesn't need makeup.
Seeing you in a dress,
you are blinding.
I put it on because you insisted,
but I don't know about this.
You and I are the only ones who'll see them anyway.
And I saw that wedding shoots are a trend right now...
with couples.
Hold on.
That was nice. Here we go.
Get closer please.
Closer. Closer.
- Are you okay? - Yes.
(Wolgyesu Tailor Shop)
My bride must be tired from the wedding shoot.
Don't show anyone else the photos when they come out.
They are for your eyes only.
Okay. Don't worry.
But why just me? You should check them, too.
Of course.
Liar.
As soon as we began the shoot,
you were posing as the photographer said.
You faker.
You'll be so bored without me, with no one to tease.
I'm back.
Hi. You're finally back.
Yes. Sorry.
Why are you sorry?
Did you go on a date with Mr Lee?
I wish you could get married...
before that jerk gets out of prison.
Here. You use this.
Why are you giving that to me?
You said you liked it.
That's because mine is so stiff.
Exactly. Take this.
Why are you giving me your scissors?
I can just get new ones.
It's a new year's gift, so please take it.
Goodness.
(Darling, Honey, My Love)
No!
I ignored 10 calls already.
I told you.
Don't answer the phone every time he calls.
He'll worry that something happened.
We're doing this to make him worry.
You need to play hard to get.
My hands are itching. It's driving me crazy.
I said no.
Look. Repeat after me.
I am in charge. Tae Yang is not.
Okay. Good.
Tae Yang.
Stop that.
(Announcer Choi Ji Yun marries Meesa Apparel CEO Min Hyo Sang)
"Announcer Choi Ji Yun..."
"marries Meesa Apparel CEO Min Hyo Sang next month"?
(Announcer Choi Ji Yun marries Meesa Apparel CEO Min Hyo Sang)
I'm heading out.
Good night.
Let's eat something yummy tonight.
I'll treat.
I forgot to tell you.
I promised I'd have drinks with some friends.
Do you have to go?
Just kidding. Have fun.
Let's go. I'll drop you off at home.
No. I have some things to finish up,
so I'll go home afterward. You should go.
Okay. Sorry. I'll see you at home.
Dong Jin.
Thank you for everything.
What do you mean?
Just. I just felt like thanking you.
You're so silly.
I'll bring you something yummy later,
so stay up and wait for me, okay?
You're such a good girl, Ms Shiny Eyes.
It's new year's eve and there'll be heavy traffic jam. Please hurry.
Okay. I'll see you later.
Ms Choi.
Hi. Are you just getting home from work?
Yes. I stayed behind to clean some things up.
You must be hungry. Sit down. I'll bring you dinner.
Actually,
I'm going to leave early tomorrow morning.
I'm sorry for making you wait for so long.
I had many things to take care of.
What is it?
It isn't much.
They are long johns for you and Mr Lee.
I don't think I'll be able to see you before I leave.
I'm very sorry for causing you concern.
I'm sorry, Yun Shil.
I shouldn't be so terrible to you,
but I have no choice because it's about my son.
I am committing such a grave sin against you.
Don't say that.
It's only natural, given your position.
Please be healthy.
I know things will pick up for you.
Thank you.
Yun Shil.
It's me.
Are you sleeping? Yun Shil.
She's asleep already.
I said to wait up.
Hey. Ms Shiny Eyes.
Bucket Head.
She must be deeply asleep.
Darn it. I should have had just one drink and come home...
so that she could eat this.
Those punks wouldn't let me go.
These are cupcakes from a very famous bakery,
so eat them in the morning.
Good night.
Dream of me.
Darling.
(Wolgyesu Tailor Shop)
What do you mean, Yun Shil is missing?
Are you putting on an act to get rid of me?
How am I supposed to handle it alone?
If it's meant to be, you'll meet again.
Young Eun looks exactly the same. Sam Do must be excited.
Sun Nyeo knows about Young Eun?
Next up is Tae Pyung.
Congratulations on making your comeback.
When I think about the heartaches you'll have to endure because of me,
I don't think I can handle it.
I was very happy because of you.