(The following content may not be suitable for viewers under 15.)
(Viewer discretion is advised.)
(Episode 38)
Yun Shil.
Are you up?
Is she still asleep?
It's so cold.
Good morning, Mother.
Good morning.
She cooked beef soup to wish you...
good luck on stage today.
Thank you, Mother.
Dad, breakfast's ready.
Come and eat, Dong Jin. You, too, Da Jeong.
Come and sit down.
Good morning.
I didn't sleep well last night. I'll go and lie down.
Dong Sook, you do the dishes.
Sure, Mum.
Is she unwell?
I don't know. She didn't sleep at all last night.
Where's Yun Shil?
I think she's sleeping in. I'll go and wake her.
Uncle's changed, hasn't he?
He has. He was so gloomy when he was married to Hyo Joo.
He's a different person now.
That's how great love is.
It changed me, too.
We can't let Mum find out. Watch what you say.
Let's eat.
- Okay. - Enjoy your meal.
Enjoy, everyone.
Yun Shil, come and have breakfast.
The milk's still here.
Yun Shil, are you still asleep?
Is she not in?
I'm coming in.
Yun Shil.
What's that?
Don't be too surprised.
By the time you read this,
I will be very far away from...
you and the store.
I thought for a long time how to say goodbye...
in a way that would hurt the least.
The best way...
was for me to leave quietly.
Over the past few months,
I felt so happy that...
I asked myself many times a day if I were dreaming.
That's why it was so hard.
The more I love you,
the less there is I can do for you.
That broke my heart.
You may call me a coward,
but when I think about the heartaches you'll have to endure...
because of me, I don't think I can handle it.
I was very happy...
because of you.
The fact that I experienced such great love...
will give me the courage to go on and be happy.
Forget about me, Dong Jin.
I wish you happiness.
The phone has been turned off. Please leave a message.
What...
What is she thinking?
The soup's getting cold.
What's wrong with her room?
Where's Yun Shil?
(Dear Dong Jin)
Wait.
Did she leave?
Dad.
Yun Shil left home.
She left early.
What do you mean she left home?
She disappeared leaving a letter for Dong Jin.
- Why? - I don't know.
She was in her room when I went over last night.
She must have left early in the morning.
Yun Shil left home.
I know.
She told me two days ago that she'd leave early today.
I told her to.
Honey.
What else should I have done?
My son's future's at stake.
I had to be firm.
She has no parents or siblings to rely on.
Where could she go?
I can't take in one person and ruin my own son's life.
I had to do something about it.
Even then.
Her husband will be released soon.
Who knows what he might do to Dong Jin?
Even if that is the case, you went too far this time.
I feel terrible already,
so leave me alone.
Who is it?
Please let me in.
Who could it be so early in the morning?
What are you doing here?
What's wrong?
Did Yun Shil come here?
She snuck in a few days ago while I was out...
and took all of her belongings and disappeared.
Why do you ask anyway?
Where is she?
- She left. - Where to?
I don't know. That's why I'm looking for her.
Are you putting on an act to get rid of me?
He's half out of his wits, so I don't think he's lying.
She must have gone because she knows Gi Pyo will be released.
He'll throw a fit when he hears she's gone.
What should I do about this?
You should maintain the inventory and manage the clients...
in the new year.
What will you do?
I told you. I'm going to learn...
tailoring for real now.
Did she teach me all that...
so she could leave?
I had no idea.
What's going on? Yun Shil disappeared?
She was at work just yesterday.
What happened?
Did she say or do anything out of the ordinary?
She gave me her scissors.
- Scissors? - Yes.
She said it was a new year's gift.
My pair's old and stiff so it was hard to use.
(Minkyung Farm)
Excuse me.
I'm the person who called for the job.
The young lady from Seoul?
Yes.
Nice to meet you. I'm Na Yun Shil.
Welcome.
Have you worked on a farm like this?
The work is much harder than it looks.
It might be tough.
I have worked on a vineyard before.
Have you?
Then you won't run away because the work's too hard, then.
I won't.
You can stay here after work hours.
The boiler's not working right now.
The electric blanket and gas heater should keep you warm enough.
Unpack and get changed.
Let's get to work.
Sure. Thank you.
She's asleep already.
Hey. Ms Shiny Eyes.
Bucket Head.
She must be deeply asleep.
Darn it. I should have had just one drink and come home...
so that she could eat this.
Those punks wouldn't let me go.
Hello, I'm from Wolgyesu Tailor Shop.
I came here once with Yun Shil.
I remember you.
Do you know of anywhere she might be...
or anyone she might call?
She disappeared and I'm trying to find her.
I tried calling all the merchants who know her.
None of them have talked to her recently.
Hello.
How are you?
Why are you here?
I haven't been able to reach Hyo Won.
I came by because I'm worried.
Did you...
- lock her up again? - No!
Don't you dare imply I'm a criminal.
Sorry.
Where is she right now?
I raised her in such a way that any princess would envy her.
And you came along and treated her...
like an old piece of chewing gum.
I find that insulting and upsetting.
I never treated her like chewing gum.
If she and your childhood friend were both drowning,
you said you'd save your friend.
I never said that.
I said I'd think about it.
That's the same thing!
I was joking.
Let me make something clear. In every conceivable way,
my daughter is above you.
Two people in love should be equals.
No! What I say goes.
- Yes, Ma'am. - I...
sorted things out for you.
Do not do anything to disrupt the peace and order.
I will not allow or accept it if you keep leading Hyo Won on.
I'm not leading her on.
It's more like she drags me around.
No!
- I understand. - Another thing.
The commercial you turned down.
They'll shoot on another day. So you'll have to do it.
They adjusted the date? How did that happen?
That was nothing to me.
You have the most talented manager in all of Korea.
Do you know that?
I do now.
Thank you. I'll shoot the commercial.
Okay, then. Hyo Won, show yourself.
Were you there all along?
Mum told me to hide between the chairs...
until she got you to promise.
Okay.
Not being able to see you...
made my eyes sting and water.
Not being able to talk to you...
almost made my fingers hurt.
- I missed you so much, Tae Yang. - Hey, you, Hyo Won!
I sorted things out for you! Don't sabotage my efforts!
You have the upper hand, so act like it!
Okay. I will.
Excuse me.
Hello.
Have you talked to Yun Shil today?
No, why?
Yun Shil...
disappeared.
What do you mean, Yun Shil is missing?
I don't know.
I went to her room and saw a letter. She was gone.
Are you saying that Yun Shil left home...
without telling you?
I'll go to the tailor shop right away.
Is that call from...
- Dong Jin? - Yes.
What happened to Dong Jin?
As far as I heard...
it seems that your friend left Dong Jin's house.
Does it mean that she broke up with Dong Jin?
I'll tell you later.
I have to leave because of an urgent matter.
I'll call you later.
Bye, honey.
What's the matter? What happened?
It seems Dong Jin and that girl...
- broke up. - Really?
What happened, Dong Jin?
Why has Yun Shil left home suddenly?
- I have no idea. - Something might have happened...
to Yun Shil while you haven't noticed.
I have no idea why she left.
I decided to be someone...
that Yun Shil can trust and rely on.
I'm so angry at myself and Yun Shil...
since I made her leave without telling me...
she was troubled.
I don't know what really happened,
but I guess she left because she didn't want to trouble you.
She'd rather trouble herself than make someone troubled for her.
Anyway, Ms Geum is calling...
every customer.
We'll find Yun Shil soon.
I'll contact every friend at hometown.
When the sun is strong,
strawberries soften up and become valueless.
That's why we have to start working early in the morning.
I see.
Since it's your first day here,
follow me watching how I do...
and start working right away.
All right. I'll do my best.
It's just picking up fruits. It's not hard.
Ms Choi, are you in there?
Are you there?
Who's calling me?
It must be Madam Ko.
What are you doing here?
It's been a long time since I saw you.
I also wanted to talk to you about our children.
That's why I'm here.
- May I come in? - I don't care whatever you do.
Well,
I guess Mr Lee is not home.
He went to a go club to play.
He entrusted Dong Jin with the tailor shop and enjoys his life.
This is...
ox tail.
Boil it and cook for Mr Lee.
Why have you brought that? I feel uncomfortable.
By the way,
why did you come here without telling me?
I'd like our children...
to be reunited, Ms Choi.
I'm talking about Dong Jin and Hyo Joo.
I heard that Dong Jin's new girlfriend,
the ex-convict's wife left this morning.
What are you saying? Girlfriend of whom?
Be careful of what you say.
How can you speak of the ex-convict's wife?
I heard that she fell in love with Dong Jin...
while her husband was in a jail.
You speak so carelessly.
She didn't finish the wedding...
nor did she register her marriage.
Yun Shil is a single woman.
It doesn't matter whether she is a single woman or a widow.
It seems that Hyo Joo...
still has feelings for Dong Jin.
So, you and I...
should plan a strategy...
and make them reunited.
If you want them to be reunited, you should stay out of it.
I feel heavy when I even think of...
being related with you.
Do you have to keep calling me Ms Ko?
I was once your son's parent-in-law.
You shouldn't call me that way.
There's nothing wrong with it.
You'll always be Ms Ko to me.
I was crazy.
Why have I come here in this cold weather?
My goodness, how are you?
Hello.
How have you been?
As a matter of fact,
I've wanted to visit you and talk to you.
It's nice to see you here.
What did you want to talk about?
Young Eun hasn't changed a bit.
I won't be surprised if she makes Sam Do's heart flutters.
What are you talking about?
I'm sorry.
There are so many other places in Seoul.
Why has she opened her bakery here?
I don't understand.
- Is she still missing Sam Do? - That's what I'm saying.
I'm sure she has a secret design.
My goodness. What are you going to do?
I want you to meet that vixen and find out...
why she has come to this town.
- Me? - You said you've known her long.
No, I don't know her very well.
I just saw her several times when she visited the tailor shop.
When I think of that vixen,
I have such a headache that I feel like I'm dying.
I might die before my time. Please help me.
I don't usually care about...
someone else's matter.
Please, Madam Ko.
All right.
I'll ask everything about her in detail.
- Wait here. - I trust you.
How are you?
Do you remember me?
You saw me at the Wolgyesu Tailor Shop before.
Yes, I remember.
How have you been?
Good. It's been a long time.
It's been so long.
- Please have a seat. - All right.
This shop is nice. It's neat and tidy.
I heard that you were living in America.
What made you open a bakery here?
It's a long story.
I see. I have plenty of time today.
We have enough time to talk.
My goodness. I haven't served you tea.
- What kind of tea do you like? - Me?
I'd like to have earl grey.
Wait a minute.
You should go.
What is happening to me?
I'd better tell them now that I can't do this.
What are you talking about, Dad?
My heart is pounding...
to imagine that I will be on a big stage again.
I feel like my heart would burst.
Goodness, Sung Jun.
You used to actively work here in the past.
Why are you being tense?
You're done at the Da Jeong beauty salon.
He looks much better with a professional touch.
Thank you, Da Jeong.
Thank you.
Let me go to the washroom first.
How many times have you been going to the washroom?
He must be nervous.
Why should he be tense? He just needs to sing as he can.
By the way, it's so amazing to see the stars I used to watch...
on television.
We should have brought your grandparents here.
Once Dad's new song gets popular,
we'll get to come to the broadcasting station often.
We can bring grandparents, then.
You're right.
Are you all right?
I don't think I am. My legs are shaking...
and my hearts is going to burst out.
I don't think I can sing, Dong Sook.
Be stronger.
Just be yourself.
There's no need to be nervous, Jun.
I brought herbal medicine to calm you down.
- Herbal medicine? - Yes, you should take some.
How do you feel now?
Tae Pyung, you're next. Please be on standby.
Okay!
- I need to use the washroom again. - What?
He's driving me crazy.
Dad!
We'll be watching you, so don't worry and do a good job.
You can't go to the washroom in the middle of performing, okay?
He won't, of course.
Let us wish you a good luck.
The gentleman of trot music, Tae Pyung.
My newest track, "My Brother Goes".
Please make it become a mega hit.
- You can do it! - I can do it!
Next up is a former rock balladeer...
turned trot singer, Tae Pyung.
The title of his song is "My Brother Goes".
Please give him a big hand.
He misses me!
- Sung Tae Pyung, Sung Tae Pyung! - Sung Tae Pyung, Sung Tae Pyung!
- Encore, encore! - Encore, encore!
What did she say? Why did she open her shop here?
That's not what's important.
Well... Young Eun's husband...
died in a car accident in the States.
Sorry? Does that mean she's single now?
(Wolgyesu Tailor Shop)
She kept asking me to take care of things...
and acted differently from usual. I should've known.
I... I was insensitive. It's my fault.
Why is it your fault?
Don't beat yourself up.
We were going to get through this together,
so I have no idea why suddenly...
I really don't get it.
Let's have soju together.
Gosh.
Hello, Mr Lee.
We're all feeling a bit down, so let's have soju together.
I think that life...
is a series of meetings and partings.
We all go through it repeatedly, you know.
You two will meet again if you're meant to be.
I know that the process will be difficult and painful,
but don't let your heart get wounded.
They say that time heals everything, you know.
You also...
couldn't forget Mi Soon your whole life.
Come!
That's why I'm telling you this now.
Why are you being like this?
When Mi Soon left me, I felt like my entire world had collapsed.
But I met your mum after that...
and made a happy family together as you know.
When you go on with your life,
all of those painful memories become faint and get forgotten.
I'm sorry to interrupt, Mr Lee.
Who is Mi Soon?
My first love.
You had someone like that, too?
You silly. I'm a man, too.
Of course I have a first love.
Hearing this is making me feel better for some reason.
But I must say,
I think that first love...
is like a volcano.
Even though you had forgotten all about it,
it can erupt like a volcano at any time.
You thought you had completely erased it from your heart,
but when you meet your first love again, you feel it more intensely.
A man's first love...
sure makes him cry.
This may sound strange,
but to me,
Yun Shil was like my first love.
No one has made my heart...
flutter as much as she did.
All right. On that note,
let's think about our first loves and drink up.
(Minkyung Farm)
Spin it like this. You see the plastic cover going up, right?
When it's warm, you can roll it up like this.
- Roll it down when it's cold. - I see.
Try rolling it down.
Okay.
You wouldn't have to roll it up at night,
but I'm showing you just in case.
I see.
And these are candles.
When the temperature drops to below 10°C,
you have to light these candles and put them between the furrows.
Otherwise, you'll ruin all of your hard work.
I see.
It'd be good to just turn on the heater,
but that will be too expensive.
Be careful with them, though. It's a fire hazard.
Okay, I'll keep that in mind.
It got stained by strawberries.
Gosh, today really isn't my day.
Grape stain is hard to remove.
What are you doing? Don't touch me.
(Tae Yang)
It's me, Tae Yang.
You have to think about people around you, too.
How can you just leave like this, Yun Shil?
Dong Jin is devastated.
It's really hard for me to watch him go through this.
So please come back.
If you can't come back right away,
call me at least. I'll be waiting.
Darling.
- I'm here. - Hey.
Did you see Dong Jin?
Yes.
You said that your friend and Dong Jin like each other.
Why did she leave out of the blue?
I can't get a hold of her now, so I'm not sure,
but I think that she left...
because she thought that she'd make his life difficult if she stayed.
My gosh.
She can't leave like that, though.
No matter what happens,
I'll never leave you.
Really?
Even if you get sick of me and beg me to leave,
I'll be glued to you...
like this and never leave you.
Thanks.
I happened to read...
news about Mr Min and the announcer, Choi Ji Yun.
Did you read the article about them getting married?
Did your mum approve it?
To be honest, my mum wasn't happy about it,
but the article has been published,
so she doesn't really have a choice now.
Madam Ko doesn't like it when rice is on the dry side.
Put a little extra water when you make rice.
I see.
What kind of side dishes does she like?
Unlike how she looks,
she loves traditional dishes.
Fermented soybean paste stew...
and all sorts of pickles.
She likes things that are salty and spicy.
Her taste is the opposite of mine.
Are you preparing for married life?
That sounds a bit too grand.
I was just asking her what kind of food your mum likes.
Shall we take a quick break?
Seeing you doing housework in an apron makes me...
feel like we're already married.
We'll be able to get married, right?
Of course. I mean, everyone already knows about it.
My mum has no choice now.
She'll have to give us permission.
Having drinks with you and Dong Jin...
is putting me in such a good mood.
Mr Lee. You're okay, right?
Don't worry about me.
Dad, I'm sorry for worrying you.
If I don't want to deal with any worries,
I should just be buried in a coffin.
This is proof that I'm alive,
so don't feel bad about it.
I completely agree with you, Mr Lee.
Those who are destined to meet will meet.
If Yun Shil and you are meant to be,
you two will end up meeting again, so don't be so devastated.
Let's go home now, guys.
Mr Lee, Dong Jin and you should go ahead.
I have to stop by somewhere.
- All right. See you at home. - Okay.
What's going on, Sam Do?
Nothing. I just have to see someone briefly. Go with Mr Lee.
Young Eun.
Sam Do.
- Did you drink? - Yes, a little.
Do I reek of alcohol? Shall I just leave?
No, I just smell it a little bit. Don't worry and have a seat.
- Do you want some tea? - Sure. Thanks.
- You're home. - Yes.
Where's Sam Do?
He said he has to stop by somewhere, so we came without him.
Where did this man go?
I'm sure he'll be home shortly.
- Okay. Good night, Mr Lee. - You, too.
You haven't heard anything from Yun Shil yet?
No.
You must be so worried and stressed out.
- I'll head to my room. - All right.
It looks like he went to see that woman at the bakery.
I'll catch them in the act...
and crush them.
What are you doing?
I'm making dinner.
Just because Yun Shil left doesn't mean things will change.
You have no reason to be here.
I know what you're trying to say,
but I'll be better from now on. Please?
Nothing is more pointless than married couples' spats.
Many couples get divorced only to reunite later.
So try to talk things through...
to clear up the misunderstandings you have.
Hyo Joo and I...
are over. Why are you being like this, Mum?
I'm sorry, Mother. Dong Jin.
Dong Jin.
I understand why you're reacting like this.
I've been reflecting on things that I've done.
- Then what's up with your attitude? - I'll try harder.
I'll put you first in everything I do.
Then don't show up before me ever again.
The company is in a big mess.
Our sales are dropping,
and the main shareholders are already turning their backs on us.
I need you to come back.
I no longer have any interest...
in running Meesa Apparel.
He's not in his right mind now...
because of that girl.
(Na Yun Shil)
Congratulations, congratulations
Congratulations on your first day at Wolgyesu Tailor Shop
Welcome, Mr Lee.
What are you doing now?
I'm congratulating you on your first day here.
Who told you that you can sell things in front of my shop?
I can do whatever I want.
- Leave immediately. - I can't do that.
Dad...
I'm sorry.
I miss you.
Dad... I miss you.
I'm...
asking you just in case.
I'm just really worried.
I know that it's complete nonsense. I'm asking you just in case, okay?
Do you...
have feelings for me by any chance?
Yun Shil left so many traces.
How am I supposed to get through this?
Why did you leave alone?
Oh, right.
Eun Sook came by earlier in the day.
You know, she used to be an accountant at your tailor shop.
How did Eun Sook know of this place?
I was in the middle of fermenting the dough. I'll be right back.
Okay.
How did Eun Sook know of this place?
Hello?
- Hello? - Eun Sook.
It's me, Sam Do.
Hey.
What makes you call me, Sam Do?
I'm sorry I haven't been able to call on the pretext of being busy.
By the way,
I heard you came by Young Eun's bakery this afternoon.
What?
Oh, I did.
How did you know Young Eun opened a bakery?
I heard it from the wife.
A wife? Whose wife?
Who do you think? Your wife.
- My wife? - Yes.
She asked me dearly for the information on Young Eun.
I couldn't refuse.
Are you saying that...
my wife knows about Young Eun?
Yes. When she heard Young Eun is single...
she got really tense.
Be careful.
Gosh, this is not good.
Even now, she might be watching...
you and Young Eun from somewhere.
Young Eun. Young Eun?
- What is it, Sam Do? - Something just came up.
I have to go home.
Is there something wrong?
(Oh Young Eun Bakery)
You are so busted.
I can't explain right now. I'll explain later.
No!
Why would you do that?
Why do you think?
You should have prepared to be grabbed by the hair...
when you decided to flirt with someone else's husband.
Honey, it's a misunderstanding. Let's talk about this.
Misunderstanding, my foot.
Were you showing off your muscles again? Is that it?
It's not like that, Honey. I'll explain everything at home.
"Honey"?
This is your wife, Sam Do?
Yes.
That's right.
I'm Bae Sam Do's wife.
You got it all wrong.
I don't think so.
You lied to me saying you don't go near bakeries.
You couldn't wait to see her and decided to cheat on me?
- Don't do it! - You'll die...
by my own hands.
Honey, let go. Let's talk this out.
No need for that. A vixen who flirts with a married man...
needs to learn a lesson.
I'm going to pull all her hair out.
I'll turn her into a naked chicken. You just watch me.
- Let go. Let's talk about this. - I'm not letting go.
Let go of her! Let's talk about this.
- I'm not letting go. - Let go!
How could you throw your own wife to the floor?
I told you.
I said I won't forgive you if you grab someone by the hair again.
Forgive me?
I'm not the one who should ask for forgiveness. It should be you.
You're the one who's cheating on your wife with your first love!
I'm not cheating. Watch your mouth, woman.
What is this if it's not cheating?
Why would you come here day in and day out...
without telling your wife?
Where are you going? We were in the middle of talking!
Confront me here right now!
You jerk.
Leave him be.
Let him go...
and have some tea with me.
- Cheers. - Cheers.
Congratulations on making a successful comeback, Jun.
Congratulations, Dad.
It's all thanks to you ladies.
Thank you very much.
By the way, it doesn't feel right to be celebrating by ourselves.
Mother and Father should be eating with us.
They're not in a very good mood because of Yun Shil. Just stay put.
Oh, right.
Why did Yun Shil run away from home all of a sudden?
She didn't pick up when I called this afternoon.
Honey.
About Mother...
She knows Yun Shil and Dong Jin like each other, right?
The only reason for Yun Shil to run away from home suddenly...
has to be because of Mother.
No way.
My mum did say some things to Yun Shil,
but I doubt she told Yun Shil to move out.
Then Mother does know about...
the relationship between Dong Jin and Yun Shil.
I was about to tell her,
but she already knew.
Gosh, what do we do?
Sam Do's here.
Sam Do, come get a drink.
What's wrong with Sam Do?
He looks really mad.
He does.
Sam Do, what's wrong?
I'm so embarrassed.
I can't stand it.
I didn't want Young Eun to see me like that.
What? What happened?
Your sister-in-law grabbed Young Eun by the hair...
and didn't let go.
She humiliated me.
Gosh.
I told you to be more careful.
I didn't do anything.
I can swear on my mother's grave.
I just felt nostalgic.
My heart fluttered and I was happy.
That was it.
And your sister-in-law ruined everything.
Are you crying, Sam Do?
What's going on?
Let's go outside.
What is it? What's wrong with Sam Do?
Did he get conned again?
It's not like that.
Sun Nyeo.
Sun Nyeo, Sun Nyeo.
Sam Do is crying.
Sam Do is crying?
He's crying a lot.
Why are you crying over something like that? Aren't you a man?
I'm sorry.
I made a mistake, Honey.
I wasn't trying to humiliate you.
It was thoughtless of me. Come on, Honey.
Come on.
Don't be like that.
Let's talk this out. Face-to-face.
Put that blanket away so we can talk about this.
I was so busy in the morning...
to go over this.
(To Mr Pretty Eyes)
Gosh.
(Ms Shiny Eyes)
The number you have dialed is not available.
Please leave a message after the tone.
Hey, Ms Shiny Eyes.
Where did you run off to after leaving me behind?
You must want to play hide-and-seek with me.
I'm not that idle of a person.
Come back right now.
If you come back now,
I'll forget about everything.
So come back to Mr Pretty Eyes right now.
If you don't,
I might really get mad.
(Mr Pretty Eyes)
Dong Jin.
I am well.
So don't forget to eat...
and attend to your job at the tailor shop.
Don't let me make you suffer.
(Delete)
(Selection exam for appointment of middle school teachers in Seoul)
Thank you for driving me, Hyo Won.
Hold on.
There you go.
- Eat this and pass the exam. - Thank you.
Wait a minute.
What is it this time?
All charged up. You can go now.
I'll call you when I'm done.
(Selection exam for appointment of middle school teachers in Seoul)
Please let Tae Yang pass the exam...
and make his dream come true.
- I pray for him. - My gosh.
Why did you have to follow me here, Mum?
You should be wishing for him to fail the exam.
What do you think you're doing? Wishing him good luck?
Why would you say that? You're going to jinx it.
Tae Yang studied really hard for years for this exam.
Why would I want him to fail?
You fool.
He needs to fail this exam to continue working as a model.
Would you rather be a celebrity's wife or a teacher's wife?
I like both of the options.
They are both good,
but which one do you think will be more profitable?
- Well... - So...
you should be wishing for him to fail this exam. Okay?
I don't know anymore. You can wish whatever you like.
- I'll wish for him in my own way. - Okay.
Please.
(Minkyung Farm)
I'm sorry to ask you for a favour in such short notice.
My husband usually goes for direct deliveries,
but an order got placed when he happens to be at a hospital.
It's okay. Where should I deliver it to?
It's a dessert cafe in Jongno, Seoul.
It's in Jongno?
We don't usually accept rush deliveries,
but they are an old regular customer.
They said they're in a hurry...
because they received a large order of cakes and I couldn't refuse.
Okay. I'll be back.
Have a safe trip.
There's no need to hurry so don't rush.
Okay.
I made up my mind not to go to Seoul for a while...
and the place of delivery happens to be near the tailor shop.
They say you don't realize someone's value until that person goes absent.
With Yun Shil gone, the shop feels completely empty.
(Chief Director Kim Jae Young)
Yes, Chief Director. I was waiting for your call.
There was a board meeting just now.
Because the annual sales and brand awareness were too low,
they decided not to place Wolgyesu Tailor Shop at the mall.
But I think I made my points...
clear about that with my presentation.
This is off the record,
but I heard CEO Min Hyo Sang of Meesa Apparel sabotaged it.
CEO Min Hyo Sang of Meesa Apparel?
Placing a tiny shop like Wolgyesu Tailor Shop...
at the mall...
not only lowers the overall quality of Jeil Department Store,
but it'll tarnish the pride...
of Meesa Apparel.
Right. Okay. Thanks, Mr Kim.
Okay, we should get a drink together soon.
Okay.
(CEO Min Hyo Sang)
How dare a tiny corner store try to enter a department store?
Mr Min came in the way of Wolgyesu Tailor Shop entering the mall.
- Hyo Sang did that? - Yes.
He threatened to pull out the men's wear stores of Meesa Apparel...
if they decide to place Wolgyesu Tailor Shop there.
How dare you spoil someone else's business...
when you can't even take care of your own?
You jerk.
Thank you for sending us fresh and nicely shaped ones.
Please send her my regards.
I will. Goodbye.
Isn't this too harsh?
Don't you think this is too much? We're not even that close right now.
I'm sorry.
(Wolgyesu Tailor Shop)
I know I'm not a welcome customer,
but don't you think it's a bit harsh...
to sigh at my face without even greeting me?
What is it this time?
I heard.
You proposed your tailor shop to be placed at Jeil Department Store...
and you got rejected.
It's none of your business.
How is it none of my business?
Your business is my business.
I'm in no mood to listen to you being pushy.
Go home.
Do you know you're in this situation because of Hyo Sang?
You can barely get a deal with a department store.
You can't deal with Hyo Sang and his mum alone.
I will help you.
(Wolgyesu Tailor Shop)
(Minkyung Farm)
(The Gentlemen of Wolgyesu Tailor Shop)
Mums love sons-in-law.
Are you looking out for him already?
Over my dead body.
I won't let you marry Tae Yang, okay?
Have you heard from Yun Shil?
I wonder if the poor thing gets three square meals a day.
I told you that...
I would get a divorce if you start a fight again.
A test? Am I dying?
Is she sick?
We have a lot of history with rain.
I miss you more when it rains.