(The following content may not be suitable for viewers under 15.)
(Viewer discretion is advised.)
(Episode 39)
(Wolgyesu Tailor Shop)
What on earth are you doing?
You have punished me...
and given me enough of a hard time.
So please...
forgive me and come back to me.
You don't belong here.
My Dad devoted his youth...
and hard work all to Meesa Apparel.
That's where your dream has to be.
Meesa Apparel is where you belong.
How many times have I told you? I'm not interested.
It's past to me.
I told you.
The company is in a difficult condition.
Some major shareholders and executive team...
are carrying forward your return.
Tell them to stop it.
I don't want to go back.
Is it because of that woman?
Wake up. Face the reality.
Can a man like you...
live humbly and be satisfied with it?
Can you calm down the ambition inside you?
She went to find her life leaving you behind...
hearing that Hong Gi Pyo will be released.
Don't you understand that she took advantage of you and left you?
Have you met Na Yun Shil?
You are not answering me. You must have met her.
What on earth did you tell Yun Shil?
Have you ever told her to leave me?
Do you think I have time for that trivial matter?
I don't understand what she has done to you.
I can't understand how such an ambitious man like you...
can be changed this way.
I don't want to listen to you anymore. Go back.
I know who you are.
You're not a man to be satisfied with this small tailor shop.
You will come back to me.
I will be waiting for you for the time being.
You will be connected to the voice mail after the beep.
It's raining.
I wonder whether it rains...
where you are now, Yun Shil.
We have a lot of history with rain.
I miss you more...
when it rains.
It's cold.
(Mr Pretty Eyes)
You left suddenly,
but you might think of me on a day like this.
If it's difficult for you to call me,
Leave me a message that you're doing all right.
I would be relieved if I could listen to your voice.
You took trouble to study for difficult exam.
Take the chicken leg.
- Thank you. - In this dish...
I put every medicinal ingredients good for heath including...
Korean native chicken, milk vetch root, ginseng and senticosus.
They say it is the mother who loves the son-in-law.
Are you already taking care of the son-in-law to be?
I wouldn't have made this if you did well in the exam.
I'm doing a favor since I heard that you didn't do well.
What do you mean?
I have a plan to make you, Kang Tae Yang,
as a Korean Wave star.
If you pass the exam, that will make things complicated.
Are you sure that you ruined the exam?
I didn't ruin it...
but I don't think I did very well.
Good. You did a good job ruining the exam.
Get nutritious food.
Help yourself.
Open your mouth.
You have a few days left until the shooting.
Let's take a facial massage after the meal.
I haven't done such a thing before.
It's an evidence of your being a natural born Korean Wave star...
that you have such a perfect skin...
even though you haven't given a facial massage before.
It's your destiny.
You seem to have too much expectation for me.
I'm working as a model just because it's paid well.
It's not that anyone can be a Korean Wave star.
I'm not a right person to be such a star.
We can make you one.
Don't worry about that.
Help yourself.
Open your mouth.
- Good. - Open your mouth.
Good job.
Eat up.
That's good.
Why did you take me here?
You're supposed to take a massage after dinner.
You should wash your face before the massage.
Here you go.
Over your face.
There you go.
Wait a minute. I can do it myself.
As you studied hard for the exam,
I will give you a facial massage today.
You don't need to lift a finger.
I'm fine.
All right.
You're so adorable.
Good.
Here you go. We are almost done.
- Do you feel refreshed? - I do.
Blow your nose.
I'm fine.
There you go.
Lie down on the bed.
Why?
You should lie down so that I can give you a massage.
I really don't need a massage.
Here you go.
You just lie down and relax.
I will give you a massage.
It tickles.
Wait for a while.
Are you sleepy?
I was tense taking the exam whole day.
I feel sleepy as you're giving me a massage.
I will give you a massage singing you a lullaby.
Get some sleep.
When Mum goes to the shade of the island
To catch the oysters
The baby is left alone
To take care of the house
He's sleeping like a baby.
He's so adorable.
As he's sound asleep,
I get sleepy, too.
- Did you meet Dong Jin? - Mind your own business.
And...
why did you meet Mother without telling me and upset her?
Do you think I had nothing to do except meeting your mother-in-law?
I wanted to make you and Dong Jin reunited.
I told you.
You mess up things.
Can't you say in a nicer way?
You seem to get old, Hyo Joo.
You wouldn't have forgiven Dong Jin before,
if he had an affair with another girl.
Watch your mouth. He didn't have an affair.
He just sympathized her.
It's all the same whether it's a dried pollack or a frozen pollack,
whether it's a yellow colored radish or a pickled radish.
Are you adding fuel to the fire?
Goodness, you scare me.
I'm home.
You're making cabbage pancakes.
Your cabbage pancakes are the delicacy of the winter.
As it rained and I felt disturbed...
I thought making some fried food would make me feel better.
It stopped raining, Mum.
It tastes so good.
Yun Shil loved your cabbage pancake.
Right?
I wonder where she is.
To be honest,
when I first found out Dong Jin and Yun Shil...
liked each other, I felt like he was losing out,
so I kind of hated her a little.
But now that she left,
I feel bad.
Stop babbling and go up to Sung Joon.
Okay.
I'll bring him...
some cabbage pancakes.
You should eat while it's still warm.
- Ms Choi, I'm here. - Hi. Come on in.
Did you have dinner yet?
Not yet.
We had tasty cabbage, so I made pancakes.
It isn't much, but I called you over to try some.
Did I bother you for nothing?
What do you mean?
I love cabbage pancakes.
Goodness. I'm glad.
Here. Have some.
How is it? Does it taste good?
Why are you crying?
It reminded me of my late mum.
She used to make me cabbage pancakes, too.
It tastes just like hers.
You poor dear.
From now on,
consider me your mum.
I'll consider you my daughter, too.
Let's lean on each other.
Thank you.
I wonder if the poor thing...
gets three square meals a day.
Are you still upset about that? Be a man.
(Petition for Divorce)
- What's this? - Can't you tell?
- Divorce papers. - What? Divorce papers?
We made a promise.
I said one more fight, and we'll get a divorce.
- Yes, but... - Keep your promise.
- I don't have my seal. - You can just sign it.
- I have no sign. - Then your fingerprint.
You know I have no fingerprint.
Are you toying with me? Sign it,
put your fingerprint or seal on it. Do it.
You've lost your mind.
Why are you asking for a divorce over something like that?
"Something like that"?
Is humiliating your husband in front of Young Eun is nothing?
This is why I had no choice but to be suspicious.
What's so great about Oh Young Eun that you're talking divorce?
I'm speechless.
I don't want to talk to you any more, so sign it.
Why would I? For whom?
I refuse.
Don't rip it up. Don't.
That stubborn mule.
I'm too humiliated to walk with my head up.
Did that witch Young Eun tell him to divorce me and live with her?
What's gotten into him?
When I was six,
I met Sam Do for the first time at the orphanage.
I was sent there after my parents died in an accident.
My entire world had changed overnight,
so I just couldn't adapt.
There was one time when I developed aphasia and couldn't speak.
I peed in my bed every morning,
so the kids teased me...
and the director scolded me.
- That's how it was. - You poor thing.
Sam Do used to stand up for me and take my side each time.
You know...
he can't bear to watch other suffering.
Well, that's true.
That's why I leaned on him...
as if he were my real brother,
and he protected me like his real sister.
Sam Do and I...
like comrades who fought a war together.
There's nothing romantic.
Still, I heard you were his first love.
That's...
because we met when we were highly emotional.
It's like a childhood memory.
Nothing that you worry about will ever happen.
But of all the neighbourhoods,
why did you move here?
After my husband suddenly passed away,
I didn't know how to survive.
I felt like there was no one in the entire world...
who was on my side.
Then suddenly...
I remembered Sam Do.
I wasn't sure whether or not...
he was still working at the tailor shop,
but I wanted to go where the last person on my side...
may possibly be.
That's why I moved here,
but if it bothers you that much,
I'll go somewhere else.
Well... Well... There's no need.
I've always received from Sam Do.
I can do that much for him.
I want him to be happy more than anyone.
She wouldn't have gone against her word...
after saying all that.
Oh, my head.
I have a headache.
We're home.
- What? - Were you asleep?
Yes.
I must've dozed off.
You look really happy.
It's all thanks to you.
I booked the hotel.
- Hotel? - For the wedding.
This is ridiculous.
How could my only son get married...
- because of reporters? - Mum.
What? Are you hurt?
No.
I'll work much harder...
and become a daughter-in-law that you like.
Just like an announcer.
What a smooth talker.
- Where's Hyo Won? - She must be in her room.
She should be with Tae Yang.
What are they doing alone in the room? Move away.
What?
Did Tae Yang come here again?
That punk.
This is so annoying.
Hyo Won.
What do you think you're doing?
Hey!
Why you crazy...
Hey! Get away from each other right now!
Why are you here?
I was giving you a facial massage...
- and got sleepy, so I slept. - What?
You're dead.
- What did you do to my sister? - What do you mean?
Like you don't know?
What did you do to that naive kid?
- Let go of him! - Stay out of it, brat.
Get up. Get up, you rat.
- Hey, hey, hey. - While we're at it, let's fight.
Why are you doing this? Please calm down.
Why should I calm down?
You're banned from our house from this moment on.
Who are you to ban him?
If you bother Tae Yang, I won't forgive you!
- You can't his your brother. - Stay out of it!
- Get out! - Hey!
Freeze!
If you keep fighting like this,
I'll break up all four of you!
Hyo Sang. Ji Yun.
Hwo Won. Tae Yang!
You fight whenever you meet.
If you keep fighting like this,
both couples will have to break up!
- Mother. - Mother.
You must be in a bad mood because of my brother.
- I'm sorry. - It was understandable.
I must have been tired from the exam.
I didn't realize I fell asleep.
I'm sorry.
It was my fault that made you grabbed by the collar.
How could you fall asleep next to a man like it's nothing?
I wasn't nothing.
I was very nervous.
But I really liked it.
Let's get married soon.
Then I can fall asleep with you every day...
without worrying about Mum or Hyo Sang.
I'm sorry.
I'm not ready yet, so give me a little time.
Go in.
Your mother and brother will be waiting.
My energy's been depleted. I can't walk home.
Let's see. To go from the gate to the door,
a 30-percent charge should suffice.
What about the walk from the door to the staircase?
Okay, 20 percent more.
I've been charged 50 percent.
But I need to go to my room from the staircase...
in order to sleep.
50 percent won't suffice?
It's not enough. Fill it up, please.
100 percent fully charged.
Okay, then you should go.
Okay. Get home safely, Darling.
What a sight.
Were you peeking?
I wasn't peeking.
I was waiting to talk to you and happened to see it.
I have nothing to say to you.
Tae Yang, are you really going to do this?
I forgot.
I should give him this.
You still haven't told Hyo Won about us, have you?
What are you thinking?
The longer you drag it out, the more hurt she'll be.
What is this about?
So please, stop.
I told you.
I don't plan to stop,
so if you're uncomfortable, break up with Hyo Sang.
Hey. That makes no sense.
Hyo Sang and I dated much before the two of you did.
Most people call that cheating.
- What? - I'll tell you one last time.
I have no intention of leaving Hyo Won,
so if our relationship makes you uneasy and awkward,
you break up with Hyo Sang.
Fine. Then I'll tell Hyo Won.
Do you think she'll love you as much as she does now...
once I tell her the truth about our relationship?
She'll kick you out that very day.
I'll take care of my own business.
Ji Yun.
Take care of your own life.
Don't stick your nose into other people's lives.
Hey, Tae Yang.
I didn't know you'd hold me back this much.
I never should have dated you!
You and I never should have met!
I need to tell you something.
What is it?
Remember I told you I was seeing someone before I met you?
Yes.
I want to tell you about her.
Are you getting back together?
I think you should know who she is.
Don't tell me. I don't want to hear it.
Please. I don't want to hear it.
So...
Tae Yang's ex-girlfriend is Ji Yun.
How could this be?
We need to talk.
I have nothing to say to you.
Get your act together.
Why do you have such poor taste in men?
What about you? Are you a good judge of women?
Hey. Ji Yun is a good catch anywhere.
A woman who leaves her man for a rich man is a good catch?
What? What are you mumbling?
Forget it. I don't feel like talking to you.
Hey. I've made myself clear.
I will never let you...
marry that jerk. Got it?
I'll give my life to stop your marriage.
I know it's a small world, but still.
How could Tae Yang's ex-girlfriend be my brother's fiancee?
What do I do now?
Are you drinking because you're upset about Yun Shil?
Would you like a drink?
Shall I?
It's nice.
Did you finish late?
Yes. A singer flaked, so I had to fill in.
Anyway, have you heard from Yun Shil?
No.
It'd be less frustrating if I knew why she left.
I'm starting to get angry.
It feels like tattling, so I stressed days and nights...
about whether to tell you this.
I feel like I should tell you, and that it will...
help you find her.
Your mother...
knows about you and Yun Shil.
She does?
Yes, according to Dong Sook,
she's known all along.
Therefore, based on my excellent deduction skills,
your mother probably...
said something to Yun Shil.
It's Dong Jin. May I come in?
Okay. Come in.
Is the room warm?
Of course.
Did you drink?
I couldn't sleep, so I had a drink.
Mother,
did you really...
do it?
What?
Did you...
tell Yun Shil...
to leave?
Yes.
I told her to leave.
I told her that I'll never accept her as my daughter-in-law,
and to leave our house as well as the tailor shop.
How could you do that to someone...
so kind and sad?
This is all she has to rely on.
How could you...
be so terrible?
Were you...
Were you such a cruel person?
Were you?
Keep your voice down.
How dare you say your mother is cruel?
Your mother knows Yun Shil better than you...
and no doubt did she care for her more than you did.
If your mother said that, she must have had her reasons.
What reasons?
What reasons could possibly explain her actions?
I...
can't bear to see my son throw himself into a fire pit.
You have bright future ahead of you.
I can't watch you ruin your life because of Yun Shil.
No matter how cruel you say I am...
and how much more you criticise me, I can't help myself.
This text is to inform you that your album has been completed.
We have posted your album to the given address...
and I have attached a few of your best shots below.
If Mother had said something like that, you should have told me.
How could you just leave like that?
(No Title)
(This text is to inform you that your album has been completed.)
Please stand closer together.
A bit more, please.
- Are you alright? - Yes.
You can't just go to work like that.
You should eat your breakfast.
(I'm not eating anything you cook.)
"I'm not eating anything you cook."
How can a man be so narrow-minded?
You're not going to eat over something like that?
I formally apologised to Yeong Eun...
and she told me she understands.
So, you should forgive me, too.
Are you really going to act this way?
Why on earth are you not speaking with me?
(I refuse to speak with you.)
People make mistakes!
Why are you acting like such a girl and refusing to talk...
over such a small issue?
That man is becoming more stubborn...
and narrow-minded as he gets older.
Gosh, I feel dizzy.
Why do I feel so dizzy?
Now that we're all here, let's eat.
Dong Jin's not here yet.
Maybe he overslept.
There he comes. Come have breakfast.
No, I'm not hungry.
I have work to do, so I'll have to leave early.
- Bye. - Goodbye.
Is something wrong?
He looks upset.
Maybe he lost his appetite because he's upset over Yun Shil.
Let's begin eating.
- Thank you for the wonderful meal. - Thank you.
This looks delicious.
Dong Jin.
Can you give me a minute?
If you act like this, what does that make me?
Don't worry about it.
I understand how you feel,
but you should try to understand Mother, too.
To all parents, their children always come first.
I know.
Your sister and I also left voice messages to Yun Shil.
The entire family is waiting. I'm sure she'll come back soon.
Don't worry too much.
Gosh.
When a company launches a new product line,
it's only natural for sales to drop until things get stable.
Why should something like that make the news?
These writers...
They can't stand to see other people succeed.
Come in.
Yes, what is it?
There's something suspicious about the CEO of Meesa Apparel.
- Are you talking about Hyo Joo? - Yes.
She's personally meeting with the major shareholders these days.
She's separately contacting...
the board members that worked for Dong Jin as well.
For what reason is she meeting with them?
My thought is that she's creating a public opinion...
regarding Dong Jin's comeback.
- What? - According to rumors,
Ms Min released the news about the drop in stocks and sales.
Oh, dear. This means trouble.
Why can't Hyo Joo just stay put?
Why does she have to go and cause trouble?
Is anyone here?
What brings such a busy person like you here?
Of course I've come to have a suit made, why else?
I'd like to see for myself what makes your suits...
so different from Meesa Apparel's.
You can't compare off-the-peg suits to custom-tailored suits.
I guess that's true.
Still, I'd like to see what makes you so confident to think...
you can sell your suits in department stores.
I'd like to wear one myself.
I don't understand...
why you care so much about the Wolgyesu Tailor Shop.
Our shop is just...
a small neighborhood shop compared to Meesa Apparel.
How dare we try and get in your way...
by trying to launch our suits in department stores?
What are you talking about?
Obviously, mass production of custom-tailored suites is difficult.
That would make it hard to meet consumers' expectations.
I only expressed my concerns that...
that sort of situation might cause a negative effect...
on the entire suit industry.
That's our business.
Anyway,
I heard Hyo Joo was going around
saying that your returning to the company.
Is that true?
Then what will happen to this tailor shop?
Do you want to fight with me again over taking control of the company?
What's coming out of your sister's mouth has nothing to do with me.
I was just about to leave, so you stay and order your suit.
Master Bae here is...
much more skilled than the experts at Meesa Apparel.
Master Bae.
Yes, Mr Lee.
Please make both a coat and a suit...
- for this young man sitting here. - Okay.
Then I'll let you take care of your business.
He always has to act so conceited.
Would you like to order a suit?
- Yes. - Please let me measure you.
Of course.
Hold your arms up towards the front, please.
Arms to the front.
- Relax your shoulders. - Okay.
Next,
lie down touching the floor with both hands.
- The floor? - Yes. That's how it's done here.
Go ahead.
Are you being serious?
Alright.
Who measures like this?
- Relax your shoulders, please. - Yes.
Goodness. I left the measurement...
recording sheets downstairs.
I'll be right back with them.
Pardon? Downstairs?
Hey. Hey. Master Bae.
You left your hot coffee on my back. It's hot!
Where do you think you're going?
Hey!
Yun Shil,
after your finished working here, could you gather up the products...
and make a delivery to the farmer's market in Seoul?
Yes, of course.
You're good at everything you do.
You're such a blessing to us all.
Have you heard from Yun Shil?
No. And I sent dozens of texts and voice mails.
Should we call the police?
I've been wondering if Gi Pyo's minions...
somehow got to her.
I don't think so. Don't worry.
Okay, then. Tell me as soon as you hear from her.
I'll do the same.
Okay. Bye.
Is Hyo Won still in bed?
(To Hyo Won)
Are you still dreaming?
Is she still asleep?
I'll be late for work.
(Are you still dreaming?)
I'll tell you one last time.
I have no intention of leaving Hyo Won,
so if our relationship makes you uneasy and awkward,
you break up with Hyo Sang.
Fine.
Then I'll tell Hyo Won.
Do you think she'll love you as much as she does now...
once I tell her the truth about our relationship?
Why does it have to be Ji Yun? There are plenty of other girls.
Hyo Won, are you still asleep?
What's wrong? Are you sick?
I'm coming down with something.
You don't have a fever.
- I want to sleep. - Okay.
Did you take some medicine?
I did just now.
Try to sleep.
If you still feel sick after that, I'll take you to see a doctor.
Okay, thanks.
He didn't mean to hide it.
He wanted to tell me and I didn't let him.
Tae Yang did nothing wrong.
No.
He should have told me even when I told him not to.
His ex is about to become my sister-in-law.
What a jerk.
I'm coming for you, Tae Yang.
Here's the menu.
Half-fried, half-soy, please.
Sure. That's our best-seller.
Half-fried, half-spicy.
Can I go to the pharmacy?
I feel so dizzy.
Why is everything spinning?
Mrs Bok. Mrs Bok!
What's wrong with you?
Mrs Bok. Are you okay?
Do you know who I am?
I'm usually very healthy and I rarely catch a cold.
Suddenly everything around me started to spin...
and then I fainted.
Did you have any other symptoms?
Such as migraines?
Yes, I've been having headaches.
Once I get them, it feels like my head's breaking apart.
My eyes are dim...
and I feel nauseous as well.
Maybe that's why, but I forget...
things I said just a while ago.
Do you have hearing problems or do your hands or feet feel numb?
Do you think your senses are dulling?
I guess you could say that.
Actually, I've been under a lot of stress lately.
That could be the cause of the headaches.
I feel better after a lie down.
I think you need a thorough examination.
An examination?
Headaches have so many causes, so I'll need to run some tests.
Based on your symptoms...
you could have a brain haemorrhage or a tumour.
A brain tumour?
Isn't a tumour cancer?
Do I have cancer?
Then...
will I die?
It's just a possibility.
The test results will reveal what it is.
We'll run the tests right now.
The results take a few days, so I'll see you then.
No wonder.
I'd been having weird headaches.
I'd never had headaches before.
Do I have cancer?
Sam Do.
What are you doing here? You didn't say you'd visit.
I came to see you.
Have a seat.
Thanks.
Wait while I bring some tea.
Forget the tea and sit down.
Okay. Shall I?
One is for your staff...
and one is for your wife.
I don't know what to say.
I'm sorry for what happened yesterday.
You don't have to apologise.
I should've stopped my wife.
I'm such a terrible husband.
I was so jealous.
You always yearned to be loved...
and it was good to see your wife loves you very much.
Her kind of love can be suffocating.
You're home early. We're...
Is she sick or something?
She had a huge fight with Sam Do yesterday.
Both Dong Jin and Sam Do are going through a rough patch.
I feel guilty to act like newly married couples.
Even my phone's letting me down.
Hello, you reached Tae Pyung, the Gentleman of Trot.
The Sparling Festival?
Yes, of course I can come and sing.
Hello, this is Lee Dong Sook, Tae Pyung's manager.
Yes.
You can negotiate with me.
What's there to negotiate? Just say I'll do it.
He should be paid as much as any competitor would pay him.
Give him 30 more dollars.
We have to pay for...
petrol and food, you know.
Yes. Of course.
Thank you very much. Bye.
Really? 30 more dollars?
(Deposit)
- Here. - Just a moment.
You're not from here, are you?
I'm not. I just started working at a nearby farm.
It's a small neighbourhood...
so I know most of the regulars.
I see.
You don't have a passbook.
I don't.
I'm back.
Hello.
How do you feel?
Much better.
What are these?
They were a gift.
One's for my wife.
What great timing.
I was wanting something sweet for dessert.
Are you in?
What's she doing back here?
What do you want?
I had some time to think.
Did you smuggle Yun Shil away because...
you got afraid my son is getting paroled?
That's not true. Please leave.
If you didn't smuggle her away,
why else would she suddenly leave?
Why are you asking us that?
We're going crazy ourselves.
I could have my son's boys go and look for her.
You can do whatever you want.
Give me this month's rent.
Why ask me for it?
Who else should I get it from?
Get it from whoever rented the place, not me.
You kicked out my tenant to move in yourself.
That's nonsense. I'm not paying you anything.
If you want your rent, find Yun Shil and get it from her.
If you don't pay up, I'll report you to the police.
I don't care what you do.
Until you find Yun Shil,
don't expect me to pay you a penny.
- How dare... - She's helplessly stubborn.
(500 dollars deposited)
It's Yun Shil.
Did she text you?
The text isn't from her exactly.
She just wired me her rent.
Can you come with me to the bank?
Someone just wired me some money.
Can you tell me which branch it's from?
I will if you give me your ID card.
Here you go.
It came through one of our branches, so I can tell you right away.
It was wired from Hwaseong Central branch by Ms Na Yun Shil.
- Hwaseong Central branch? - Yes.
What are you doing in Hwaseong?
If my mum said that to you, you should have told me about it.
Why did you just leave?
Wait for me. I'm coming over.
How could sweet Dong Jin talk back at me like that?
My heart's still pounding.
He got frustrated...
and raised his voice. He didn't talk back.
Don't get too upset.
Even so,
how could he call me cruel?
I cried my heart out once Yun Shil left.
Dong Jin left this morning without even...
looking at me.
Kids are useless. There's no point in having them.
Do you really not know?
You know where she is, don't you?
Do you not believe me, either?
I said I don't know where she is.
If someone were...
sending you away,
would you tell the person where you're going?
She wouldn't want to.
My goodness.
I'll see you again soon.
Bye.
Hello? It's Yun Shil.
I just dropped off the last one.
Okay, see you soon.
(Mr Lee Man Sool)
(Accept call)
- Hello? - Yun Shil.
Hello, Sir.
I feel better now that...
I heard your voice.
I'm sorry.
I had to leave without saying goodbye.
Don't apologise. We practically threw you out.
I should apologise.
But Yun Shil.
I think we should meet up.
I'll come to where you are.
I'm sorry, Sir.
It's an old man's wish.
I will...
lose my sight soon.
Even if I want to see your face...
I won't be able to.
Let's meet up.
Where are you?
I will come to you.
How is...
everyone doing?
What do you think? You just upped and left.
- Sorry. - You shouldn't apologise.
It's on me and my wife. We said that...
we cared for you like our own and we sent you away.
No.
You both were so good to me.
I betrayed you.
It's not wrong for people to fall in love.
Don't feel bad for me...
or my wife.
Yun Shil.
I think that...
Dong Jin is really struggling.
He's running about looking for you.
I know you feel bad for leaving,
but the people you left behind feel just as tortured.
I'm so sorry.
I'm really sorry.
Shouldn't you be saying that to Dong Jin, not me?
So...
come back to the store.
I'm really sorry but I can't do that.
Will you...
give up your dream of becoming Korea's greatest female tailor?
Your relationship is important,
but don't forget that you're a tailor.
You're picking fruit when you should be making suits.
That makes no sense.
I understand what you're saying,
but now is not the time.
I gave Ms Choi my word...
and if I stay here...
Dong Jin will find me.
I don't want him...
to go against his mother because of me.
I'm looking for someone.
I heard she made a deposit here a few hours ago.
This lady...
She said she works at an orchard.
What's the matter?
An orchard?
Have you seen her?
Does she work here?
No, she doesn't.
(Shiitake Mushrooms)
Have you seen this woman?
No, I haven't.
Could you take another look?
- I was told she works nearby. - I haven't seen her.
(Shiitake Mushrooms)
Your relationship is important,
but don't forget that you're a tailor.
The man you told me about?
His girlfriend betrayed him...
and went to a rich guy. What's his name?
Who's the jerk who's giving you a hard time?
I'd like to see his face.
It's Kang Tae Yang.
I'm not the kind of person for you.
I'm poor and from a worthless family.
I doubt anything will improve.
Is there any other reason we can't get together?
I have no intention of dating Min Hyo Sang's sister.
Hyo Won.
There's something I didn't tell you.
Before I told you I liked you,
- I wondered if I should tell you. - Is it serious?
- A bit. - Must you tell me today?
If I don't tell you today, it could cause a misunderstanding.
I'd rather not hear it.
Today's a happy day because you told me you like me.
Don't ruin the mood.
Remember I told you...
I was seeing someone before I met you?
I feel like I'm deceiving you.
I think you should know who she is.
Don't tell me. I don't want to hear it.
Please.
I don't want to hear it.
- Hyo Won. - It's in the past.
He's extra handsome today.
How can I leave someone like him?
I can never break up with him.
- Hello. - I texted you this morning.
I had a fever and slept after taking some medicine.
- Sorry. - Are you very sick?
- Just a bit. - I'll come by after work.
No, don't.
Why not?
I have the flu and it's very contagious.
I'll call you when I feel better.
Then...
drink some warm water and rest.
Honey.
What did you just call me?
I said "honey".
This is...
the first time...
you said that.
You said you're sick and I wanted to cheer you up.
Get some rest.
I'll call you after work.
Honey.
That was so embarrassing.
He's...
the first man who called me that.
I can't leave him.
I can't.
Never ever.
(Minkyung Farm)
How did he find here?
Excuse me.
A man will come here and ask whether I am here.
Tell him I'm not here and you don't know me.
Is he a creditor?
Right. He's a creditor.
So don't tell him I'm here, please.
All right.
Excuse me. I'm looking for someone.
It's her.
Is she working here?
I don't know.
I haven't seen her before.
That person is not working in this farm.
I see.
Why would such a young girl...
work in a farm like this?
She's not in the neighbourhood.
(The Gentlemen of Wolgyesu Tailor Shop)
You don't have a consideration for someone left behind?
Is the promise you made with me nothing to you?
My son my might die soon.
I'm sorry, Dong Jin.
Why have you been to the obstetrics?
We should get married.
How can you talk about getting married so easily?
Please forgive me. I'm begging you.
What are you doing here?
After you left, the company has been in a mess.
- Are you going to go back? - An interview?
Is your face going to be on the newspaper?
Seung Woo needs a dad.
I found out where Yun Shil is.
Yun Shil, Yun Shil!