(The following content may not be suitable for viewers under 15.)
(Viewer discretion is advised.)
(Episode 4)
- Who are you?
-  Who are you?
- Thief!
-  What?
You're the thief.
My gosh.
What are you doing here?
It's you again.
Did you follow me?
What... What are you doing?
Don't... Don't come near me.
I'll call the police.
Stay away.
I said stay away!
Hey!
Let me say something, too.
Who are you?
Why did you sneak in here like a little cat?
What little cat?
What more do you want to know about Gi Pyo, and why did you follow me?
How long have you been tailing me?
Do you think I'm that bored? Why would I tail you, lady?
Tell the truth before I call the police.
What were you doing in someone else's store?
This isn't someone else's store. It's mine.
Is this store yours?
I'm not getting through to you. I should call the police.
Do whatever you want. Call the police.
My goodness.
There you are.
What's going on?
I caught a thief.
A thief?
It's been a while. How are you?
Fine, thanks.
- He is Mr Lee's son.
-  What?
Do you know her?
Have you two never met?
She works here.
What?
I should go, then.
Your mother's having a hard time. Look after her.
Call her often.
I will. Bye.
He's not at all like his father.
He's a jerk. A scumbag.
What happened between you two?
It's a long story. I'll tell you on the way.
I don't get it.
Why did Dad hire such a useless woman?
She isn't useless.
People like her are rare these days.
She respects her elders,
she's good at her job and she works hard.
Poo is the only thing she makes that's worth throwing out.
Not at the table, Mum. That's gross.
It's not gross.
When will Yun Shil's husband get out of jail?
It depends on the sentence.
I'm worried about your dad,
but my heart breaks when I think of Yun Shil.
She shouldn't have married that man.
Don't let your heart break.
A hopeless romantic who'd give up a kidney...
for the woman he loves is very rare.
It's like a romantic novel.
I'm so envious.
You're stupid for being so, then.
The scoundrel used that to lure...
poor Yun Shil into marrying him.
Oh, dear. What a day.
Silly me. I'm supposed to give the grapes to Ms Choi.
What a waste.
Too bad.
I'll eat it, then.
Oh, dear.
My goodness.
They're from my mother-in-law.
I wasn't able to bring much, but I hope you enjoy it.
Thank you so much.
Come in for dinner if you haven't eaten yet.
It's late. I should go.
Come in, Yun Shil.
I think you have a guest. I'll come by tomorrow.
He isn't a guest. He's my son. Come on inside.
Come in and eat.
- But...
-  Come on.
Come with me.
Come on. Get inside.
Come in.
Hello.
Have some dinner.
- Come and sit.
-  No thanks.
Sit down already.
I already ate at home.
You were put to work under the summer sun.
You got a tan already.
Did you work the whole weekend?
No. My mother-in-law is sweet. She let me take a long rest.
I saw her in person at the wedding.
I don't believe you.
The grapes are lovely and sweet.
- Do you want some?
-  No thanks.
I hate grapes.
Why? They're nice.
You two haven't met, have you?
Say hello.
He's my parents' pride and joy. He's my little brother Lee Dong Jin.
She's Na Yun Shil, and she works at the store.
Now that I said hello, I think I should go.
Already?
I'm tired. I'd like to go to bed early.
Bye. Good night.
That was terribly loud.
Is your forehead okay?
Yes. It's fine.
My goodness. Yun Shil, what's wrong with you?
Are you okay?
Of course I am. I have a really hard skull.
- What's wrong with her?
-  Does she have heatstroke?
How stupid.
Why did I have to bash my head?
I'm so stupid.
Is anyone in?
Hello. Is this Lee Man Sool's residence?
Yes, it is.
Have you found him?
Yes, we have, but...
Ms Choi, Dong Sook, come outside.
The policemen are here.
They found Mr Lee.
Are you... Are you serious?
At last. Thank you so much. Thank goodness.
Where is he?
Because Mr Lee is quite old,
we had to consider the fact that he could be senile.
So we put him on a list...
and kept trying to contact him while trying to trace his whereabouts.
Stop trying to explain everything.
Get to the point.
Where is my father right now?
Was he in an accident?
No, not at all.
He's in good health.
It's just that he expressed his wishes that...
we don't tell you where he is.
He only asked us to give you this letter.
Thank you.
He asked us to cancel the missing person's report.
We gave you the letter, so that's our job done.
- Thank you.
-  Bye.
What was all that?
Read the letter, Dong Sook.
What? Okay.
"My dear partner Gok Ji."
You must have been very surprised.
I'm sorry.
You have nothing to worry about.
I am healthy and well.
I have no complaints other than that I miss you.
So please stop trying to look for me.
Dong Sook and Dong Jin.
I'm leaving your mother under your care.
Care for her well.
Even animals, when they sense their end is near,
leave the flock to spend time alone.
I am human.
I am almost 80.
I need some time to look back on my life...
and plan and prepare for the future.
I am saddened that no one will inherit the family business,
but I believe that also is a part of life.
I do not blame you. However,
I cannot close the business myself.
As I said in my previous letter,
Dong Jin, I want you to close the store.
If you were to do that for me,
that would relieve at least a little of the guilt I feel...
towards my ancestors.
Do that for me.
"Do not worry about me."
"Do your best in whatever you do in the future."
"I will return soon."
- Ms Choi.
-  Mum.
Mum.
He said he is fine.
Let's not worry about him any more.
Call the real estate agent tomorrow.
Let's sell the store.
- Mum.
-  Take my hand.
Calm down, Mum.
He must have a good reason for doing this.
I know Mr Lee. He wouldn't do this for no reason.
It's a family matter.
Stay out of it.
Something isn't right.
Let's see...
So you smashed this man's guitar.
I didn't smash it.
It got smashed when he fell over.
You punched me and caused me to fall over.
That's how it got smashed.
I just remembered.
Add assault to the list of charges.
No one hit him.
He did all the falling over on his own.
Be quiet, lady. You weren't even there.
- Did you hit him?
-  I did not.
It was just a graze.
A graze?
Are you Mike Tyson? You punched me square in the face.
Get to the point.
Will you press charges?
If you insist on doing so,
you will be sued for trespassing,
not paying for food... and refusing to leave.
Even if Mr Bae agrees to settle,
all those criminal charges will go on your record.
And you'll be charged with property damage and assault.
Even if Mr Sung settles, you'll be punished, too.
Do you still want to press charges?
What's the punishment?
It could be a fine or a stint in jail.
That's up to the prosecutor and judge.
- Jail?
-  Jail?
Wait.
Let's do as the policeman said.
Let's not make things any worse.
We can each take a step back and compromise.
- Okay.
-  Deal.
Good.
I get that the guitar means a lot to you.
I get that.
People like us live from day-to-day. 2,000 dollars is a huge sum.
- 1,500 dollars.
-  No way. 500.
500 dollars? For a guitar like that?
I won't pay you any more.
Please.
Where are you going?
If we can't settle, we have to go to court.
Do you think that scares me?
Will you both calm down?
Take a step back, both of you.
1,000 dollars.
- Deal.
-  Okay. You?
- Okay.
-  We have a deal.
- We're good, right?
-  20-month instalments.
You want to pay me over 20 months?
50 dollars a month.
What is it this time?
I can't deal with her. She lacks common sense.
People like her are really rare.
You stole the words out of my mouth.
You're taking a grand from us over a guitar.
You're worse than...
Kim Seon Dal, a conman who sold the Han River.
That was the Daedong River, not the Han. You're so ignorant.
Yes. I'm ignorant.
I didn't finish high school.
What do you care?
There you go again.
Why do you keep saying that?
- That has nothing to do with me.
-  Calm down, both of you.
We were doing so well.
I am trying to be very neutral and objective here.
Take one more step back.
We'll pay you 100 dollars a month for 10 months.
Deal. I'm sick of dealing with her.
Let's end it all here.
- What about you?
-  Thank you so much.
You said what I wanted to. It's a deal.
Perfect. Give us your account number and we're done.
- Okay.
-  My gosh.
Let's not meet again, even by chance.
Let's not.
Let's go home.
Okay. What then?
What?
- You called a real estate agent?
-  Yes.
Mum's so angry that she wants nothing to do with the store.
She shouldn't get so emotional.
Can you put your mother on?
Sure.
Mum, do you want to talk to Sam Do?
No.
She said no.
She's too weak to answer the phone.
It's a relief that Mr Lee's well.
Forget about the real estate agent.
Let's talk again soon. Bye.
Who was it?
What?
- Mr Park from the gas station.
-  What is it now?
His in-laws keep suits... They keep bees.
He asked if we need honey.
How much is it?
- 50 dollars per bottle.
-  That's too expensive!
So I said no.
- Why is it so expensive?
-  What is?
Other places serve 200g per portion.
Here, they only give you 150g.
Where's the manager?
Can you please just let go on a day like this?
Let's just eat.
Why is today special?
Why isn't is special?
We finally settled the terrifying guitar case.
I still think 1,000 dollars is way too much,
but you seemed so stressed.
That's why I said yes. Just to get rid of the guy.
Thanks.
You really are a warrior.
You'll...
do just fine without me, won't you?
Be honest. You saved up quite a bit, haven't you?
I don't have any money.
You say that, but I know you do.
You'll do just fine without me, as long as you have that.
Right?
I heard you'll run for president for the market committee.
People keep saying I should.
I don't have a choice.
If you actually get elected as president,
you'll have a lot of influence.
You'll do just fine without me, won't you?
Are you going somewhere?
- No.
-  Then why...
do you keep saying I'll do fine without you?
I'm just trying to express...
what an incredible person you are.
Eat up.
Hello.
It's been a while.
Where's Tae Yang?
It's nothing. A college friend got hurt.
Badly hurt?
No. It was a fender bender.
He needed a guardian.
Don't worry, he's fine.
It's time for your medication.
See you tomorrow.
"All the work."
He had to do everything.
Let's move on to the next sentence.
"Recently" means not so long ago.
What's this?
You need to get your hair and makeup done for the interview.
You paid for my classes, too.
I owe you so much.
I feel bad that I can't do more.
If you find a job first, don't find another girlfriend.
I would never do that.
You might, though.
What?
Hello, this is KBC News.
Loneliness can lead to...
Mum, what do you think about her?
She has a pretty common face.
She does not. Take a closer look.
She has class and looks intellectual.
Do you like her?
I think you're already working on her.
Why? Can't I?
You can't.
You're the CEO of Meesa Apparel.
You need to upgrade your standard accordingly.
Dong Jin, welcome home.
Have you eaten?
Yes.
I'll go upstairs.
You came out to welcome your husband.
That's a change. I find it perplexing.
- Me, too.
-  It's a personal matter.
I guess they reconciled. I'm so glad they did.
They shouldn't be getting along at a time like this.
Something's off.
I agree.
Will it all work out?
Will you become president again?
Did you call my mum?
I forgot. I'll call her tomorrow.
You should visit her.
Why should I? Can't I just call her?
Okay. I'll pay her a visit.
Shall I run a bath?
No. I have some reports to read. Go to bed.
Why did his dad leave home and cause this mess?
I've had enough of this.
Meesa Apparel dropped the libel charges...
and handed in a petition asking for leniency...
stating the fraud was just a misunderstanding.
He'll get off lightly.
The CEO really did take the matter into his own hands.
Can you meet the lawyer Hong Gi Pyo hired?
I can, but we won't get anywhere.
It's Choi Cheol Woo, Madam Ko's personal lawyer.
How could she use him for a case like this?
It's like admitting she's behind it.
It is, but they don't really have any evidence yet.
Okay. Thanks.
It would all go well...
if that lady convinces her husband.
Which way did he go?
- Hong Gi Pyo...
-  I'm sorry, Sir.
Get her out of here.
-  Please.
Thief!
Stay away.
Hey!
I had no idea who he was.
How am I going to face him now?
For an old store in an old building,
it's well-maintained and in a nice spot.
I want it over and done with soon. Sell it as soon as possible.
Can you please reconsider?
You can't sell the store while Mr Lee's away.
You were there when Dong Sook read his letter.
Get over it, both of you, and find another job. Be smart.
She's really upset.
I'll sell it off as soon as possible.
Please do.
Look who's here.
You look familiar.
Don't be so sarcastic.
How are you?
Fine, thanks.
- I have a lot of people to meet.
-  Dong Jin's wife.
I also do a lot of charity work.
I was too busy to visit you.
Please understand.
I bet you were busy spending money.
You didn't do any charity.
Have you decided to sell the store?
- Yes.
-  I'm so glad you did.
Who would buy a suit at a rundown old store?
Now that Father's gone, sell the store right away...
and spend the rest of your life traveling.
What did you say?
"A rundown old store"?
Am I wrong?
No one goes to a store like this these days.
They can get an Italian suit for the same price.
What do you know about suits?
Even foreigners acknowledge the quality of my dad's suits.
It's not just a luxury item. It's a work of art.
Come on, Dong Sook. A suit is just a suit.
"Just a suit"?
- Watch what you say.
-  Let it go, Dong Sook.
I have a headache.
Get her out of here right now.
Let's go.
My dad's been gone for days, and you finally come by?
Hyo Joo, you need to learn some manners.
I should just...
- beat her up.
-  Dong Sook.
I was only being honest. What's her problem?
Was that such a huge mistake?
Goodness, I should just die so that I don't have to deal with this mess.
- Calm down.
-  Gosh, let go of me.
Just a second.
- Dong Sook, have some water.
-  Thanks.
Gosh, she's so rude.
I know her father was the chairman of Meesa Apparel, but so what?
- Her father owned Meesa Apparel?
-  Yes.
Let me tell you.
She rubbed me the wrong way from the first moment I saw her...
when Dong Jin brought her to our place.
She's from a rich family, so she sat with her nose in the air...
and drove me crazy with her obnoxious attitude.
Dong Jin must have to put up with so much to live with that fool.
I can just picture it.
I'll go straight home from the meeting.
I'll leave everything in your hands. Make sure everything gets done.
Sure thing. Please don't worry about it.
What's this smell?
It smells like grapes.
Oh, no. What a waste.
These grapes are starting to get all mushy.
Why did you buy so many grapes by the way?
- We don't take credit cards.
-  I know. Cash only. Here.
I have no time. Let's go.
Here. Share them with the employees.
All of these?
You should take some home.
No, I hate grapes.
You guys can take leftovers home or do whatever you want with them.
Take all of them, please.
He must be allergic to grapes.
What are you talking about now?
So are you saying that Dong Jin...
got demoted and was transferred to a branch office...
in the countryside because of his mother-in-law's ruse?
- He didn't say anything to you?
-  No, he didn't.
He probably didn't tell you because he didn't want to worry you.
I shall teach this woman a serious lesson.
Call your stepmother right now.
This may be a disrespectful thing to say about the deceased,
but you're looking more youthful after the chairman passed away.
You look like a young, unmarried lady.
Gosh, no way.
I'll just take it as something...
you're saying to console this widow.
My gosh! I'm not just saying it. I really mean it, Ms Ko. Goodness.
Let's see.
What's going on? You rarely call me.
- How dare you trick my son!
-  Goodness.
Who is this? Why are you yelling at me?
Who do you think I am? I'm Dong Jin's mother.
Your stepdaughter's mother-in-law!
I beg your pardon? I know that we're close,
but you should be more respectful towards me.
Stop talking rubbish.
How dare you ruin my son's career!
You witch...
- Please don't swear at me, Ms Choi.
-  What?
You yell and swear at anyone that comes your way.
That must be why your husband left home.
How could you... Shut that lousy mouth of yours.
Listen!
How can I say something nice to someone...
who is trying to ruin my son's future?
You're mistaken.
I didn't want to send Dong Jin to the countryside.
It's what the executives wanted.
Let's talk in person and find out if that's true or not.
- Come to my shop immediately!
-  I don't want to.
- What?
-  You come here if you want to talk.
I don't even want to let my gas out in that direction!
It sounds like that was Grandma on the phone.
Would you like some cold water?
Forget it.
Gosh, she's so scary.
(Meesa Apparel)
Hello? I'm one of the participants of the medical testing,
and I'm feeling very dizzy.
It could be a temporary reaction to the drug.
It's not really a side effect,
but you should visit the hospital if you start vomiting.
(The 41st Open Recruitment, 2016)
(CEO Min Hyo Sang)
I had a quick look at your resume...
and saw that you haven't had a real job since graduating...
from university aside from a few part-time jobs.
Why haven't you found a job yet?
I heard that young people these days have such high standards...
and that they only apply to major corporations.
- Was that the case for you, too?
-  No.
Then why do you want to work at Meesa Apparel?
I want to participate in Meesa Apparel's pursuit of the values...
and mindset it seeks to obtain.
Then in your opinion, what are the values...
and mindset our company is pursuing?
Meesa Apparel's values...
- I'm sorry. I'll say it again.
-  Yes, take your time.
Meesa Apparel's history began 45 years ago...
when we just got out of extreme hunger and poverty.
With a motto, "Clothes complete one's dignity", the company...
has been working on improving Korea's status in the world.
Most of all, it showed us an example of how warm,
safe and family-like a company can be.
That'd be all.
You guys should learn from him.
I apologise.
What's wrong with him?
He seems to be feeling unwell.
I thought we found someone useful for a change.
Excuse me, Sir! This is the women's washroom.
- My gosh!
-  He must be a pervert!
We must call security. Where's the security guard?
Just a second.
I don't think he's a pervert. It looks like he's sick.
Excuse me. Are you feeling unwell?
Shall we call the ambulance?
He's not sick. I'm sure he just drank a lot last night.
Look. Are you throwing up because of a hangover?
(Applicant Name: Kang Tae Yang)
My goodness. He's here for an interview?
Look, Mr Job Seeker.
- Do you think this place is a joke?
-  Pardon me?
You're here for a job interview.
How can you drink until you drop the night before?
You obviously don't have the right attitude to work here.
Look at this. You don't even look put together.
You're lazy, and you must have poor work ethics, as well.
You're certainly not qualified to work at Meesa Apparel!
Whether I drink or not, what does that have to do with you?
You're so rude.
Look, Mr Job Seeker.
I can easily make sure that you don't pass the interview.
What's wrong with this woman?
I'm not done yet.
Listen! Don't waste your life like that! Wake up!
You dropped this. Goodness.
Judging from that expensive-looking suit, he must be from a rich family.
He's so cluelessly audacious.
Kang Tae Yang. The company will be doomed if someone like him gets in.
Why do you look so down?
You look so pallid, too. Are you feeling unwell?
I think I'm coming down with a cold.
I just had a job interview.
Did it not go well?
I really wanted to do well this time.
I thought it'd help me and Ji Yun go back to how things were before.
Why is it that nothing ever goes my way?
Did you two have a fight?
I've been unemployed forever, so she must think that I'm pathetic.
Ji Yun didn't do anything wrong.
I'm really trying my best,
but things just keep getting worse and worse.
I don't know why I have to live and what I live for.
I have no hope.
You've been holding out well so far. This is very unlike you.
I don't think I can do this any more.
You must stay strong, Tae Yang.
You're almost there, so hang in there. All right?
Gosh.
I see that you step out whenever you want in your boss' absence.
You're such a slacker.
Do you think this is acceptable? Answer me, Ms Na.
I just stepped out briefly to have dinner.
Mr Lee allows us to step out for dinner breaks.
What brings you here again by the way?
I'm here to give you a chance.
A chance?
You made those mistakes not knowing who I am.
I'm here to give you chance to redeem yourself.
- Can you start cooperating?
-  What are you talking about?
Min Hyo Sang instigated your husband to commit crime.
Get him to confess.
Of course, I'll make sure you get paid, too.
Gi Pyo already denied it. Why do you keep saying that?
Listen carefully.
Your husband was convicted three times already.
Who do you think is telling the truth here?
Didn't you hear anything about me?
I heard you went to the best university in the country.
You were good at your job, so they made you their son-in-law.
That's right.
That's the kind of person I am.
- So what?
-  What do you mean?
What does that have anything to do with someone telling the truth?
You really don't get it do you? Listen to me.
I'm Lee Man Sool's son.
The person you respect the most is my father.
So as his son, why would I ever lie to you?
Mr Lee used to say that...
his son is nothing like him.
He said he couldn't believe that you're his son.
That's because I wasn't interested in taking over the tailor shop.
Sorry, I have work to do.
This woman is driving me crazy. What's wrong with her?
(Train Ticket)
(Departing at 6:30am from Daejeon Station to Seoul Station)
Oh, gosh.
- Are you okay?
-  I'm fine.
Here, I got it.
What's gotten into you?
Why? You don't like it?
You never do house chores.
I'm just curious why you're acting differently.
I'm sorry.
About what?
I know you're always so tired from work.
I should have helped out more.
I'm a bad husband, aren't I?
Look at you all grown up.
I'm proud of you.
Let me go get something.
I told you to throw this out. There's a hole in it.
Give me that.
Why would you throw this out? I can still wear it.
Why would you wear that?
It doesn't matter what I wear.
- Honey.
-  Stop being like that.
I've been wearing your underwear all this time.
What's with you today?
I even made you wear my worn out underwear.
I'm the worst husband ever.
Are you crying?
My goodness.
It's nothing to worry about. Why are you crying?
Is there something wrong?
I'm sorry, Sun Nyeo.
What's wrong? Stop crying.
Did you eat something wrong?
Stop crying, Honey.
(Account balance: 1,190 dollars)
I'll go broke at this rate.
Sung Jun!
You scared me.
I knew it was you.
I was just passing by.
And I saw you sitting here.
Can I sit down?
Of course, take a seat.
I'm sorry about last time.
To be honest, our customers don't have great taste.
It must have hurt your feelings.
I think myself as an artist.
I'm not seeking for attention.
Art is created in solitude.
You sound so sophisticated.
You lent me the towel and even offered me ramyeon.
You can order anything you want. It's on me tonight.
I don't eat much.
- Can I have a bowl of noodles?
-  Okay.
Don't put too much in.
All right.
Do you live nearby?
I see you around a lot.
Yes. I live near the...
I own an apartment in Gangnam.
I didn't know I'd come back so soon. So the people on lease...
couldn't find a place to stay yet.
I see.
I'm living with a friend at the moment.
I have a vacant room ready if you want.
What am I saying? You have an apartment in Gangnam.
You couldn't live in such a place.
I'll only be a month or two.
How about this? I'll give you my number.
Think about it and give me a call.
I'll do that.
Here, give me your number.
Okay, Sung Jun.
Now that I have your number,
I'm going to make you mine in a month.
She must think she got me just because I gave her my number.
I'm not as easy as you think.
You've been getting off work late.
I didn't know there was so much work at the distribution centre.
You're always working until late.
I have something to tell you.
What is it?
Is it serious?
Take a look.
(Clothing Inventory and Returns Report)
(Change of label)
This is a report of the label fraud.
What are you suggesting?
I'm sure you're well aware of this.
In February, Hong Gi Pyo was sued for changing our products' labels.
I don't know anyone by that name.
His lawyer is Choi Cheol Woo.
You're friends with him, aren't you?
Stop beating around the bush and get to the point.
What are you trying to say?
You labeled the old products as new ones and took advantage of it.
I'm not going to ask you what you did with the money.
What on earth are you talking about? Do you have any proof?
You left a lot of traces.
Think carefully.
I'll give you a week.
Are you blackmailing us?
I just want things to be right again.
If you make things the way they used to be in that time,
I'll make sure your son stays at Meesa Apparel.
If you refuse this offer,
you'll suffer a fatal wound that you will not recover from.
- What did you say?
-  I hope...
you make a smart decision. I'll get going now.
How dare he?
I don't think he was bluffing.
What are we going to do, Mum?
What do you mean?
Don't let him scare you. We didn't do anything wrong.
Listen carefully.
Your husband was convicted three times already.
Who do you think is telling the truth here?
Gi Pyo is surely hiding something.
Welcome.
I see nothing's changed.
It's the same as it was in the past.
Is Mr Lee in?
He's not here right now.
Did he get off work already?
There's been a situation. He won't be coming in for a while.
Why is that?
Is he sick?
No, it's not that.
Something came up.
This is the first time in 50 years that I've been here.
What am I going to do now?
What's this?
When I got dispatched to a country abroad 50 years ago,
my father worked hard and gathered money,
and he got me a suit right here at this tailor shop.
I know it's worn out, but it means a lot to me.
I wanted Mr Lee take a look at it.
I see.
You came after such a long time. I'm sorry for not being able to help.
When is Mr Lee coming back?
I can't tell you exactly when.
When he comes back,
please tell him I was here.
This suit allowed me to...
endure the difficult times...
when I lived abroad.
Tell him that I'm grateful.
I'll make sure to tell him that when he returns.
(Wolgyesu Tailor Shop)
(Daejeon Station)
Wolgyesu Tailor Shop became my home...
after I ran away from the orphanage.
I spent my youth there, and it also gave me a dream.
I can't just sit here and watch...
when such an important place is about to get taken down.
(To Sun Nyeo)
You're a strong woman.
I know you'll do fine without me.
This wasn't an easy decision,
but I have to do this.
I want you to understand.
I also left you a gift while you were sleeping.
Please take it as a symbol of my apology.
Bae Sam Do.
You're a dead man.
Are you kidding me?
Hey, Dong Sook.
Dong Jin, I have bad news.
What is it this time?
Mum got shocked after hearing that you got demoted.
She cried all night saying that she couldn't accept it.
She won't even drink water.
I told her not to worry about it and that it's not a big deal.
I think you have to talk to her in person.
After hearing what happened to you on top of everything going on,
she's in quite a shock.
She might actually fall ill if things don't get better.
Okay, I'll be right there.
- Are you going to Seoul?
-  Yes.
My mother is sick. I think I have to go visit her.
Of course, go ahead.
I'll take care of this place while you're gone.
- Dong Sook, I got some medication.
-  Thanks.
Mum, Yun Shil brought some medicine.
Get up and have some of this.
Something might really happen to you if you keep this up.
I'll just die then.
Why do you keep saying that?
My husband ran away from home. I don't even know where he is.
And my son who's known for being smart...
got demoted off to nowhere.
How am I supposed to swallow anything in this situation?
Stop being so stubborn.
Mum, open up. Come on.
- Are you okay, Dong Sook?
-  That hurt!
You're driving me crazy.
I'm just going to lie here and enter my coffin like this.
Then I'll get buried like this.
So please just leave me alone.
That really hurt.
Hello.
It's me, Dong Sook.
Hey, Sung Jun.
Could I stop by and see that room you were talking about?
Of course.
The room is empty. You can stop by whenever you want.
I was about to have some brunch.
I think I'll be able to make it in an hour.
Sounds good.
Just come to the address I wrote you yesterday.
Okay, see you later.
This is yours, isn't it?
Why do you have that?
Did you not see the sign saying not to wash clothes in saunas?
- The airplane...
-  Do you think this is a laundromat?
Why do you leave your underwear lying around?
I get it, so stop. It was a one-time mistake.
The next time I see your underwear lying around,
you're going to get kicked out.
Wait, have we met before?
Clean up after yourself. Do you know how messy it can get?
Is she a doppelganger?
She looks exactly the same.
My goodness.
How did I end up like this?
I'm already depressed from getting deported from the US.
Now, I'm about to get kicked out of the dry sauna.
What am I going to do with my life?
The phone is currently turned off.
Please leave a message after the tone.
You don't even answer my calls?
Bae Sam Do.
Do you really think you can get away with this?
Bae Sam Do, you jerk.
I'm going to kill you.
I'm here, Ms Choi.
Is anyone home?
Hey, Sam Do. What a surprise.
How's your mum doing?
She's being so stubborn.
She doesn't even drink water.
Sam Do, what's in the brief case?
Let's talk inside.
So you're telling me...
- you left your home?
-  Yes.
The tailor shop means a lot to me.
Mr Lee spent his entire life there.
It's also where I grew up.
I can't just let other people take over it.
Does your wife know about this?
I wrote her a letter and left in the morning.
Is that some kind of a trend these days?
What's up with everyone?
Oh, gosh.
I know how your wife can be.
I can't deal with her. Go back home.
I'm even ready to get a divorce.
I can't just go back now.
If Mr Lee hears that I'm back and running the tailor shop again,
he will return as soon as possible.
I'm sure of it.
Yun Shil.
What do you think?
I agree with him.
If we open the tailor shop again, Mr Lee will definitely return.
You haven't had a real job since graduating from university.
Why haven't you found a job yet?
I'm sure he's the guy who gave Ji Yun the watch.
(Tae Joon)
Hey, Tae Joon. What's up?
Mum's in the hospital.
What are you talking about?
She hurt her legs real bad when she fell yesterday.
She's ruptured ligaments and injured the cartilage in her knees.
The doctor says she needs surgery.
She told me not to tell you,
but I can't deal with this on my own.
It was good of you to call. Don't worry too much.
Get her to take the surgery right away.
I'll take care of the money.
Okay.
Mr Lee paid me in advance, so I got some money to spare.
It should cover the surgery.
Don't thank me. What are friends for?
Come over, I'm at Mr Lee's place.
It should be around here.
Oh, there it is.
The change...
is yours.
Salute!
You're here.
I think I was out of line yesterday.
I'm sorry...
I'm here, Mum.
What? He's going to ignore me?
Is anyone home?
Who is it?
Oh, who do we have here?
You're the bride who didn't pay me.
Oh, the money... I'll...
That's not what I'm here for today.
Do you live here?
No, my boss does.
Does Lee Dong Sook live here?
Are you here to see her?
That's right.
Dong Sook, you have a guest.
Hey, Sung Jun.
Hello.
Is this...
Yes, it's my home. We have empty rooms upstairs.
I like the place.
Could I take a look at it first?
Of course, Sung Jun.
After you.
What's going on with her?
Dong Sook. Prepare some nice cereal smoothies for us.
I'll get it for you instead.
Lee Man Sool.
This is the place.
(Rooms available for lease)
You just wait right there.
There are two rooms and a big living room.
I think it'll be enough for you to live alone.
This is more than enough.
I bet the monthly rent is pretty expensive.
It's not for monthly rent. It's for lease.
Lease?
How much is it?
- 10 thousand dollars?
-  My goodness.
You've been out of the country for too long.
You don't know how things are around here, do you?
It's not 10 thousand. It's 100 thousand dollars.
100 thousand dollars?
We can't keep the shop closed.
It's not like we can let other people...
Where did Dong Sook run off to?
She has a guest over.
Come on out, Bae Sam Do.
What was that?
I think she just called your name.
Don't you hear me?
Where are you, Bae Sam Do?
Get me Bae Sam Do right now.
Isn't that your wife?
Yes, she's driving me crazy.
I guess Sam Do's wife followed him all the way here.
She's going to make quite a scene. What should we do?
Let's go out there.
Okay.
Oh, my goodness.
Is she crazy? Get down from there.
No.
I won't.
Have you been drinking?
Yes.
I felt like I was going to go insane...
without alcohol.
So I had three cartons of soju on the train.
Three cartons? You're making me insane.
This is a noisy neighbourhood. What's going on?
What?
- My gosh.
-  What's she doing up there?
What? It's you again.
What are you doing here?
My goodness. Do you guys know each other?
No.
My goodness. What are you doing up there?
Stop embarrassing me and get down from there.
Promise me that you'll go back to Daejeon with me then.
Then I'll go down.
I told you. I'm going to start working at the tailor shop again.
Then that'll be the end of the both of us.
- What's she doing?
-  My gosh.
Do you know what this is?
What is that?
Isn't that fuel?
You got that right.
What are you trying to do with that?
You know what I'm going to do.
I'm going to put myself on fire.
She's a woman of her words. Nobody will be able to stop her.
How do you know that?
I'll go up there.
Don't let anyone up here.
If you do,
I'll use this lighter.
- Oh, my goodness.
-  Gosh.
- You're here.
-  What's going on?
Well, the thing is...
It's hard to explain.
This is your last chance.
Bae Sam Do. Are you going back with me or not?
Stop making me repeat what I said.
I'm not going back!
Okay.
We all die then.
- Oh, no.
-  Stop it.
Don't do it.
Sun Nyeo, are you crazy?
Sun Nyeo, don't be so emotional.
Let's talk this out.
I'm sick and tired of talking.
I've had enough.
What's wrong with that lady?
I'm not exactly sure what's going on, either.
This is not looking good. Call 911.
In Korea, it's 119, not 911.
My gosh. I've lived for too long.
I should just kill myself so I don't have to deal with this.
- Ms Choi.
-  Calm down, Mum.
Let's die!
- Let's all die!
-  Sun Nyeo, no! Don't!
(The Gentlemen of Wolgyesu Tailor Shop)
What happened? Why am I here?
They seem to like it. They want to sign the contract.
Don't come to work tomorrow.
What gives him the right to say that?
Let's end it. I'm sick of you.
Why have you changed?
What happened to you?
Rumours?
I'm not a pushover.
I'm so sorry. I will make no excuses.
Thank you for helping me with...
Wolgyesu Tailor Shop's last official deal.