(Episode 40)
(Minkyung Farm)
That man.
He's your husband, isn't he?
- What? - He showed me his phone.
He showed me your wedding photo and asked about you.
I looked him over and...
he doesn't seem like the abusive type.
Why are you avoiding him?
It's personal.
What did he say?
Wait.
He gave me his business card and asked me to call...
if I ever saw you.
Does your husband...
own a tailor store?
I don't know what's going on,
but you should quit the hard work and go back to him.
Being with your husband is better than anything.
Did you catch a cold?
I took some medicine. I'll be fine.
(Wolgyesu Tailor Shop)
What happened? Did you find her?
I went to the neighbourhood the bank teller pointed me to.
- She wasn't there. - It'll be impossible to find her.
I'm sorry you went all the way there for nothing.
I'll make you some tea.
No thanks.
I have a headache. I should go home early.
- Sure. Go on. - Sorry. See you tomorrow.
You're home early.
Yes, to get some rest. I'm not feeling well.
How exactly do you feel?
- I'll run to the pharmacy. - I had some aspirin.
I'm sorry about yesterday.
She'd had a tough life so far and...
the fact that she left us...
as if she was pushed by someone...
made me angry and sad. That's why I behaved like that.
I felt the same way.
I got sleepless after I asked Yun Shil to leave.
You would understand me after you have your own child.
It's more painful when your child has...
a little cut on the hand than you have your finger cut off.
Even though Yun Shil was like our own daughter to me and your dad,
I couldn't leave the matter as it is...
when I knew it wouldn't be good for you.
Sometimes things don't turn out as you wish.
You and Yun Shil...
are not meant to be together.
When I was having rough times,
Yun Shil was there for me.
Thanks to her,
I could laugh and felt alive,
and that made who I am today.
I can't go back to the past.
I don't want to have much money or to be in a high position.
Such things are useless when you don't feel happy inside.
Still, I don't want you...
to spend rest of your life in a small tailor shop.
I wish you to work in a bigger company.
I know what you think.
I know what Hyo Joo tells you attracts you, too.
However, I'd rather stay single for the rest of my life...
than reunite with her...
to take back the position of CEO in the company.
Dong Jin.
I need to take some rest.
(Ms Shiny Eyes)
The phone has been turned off. Please leave a message after...
Don't you consider for someone who's left behind?
Don't the promises you made with me mean anything to you?
Where on earth are you now?
I've tried to understand you up to now, Yun Shil.
If it gets any longer,
I would be angry.
(Ms Shiny Eyes)
It's me, Ji Yun.
I called you to let you know our wedding invitations are done.
I'll call you back later.
What's the matter?
Break up with Choi Ji Yun right now.
- What? - You can't marry her.
What are you talking about?
Our wedding invitations are printed out today.
Do you want to marry a woman such as Choi Ji Yun?
What about a woman such as Choi Ji Yun?
No way! Kang Tae Yang and Choi Ji Yun are...
You're right. I know everything.
Are you still not going to break up with Kang Tae Yang?
Why do I have to break up with him? You should break up with Ji Yun.
- What are you talking about? - Choi Ji Yun...
likes your background, not you. Wake up!
Do you know how Kang Tae Yang harassed Ji Yun,
following her everywhere like a stalker?
You should wake up, girl!
Kang Tae Yang doesn't like you. He approached you...
to take revenge on Ji Yun and me, you fool.
That's a nonsense.
Tae Yang didn't know that I'm your sister...
and a daughter of Meesa Apparel's owner at first.
After he found out who I am, he tried to keep away from me.
You're so innocent.
He pretended he didn't know.
- Don't blame a decent man. - Goodness.
You're totally out of your mind.
You are totally out of your mind.
How can you fall for a woman who left someone...
she had been dating for nearly ten years just because he's not rich?
She's materialistic.
She's not materialistic. She's realistic.
Think about it. Would a sane woman want to marry...
someone who work part time for several years as he can't get a job?
You can't blame Ji Yun.
Then, she could leave you if you lose your money, right?
What are you talking about?
Anyway, I can't give up Tae Yang.
You should give up Ji Yun.
Ji Yun and I are getting married late this month.
If we get married before you do,
you and Kang Tae Yang cannot but break up.
Do you understand, Min Hyo Won?
Min Hyo Sang and Choi Ji Yun.
We win.
Min Hyo Won and Kang Tae Yang are...
losers.
I don't think things will turn out as you wish.
She's probably out of her mind to act that way.
I'm home.
Where have you been? You said you caught a cold.
Did you meet Kang Tae Yang?
Where have you been, then?
I went to the obstetrics.
Why do you go to the obstetrics when you have a cold?
Did you go to the obstetrics?
Why did you go to the obstetrics?
I'm pregnant.
Are you...
pregnant?
How...
could you say that so lightly?
You must be crazy.
You must be totally crazy.
I'm still in my early pregnancy. Please don't hit my tummy.
I'll let Kang Tae Yang pay for this.
Tae Yang doesn't know yet. You're the first one I told it.
My goodness.
Oh, my goodness
I'm sorry, Mum.
I've raised you so dearly...
and preciously.
I brought you up like a princess.
Oh my!
She got pregnant...
before she gets married.
What a shame!
My goodness.
They say a baby is the best wedding present nowadays.
Stop talking!
I'm sorry, Mum.
By the way, when did you get pregnant?
Was it when you visited Kang Tae Yang's home?
What?
Well, that's right.
I told you that I went all the way with him.
They say every evil doer has his reasons.
How can you talk back to me like that?
You are such a trouble maker!
I'm in my early pregnancy. Please be careful, Mum.
My baby.
So...
I think I should get married soon.
I can't stand it anymore.
It's shameful if people can notice that I'm pregnant on the wedding.
Right.
Then, I'll let Hyo Sang get married first...
and then you can get married.
What about I get married...
before Hyo Sang gets married?
I will be all right,
but I'm worried that your pride might get hurt.
If I get married as soon as possible,
we can tell people that I got pregnant during my honeymoon.
During your honeymoon?
I'm still in my early pregnancy.
All right.
Then, you should not tell anyone except me...
that you're pregnant.
You shouldn't tell that even to Kang Tae Yang.
He's the dad of this baby. He should know.
If he knows that you have his baby,
he might act like he's the king.
So, let's tell him later,
after you finish your wedding.
Do you understand?
- Okay. - All right.
You're a trouble maker.
How do you feel?
I'm totally fine.
You didn't sound good in the afternoon, but you sound good now.
I took a hot bath and cleared my head.
I feel better now.
That's good. I worried about you.
By the way, Tae Yang,
we should get married.
What do you mean that we should get married?
I suddenly...
- want to get married. - Hyo Won.
I'll get everything ready for the wedding.
All you have to do is being beside me on the wedding, Tae Yang.
It won't be difficult for you.
What are you talking about?
Tae Yang, may I come in?
Hyo Won, I'll call you back later.
Why does she want to get married?
What do you think? Doesn't it look perfect?
It's not easy to fry an egg without breaking the yolk.
You must be good at cooking.
If you want to eat a perfect fried egg like this,
you can just say yes to my proposal.
Then I will make it for you for free for the rest of your life.
I've never imagined that he would come here to find me.
I'm so thankful and sorry, Dong Jin.
Dong Jin.
Can I come in?
Yes, you can.
Your mum's worried that you're sick.
- Are you okay? - Yes.
I took some aspirin. I feel better now.
I see. Let's sit down.
Earlier today...
I met Yun Shil.
Did you actually see her?
I insisted that we meet up.
I guess she couldn't refuse an old man's plea.
Did she...
look well?
She looked somewhat thinner,
but I think she's fine.
Where exactly is she staying?
She wouldn't say.
She's working at a farm.
A farm? Which one? Where?
She didn't say, but I think she's fine.
I told her...
not to give up on her dream of making suits,
regardless of her relationship with you.
She said she'll call when she's ready, so let's give her time.
Did she say if she's sick?
I think she's hanging in there.
Uncle. Grandpa.
Let's watch TV.
Dad's episode of "Music Stage" starts soon.
Okay, then.
- Let's go. - Sure.
How's your headache?
I feel much better now.
You didn't eat dinner. Shall I boil you some rice?
No, I'm not hungry.
Tae Pyung.
- Congratulations. - Thanks.
I sang my heart out...
but I'm not sure how it'll look.
Don't even go there.
He went to the toilet so often he almost missed his cue.
Just thinking about that moment gives me the shivers.
I have diarrhoea when I get too nervous.
Dad, not while we're eating.
Sorry about that.
These are really sweet.
- Your dad bought them today. - They're lovely.
Are these from the shop at the crossroads?
I met someone earlier today...
and the person said these are fresh from the farm.
Anyway,
is that lady...
- really your wife? - Pardon?
I was just asking.
She looked so pretty in the photo.
If you ever see the woman in the photo,
please give me a call. Please.
Sure, I will.
The strawberry farm.
She has to be there.
Please be there, Yun Shil.
I think this is it.
Is anyone here?
Yun Shil?
Dong Jin.
How did you find me here?
Did you think I wouldn't be able to?
Try harder next time.
I'll go to the end of the earth to find you.
Is this where you're staying?
It looks a mess but it isn't that bad.
Come home with me.
I can't go back.
I won't.
Is this...
about my mum?
- It's not. - I know that...
- she said terrible things to you. - It's not about that.
Everything she said makes sense...
and she didn't say terrible things to me.
Even if you understand where she's coming from,
it would still hurt.
You're right. It hurt and I'm in pain.
But...
not because of your mum.
It's because of you.
It took so much courage to leave the store.
I'm practically forcing myself to stay here.
Why did you come looking for me?
If I give up and leave,
no one else will get hurt.
So leave me alone and go back home.
What nonsense is that?
Don't you see the pain that...
you're causing me?
The two of us...
only met a few months ago.
We fought for most of that time.
So even if we break up,
we'll get over it soon enough.
Is that all you felt about me?
I...
I can't be happy without you.
You did this to me and now you want to break up?
Do you think I'll say yes?
I'm sick of it now.
About you and your mum...
and Gi Pyo and his mum.
It's too much for me to handle.
Why do you think...
I decided to leave the store and come here?
Just go home.
I'll be unhappy without you.
How can you talk about breaking up so easily?
If we stay together we'll only make each other unhappy.
It's cowardice to run away without trying.
You're right.
I'm a coward.
To be with you...
I have to fight everything that comes our way.
I can't do that.
I'd rather be a coward and run away.
Do I...
Do I make...
your life that tough to live?
This is the best for me.
If you care for me,
please go away.
Is that what you want?
Yes.
So please leave.
And never come here again.
I'll ask one last time. Do you...
really want me to...
give up on you?
Yes.
I've given up on you.
However hard it got,
I thought we could fight through it together.
I was confident we could.
I guess I was wrong.
If I make your life tough,
I won't force you.
(Minkyung Farm)
It's the trot singer, Tae Pyung.
The title of his song is "My Brother Goes".
Please give him a big hand.
Jun looks amazing on television.
He does. Doesn't he look so handsome?
That suit looks incredible.
Gosh. You sure are a tailor, Dad.
I guess his suit caught your eyes before him.
- I like the song. It's very catchy. - I agree.
I never thought I'd see him on television.
I thought he was just a busker...
who carries his guitar around,
but he's actually pretty good.
Thank you, Father and Mother.
The gentleman of trot music, Tae Pyung, speaking.
Newspaper?
This is Tae Pyung's agent, Lee Dong Sook.
Yes, you can speak to me about it.
An interview?
Do they want to interview me?
His schedule is fully packed.
I need to check his schedule first.
We have nothing booked.
Fortunately, he has some time in the afternoon.
Yes. Right.
Okay. See you tomorrow, then.
Do they want to interview Dad for a story on newspaper?
Yes. Okay!
Does that mean your face will be on a newspaper?
Well, I guess so.
Mum, you're lucky to have a famous son-in-law.
Yes. I'm going to think differently of you from today.
I'll work harder to make you more proud.
All right. That sounds good.
Headaches have so many causes,
so I'll need to run some tests.
Based on your symptoms,
you could have a brain haemorrhage or a tumour.
Gosh, I cannot die like this.
I've been so stingy on myself...
and have had such a tough life.
Did I go through all of that to die at such a young age?
If I die, Sam Do will be thrilled.
I absolutely cannot die.
For whom should I die?
What are you doing now?
How dare you hit on my husband in broad daylight?
Are you going to go with me or not?
I said that I won't!
Okay. Then I'm just going to end it all.
I'm sure that I am pregnant.
Are you kidding me right now?
How can you lie to my face about being pregnant?
- Stop it. - Does it hurt?
Sam Do, you'll die in my hands today.
- Gosh! Don't! - You.
You'll die in my hands today. Got it?
Honey! Let go of her.
Right.
Sam Do has also been through a lot of trouble since he met me.
Hey, Sam Do.
You've been through a lot because of me.
What's she talking about now?
Bring the divorce papers.
I'll sign them right away.
Are you sure?
Now you're talking.
You look thrilled to hear that.
Right, we only live once.
You should live with a woman whom you want to be with.
Go ahead and live with your first love.
I'm going to watch how happy you two can be together.
You're joking now, right?
No, I'm not. I'm serious.
You will sign the divorce papers?
You asked me to. Wasn't it your wish?
Yes, but why would you want to grant me that wish now?
Are you terminally ill or what?
That's right, you jerk. I'm terminally ill.
Are you happy that I'll die?
Why are you hitting me? Have you lost your mind?
I'm sick and tired of having to clean up your mess all the time.
Let's split up and go our own ways.
Gosh, what is wrong with that woman today?
My gosh, my head is splitting.
I guess I don't have many days left...
(Min Hyo Sang and Choi Ji Yun)
What do you think, Mum?
The design is simple and elegant.
Ji Yun picked it.
She has such great taste.
All you talk about is her.
- Who is it at this hour? - I'll get the door!
Don't run.
What are you going to do if you fall?
Just be careful. The stairs are slippery, you know.
I forgot. Sorry, Mum.
Who's here this late at night?
Darling!
Gosh, why is that punk here again...
Why are you calling him a punk? Watch your language.
Have a seat, my future son-in-law.
- "Future son-in-law"? - What does that mean, Madam Ko?
You must be tired from work.
Are you feeling all right?
I'm feeling great.
Have a seat here, you two.
I asked all of you...
to gather here today because...
I want Hyo Won and Tae Yang to get married...
on the day that Hyo Sang and Ji Yun are supposed to get married.
Exactly one month after that,
Hyo Sang and Ji Yun can get married.
That's why I asked you all to be here.
- Mum! - Madam Ko.
What do you mean by that, Madam Ko?
Let's just do as Mum says,
Darling.
How can you do this to us, Mum?
Why do we have to postpone our wedding?
Why on earth do we have to do that?
That is unacceptable, Madam Ko.
When an elder says something...
"Sure, okay."
"I'll do as you say." That's all you have to say.
Why do you have so much to talk about?
What did you just say?
Let me make it clear to you once again.
For the life of me,
I cannot allow Hyo Won and Tae Yang to get married.
Look who's talking.
I cannot allow you and Pooper to get married...
for the life of me!
What's wrong with you two?
Why can't you allow each other...
to get married for the life of you?
Why? What's the reason?
Tell me!
Hey, Kang Tae Yang.
What on earth did you do to my mum?
Please let go of me.
Let go. Let go of him immediately or I'll bite you!
You little... You're going to bite me as if kicking me wasn't enough?
How dare you!
Calm down. Your mum will be worried if she finds out about this.
Tae Yang didn't do anything wrong.
I pestered Mum about allowing us to get married as soon as possible.
- Hyo Won. - We might not be able...
to get married if Hyo Sang beats us to it.
- What do you mean... - Hyo Won now knows everything,
you idiot.
Hyo Won.
- Then... - Yes.
Hyo Won is rushing to marry Tae Yang because she found out...
that he and you used to date in the past.
Hey, Hyo Won. Does it not even bother you...
that your boyfriend has a past with another woman?
Why should it matter?
I went on many blind dates and had crushes on many guys, too.
What about you? Does it not bother you that Ji Yun used to date him?
Hey, how can I get jealous of a guy who's nowhere near my league?
This guy is nothing compared to me.
Okay. I feel the same way.
It's impossible to compare Pooper to me,
so it doesn't bother me at all. Not even a tiny bit.
I'm sorry.
I should have told you about it first.
I was hesitant because I didn't want to hurt you.
I know that you tried to tell me numerous times...
but I stopped you.
You didn't do...
anything wrong.
Thanks for being so understanding.
I really mean it.
When I first found out about it, I was surprised and upset.
But I've decided to be understanding.
Past is the past. What matters is to live in the present.
Thanks.
I'll thank you for the rest of my life.
So...
we'll get married this month, okay?
I'll take care of everything from booking a wedding venue...
to finding a place for us to live,
so you just need...
to walk down the aisle, okay?
Hyo Won.
We can't do that.
- Sorry? - We can't rush it like this.
Do you know what I said to Mum today to get her approval?
Never mind. You don't need to know about that.
Anyway, I went through hoops to get her permission,
and we can now beat Hyo Sang and Pooper by one month.
Why don't you want to do it?
I don't want to get married like this.
Why should your brother's marriage affect us?
My feelings for you...
are solid enough not to get affected by things like that.
What if my mum finds out...
about you and Ji Yun and disapproves of you?
I'm confident that I can persuade your mum.
I don't feel rushed or anxious at all,
so just trust me.
You don't love me.
What are you talking about?
You can't do this if you love me.
Your girlfriend proposed to you first. How can you reject it?
- That's not what I meant, Hyo Won. - I don't want to hear it.
Hyo Won.
Don't get me wrong, Hyo Won.
Don't drink on an empty stomach.
I need to drink this to be able to fall asleep.
Good night.
I'm so worried about him.
I'll ask one last time. Do you...
really want me to...
give up on you?
Yes. I've given up on you.
However hard it got, I thought we could fight through it together.
I was confident we could.
If I make your life tough, I won't force you.
Do you think marriage is a joke or what?
How can you talk about it as if it's not a big deal at all?
She's doing it for a reason.
I must say, you're the one who is acting the strangest.
You should be yelling at Hyo Won and going on a hunger strike.
How can you take her side?
Tell me the truth.
You two are hiding something from me, right?
- No, we're not. - No, we're not.
Then why are you rushing to get married all of a sudden?
My gosh! Just eat your food already!
Stop talking to me!
Goodness.
I almost jumped out of my skin.
I forgot.
Did I startled you a lot?
I'm okay.
- Can you do me a favour? - Sure.
For dinner,
- buy some oxtails and braise them. - Oxtails?
Yes. I want Hyo Won to eat something nourishing.
Why does she need to eat something nourishing?
I need it more as I'm burned out from work!
Fine! You can eat it with her.
Gosh, are you two kids or what? Why are you fighting over food?
Gosh, seriously.
By the way, where is Hyo Joo?
She left for work early today.
Really?
I asked you all to meet with me even though I know how busy...
you are because I wanted to discuss the company's future with you.
Mr Kim, please tell me what you think.
Sure. All of you must know that the company...
is in bad shape overall at the moment.
The numbers aren't looking good even after launching...
the new outdoor line in which we invested a lot.
As a result of that, we didn't get proper marketing support...
for our off-the-peg clothes,
and our sales are dropping overall.
It could be because Mr Min is young and inexperienced.
He hasn't come up with any solution to overcome this crisis.
I've spoken to a number of our main shareholders,
and all of them are deeply concerned.
Hence, I'd like all of you...
to work on appointing Mr Lee Dong Jin as a new CEO...
who can help the company overcome this crisis...
as a way of preparing for the upcoming meeting with shareholders.
The company has been in a mess ever since you left.
Almost all numbers are dropping quickly.
The employees...
are very concerned, too.
Everyone wants you to come back...
and sort out the situation.
Mr Min rushed to launch the new outdoor brand...
in order to prove himself as a CEO,
but it resulted in the company's system falling apart.
All of our major shareholders are deeply concerned, as well.
Most importantly, investors are turning...
their backs on the company.
The value of our stocks have dropped...
by 30 percent compared to when you were the CEO.
Appointing a new CEO...
will be discussed at the upcoming meeting with the shareholders.
Please come back for us...
as well as for the company's sake.
I didn't expect any of this, so all of this is too sudden for me,
but I will consider it seriously.
(Kang Tae Yang)
Hello?
Hello? Yun Shil.
It's you, right?
Yes, it's me.
Where are you now? What have you been up to?
I'm sorry for worrying you, Tae Yang.
I asked you where you are now.
I'm at a strawberry farm.
Strawberry farm?
There's a package for Ms Na Yun Shil.
- Thank you. - Have a good day.
Dong Jin, I found out where Yun Shil is.
Come with me. You'll be able to see her.
No, you go ahead.
What's wrong, Dong Jin?
Here. This came for her, so pass it along to her.
I'm feeling down today,
so shall I put in three spoons of sugar?
She even changed how I drink my coffee. Yun Shil,
you're bad.
Bring the divorce papers.
- I'll sign them right away. - Are you sure?
Now you're talking.
You look thrilled to hear that.
Right, we only live once.
You should live with a woman whom you want to be with.
Go ahead and live with your first love.
I'm going to watch how happy you two can be together.
She's saying she'd sign the papers.
Shall I just go ahead and get divorced?
This is kimchi I made.
It's perfectly ripe now. I hope Seung Woo likes it.
Thank you. I'm sure he will like it.
- Where are you going? - I should make you some tea.
No. I already had some at home, so please don't worry about me.
Just have a seat here.
Please feel free to talk casually.
You're Sam Do's wife,
so you're like a sister to me.
Shall I?
Where's Seung Woo?
- He's at the kindergarten. - I see.
I'm not sure how this will sound,
but shouldn't Seung Woo...
have a father?
- Pardon? - I don't think...
you should raise him by yourself forever.
It hasn't been long since my husband passed.
And I have no desire to get married again.
Someone like Sam Do...
could raise him like his own.
To tell you the truth,
Sam Do loves children.
It's just that I can't carry babies.
If he had children,
he'd be such a good father...
and love his children more than any other parent.
Sun Nyeo.
What's wrong?
It's okay.
I think I'm going through a menopause.
I get tearful easily.
My mood swings got severe.
Can you give me some water? I need to take some pills.
Okay.
What are the pills for?
I have a headache.
I think it's the stress.
My head has been killing me.
It's not like I'm going to die.
It's just...
temporary.
Your bankbook has been updated.
(Personal Checking Account)
If only I didn't lose that money,
I could've been able to given Sam Do more alimony.
The transition from a ballad singer to a trot singer...
must have worried you a lot.
Was there a special motive behind that?
I think music is equal.
Whether it's rock or trot, it's still music.
If I can make people happy and comfort them,
the genre doesn't matter.
You look very good in that suit.
Is that right? Thank you.
For your information,
I only get my suits sponsored by Wolgyesu Tailor Shop.
Wolgyesu Tailor Shop?
Yes. It's the best tailor shop in the country...
with the oldest history and tradition.
They're responsible for my outfits.
I see.
Your suit really is nice.
Can you look over here, Tae Pyung?
Okay.
All right. Once more.
That's very good.
Your sudden departure to the US 15 years ago...
was quite the shocking news.
I don't want to...
talk about that. No comment.
Okay. Then you have to answer this question.
Are you married?
Yes, Of course I'm...
He's not.
Tae Pyung is an artist who is married to music.
He is still everyone's lover.
Yun Shil.
Do you know what look you have on your face?
You worry about Dong Jin and you feel terrible.
Dong Jin has the same look on his face.
You should cheer him up. Please do that for me.
That's not what I'm capable of.
You're not doing him any good by running away like this.
I like Dong Jin a lot.
If I'm by his side,
he might get hurt.
And for his family, too.
I'm not sure if I can live with that.
Why is life so hard and difficult?
This is so hard.
I know how you feel, but do think it over.
The harder it is, the more you should rely on each other.
I don't think what you're doing is right.
Are you okay?
I just have a little cold.
You should go. You said you have work.
Both you and Dong Jin don't look very good.
Here.
This was sent to you. Dong Jin wanted me to give you this.
I'm sorry you had to come all the way out here.
I'll go for now. I'll be back later.
Don't leave your phone off and stay here.
Okay.
It's me, Dong Jin.
I just met Yun Shil.
I gave her what you asked me to.
Okay, thanks.
I wish I could tell you...
she's doing well.
But I don't think she is.
She even looked sick from a cold.
Did she take medication?
She should go to the hospital.
If you worry her so much, you should've gone there yourself.
This is hard for you and Yun Shil.
I don't understand why both of you are being like this.
I don't want to make things harder for Yun Shil.
Yun Shil didn't leave...
because you made it hard for her.
It's because she was afraid of hurting you.
That is why I am more upset.
I should be the one protecting her and someone she can rely on.
Why would she run away trying to protect me?
So you're upset...
because she didn't rely on you. Is that right?
Should I say you're sullen?
That's nonsense.
Yun Shil had a look on her face...
that says she can't stand not seeing you.
You had the same look, too.
That's not true.
Being stubborn runs in you both.
Let's hang up.
What is it this time?
I need to talk.
I've been absent for too long. I have to go back soon.
Make it short.
I'm sorry, Tae Yang.
I know it's been hard on you because of me.
You must have felt betrayed.
I said most of those things...
to purposefully distant myself from you.
That's why I was so cruel.
Why would you say that now?
So...
Please forgive me.
I'm begging you.
Why are you begging me?
- Are you trying to get back at... - I told you many times.
You're not someone I want to have revenge on.
Having revenge requires interest in that person.
Even though it's long in the past, we used to love each other.
I'm not that low of a person to avenge someone like that.
So don't get any wrong idea.
If you're not trying to get back at me,
please don't marry Hyo Won. Please.
Are you that insecure about your relationship?
- What? - It has nothing to do with you...
whether I marry Hyo Won or not.
I'm not ready yet, so I can't do that right now.
But one day,
I will definitely marry her.
So don't stick your nose in my love life.
I'm not intending on interfering with yours, either.
I don't want to get married like this.
What?
I want to see you right now.
I'm not that idle of a person to meet someone who doesn't love me.
I'll wait until you come out.
What is this?
I asked you what this is.
Can't you read? It's divorce paper.
And why are you giving it to me?
I told you.
You should live with a woman you want to be with.
I'll let you go now.
You can fly away to your first love.
What's gotten into you?
And...
this is alimony.
- Alimony? - I should've made more money.
It's not a lot.
It's not a lot,
but I want you to have it. Please accept it.
Why are you doing this? You're scaring me?
Why would you be scared? I'm granting your wish.
What's wrong with that woman?
Why is she acting like she's going to die tomorrow?
Lucky you, Sam Do.
You won the lottery.
Why would someone who doesn't want to get married...
go on a date?
You know that's not true. Why do you keep being unreasonable?
I hate you so much.
If you keep being mean, I won't give you the gift.
A gift?
What is this? You must like gifts more than me.
What's the gift?
Do you think I'm some kind of a baby?
Oh, you don't like cotton candy?
- I'll eat it, then. - No.
Give it to me. It's mine.
I haven't had cotton candy for so long.
It must be because it's festive season.
They were selling cotton candy nearby.
It looks delicious.
It melts in my mouth.
Is it good?
You were really upset...
because of me yesterday, right?
I trust you, Hyo Won.
So I don't feel pressured...
or anxious. You must not trust me.
I finished it already.
- What's this? - It's for you.
It's for me?
I'm not ready yet and don't have much...
so I can't officially propose to you.
But Hyo Won is mine.
I want to tie you down with this ring.
This feels nice.
It doesn't have jewelry, but I put my heart in it.
Will you happily accept it?
If it's a ring coming from your heart,
it has to be the most expensive ring in the world.
Hyo Won...
You were the beam of light shining through darkness...
when the sky of my youth was falling down on me.
You were so bright...
that I don't even remember...
being in the darkness.
Thank you.
Are you really thankful?
For real?
Then...
You should kiss me instead of talking.
Did I run out of gas?
- Yun Shil. - Yes?
I'm coming in.
Let me feel your forehead.
You're burning up. Shouldn't you go to the hospital?
It's fine. I took pills a while ago.
The fever will come down soon.
This is ginger tea.
Drink a cup of this and get some sleep.
If you feel really sick later, you should call me.
Okay. Thank you.
I'm scared something might happen to you.
(Ms Shiny Eyes)
- What is it? - What kind of a greeting is that?
Can't you be more welcoming?
Were the directors here?
Did you send them?
Don't force them to do your bidding. It'll only create more victims.
You just have to come back.
Come back...
and help them get back on their feet.
It's easier said than done.
Would I have left Meesa if it were that easy?
Hearing you say that...
makes me think you regret leaving.
Yes, I did at first.
I didn't know what to do with my life,
but things have changed now.
I don't think so. People don't change so easily.
I'm tired of arguing with you.
Please leave.
And stop coming here.
This is my workplace...
and you aren't welcome here.
Hello, Lee Dong Jin speaking.
Is this Na Yun Shil's husband's number?
Pardon?
Yes, it is.
I'm the owner of the strawberry farm.
I called because I'm afraid something terrible could happen.
Yun Shil is very sick.
I thought it was a cold. Is it serious?
I'll be right there. Thank you.
You can't leave mid-conversation.
I have nothing to say.
Where's he going? Is he off to see Yun Shil?
(Minkyung Farm)
Yun Shil.
Are you inside?
Yun Shil!
Yun Shil.
Wake up, Yun Shil. Yun Shil.
(The Gentlemen of Wolgyesu Tailor Shop)
What do you mean he is with her?
I'm sick and tired of living.
Poor Sam Do.
Her mood swings multiple times a day.
What's wrong with her?
I just don't get it.
Why do you want Hyo Won to marry Tae Yang?