(The following content may not be suitable for viewers under 15.)
(Viewer discretion is advised.)
Move away.
(Episode 41)
In 1, 2, 3!
Is she in a bad condition?
How is her burn?
She's burned on her leg,
but it's not that serious. Don't worry.
She is poisoned by carbon monoxide,
and seems to have a flu.
- I recommend her further check up. - I see.
Send her to the general ward...
and proceed a CT scan.
(Nowadays I think about the future and look back on the past.)
Hello?
- It's me, Father. - Hello, Dong Jin.
I don't think I can go home today.
- What happened? - It's about Yun Shil.
- She is in the emergency room. - What happened to Yun Shil?
What?
I see.
All right.
She's not in a life-threatening situation, right?
What do you mean by a life-threatening situation?
I see. Call me immediately if something happens.
All right. Bye.
Did something happen to Yun Shil?
Yun Shil was working in a strawberry farm in Hwa Seong.
There was a fire in her room and she was taken to the emergency room.
What?
Don't worry. She's not in a life-threatening situation.
My goodness.
Did she get a burn, then?
Her burn is not serious.
She lost her consciousness since she inhaled the smoke.
Did she lose her consciousness?
Are you sure it won't affect her life?
It's a bolt out of the blue.
What on earth is going on?
It's all my fault.
She might have died because of me.
What shall I do?
- Here, here! - Help me!
- Help me! - Come here!
- Quickly! - Here!
Please Stop.
Look at them
What do you think?
I think it fits,
but I should tie the shoe laces, though.
I can do it.
- No, I can do it myself. - No, I will do it.
You're wearing a skirt.
Give me your hand.
Ms Na Yun Shil.
Her temperature is going down fortunately.
Considering her blood test, ECG and chest X-ray...
she was lightly poisoned by carbon monoxide.
Also, her flu test result is negative.
I see.
Her CT scan result shows no other infection.
- Please remove the oxygen mask. - Yes, doctor.
When will she wake up?
She didn't lose her consciousness. She fell asleep.
She will wake up after a good sleep. Don't worry.
She needs to take enough rest...
and eat nutritious food.
- I see. Thank you. - Thank you.
I shouldn't have left you alone...
even if you pushed me away.
I'm sorry, Yun Shil.
It's all my fault.
It's so glittering, isn't it?
You're bluffing.
It's a 14K gold ring without a gem. How can it be glittering?
It's strange. Why is it so glittering to me?
It's dazzling. I can't even open my eyes.
I'm sorry.
If only I had enough money,
I would have proposed you confidently.
Come to think of it,
dating is better for my age than marriage.
I was impatient because of Hyo Sang and Ji Yun.
Thank you for understanding me.
You'd better do your best after you marry me.
I will for sure.
I'll be 10 times better.
No, 20 times better than you expect me to be.
That sounds good.
I'm home.
I made a reservation at a wedding dress store tomorrow afternoon.
Call Tae Yang to set aside some time.
We decided not to get married.
What do you mean?
Tae Yang says we can do that later.
Later? Why?
He says he's not ready.
Anyway, we will get married later.
When are you going to marry?
Do you want to get married when you're heavily pregnant?
Why would I be heavily pregnant?
You're out of your mind.
I mean your baby inside you.
My baby? I get it. My baby.
Do you want to do the bridal march when you're heavily pregnant?
Do you want to put me to a shame?
Well,
that will never happen.
What do you mean?
Well, I mean...
I won't be heavily pregnant.
Wait.
Did Tae Yang notice by any chance?
- What? - I mean,
did Tae Yang tell you to abort the baby?
Well. Mum,
I want you to calm down and listen to me carefully.
I swear he will pay for this.
Mum, Mum!
I'm so scared to tell her that I lied about my pregnancy.
(Peace Gosiwon)
Why is she visiting me at this late hour?
- Honey. - Hi.
You!
- You punk. - What's going on?
Calm down, Mum. You shouldn't use violence.
Do you think I can calm down?
You ruined my daughter's future,
and now you want to delay the wedding?
- Pardon? - You seduced an innocent girl.
How can you feign innocence?
What do you mean I feign innocence?
You should take the responsibility for what you've done.
How can you play innocence?
I don't understand what you mean. Please tell me precisely.
Why don't you want to marry my daughter?
How dare you boss around?
There must be a misunderstanding.
Right. It's a misunderstanding.
Let's go home and talk with me in a calm and orderly way.
You should back out.
Will you marry my daughter or not?
I will marry her for sure.
But I'm not ready to support Hyo Won yet.
What about my daughter and the...
Mum.
Anyway, I will take the responsibility for everything.
- You should just get married. - Pardon?
You're driving me crazy.
We should go home and talk.
Don't lay one on me later.
You should get married by this month.
Otherwise, it's the end for both of us.
- Okay. You can talk with me, Mum. - My goodness.
My goodness.
Hold on a second.
Calm down, Mum.
What happened, Hyo Won?
It's nothing.
Mum seems to have a little misunderstanding.
Don't worry about it. Good night, Tae Yang.
I mind a lot.
Don't say a word. Get married by this month.
Honey, it's cold. Get inside and I'll call you later.
As long as I'm alive,
you can't do anything funny.
Mum, buckle up.
Honey, get inside.
Why is she doing that?
She said we should never get married.
Why is she telling us to get married?
My goodness.
Calm down.
We need to talk, Mum.
What do we have to talk about?
They say every evil doer has his reasons.
How can you back-stab me like this?
My goodness.
What happened? Are you crying?
What on earth is going on? Why are you crying, Mum?
Oh, my goodness.
What happened to Mum?
- Did you make a trouble again? - Not me, you did.
- What are you talking about? - You want to marry Pooper.
Isn't that a trouble?
Why do you call her Popper when she has a decent name?
She will be your family. What a nerve!
She won't be my family.
You can't marry her.
There's nothing special about Kang Tae Yang.
She must be out of her mind.
Will.
I,
Bok Sun Nyeo,
is near...
death.
Before I die,
I pass along...
several requests...
to my husband, Bae Sam Do.
First,
on my last moments,
Bae Sam Do...
should hold my hands...
and kiss on my forehead.
Second,
at the same time,
he should whisper...
(Second, at the same time...)
in my ear...
that he loves me.
(He should whisper in my ear that he loves me.)
Poor Sam Do.
Poor thing.
You came home late.
I had a lot of orders.
Change your cloths. I'll set the table.
Wait a minute, honey.
Do you need to tell me something?
Here you go.
- What's this? - Divorce paper.
Divorce paper?
You told me yesterday that you would stamp on it if I bring it.
- What? - I already put my stamp on it.
You are a jerk!
Why do you hit me?
You told me you would stamp on it if I bring the divorce paper.
Did you really have to bring it?
You're so mean.
You keep two tongues in one mouth. You told me you would stamp on it!
You'd rather wish me dead.
You won't take the trouble to go to the court if I die.
What are you talking about? Who's going to die?
You suggested divorce first.
Why are you picking on me?
What's this fuss about?
I was going to leave you...
even without this kind of paper.
How can you bring this?
Couldn't you just wait any longer?
Are you that sick and tired of me, Bae Sam Do?
What on earth did I do wrong...
to you?
- Calm down, Sun Nyeo. - Right. I'm sick of you.
A day feels like an eternity for me.
Now that you suggested divorce, I brought the paper cheerfully.
I'm so sick of you when you're acting like this.
- I'm so tired of you. - Calm down, Sam Do.
This is not like you.
She always change her words. I'm so sick of that.
Sam Do, calm down and get inside. We need to talk.
Let's get in. Let's go.
Get inside now.
Why do yo say something you don't want to?
You don't want to divorce him.
I don't know what I want.
I feel pity for him,
Bae Sam Do.
And I sometimes hate him.
I don't know how I feel.
Calm down, Sun Nyeo. Calm down.
You don't really want to divorce Sun Nyeo, do you?
I don't really want to divorce her,
but this kind of opportunity doesn't come every day.
So I wanted to get her stamp on the paper to cure her of the habit.
You're so innocent.
Do you think she really means it?
That's what I'm saying.
Why does she get me all riled up...
when she doesn't want to divorce me?
You're right about that.
By the way, why did she suggest divorce all of a sudden?
She's trying to pick on me.
My goodness. She's like a bull dog.
(Hwa Seong Hospital)
You went to so much trouble.
You're all right now.
You're in the hospital. Don't you remember?
A fire was set on your room. It might have been a disaster.
Why are you here?
- Yun Shil. - I told you to never find me again.
Why are you doing this?
Then,
you shouldn't have been sick.
I turned away since you told me you were in a trouble because of me.
Then you should have been good by yourself.
How can I leave you...
if you got sick like this?
I just got a cold.
I just lost my consciousness due to a fire.
- It was just an accident. - No.
You didn't want to break up with me, but you tried to push me away.
That's why you got sick.
I gave up my feelings for you.
I don't care.
I can't give you up...
and I don't want to give you up.
Don't be unreasonable and go back.
You should stay calm.
We can talk about it later. Lie down.
Get out of the way. If you don't leave, I'll leave.
Please!
Lie down if you don't want to collapse again.
I'd rather collapse...
and never wake up again.
However I try to hide, you find me.
I don't even know where to hide any more.
I'm exhausted.
Don't be exhausted alone.
I'll be beside you.
You make me exhausted.
How many times do I have to tell you?
It's over between us.
I don't want to see you again,
so don't tear me up like this.
What shall I do...
if being worried...
and heartbroken...
to see you sick...
makes you feel like that?
Did you even love me?
Why does that matter now?
Please, just go.
Fine.
If you hate my being here so much, I'll have to go.
I'll go.
You feel sick...
because of me?
Goodness.
You should be in the hospital.
Why were you drinking?
Hi, Mother.
I'm sorry, but I think I'm drunk.
Get it together and tell me.
What did you do with Yun Shil? Why did you drink so much?
Yun Shil? Na Yun Shil...
She's in the hospital.
You left her there alone and drank?
Yes. She kept...
telling me to leave.
She said you'd be upset if I stayed in the hospital.
She kept telling me to leave, or she'd leave the hospital.
So I had no choice but to come home.
She is impossible.
She is a total fool.
Why is my gentlemanly brother-in-law so drunk?
I'm not.
Yun Shil is hurt and in the hospital,
but I left her there alone.
I had no choice but to leave her there...
and it just hurt too much.
I thought it would help if I got drunk, but it was no use.
It didn't help at all.
Okay. Let's go in. You're drunk. You drank a lot.
I'll help you. Come on.
Good night, Mother.
It's all my fault.
I've sinned too much.
Come in. Here.
There you go.
No. I'm fine.
I'm not drunk.
Drunk people always say they aren't drunk.
Fine. You're not drunk. You're not. So let's lie down.
Sung Jun. Why is life...
so exhausting?
I have...
no energy any more.
I'm so exhausted now.
He's having such a hard time.
Let's give them our blessing.
I feel like I should give in and not make my son cry,
but then again,
it's just too much.
Once that thug gets released from prison,
poor Dong Jin will suffer. It's clear as day.
Don't think only about Dong Jin,
but Yun Shil, too, whom we considered our daughter.
We can't make decisions out of fear.
Must our precious son...
live with so much pain because of that thug?
Did you even love me?
Why does that matter now?
Please, just go.
Fine. If you hate my being here so much, I'll have to go.
I'll go.
I'm sorry, Dong Jin.
Dong Jin, are you still sleeping?
No, Mother. I'm up.
Have some honey water.
Okay.
I know you're upset, but why did you drink so much?
I'm sorry.
Get it together and lead the way.
Lead the way? To where?
Where else? To the hospital where Yun Shil is.
Mother.
Are you leaving without having breakfast?
I'm sorry about last night.
I apologize.
You can't fool me twice.
You'll apologize and then stab me in the back again.
I won't fall for it.
It's because I'm not ready yet.
I'm not doing it to hurt you, so please understand.
Ready for what?
I'll tell you later. I'll tell you everything later.
What's this?
What else? Spend it for today.
This is for today? For one day?
It's 50 dollars.
That's a 10 times increase.
You need days like this, too.
Use this to have a good lunch...
and have some nice tea, okay?
She keeps flip-flopping several times a day.
What has gotten into her?
Have you heard about Yun Shil?
Dong Sook says she woke up, so she should be fine.
Thank goodness Mr Lee went right at that time.
I know. He saved her life.
Is anyone in?
Why is she here so early in the morning?
Where's the boss?
It's none of your business where our boss is.
Why are you here?
Where did you hide my daughter-in-law? Spill it.
I told you already.
We're going crazy trying to find her ourselves.
Gi Pyo's boys can find her in half a day.
If you're hiding her somewhere,
my son will kill all of you.
If you can find her in half a day, why are you annoyingly asking us?
My sentiments exactly.
Why you...
Yes?
Mr Lee and Ms Choi. How are you...
You poor thing. You must have been so shocked.
Thank goodness it isn't worse.
We were so shocked when we heard.
I'm sorry for worrying you.
I know you're trying hard to keep your promise to me,
so don't be sorry.
I only said it with my mouth that you were my daughter,
and was terrible to you. I'm sorry, Yun Shil.
What is Dong Jin doing outside?
Dong Jin.
Are you offering your food to the dead or something?
Why are you just staring at it?
Go on and eat.
Stop crying.
It'll tire you out. Eat.
Here.
You'll get sick. Chew well.
You need to get better so that you can come home,
and you need to eat so that you can get better.
Mother.
Do you mean...
I think your mother means...
she'll let the two of you date or something like that.
Right, honey?
When you come home,
I'll make you cabbage pancakes, which you like.
Mother.
You feed her the rest.
She keeps crying because I'm here.
Yes. We should bow out.
I'll clean your room, so get better and come home.
Thank you.
Sure. You take good care of her.
I will. Thank you, Father.
I came because your mother wanted to. Don't thank me.
We're going.
Okay.
I'll go see them out.
What could Hyo Won's mother want now?
Hello, Mother.
Come to the wedding dress shop right now.
Wedding dress?
Hello.
Hi, darling.
Hi. Why are we here?
She's trying on wedding dresses at a wedding dress shop.
Do you think she's here to buy candy?
I understand,
but why a wedding dress?
She needs a wedding dress before the wedding.
Don't look at her.
She wants to get married later, but I insisted.
- Mother, I... - Stop talking.
Hyo Won, try on the dresses.
Tae Yang, try on the tuxedos.
Now!
Sorry.
I just don't get it.
Why is she suddenly insisting...
on marrying Hyo Won and Tae Yang?
Do you think Mother...
found out about Tae Yang and my past...
Definitely not.
With her temper, if she found out,
she would have blown a fuse over and over.
She wouldn't let it slide like this.
Forget it.
I need to talk to her.
- Hello? - Hi, Mum. Where are you?
At a wedding dress shop.
A wedding dress shop?
Why did you go there? Why?
Okay.
Not bad.
Ms Lee.
Don't you have anything else?
- Something more feminine. - My goodness.
How many times will you make me change?
And I told you, we decided not to get married.
That's right. We decided to get married once I've saved up enough.
Ms Lee.
Please excuse us.
Yes, Madam.
When will you save up enough?
- I have my part time job and... - How can you support...
Hyo Won and the baby...
with your part time job?
What baby?
Why are you asking me?
What's going on?
I'm sorry.
- Darling. - Why are you sorry?
He should be sorry for spreading his seed when he has no money!
I've never done that, Mother.
What do you mean, you've never done that?
I totally misjudged you. You are utterly irresponsible!
How could you play dumb?
I wanted to marry Tae Yang as soon as possible,
so I told a teensy-bitsy lie.
I'm sorry.
How could you?
- Please, calm down. - Of all the lies!
How could you lie about that?
- Darling, are you all right? - Are you out of your mind?
Mum. What's wrong?
What is it?
That freak-show.
See? What did I say?
I told you Tae Yang is a total doofus.
Not Tae Yang. Hyo Won!
She wanted to marry him so much...
that she lied about being pregnant.
- What? - What?
I'm sorry.
I overdid it slightly.
Overdid it slightly?
- Please don't hit her. - Mum!
You stay out of it, punk!
Why do you keep grabbing him by his collar?
Let go of him!
- Tae Yang. - Are you okay?
What are you doing to your brother?
Did you just yell at me?
How dare you yell at her?
- I'll do the same! - I'll grab her by her collar...
so that she comes to her senses!
- Why you... - Let go!
How dare you...
You're driving me crazy!
Everyone freeze!
You didn't eat enough.
The doctor said you need to eat and sleep well in order to recover.
I've thought about it, and this isn't right.
So please, go home.
There you go again. Didn't you hear my mother?
She said that because I'm hurt and she feels sorry for me.
I can't be shameless and pretend she meant it.
Are you saying...
my mother said things she didn't mean, just to look good?
- That's not it... - Exactly.
My mother was genuinely worried about you and told you to come back.
If you refuse, you're the bad person here.
I'm not saying I don't want to do it.
I just don't think I should.
So you should go home for now.
I can take care of myself.
Do you really...
want me to be a loser who gets angry at someone who isn't well?
Be honest.
Why do you keep saying things you don't mean? It isn't like you.
Come in.
You're finally awake.
So, are you okay?
You must have been worried.
I'm sorry.
Why? It's not like you did it on purpose.
You were just unlucky that happened.
Plus, your husband paid for the repairs,
so I'm thankful.
The repairs?
It's because your husband ran over right in the nick of time,
that he put out the fire and you weren't more injured.
It could have been really dangerous.
But she doesn't remember any of it...
and keeps scolding me.
Why are you scolding him?
You should be singing his praise.
Also,
Yun Shil, I brought all of your things.
Once you're recovered, go to Seoul with your husband.
But...
Just because you had...
a little fight, you shouldn't...
pack your bags and move out.
It'll become a habit.
I should have treated my wife better.
My goodness. You are handsome,
and sweet, too.
You'll never find another man like him.
If my husband were just a tiny bit like him...
I'd carry him around all over the place.
Get well soon and carry me around.
Dong Jin's with her right now?
What do you mean?
I guess we have no control over relationships.
I did my best to break the two up,
but it's out of my hands.
What do you mean?
You said she left.
She moved away to distance herself from us and our family...
and she got into an accident.
- An accident? - A fire.
She was hurt.
I don't think Dong Jin and Yun Shil...
will be able to break up.
You can't say that, Mother.
You can't do this to me...
when I gave up my pride to beg the majority shareholders...
to bring him back to Meesa as CEO.
I'm grateful that you still think so highly of Dong Jin,
but I think the flame that you two had...
burned out long ago.
I would like it if you gave up.
Don't beg to make the impossible possible.
I thought you would take my side.
I'm disappointed.
I won't give up on Dong Jin.
I will...
bring him back to where he belongs.
I'll come back again.
She should have been nice to him when she had the chance.
Have you accepted Yun Shil as your daughter-in-law?
What are you saying?
I never said that.
That's what you just said.
I said she can stay because I feel sorry for her.
That's all I meant.
I will never understand.
Why does she have to be so stubborn when she will accept her in the end?
What did you just hide?
It's nothing.
It's not nothing. You were looking at something.
Do you read racy magazines when I'm not looking?
What are you talking about?
What did you hide, then?
Our wedding photos?
You should have said so.
Why did you hide them in a hurry?
I'm going crazy inside.
Everyone will suffer because of me.
That's why I should leave you.
That's the right thing to do.
Yet, I still want you and want to be with you...
and I hate myself for being like that.
You're driving me crazy.
You ran away and said you want to leave me.
That broke my heart to pieces...
and now you're being so sweet.
I just can't hate you even if you do something so hateful.
It's driving me crazy.
I'm not joking. I'm serious.
Corny comments sound worse when they're said in a serious tone.
Can't you give me a break?
I feel like I aged 10 more years while you were away.
Do you see my dark circles?
Once we get home...
I'll tell my parents that we'll get married.
- You can't run away. - You can't do that.
You met my mum and dad, didn't you?
They only allowed me to come home.
They didn't say we could get married.
It's the same thing.
How is that the same thing?
I know my mum.
Eat well, sleep well and get well soon...
so we can ask for their blessing, okay?
I'm so tired.
I'm exhausted. I could pass out right now.
Are you okay?
Can't you just give me an answer?
Will you?
This is the obedient Shiny Eyes I'm used to.
Lean on me.
Come on.
Here.
I like this one.
I'm really sorry, honey.
Don't call me that.
You said you were pregnant like it was nothing...
because you act like we're married.
I will get pregnant when we get married.
Can't I use the excuse a bit in advance?
Is it that wrong?
You still don't get it, do you?
I apologise.
How could you lie about that of all things?
I didn't want Hyo Sang and Ji Yun to get married before us.
I told you that...
we'll go at our own pace, regardless of them.
I'm sorry.
I apologised sincerely.
Will you accept it?
I should apologise to you.
You were anxious enough to lie about being pregnant.
I'm not good enough.
Don't say that. You did nothing wrong.
Then come with me...
and ask for forgiveness.
Will you?
Does that mean you forgive me?
I said I should be the one to apologise.
Then can I go back to calling you "honey"?
Honey. Honey. Honey.
You already did.
You smiled. My honey smiled.
Honey.
Honey. Honey. Honey.
- Honey. - Honey.
Honey.
Watch your step.
Gosh, it's freezing.
Here. You can wear this, Dong Sook.
Here.
No.
You have to sing. Keep your throat warm.
I said I'm okay.
Let's wrap you up.
- There. - Thanks.
We should get a car so we can drive to all your gigs.
We had to take three different buses today.
It took us half a day to get here.
You're right.
Anyway,
there's not a single soul, it's so cold.
What kind of a festival is this?
We'll see. Let's go.
Okay.
(Trout and Smelt Festival)
- Get on. - What?
- Let's go. - We're off.
Round, round, round
Your eyes are so round
I have fallen, fallen, fallen into them
What should I do?
When you are tired
Lean on my shoulders
Sung Tae Pyung.
When you are sick
Don't hesitate to give me a call
I love you, baby
My brother goes, goes, goes
- He goes at full speed - Sing along with him.
He is coming to you
Do not say a word
Just hold me tight
To you, right now, immediately
My brother goes
Sung Tae Pyung, Sung Tae Pyung.
Encore, encore, encore.
Sung Tae Pyung.
(Bok Sun Nyeo)
(Will)
First, on my last moment, Bae Sam Do should hold my hands...
and kiss on my forehead.
(Will)
At the same time...
he should whisper in my ear that he loves me.
Third.
After I die, cremate me...
and leave my urn in Youngsung Remembrance Hall.
I reserved another spot next to me.
Bae Sam Do will be with me even in death.
Fourth.
A fifth of the payouts from my life and health insurance policies...
should be given to my brother, Bok Sun Dong.
I feel dizzy.
I think...
it's terminal.
Why else...
would I be in so much agony?
I can't die before...
I take care of everything.
I can't...
waste time like this.
What did the doctor say?
I see.
Okay.
Mother, a customer just came in.
I'll call you back. Bye.
Hello.
Do you have plans this evening?
I don't think I do. Why?
Come over to my place for dinner.
Is it a special day?
No.
Then why are you inviting me?
I want to apologise for causing a ruckus last time,
and I want to tell you something, too.
I'll only set out an extra pair of chopsticks,
so there's no pressure.
Okay.
Sun Nyeo.
You don't look good. Are you sick?
I didn't sleep well last night.
See you later.
I can wash my own face.
Not with a huge needle stuck in your arm.
You have a cold and cold water's bad for you,
so we'll make do with this for now.
Someone might think I'm seriously ill.
You had a 40-degree fever,
carbon monoxide poisoning and got burned.
That's bad enough.
Now your whole face is shiny and clean.
It's time to put on some lotion.
- It's fine. - It's not fine.
- Close your eyes. - Why should I...
close my eyes?
They'll sting if you don't. Close your eyes.
Hey.
I'm putting lotion on your face. Why are you sticking out your lips?
What does lotion have to do with lips?
Did you think I brought this so I could kiss you?
It's not that.
I was just hoping...
you'd moisturise my lips, too.
The room's dry...
and my lips got chapped.
I see.
I got imaginative.
You're so silly.
Close your eyes...
and I'll moisturise your lips.
Put this on yourself.
I knew you'd do that.
You just made me feel silly.
You're back to being your cute self.
My Shiny Eyes is back.
Just a moment.
Lee Dong Jin speaking.
Hey, Gianni. Thanks, happy new year.
Happy new year, Dong Jin.
I've got some good news for you for the new year.
What's that?
As you know, Tonelli...
and Meesa Apparel had been discussing...
opening a flagship store in Asia.
But we decided to postpone it.
I'm excited to tell you that Tonelli has decided...
to partner with Wolgyesu Tailor Shop.
As an Asia partner company?
I mean it's...
It's great news.
Yes. I've got more great news.
I've just been appointed to be the Asian Rep. Director...
and I just got to Seoul.
Let's set up a meeting and discuss the details as soon as possible.
Okay, I'll wait for you. Okay, bye.
Was it good news?
Do you remember Gianni Moravia?
The designer who got a suit made at our store?
Yes, him.
He's head designer of an Italian company,
one of the best in the world.
His company wants to work with us...
as an Asian partner.
- Really? - When I was in Meesa...
I tried so hard to make this happen.
It actually happened after I met you.
Should I call this the Na Yun Shil Effect?
Don't be silly.
I didn't do anything.
I should tell Father and Master Bae.
Go on. They'll be very pleased.
(Min Hyo Sang)
Come in.
Mr Kim.
Tonelli's Gianni Moravia arrived in Seoul today.
What for?
A fashion magazine reporter said...
he's here to discuss opening an Asian flagship store.
He came via Hong Kong.
That means he's looking for a partner.
Isn't it strange that he didn't contact us?
Find out where he's staying.
Yes, Sir.
I have a bad feeling about this.
It smells great.
- Add the smelt you caught. - Okay.
Smelt, my dear smelt
Isn't this supposed to be a festival?
Why are there so few people?
No one in Korea is in the mood to have fun.
Too many bad things happened recently...
and now the bird flu's back.
We're lucky that...
- we get to eat noodles here. - We are.
It's delicious.
- I'm sorry, Dong Sook. - For what?
For dragging you here...
in the freezing cold and feeding you instant noodles.
Why is this a problem?
It's a memory.
This is how every singer starts out.
Don't let it get to you.
Let's eat the noodles and cheer up.
Shall we?
It's cooked.
Let's have a bite.
That is delicious. Your turn.
The soup is just amazing.
The fish is cooked, too.
You came in together.
She came over to the store and walked me back.
I see.
Sam Do says you like cheesecake.
I don't like cheesecake. I like sweet potato cakes.
You know nothing about me.
Sorry.
It happens.
Cheesecake or sweet potato cake.
Who cares what it is?
Hello, Seung Woo.
How are you?
You're so polite. I wonder who you take after.
I think...
Seung Woo looks a bit like you.
What are you talking about?
If people saw you, they'd take you for...
father and son. Right, Young Eun?
- What? - I was kidding.
Come and sit. Sit down, Seung Woo.
There's not much but I hope you enjoy yourself.
Thanks, Sun Nyeo.
Let me tell you a bit about my chicken stew.
I got the recipe from my great grandmother...
and I added a bit of my special sauce.
I'll tell you the recipe...
and how to make my special sauce.
- Me? - Yes.
Sam Do can't stand chicken,
but he likes this dish.
What are you talking about?
Later.
I'll tell you later.
Let's just enjoy a nice dinner together today.
Eat.
What...
Honey, are you crying? Why?
No.
Sorry. I was thinking about something.
You know,
the three of you look good together.
It looks good.
Sun Nyeo, why do you keep saying strange things today?
It's nothing. Let's eat.
Seung Woo. Eat up, okay?
Eat.
Goodness.
Come in.
You wicked brat!
Please calm down.
How did I give birth to something like that?
What did I do wrong when I was pregnant,
that I gave birth to a liar like that?
I'm sorry, Mum.
Tae Yang scolded me this entire time,
so don't be angry.
That's right. She's repenting, so please forgive her.
Please forget that I grabbed you by your collar...
because of the misunderstanding.
Of course. Here.
It's for you.
What is this?
He got paid for his modelling gig.
I got a ring yesterday.
That's your gift.
You didn't need to get me anything.
How could I not? You're my manager.
Oh, my gosh.
What are these?
Why don't you try wearing lower heels for your health?
You're the only one who thinks of me.
That's right. Someone as upright as you...
would not have done something like that.
I can't trust my daughter, but I should have trusted you.
I was a little short sighted.
Her fever's down and her breathing looks good.
The test results were good, so you may be discharged tomorrow.
Thank you.
- Thank you. - Sure.
Congratulations.
You did all the work. Thank you.
- My back. - Did you hurt your back? It hurts?
I slept scrunched up on the couch,
so it's all knotted up. It hurts.
- What should we do? - What else?
I'll just have to squeeze in and sleep with you.
Wait.
What? On this tiny bed?
It isn't tiny. It's big.
Come here. Lie down.
It's okay.
What's okay? Come on.
You're unbearable.
What do you mean? You'll have to live with me.
You smell nice.
I smell like sweat.
Even your sweat smells nice.
Stop teasing me.
I want to get married soon...
and lie down together like this, sharing our body warmth,
and listening to your breathing as I fall asleep.
Be honest. You feel the same, don't you?
It's too uncomfortable for me.
It's uncomfortable? How about this?
I can't breathe. I'm a patient.
You're not a patient any more. Stop whining.
Come here.
Why did we come here?
Listen to what I say and repeat after me.
I, Na Yun Shil, swear I will not run away any more, no matter...
how difficult or rough things get,
and I swear I will never leave Lee Dong Jin's side.
Dong Jin.
Go on.
I won't run away. I mean it.
Not like that. Say it the way I just did.
It's because I still don't feel assured.
Okay.
I, Na Yun Shil, swear that I will not run away like a coward anymore,
no matter how difficult or rough things get,
and I swear never to leave Lee Dong Jin's side.
You swore. You can't change your tune later.
I won't.
What happened?
They had to remove it...
when they were examining you, so I held onto it.
You didn't even notice it was gone.
Sorry.
Okay. Don't ever take it off again.
(The Gentlemen of Wolgyesu Tailor Shop)
I'd like to get married.
Who says they can get married?
Marriage is reality.
That rat came out of nowhere and ruined the family.
Your funeral photo?
I don't think I have much time left.
I think Sun Nyeo is sick.
Dong Jin belongs in a big world with me.
He isn't someone who should rot in a tiny tailor shop with you.
Our happiness begins now.
Can we really do this?
Can I really marry you?