(The following content may not be suitable for viewers under 15.)
(Viewer discretion is advised.)
(Episode 42)
(Wolgyesu Tailor Shop)
It must feel refreshing yet strange to be back.
I never thought I'd be back.
Thanks, Dong Jin.
Oh, right. Yun Shil.
- Submit a written explanation. - A written explanation?
You didn't come to work without giving any notice and disappeared.
You affected the shop's business negatively.
An apology is all that is necessary. Why do I have to write such a thing?
Our shop is just like any other company. I can't just let it go.
Reflect on your mistake...
and write it sincerely.
So are you asking me to write a letter of apology now?
I bet you wrote it many times in school.
I was such a good student.
Stop saying things that can't even be confirmed. Anyhow,
I want to draw a clear line between work and personal life,
so I'd like you to submit it right away.
Welcome back, Yun Shil.
I'm so glad you're back.
- How are you feeling? - Good.
I'm so sorry to have worried you, Ms Geum.
I'm sorry and grateful for everything, Master Bae.
Dong Jin was so worried about you.
I told her to write a written explanation.
- Written explanation? - Written explanation?
I'll reject it if I don't like it,
so you better write it with all of your heart, Yun Shil.
Okay, I will.
Did you guys go home yet?
Not yet. We came here first.
Mr Lee and Ms Choi must be waiting. You should go.
Okay. I'm really sorry for worrying you.
I apologise again.
I'm back, Mr Lee.
Yes, welcome back.
- How are you feeling? - I'm a lot better.
I'm sorry you went through that.
- Where's Mum? - She's making lunch.
Let's go in, guys.
Dad.
My gosh, Yun Shil.
I'm so sorry that you had to go through that.
Are you feeling all right now?
Yes, I'm fine.
Dong Jin looks happy now that you're back, Yun Shil.
- Congratulations, Dong Jin. - Thanks.
My heart ached so much after you left like that.
I'm so sorry that I wasn't there for you.
Please don't say that, Dong Sook.
Ms Choi, I'm back.
Welcome back. I've been waiting for you.
- All right. Let's sit, everyone. - Okay.
Mum has been cooking up a storm for you since this morning.
Eating and sleeping well is the best remedy.
Don't worry about anything and get as much rest as you can.
I will, Ms Choi.
All right. Let's eat, everyone.
Yun Shil.
Mum made napa cabbage pancakes which you love.
- Eat it while it's still hot. - Okay. Thank you.
Try the deep-fried smelts, too.
I went fishing and caught them myself.
You went there to make money but came back...
with smelts instead of money.
You performed on "Music Stage",
so I thought you'd make it big soon.
When will you start earning an income?
His song is getting good feedback, so it'll become a big hit soon.
Look forward to it.
Here.
- It's okay. - You should eat more.
You didn't even have a proper breakfast.
You two are wearing matching rings.
Are you guys getting married? When?
I thought Mother approved of it.
Isn't that why you decided to come back, Yun Shil?
My back is killing me. I should go lie down.
Yun Shil, eat up.
Thank you.
Why did you follow me?
I want to tell you something.
Mum.
We want to get married. Please give us permission.
Do you have to rush it like that?
I'm not against it.
It's just that it's the most important decision in life.
I think you should take more time and think about it carefully.
I feel like something else...
will get in the way if we don't do it now.
Hardships won't deflect just because you guys are married.
From that woman who claims to be Yun Shil's mother-in-law...
to the jerk who will show up saying that he's her husband,
you'll have to put up with everything.
If you're not confident about overcoming it all,
don't even start.
I will not avoid anything. I'm confident, Mum.
Good.
I haven't completely made up my mind yet,
so just give me a little bit of time to think.
My goodness.
Oh, my goodness.
The housekeeper...
made the porridge with pine nuts which you love.
You should eat this, Mum.
Are you kidding me right now?
Before I could even get out of the shock from you being pregnant,
you told me that it was all a lie.
Tell me. How long were you planning on fooling me?
I was going to tell you the truth...
after we get married.
Gosh, you fool.
Madam Ko, I'm here.
Goodness. Why is Pooper here again?
My goodness.
Oh, my goodness.
Hyo Sang told me that you're unwell.
I came to see you because I was worried.
I see. Thanks for coming.
How have you been?
Eat this, Mum.
You must be so upset.
You probably coddled Hyo Won a lot because she's the youngest.
That's why she doesn't know how the world works.
That's what I'm saying.
But...
being out of touch with reality isn't good.
Don't you think you should make her expand the range...
of people she hangs out with and meet more guys?
You are right.
She's still so young, yet she's not even going to work.
All she does is obsessing over her boyfriend.
She's being so anti-social and ineffective.
Are you criticising my daughter right now?
No, that's not what I meant.
Do you not respect your future in-laws?
How dare you badmouth your future sister-in-law?
I wasn't badmouthing her. I'm just worried about her.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry to say this to you, but...
Hyo Won.
You should know the reality of marriage.
You grew up without any hardships.
I can't understand why you want to marry a guy like Tae Yang.
Then don't try to understand.
I don't even want to be understood by someone like you.
Someone like me?
You betrayed Tae Yang...
and chose another guy because Tae Yang is not rich.
No wonder you can't understand me.
What did you just say? Don't you think you're out of line?
There was a materialistic aspect. That I'm not going to deny.
But essentially, what I hated more about him...
was how he had no ambition or dream.
That's why I was attracted to Hyo Sang who is the exact opposite.
I guess you can say that he's chilled if you want to sugarcoat it.
But to me, it just looked like he was trying...
to look chilled when he's actually lazy and incompetent.
He chose to postpone his dreams in order to help...
and take care of his girlfriend who was poor.
How can you call someone like that lazy and incompetent?
Shouldn't you be thanking him?
I already repaid him for everything he did for me, so I'm not indebted.
I'm speechless.
Don't just try to see the good sides.
Look at the situation objectively and carefully.
Is Tae Yang living like that because he's chilled and down-to-earth?
Or is he trying to justify the fact that he's a lazy loser?
What are you doing now?
I really wanted to avenge Tae Yang.
- What did you just say? - Also,
you can't use the word "loser" to describe anyone and everyone.
It should only be used to refer to someone like you...
who chooses money over love.
That little...
Hey, Tae Yang.
Did I catch you at a bad time?
No. I just got home. I'm writing a written explanation now.
I'm sorry I couldn't visit you at the hospital.
What's that written explanation for?
Mr Lee asked me to submit it.
I must say that you're at fault this time.
You know that, right?
Yes. I'm regretting what I did.
I've decided to stay strong...
and not get swayed by little things.
Of course. I'm fine now.
Yes. Let's talk again soon.
(I sincerely apologise. Also, I didn't mean it when Mr Lee...)
I'm coming in.
Did you finish writing it?
Do I really have to write it?
I told you. We have to draw a clear line between work and personal life.
Okay. All right.
Here you go.
Okay, let's see.
"Written Explanation".
"I missed work for 2 weeks without notice in January 2017..."
"and ended up negatively affecting the shop's business."
"Then I ran away like a coward..."
"and distressed Mr Lee Dong Jin."
"I sincerely apologise for what I have done."
"Also, I hurt Mr Lee's feelings by telling him to leave me alone..."
"when he found me, but I didn't actually mean it."
"My heart broke as I was uttering those words."
Why are you reading it aloud like that?
You wrote a love letter instead of a written explanation.
"Mr Lee always takes such good care of me and gives me so much love."
"I'll be sure to keep all of the promises I made..."
"so that I never hurt his feelings or break his heart again."
"In addition, I'll love..."
"and care for him more from now on."
You kill me.
This is the sweetest and most memorable written explanation.
Hold on. Something is missing.
You didn't sign it.
- Do I have to sign it? - Of course.
That kiss will serve as your signature.
Please don't be like this all the time.
We live with your parents, you know.
I know you like it. Don't be all coy.
Let me see.
You still have a mild fever.
I'm fine now.
You still can't overexert yourself, okay?
I have to head out now for a meeting. Get some rest.
- Why are you following me? - I want to see you out.
My gosh, I'm honoured.
Good. I really like this.
Young Eun, what brings you here?
You were home.
Thanks so much for dinner yesterday.
I brought the sweet potato cake you like. Try it.
You didn't have to bring anything.
Have a seat for a cup of tea.
Someone's watching the store for me, so I have to go back quickly.
By the way, are you feeling sick? You look pale.
My head is pounding a little.
You've been talking about your headache for a while.
You should go see a doctor.
It's nothing serious. Don't worry.
I should go lie down. Get back safely.
Thanks for this.
My gosh, Sun Nyeo. Are you all right?
I'm fine.
I was just dizzy for a few seconds. I'm really okay.
(Wolgyesu Tailor Shop)
Hey, Young Eun.
What brings you here at this hour?
I want to talk to you about Sun Nyeo.
- My wife? - I think she's ill.
She's ill? How?
I'm not too sure,
but she has been looking unwell for a while.
Take her to a doctor.
Yes. I mean, Wolgyesu...
cannot just be a branch office of Tonelli...
but an active cooperative partner.
Yes, I agree. Wolgyesu's production system...
and Tonelli's technical certification...
will be a great collaboration.
It'll certainly lessen the burden on our side.
It's much more efficient to have Wolgyesu manage production...
than to station the technical director...
from the Tonelli headquarters.
But how will the master tailor handle all those orders?
We have many skilled craftsmen in Korea.
So I'm thinking of establishing a co-operation...
by getting together those craftsmen.
You mean, when all the orders are received,
each master will be responsible for production?
You know what?
Can you provide Tonelli with videos of the production process?
That's exactly what I was thinking.
That will enable the company to collect a comprehensive database...
of Asian body types and preferences.
My company will love it.
And it'll be a true collaboration.
Gianni, I think we have a great chemistry.
I think so, too.
Mr Moravia met with Mr Lee.
Gianni met up with Dong Jin? For what?
I think they talked about opening a store.
That is crazy. People at Tonelli think so highly of the company.
Why would they want to open a store with him?
Are you saying they talked about opening their first store in Asia?
Are you sure?
Mr Lee has been discussing it with Tonelli...
since he used to work here at Meesa Apparel,
so they could trust him.
Then come up with a solution.
No. First, find out whether it's really true or not.
- There's no way it's true. - Yes, Sir.
And call an emergency executives' meeting when you're ready.
Yes, Sir.
It's never-ending. I'm seriously going crazy.
Come in.
Hey.
Why do you look so upset? What happened?
It's about Hyo Won.
What about her? Did she cause trouble again?
I stopped by to see your mum...
and gave her advice about Tae Yang because I was worried about her.
Then she dumped water on my face all of a sudden.
What? Has she lost her mind or what?
I shall teach that girl a lesson.
Calm down. If you call her now,
it'll just look like I caused a fight between you two.
What did you tell her...
to make her dump water on you?
I said that I broke up with Tae Yang not because he's poor...
but because he looked like a lazy loser compared to you.
She dumped water on me as soon as I said it.
Everything you said is true.
It was hard for me to bring it up to her.
I'm so upset.
That lame idiot from who knows where...
is ruining my family.
Hi, Mum. What's up?
You mean now?
All right. I see.
What does Mother say?
She told us to come home now.
What happened?
What's the urgent matter you want to discuss, Mum?
Min Hyo Sang and Choi Ji Yun...
can have a wedding this month...
as planned.
Mum!
And about Min Hyo Won and Kang Tae Yang,
we'll discuss later. That's all for today.
Where are you going?
I'll tell Mum everything.
Min Hyo Won, are you out of your mind?
Mum should know...
what kind of woman Choi Ji Yun is.
What kind of woman am I?
You left your poor boyfriend...
and chose a rich man to change your life.
- Hyo Won. - Am I wrong?
What are you thinking? Let's say...
Mum finds out the truth. Do you think she will reject only Ji Yun?
She will also reject Kang Tae Yang right away.
I suggest...
we make a gentleman's agreement.
- A gentleman's agreement? - A gentleman's agreement?
If you promise...
you won't sabotage our marriage,
we'll agree to your dating, too. Do you understand?
Deal.
I feel like we're fooled.
Let's wish them happiness.
That would bring us good luck.
All right.
By the way,
are you all right?
Will you be all right...
if Choi Ji Yun and you become family?
I wouldn't have dated you if it mattered to me.
Don't worry about it.
All right.
There's no problem, then.
Let's do tarot card readings.
Why would we do that?
I feel restless.
Let's do it just for fun. Can't we?
I have a CF shooting later today.
It won't take long.
Let's go in now.
Come in.
It's nice here, isn't it?
I think so.
I don't see anyone waiting.
- Hello. - How are you?
He looks familiar.
Welcome.
Have you ever tried it before?
- No. - You haven't.
First, it's important to open your minds...
so that I can read your fortune.
You have to believe in supernatural phenomena.
For example,
let me borrow your coffee.
- What happened? - It's amazing.
Well, something like this.
You can drink it.
It's water.
Let's start fortune telling now.
It's amazing.
Now, lady should...
think of your boyfriend...
and carefully pick three cards.
Do it carefully.
- You have to be careful. - Goodness.
You have to pick the right card.
Think about your lover sincerely and pick the right card.
I can feel the energy.
This is the last card.
This one?
This one.
You picked three cards.
Let's see. The first card.
- It's the lover. - The lover.
Well, it's the lover card,
but there's a problem.
If the card was put towards you,
it could have been a good card.
However, it's put against you.
This card means...
your relationship is good currently,
but in the near future...
you might not be together,
- as I interpret. - You're a total swindler.
- What do you mean? - It won't happen to us.
We can't break up.
Please calm down.
Let's see the second card.
What is it? It looks like a very bad one.
It's a tower card.
Even though it doesn't look good,
it would have been bad if it was put towards you.
However, it was put against you.
So, this card means...
in the near future,
a serious trouble can happen to you,
but if you overcome it together,
it would cement your relationship.
So, it's a very good card.
- Don't worry. - What a relief.
Let's see the last card.
Goodness. It's your card.
The sun. Is it a good card?
Right. It's a happy ending.
I'm not sure whether I should tell you this,
but I guess you would make a baby before you get married.
- That would never happen. - You're so sure of it.
All right. Let me explain it.
This card means a good result...
after a severe hardship.
From my experience,
a lot of soon-to-be married couples...
who made a baby before the wedding have picked this card.
If that's not the case,
you can pass an important exam,
or you can...
- unexpectedly make a big fortune. - That's amazing.
This card can mean those things.
He's excellent.
Tae Yang, I think you'll pass the exam.
- I hope so. - You're excellent.
Anyway, it means a great luck, right?
Something good will happen soon.
He's excellent.
My name is Hyun Woo.
I guess I've heard of him.
I'm home.
You're back.
- Mum, I'm home. - All right.
- Have you had dinner? - Not yet.
I'll set the table. Wash your hands and come.
Yun Shil will set the table. You can rest, Mum.
It looks delicious. Thank you.
How was your business?
I think something good will happen soon.
- You can count on it. - Are you sure?
I'm glad to hear that.
You're so amazing, Dong Jin.
I know I'm good at work,
but I guess it's thanks to "Na Yun Shil effect" this time.
That's nonsense.
It's because you're good at what you do.
Thank you for the dinner.
- What's wrong? - I bit a fishbone.
I'm sorry. Spit it out.
It's a small one. I'm fine.
You're not good at boning fish.
You tend to be careless sometimes.
What?
Can't you say thanks to someone who prepared your dinner?
Here you go.
I had a meeting for two hours...
in English with that Gianni guy.
I'm too tired to hold my spoon. You should feed me.
You give a patient too much work!
I want that one.
What's wrong?
Good boy.
It's been a long time since he smiled like that.
He looks so happy.
I heard that you came back.
- Do you feel better now? - Yes, I feel much better.
Are you all right? You don't look good.
Life is short.
Don't care about others.
Do what you want to do.
Everything is futile at the end.
What happened?
Nothing happened.
I told you that since you're like my own sister.
I didn't visit you in the hospital. Buy some fruit with that.
- I'm fine. - Receive it when I can give it.
I won't see you for long anyway.
She won't see me for long?
Is she going somewhere?
- Thank you. - I hope you enjoy it.
Look at this octopus and abalone.
I should eat this drumstick.
Are you the only one here with a mouth?
Can't you offer me first if you think it looks that great?
All you think about is yourself.
You prefer chicken breast over drumsticks.
Gosh, you fool. I only said that to give you drumsticks.
Why would I like chicken breast which is so dry?
Then you should have just told me. You can eat this drumstick.
Eat up.
Why are you crying now?
People are looking at us. What's the matter?
What's wrong?
Fine, I'll stop crying.
(Divorce Application)
This is the last gift I can give you.
Forget it.
Take it while the offer is on the table.
I don't know when I'll change my mind.
Honey.
You're hiding something from me, aren't you?
You have...
an illness, don't you?
What? Sorry?
I've been watching you for the last few days,
and I think...
that you...
You must be going through perimenopause. Aren't I right?
I heard that women become irritable...
and throw fits all the time before or during menopause.
I also heard that they get ill. That's what's happening to you.
That's what it is, right?
I guess so.
Why did you rip it up?
I can't divorce you because I don't want the universe to punish me...
for abandoning my old wife who's going through menopause.
What?
Also, what if I end up with a woman...
who's even meaner and scarier than you after divorcing you?
I can't divorce you because of that fear.
You have your first love, Young Eun.
Gosh, I loved her when I was young and immature.
Now, she's like a sister to me.
Why would I marry my sister? Who does that?
Are you sure?
Yes, I'm sure.
Will you not regret this?
Also,
trying to change your life at this age expecting a big fortune...
can completely ruin your life.
Eat this abalone.
My gosh, it's so plump.
Try it.
Eat up.
- Are you here to take a photo? - Yes.
For your identification card or passport?
For my funeral.
Your funeral?
Are you ready?
- Yes. - I'll take it now.
Sir.
It's also for my memorial service, so please make sure it looks good.
I guess you're very ill.
Yes.
I don't think I have that much time left, so I want to get ready.
They say that taking a photo...
for your funeral in advance can help you live longer.
So try to forget everything and just relax now.
I'll take it now. Please tilt your head a bit to the right.
Sir. By the way,
I want to have a big smile on for the photo.
That would be great. Please go ahead and smile.
Okay.
Goodbye, Sam Do.
I'm leaving this world before you.
All right. Here we go. In 1, 2, 3.
Please smile again. I'll take another shot.
Are you all right?
Do you want to do it some other time?
I'm so sorry, but could you please give me some time alone?
Sure, no problem.
I'm still young.
I can't believe I have to take a photo for my funeral at this age.
What kind of cursed fate is this?
The more I think about it, the more upset I get.
I cannot die like this!
Mum...
Mum, I miss you.
Would you like to come back another time?
No, I want to do it now.
All right. Here we go.
Goodbye, Sam Do!
I don't think Dong Jin and Yun Shil...
will be able to break up.
You can't say that, Mother.
You can't do this to me...
when I gave up my pride to beg the majority shareholders...
to bring him back to Meesa as CEO.
I'm grateful that you still think so highly of Dong Jin,
but I think the flame that you two had...
burned out long ago.
I would like it if you gave up.
Don't beg to make the impossible possible.
Those two haven't changed one bit.
Hello?
Isn't this Mr Lee Man Sool's residence?
It is. Who is this?
What about you?
Are you Ms Na by any chance?
Yes, this is Na Yun Shil.
Who are you?
I'm Dong Jin's ex-wife. What are you doing there?
I thought you were at a hospital.
I got discharged and came home today.
I thought your injury was serious. I guess that wasn't the case.
Anyway, let's meet. I'll go to that area now.
- For what? - For what?
Just do as I say. Why are you so full of questions?
I'll go to your place if you don't show up, so just come meet me.
I heard that you got injured, but you look totally fine.
You put on a show and acted like you were leaving to worry the elders.
Then you acted like a patient to win Dong Jin's heart.
You don't even know anything. Watch what you say.
I hate repeating myself.
Stop using his sympathy...
to cling to him.
Leave him right now.
I don't want to.
- What? - He doesn't want me to leave him.
I don't want to leave him, either.
That's why I can't leave him.
I'll make it easier for you to understand.
Dong Jin belongs in a big world with me.
He isn't someone who should rot in a tiny tailor shop with you.
Do you think that's what he wants?
He might want to leave the store...
to do much more in the wide world,
but he doesn't want to do any of it with you.
I think you're still recovering from the accident.
Dong Jin and I...
overcame a tough time together.
We promised never to break up again.
You're too shameless.
You have a husband in prison.
You might want to use Gi Pyo...
to force me to leave Dong Jin.
Give up.
As you already know,
Gi Pyo and I have no legal obligations to each other.
Just like you and Dong Jin.
This is the last time I hold back.
I hope we never meet again.
How dare she?
(Mr Pretty Eyes)
Hi, Dong Jin.
Where are you? You left without a word.
I came out to get something.
- What? - Dressing for my burns.
You could've asked me to go. It's cold outside.
Are you at the pharmacy?
Wait there. I'll come over.
(Pharmacy)
From now on, tell me if you need anything.
Don't come out alone at night.
I used to come out at night all the time.
You're being overprotective.
It's your fault that I'm like this.
You keep getting into trouble.
I get worried when you're out of sight.
Okay.
Did something happen?
You look a bit downcast.
I'm fine. What could've happened during such a short while?
This won't do. You need to top up your energy.
What do you mean?
- Enjoy. - Thanks.
You don't like chicken feet.
I didn't at first,
but it's spicy and chewy.
It's quite addictive.
Just like you.
What?
Are you saying I'm like chicken feet?
You lost track of my sense of humour already.
I'm not saying you're like chicken feet.
I'm saying I'm addicted to you.
I see.
Is that it? "I see"?
Don't you think...
you should say something like, "I'm addicted to you, too"?
Have some chicken feet.
It's good. Have some.
- It's good. - Is it?
- Yes. - Have some more.
Let me.
You first.
I ate too much.
I'm too full to walk.
Are you?
Get on my back.
- What? - If you can't walk,
I'll carry you home. Hop on.
Don't be silly.
I don't offer to carry just anyone.
Get on while you have a chance or you'll regret it.
No, I'd rather walk.
You said you can't walk.
I'll carry you.
No thanks.
Stop right there.
I don't know what I'll do if I catch you.
Don't come closer.
- Let's see what happens. - Don't come closer!
Who's that?
Isn't that Yun Shil?
Don't. Stay away from me.
I might do something.
She was in the neighbourhood...
and everyone ganged up and lied to me.
I should just...
Don't come closer.
- Leave me alone. - I'm coming for you.
No, no, don't. My leg!
Just a moment.
You still have a fever.
I feel fine now.
You need to be careful.
Let's dress your wound and sleep. I'll put you to bed.
He'll do what?
Put her to bed?
That means...
Yun Shil's living with him under his parents' roof.
Then was she pretending to be missing all the while?
How dare she!
I caught you at it.
You're worse than any criminal I've known.
You told me that Yun Shil was missing...
but she was here all along.
Don't you know any shame?
- You're mistaken. - Am I?
I saw you and followed you here.
Have you moved in with him?
- Let her go. - Stay out of it.
My son loves no one but you.
How could you shack up with...
another man while he's behind bars?
I said let go!
Did you just hit me?
I did not.
My parents are asleep, so please leave.
Go inside.
How could you do this to Gi Pyo?
After all he did for you!
Karma will get you!
Let her go this instant!
Yun Shil's part of my family.
Get your hand off her!
She's part of your family?
Are you saying you're stealing someone else's...
daughter-in-law?
You're talking nonsense.
She never was your daughter-in-law to begin with.
Your son must have gotten his terrible manners from you.
I don't believe this.
Get out of my house!
I'm so sorry for causing trouble.
I don't know what to say.
When we decided to let you back in,
my wife and I knew we'd have to go through this.
Don't apologise.
Dong Jin.
I'm not...
the kind of mum...
who wants to make her son marry into a rich family.
I thought highly of you,
and so...
I thought you should and would be happier...
to swim in larger waters which is why I pushed you.
I give up now.
Marriage is a big deal...
and I was afraid that rushing it would jinx us all.
I thought about it...
and I worried myself about it.
I think that fate...
brought you together...
the day Yun Shil came to work at the store.
Let's get you married.
- Mum. - Ms Choi.
Are you with me?
Without a doubt.
Let's get you both married before...
Gi Pyo gets out of prison.
Thank you, Ms Choi.
I know I'm not good enough,
but I will do my best to look after Dong Jin.
I'll also serve you as best I can.
I mean it.
Thank you, Mum and Dad.
I wish you the best.
That is...
all I want.
What did you do that for?
Don't embarrass me in front of the kids.
I adore you.
I like you an extra lot today.
Stop it.
You're so cheeky.
I think your dad has lost his mind.
I don't believe this.
What's wrong?
Come back to earth.
Can you pinch my cheek?
I think I'm dreaming.
There you go. Does it feel real now?
It's not a dream. It's all real.
I told you that Mum would give in.
Is it really okay to do this?
I'm just grateful to be by your side.
Is it okay for us to get married?
Of course it is. Now we can finally be happy.
Are you smiling or crying?
Both.
I'm so happy that I can't stop smiling...
or crying.
I'll make up for all the trouble...
for the rest of our lives.
Why can't I stop crying?
I'm not sad at all.
I'm really happy, but the tears won't stop.
My Shiny Eyes is a crybaby.
Thank you.
Isn't it cold?
- Honey. - Dad.
What are you doing here?
Why are you here, Da Jeong?
I came straight over from work to walk you both home.
You were awesome tonight.
Was I? Thanks a lot.
I feel so much better to have two lady fans.
Well done, dear husband.
I cooked some pork with fermented kimchi.
Let's go home and eat.
Okay. Let's go.
Kimchi stew with pork sounds great.
- It's freezing cold. - Let's hurry home.
- She'll pay. - Three people, please.
It's so cold.
Thank you.
Dad.
This is Dad's song.
It is. People must be asking the radio stations to play it.
Excuse me. Aren't you a singer?
Pardon?
Didn't you sing this song?
I think I saw you on "Music Stage".
You're right, that was me.
I can't believe I'm on a bus with a singer.
I guess it's my lucky day.
You're much more handsome in real life.
Thank you.
This song is my favourite...
and I sing it whenever I go to a karaoke bar.
Thank you, Sir.
Let's make the most of this meeting.
- Could you sing for us? - What?
Please, sing something for us.
Not in a moving bus.
Driver, would you mind?
It would be an honour.
Come on, then.
- Sing for us. - Stand up.
Sing your heart out, as if you're on "Music Stage".
Good luck, Dad.
- Applause! - Come on.
There's no need to be shy.
- Sing something. - Just one song.
Hello, everyone.
Hello, I'm Tae Pyung, the Gentleman of Trot.
Right now I spend...
most of my days singing at nightclubs.
I dream of...
becoming King of Singers.
I believe that all of you here...
did what you could today to get a step closer to your dream.
I cheer for you and support you...
as you strive towards your goals.
I'm hardly good enough, but I dedicate this song to you.
Round, round, round.
Your eyes are so round
I have fallen, fallen, fallen into them.
What should I do?
When you are tired.
Lean on my shoulders.
When you are sick.
Don't hesitate to give me a call
I love you, baby.
Do not say a word.
Just hold me tight.
To you, right now, immediately.
My brother goes.
Go, go, go.
Where are you going?
Tae Yang shoots a commercial today.
Is that today?
I might end up coming home early in the morning.
Don't wait up.
I'm coming, too.
Why would you want to come along?
I'm his manager. You can't do anything without me.
She's so nosy.
You look extra pretty today.
Wait.
Get closer.
Here you go.
The closer they get...
the better you can capture his face.
Right?
I guess.
Let's do another take.
Will you stop it?
Action.
You look extra pretty today.
Wait.
What is it this time?
Your face...
is way too stiff.
Is it?
Try to flirt with her.
- Flirt? - Yes.
"You look extra pretty today."
You look extra pretty today.
Okay. That's it.
Manager.
- Me? - Get out of here.
Why? Hey.
Kang star.
Flirt with the camera. Try to look sexy.
Okay? With your eyes.
- Flirt and sexy. - Let's check the lighting.
You're doing pretty well for a rookie.
Thanks.
Give me your number.
I'll teach you how to walk like a model.
People call you a walking glue stick.
You really do try to get any man you can.
What?
Tae Yang is taken, so hands off.
Work on your own career.
You're in no position to teach others.
Kang star.
Hyuk Jin! I quit. I'm going home.
I've had enough. I'm leaving.
Don't be like this.
Simmer down. Let it go.
- That brat ruined my mood. - Relax.
- Hyuk Jin, get my bag. - Help her relax.
- Let go! - Calm down.
Who is that kid anyway?
- A kid? Me? - No, no.
Calm down.
Why am I a kid?
Can you please relax?
What did I do to deserve this?
Hey, I...
Why did you get kicked out?
I don't know. I'm so annoyed.
Did you try to fix his makeup like last time?
No, I did not.
I hope that witch won't get Tae Yang's number.
You might want to use Gi Pyo...
to force me to leave Dong Jin.
Give up.
As you already know,
Gi Pyo and I have no legal obligations to each other.
Just like you and Dong Jin.
How dare she lecture me?
She should know her place.
There you go.
Thank you.
You took your medicine...
and changed the dressing.
You can sleep now. Lie down.
- I will once you leave. - What?
I will sleep here.
That's a nonsense.
Why do you overreact? I just want to care a patient.
What are you imagining?
Stop it.
I can sleep alone. You can go to your room.
You used to sleep in my arms when you were in the hospital.
Why do you play innocence now?
It was because you said you had a backache.
Stop teasing me.
All right. I'll stay here until you fall asleep.
Lie down.
Here.
Why do you play innocence when you're going to lie down anyway?
Your parents might hear that.
All right. So go to sleep.
Thank you for not giving me up...
and waiting for me, Dong Jin.
I thank you for coming back to me.
The tailor shop is closed tomorrow.
Let's visit your father.
- To Dad? - Sure.
We should tell him that we received the consent for marriage.
I'm worried he might not like the son-in-law to be.
He would like you.
If he sees you, he would fall in love with you...
at first sight.
I agree with you on that.
All right.
Do you think I have to dress up?
- Stop it. - I wanted to pinch you.
Hello?
I must have woke you up. I'm sorry.
It's all right.
What made you call me in the morning?
I suspect...
you got a call from a model asking you out?
It's nothing like that.
What happened?
The result of preliminary exam for teacher certification is out.
- What does it say? - I passed.
Congratulations, Tae Yang!
You took so much trouble so far.
You brought me good luck.
That's true.
When do you start working?
I just passed the preliminary exam.
I still have secondary and tertiary tests to go.
I see. You passed the hardest exam.
You will easily pass the secondary and tertiary tests.
I put Korean hard Taffy on the school gate and prayed.
I think it worked.
Did you put Taffy on the school gate and pray?
I sure did. I prayed so earnestly.
I assist you so well, don't I?
(Board President Min Hyo Joo)
What made you call me?
- A serious thing happened. - A serious thing?
They are going to get married.
- Who are going to get married? - Don't you know?
My daughter-in-law and the CEO of the tailor shop, of course.
What did you say?
(Mum)
Hello, Mum.
Yes, I came to see Father with Yun Shil.
Do you have a temperature?
No, I'm fine.
She says she's fine, Mum. All right.
(Na Kyung Ho, father of Na Yun Shil)
Father, my name is Lee Dong Jin.
I'd like to marry Yun Shil.
I came here for your consent.
I'm sure you like your son-in-law to be very much, Dad.
I still can't believe...
that I will be his wife.
Neither can I, Father.
I will take the responsibility for Yun Shil from now on.
Don't worry anything.
Please see through us, Father.
What brought you here?
You look like you don't know anything.
Well,
you can't do anything even if you know.
I don't know what you're talking about.
My husband and your wife...
are going to get married.
What did you say?
Dong Jin's parents allowed their marriage,
and they will get married soon.
Who said they can get married?
Darn it!
What are you going to wish?
You're not supposed to say what your wish is.
- What is your wish? - I'll keep it a secret, too.
(I want to live happily ever after with Mr Pretty Eyes. Na Yun Shil)
(I want to live happily ever after with Ms Shiny Eyes. Lee Dong Jin)
(I want to live happily ever after. Na Yun Shil, Lee Dong Jin)
(The Gentlemen of Wolgyesu Tailor Shop)
Stop screwing around...
and come back to Gi Pyo when I'm saying it nicely.
I'm like a dead man if I'm not with you.
Wake up and come back to me.
What are all these pictures and letters? Tell me now!
Why did you come here so late? Didn't you feel strange?
I have a bad feeling about this.
A rumour? What kind of a rumour?
You have to help me and Mother to be close.
I tried to break them up when they like each other like that.
- Are you that happy? - It's like I have a real family.
I feel secure and happy.