(The following content may not be suitable for viewers under 15.)
(Viewer discretion is advised.)
(Episode 43)
It's time to wake up, honey.
- I don't want to wake up. - You don't want?
Then shall we just go back to sleep?
Shall we?
Okay.
What do you think? Do you like our new room?
Yes. I love it.
I love the room...
and my husband.
Your becoming more aggressive in expressing your affection now.
You're doing well, Ms Shiny Eyes.
- I learned it from Mr Pretty Eyes. - Right?
That hurts!
This model is popular among newly married couples.
What do you two think after lying on it?
I like it. How about you?
If the bride likes it, we should get it indeed.
- We'll take this. - Then please follow me...
so I can help you fill out an order sheet.
Okay.
Here.
Now that we've ordered the bed...
let's go look at wedding rings next.
We don't need wedding rings.
This is more than enough for me.
That's our couple ring. A wedding ring should be a diamond.
I don't need a diamond ring.
You'll regret it some day.
You're more valuable to me than a diamond.
We don't need to waste money, okay?
Why are you looking at me like that?
If you say something that sweet,
how can I not hug you like this?
- People are looking at us. - It's okay. Stay still.
Thank you for saying that I'm more valuable than a jewel.
Now I see why men say that there's no one like their wife.
Then we'll skip the ring.
Now let's go to a travel agency.
Let's go to a hot spring...
with your parents for our honeymoon.
We're not living in the 1970s.
Who goes to a hot spring on their honeymoon?
Would it be weird?
Then how about Jeju Island or Gangwon Province?
I wonder if Ms Choi and Mr Lee would be happy.
The bride should go where she wants to go.
A honeymoon is a once-in-a-lifetime chance.
I can go anywhere if it's with you.
I think Ms Shiny Eyes is in big trouble.
You're so fascinated by me that you've lost your senses.
Your world is filled with me.
Why does that mean I'm in trouble?
I know your world is filled with me, too.
Of course.
Then what about our wedding shoot?
We did that already. Why do it again?
If you say no to everything everyone does,
then what on earth do we have left to prepare?
We have each other...
and we have family members who give us their blessings.
What more can we ask for?
I just want a quiet and simple wedding.
You're so sweet and kind.
What's wrong?
It's nothing.
I was just a bit startled because I stumbled.
Are you okay? Are you hurt?
No, I'm okay. Let's go.
- Did you enjoy your honeymoon? - Yes.
Madam Ko.
We've returned safely from our honeymoon, Mother.
Welcome back. Did you enjoy the trip?
Yes, Mother.
Min Hyo Won.
Stop right there.
Your brother and sister-in-law have returned from their trip.
You're not going to greet them?
Hello.
It's been awhile.
I've missed you.
Mother, we'll go and change clothes and come make our deep bows.
I don't need your deep bows.
Ji Yun said it's a custom to bow deeply...
to the elders in the family...
to show that we've become adults after getting married.
We'll be right back.
Mum,
I want to move out.
- What are you talking about? - I can't stand living under...
the same roof as pooper.
How dare you call your sister-in-law pooper?
You two got along fine until not long ago.
Why do you hate her so much all of a sudden?
The fact that she is two-faced...
gets on my nerves.
You're already starting to act like a wicked sister-in-law.
That's not right!
What's with the hanbok?
Mum, please receive our bows.
Are you okay?
You should have been more careful.
Your clumsier than you look.
Honey.
What's wrong? You look upset.
Hyo Sang and Ji Yun came back from their honeymoon.
How can I live in the same house with them?
I feel hopeless.
I told Mum that I want to leave the house, but she wouldn't let me.
They are your family now. Don't focus on the negative effect.
Isn't he the model from the cosmetics commercial?
You're right.
- That's him. - Goodness.
You look better in real.
- You look prettier today. - You look prettier today, you said.
- Exceptionally! - Exceptionally!
- Pretty! - Pretty!
Can I take a picture with you?
I can take the picture for you.
- Excuse me. - I want to take the picture, too.
- Hyo Won. - In 1, 2, 3!
- Come quickly! - I want to take, too.
- Honey! - I haven't given my autograph.
- Honey! - Give me your autograph.
- Exceptionally pretty! - Exceptionally pretty!
- Honey! - Exceptionally pretty!
- Exceptionally pretty! - Honey!
- Exceptionally pretty! - Exceptionally pretty!
- He looks so happy. - Exceptionally pretty.
- Exceptionally pretty. - Hyo Won!
- Where are you going? - Wait.
- Hyo Won, wait. - Where are you going?
- Don't go! - Where are you going?
Hyo Won!
- It's a misunderstanding. - Stay here.
- Hyo Won. - Give me your autograph.
I didn't know that Tae Yang is such kind of person.
He was so happy to see all those high school girls.
Does it mean that he likes young girls or what?
- How are you? - Hello.
I heard that you went to see the furniture. How was it?
As we don't need much,
we just bought a bed and a closet.
It's not that we don't need much, but our room is so small.
As my parents recommended, it might be a good idea...
if we live just the two of us for 1 or 2 years.
I want to live with them.
I am their son and I want to leave my parents.
But their daughter-in-law, Yun Shil wants to live with them.
Such a daughter-in-law is not common nowadays, right?
Are you bragging that Yun Shil is a devoted daughter-in-law?
You're right. He's such a dullard even before he gets married.
I'm just telling you the truth.
I need to wash my hands.
Dong Jin, you got a phone call.
Who is it?
- Why are you calling me? - I'm near the tailor shop.
Shall I go in or will you come out?
I'm going out. Wait.
I'll be out for a minute.
I need to be out for a minute. I'll be back soon.
All right.
Excuse me.
Is Ms Na Yun Shil here?
I am Na Yun Shil.
Here's a registered mail for you.
A registered mail?
(To Na Yun Shil, Wolgyesu Tailor Shop)
(From Hong Gi Pyo, Cheongsol Penitentiary)
(From Hong Gi Pyo to Na Yun Shil)
I'm not sure whether you might remember the picture inside.
It's the first one we took together when you graduated high school.
(2008 Hwa Moon High School Graduation Ceremony)
Yun Shil.
Why are you here? I don't have any money.
I came here today to celebrate your graduation.
This is for you.
(Congratulations on Your Graduation)
You do have temper.
We need to take a picture on a graduation day.
- Jeong Won. - Yes.
Take our picture.
Photos stay with you at the end. Let's take just one picture.
Why do I have to take a picture with you?
If you don't want to take with me, take it alone. Is it okay?
- I don't want to. - Wait.
Why do you play so hard to take a picture?
You won't regret later if you take a graduation picture.
You don't understand.
If you don't want to make a scene, take just one picture.
Look at the camera and smile, okay?
All right. She's ready.
I'm not going to be in the picture.
- Take a good picture. - All right.
Can't you count down?
It's been a long time since we knew each other.
Whenever you were in a trouble,
I protected you at the risk of my life.
Still you want to leave me and marry another man.
You shouldn't do this to me when I'm in a prison and can't do anything.
I beg you for the first and last time.
I'm a dead man without you.
Please wake up and come back to me.
I don't want to meet you like this any more.
I didn't ask you to see me for a personal matter.
Everyone's keeping it a secret as it might do harm to the company.
According to the finance department,
the company cannot hold out with the current funding position.
If the bank reduces the credit line,
it can be a great hit to the company.
Dad devoted his life to make Meesa Apparel.
I can't let this company collapse.
We have set up a robust system.
It won't fall apart so easily.
As you know, Hyo Sang committed...
a crime to take over the control of the company.
We never know what kind of trouble he would make.
Although Hyo Sang is immature and greedy,
he's not such a bad person.
Also, even if I come forward now,
he wouldn't yield full control of the company.
It would make the matters worse.
I've met all the major shareholders.
Most of them are willing to help only if you come forward.
The only executive who can settle down the company...
is you.
If you can't come back because of me,
you can make your decision without thinking about me.
I'm asking you formally...
as the eldest daughter of Meesa Apparel.
Are you serious?
I'm serious.
You can trust me.
(Will)
I should tell Sam Do everything.
I should give him some time to prepare, too.
My head aches.
Goodness. That surprised me.
Hello?
Hello. I'm calling from the hospital.
Am I talking to Bok Sun Nyeo?
Yes, this is she speaking.
Your reservation date for your test result has passed.
I'm calling you since you haven't visited yet.
Do I...
have a cancer?
I'm in the late stage, right?
I can't inform your test result on the phone.
When do you want to make a reservation?
Well, I'm not mentally ready.
I'll call you again when I'm ready.
Considering that the hospital is calling me like this,
I must have a serious disease.
(Oh Young Eun Bakery)
She didn't open again.
Is she in trouble or what? I can't even get a hold of her.
I'm getting worried.
Honey, I'm home.
You're lying down again.
I feel dizzy and sick.
You're acting peculiar.
I've never seen such a serious case of menopause.
You're telling me.
Why don't you go and see a doctor?
Do you want me to go with you?
No.
What do you mean? I'll go with you tomorrow morning.
What? Why are you getting up?
You should eat dinner.
I can just eat some noodle with leftover rice.
Don't worry. Lie down.
How will I be able to die...
leaving that man alone?
Yes?
I wonder who it is.
Surprise, surprise, surprise.
Hyo Won.
What do you think?
What's with this outfit?
People have always said I look younger than my age.
If I go out like this, people would think...
- I'm in high school, wouldn't they? - Pardon?
I wanted to feel like a high school student for a change.
Don't I look prettier and younger than those girls earlier?
So you're telling me you wore a uniform because you were jealous?
That's right.
I'm just as pretty and young as them.
I wanted to prove that to you,
so I dug out my old uniform in my closet.
No one can stop you.
You must only look at me from now on.
Don't you dare look at other girls.
Fix your eyes on me.
You're so greedy.
I wonder what all that greed is for?
You.
It's me, Man Sool.
Did you receive the document...
from Wolgyesu Tailor Shop?
That's right.
I've heard Dong Jin's plan...
and I've agreed to it. So read through it carefully.
It's time for tailors to start a new method of work. Don't you think so?
It's not because it's my son's idea.
I believe it will open new doors to tailors.
Thanks.
Let's meet soon.
My husband, Man Sool,
looks excited for a change.
Our Dong Jin is planning...
something that no one else has thought up of before.
I'm proud of him not just because he's my son.
Dong Jin is indeed a man of great capacity.
What is this man doing?
What are you doing with your cellphone so close to your face?
My eyes are bleary. It must be because I'm tried.
- Should I help you? - It's okay.
Go to the eye clinic tomorrow.
You should have your eyesight tested again and get new glasses.
Otherwise, you'll ruin your eyes.
All right. I was going to go anyway.
I'm home.
Welcome back.
- Did you have dinner? - Yes, I ate out.
I was in the middle of calling my fellow tailors.
Regarding your plan,
I think some are excited and some are worried.
If I explain to them in detail in person,
I'm sure they'll feel more relaxed.
By the way, where's Yun Shil?
Weren't you two at the tailor shop together?
I thought she had come home first because she wasn't at the shop.
She must have had some business to take care of.
- Go get some rest. - Okay.
It's me, Yun Shil. I'm coming in.
What brings her here on her own?
What brings...
our precious Yun Shil all the way to this humble place?
What is this? You should eat a proper meal.
Did you come to make me angry?
Why do you think I can't eat properly?
So go back to Anseong...
and live in comfort.
Why? Is it because you want to send me away...
and get married to Dong Jin?
Stop screwing around and come back to Gi Pyo...
when I'm saying it nicely.
The man I love is Dong Jin, not Gi Pyo.
Who do you think you're talking about love to?
I tried...
really hard to like Gi Pyo.
He can be tough but he's a good person.
I thought I could like him eventually...
if I try hard and live together.
I thought we'd be able to live together somehow.
But no matter how hard I tried, it didn't work.
I wanted to run away from him several times a day...
because I was scared of him.
How dare you talk like that after all that he's done for you?
You ungrateful brat!
I'm not asking you to understand me.
I'm telling you my feelings...
so that you can help Gi Pyo...
forget about a girl like me...
and meet a better person and live happily.
That's what I'd like to say.
To be honest, I have no intention of...
seeing a girl like you with no family...
and who has been with another man as Gi Pyo's wife.
But Gi Pyo says he can't live without you. What should I do?
In order for Gi Pyo to change his mind, go back to Anseong.
I'll get going now.
You're telling me to take this piece of meat and some fruits...
and leave for good?
Are you looking down on us?
Good bye. Take care.
Hey, stop there. I'm telling you to stop!
Darn it.
Yun Shil.
Where have you been? You didn't even answer your phone.
Did it hurt you that much?
Are you upset because I left after answering my ex-wife's call?
You went through much more...
but still understood me and comforted me.
How could I get upset over a small thing like that?
I got worried not knowing your thoughts.
Hyo Joo was here...
to ask for help because Meesa Apparel is having trouble.
You didn't have to explain.
If I were you, I would want to know why she was here.
That's why I'm telling you.
I have something to tell you, too.
I received a letter from Gi Pyo.
Do you mind if I ask you what it was about?
The same as usual.
So I'm on my way back from meeting Gi Pyo's mother.
What were you thinking by going there alone?
I went to ask...
or even beg to end things,
but it didn't go well.
It's okay since you're back safely.
Let's promise to continue being honest...
without hiding anything as a married couple. Okay?
Mum, Dad. Come out.
Da Jeong, what is it?
There's a video...
of you singing on the bus posted on the Internet.
You won't believe how many viewers have watched it.
Look here.
Oh, my goodness.
A passenger on the bus must have recorded a video.
People are praising about how heartwarming this video is.
You've become the hero in a moving story.
This is embarrassing.
I'm really proud of you, Dad.
I'm proud of you, too, honey.
This is so embarrassing.
Hello? This is the gentleman of trot, Tae Pyung.
A radio show?
They want you to appear on a radio show?
- Amazing! - Yes.
Hello?
Yes, this is Tae Pyung's manager speaking.
You'd like him to appear...
as a guest singer at the Ice Flower Festival?
- Oh, my goodness. - Okay.
I'll call you right back after discussing things with my manager.
Yes, thank you.
Yes, please text us about the schedule first.
Yes. Okay.
You're getting a lot of calls. It looks like things will go well.
I guess.
Then let's cheer up to get this going.
Should we?
Gentleman of trot, Tae Pyung.
My new song, "My Brother Goes".
Please let it be a big hit!
The magical cheer in 1, 2, 3.
- Let's go! - Let's go!
- Let's go! - Let's go.
You look exceptionally pretty today.
Is that really Tae Yang?
He looks so awesome.
Hey, I was watching.
- Mum, will you be like this? - What?
I've told you numerous times that I can't let Hyo Won and...
Tae Yang get married, not even over my dead body.
But if you keep adoring Tae Yang like that,
will she listen to me?
Why do you disapprove of Tae Yang...
I mean, Kang Tae Yang so much?
Mum, after you find out what kind of a guy he is,
you will be more than shocked.
- Hey. - We're back.
Hey, what's with your outfit?
I dressed up for Tae Yang.
Hey, Tae Yang.
You've gone so far that you have gone insane.
I hate them.
You. You have an odd taste.
Are you...
disabled somewhere?
No. I didn't ask her to dress like this.
My goodness. Unbelievable.
Get changed right away!
Fine.
You're home, Hyo Won.
You're here.
Yes.
Dinner is ready, Mother.
Oh, okay.
Grab a bite before you go.
I just had tteokbokki and gimbap. I'm fine, Mother.
Tteokbokki and gimbap are not real food.
Have a meal with a bowl of soup.
Come on.
Go.
What was that? What's with her?
I heard your TV advertisement is receiving a lot of attention.
It's not a lot, but people did notice.
Ta-da.
Why are you wearing hanbok?
I dressed up...
for Tae Yang.
Did you ask Hyo Won to wear hanbok?
No, I didn't.
Do I look prettier in hanbok,
or does pooper look better?
You look much prettier.
I can hear you.
What a scene.
I lost my appetite.
I like this mood.
You're home.
Did you have fun on your honeymoon?
I did.
You should have had fun.
You won't be laughing again for a while.
What are you saying?
You should eat, Hyo Joo.
I don't want to break up this cheerful mood.
Have a great one.
- I don't like her. - Me, too.
She's just sour that things aren't going well with Dong Jin.
Anyway, is Dong Jin still dating...
your old friend?
Yes. They set a date for a wedding.
- A wedding? - A wedding?
Ms Shiny Eyes, come and take a walk with me.
Grab your coat and I'll see you at the door.
A walk at this hour?
This is great. I forgot to give it to him before.
(Let's be pretty and shiny for all of our life.)
- Why are you laughing? - What's with that flower pot?
Instead of a bouquet, I thought we could...
grow this plant together.
Was that funny?
It wasn't funny,
but I've never seen anyone give a flower pot during a proposal.
I wanted to make it special.
I thought I'd change it around.
But we already have a date. Why are you proposing now?
That's exactly why. You won't let me throw you a huge wedding...
or let us live in a huge house.
I wanted to at least give you a proposal.
You don't even know anything. On top of that, you laughed.
This is a mess.
I'm sorry. I laughed because you looked cute with a flower pot.
Was I cute?
Okay. It's too cold. Let's get in the car.
You can't laugh now.
subtitles ripped and synced by riri13
This is my proposal gift.
I heard you gave your scissors to Ms Geum.
I wanted to give it to you. It's a bit belated.
I'm giving you this...
to let you remember that your dream was to become...
the best tailor in the country, so you have to achieve your dream.
Thank you.
I will try very hard to become just that.
And this is my gift to you.
Come to think about it, I forgot to make a tie with the suit.
I made that myself think it would look great on you.
Do you like it?
It's great.
When a woman gives a man a tie as a gift,
that means she wants to have him.
Are you saying that Dong Jin is now Yun Shil's?
It's a warning for you...
to never take your eyes off of me.
Wow, if that's the case, I'll take that warning to my heart.
Thank you, Dong Jin. For being mine.
Those were my words.
My goodness. You're the best.
- Wait. - What?
I'm not sure which one is the flower and which is you.
- Come on. - Hold it up again.
You're making fun of me.
Yun Shil.
Yun Shil, say something.
- Stop it. Come on. - Yun Shil.
Yun Shil.
You two are so loving, yet I tried to split you up.
I'm so sorry.
Yun Shil, may I see you for a minute?
What's this, Ms Choi?
It'll take a fortune to prepare for a wedding.
Please take it.
I can't, Ms Choi.
You haven't married Dong Jin yet,
so think of this as a gift from your own mother.
Ms Choi...
Once you two get married,
I may be an in-law, but I'm still your mother.
You can stop calling me Ms Choi.
Thank you. Thank you so much.
Sure.
What are you doing out in the cold?
It's not much, but use it for your wedding.
Mr Lee.
I've got enough money.
I also got some from Ms Choi, too.
It's from your father, so take it.
How many more times...
could I give any pocket money to you?
Don't say that.
I'm saying...
you two will have to give pocket money...
to us from now on and longer.
So don't worry about it and use it for your wedding.
Oh, that's what you meant.
Thank you.
I'll do my best.
I'll be good to you both and I'll work hard...
to give a lot of pocket money to you two.
Of course. I look forward to it.
- You should rest. - Thank you.
- Goodnight. - Sure.
My goodness!
What are you doing?
- I'm sorry, did I surprise you? - What are you doing?
I was watching you sleep.
How can you be...
so sexy and cool even when you sleep?
You're an odd one.
Didn't you know that before?
I did, but today,
you looked even sexier and cooler.
Stop saying nonsense and let's sleep. I'm sleepy.
Hey, Honey.
About Young Eun.
She closed down her store for a few days. Has she gone somewhere?
How would I know?
- Don't you really know? - No.
Her phone is even turned off. I wonder what's going on.
I have to go to work tomorrow.
Let's just go to sleep.
I'm sorry.
Aren't you going to sleep?
I can't seem to sleep. You can sleep first.
She is overly suspicious these days.
What's going on?
He's such a carefree soul.
How could I tell him that I'm dying?
I really can't do this.
Why are you drinking soju without any food?
Did you fight with Sam Do?
- No, I'm just depressed. - Sun Nyeo.
I asked him man-to-man.
There is nothing going on between him and that women from the bakery.
He's right.
Sam Do isn't the type to be in an affair.
Of course.
He may sound cold, but he only loves you.
I can guarantee that.
I wish he'd have an affair.
- What are you saying? - What are you saying?
Anyway.
I'm so glad you two got together.
When you become a famous singer,
don't ever disregard Dong Sook.
You should be good to him, too.
I'm not concerned about anything else,
but I'm sorry about the time I gave you a hard time...
when you first came to get the money to fix your guitar.
I should have made your favourite stir-fried chicken more often, too.
Those are both on my mind.
Why do you bring up such an old story?
He's right. It's as if you are leaving to somewhere far.
What's wrong?
Just because.
I just thought of this and that...
as I grabbed a drink.
Goodnight.
It's as if she is about to die any day soon.
Wait, could she be diagnosed with a terminal illness?
No way.
No, something is off.
She would never drink just soju.
- Who is it? - It's me, Mother.
Oh, okay.
Come in.
Tae Yang is leaving.
- Already? - It's over 11pm already.
Oh, right.
Can you play just one round with me before you leave?
Do you know how to play cards?
I've seen my grandmother play.
I can play a bit.
That's great. Let's play just one round.
I can't seem to fall asleep.
My gosh. You're embarrassing.
What's there to be embarrassed...
between Tae Yang and I?
Tae Yang, am I embarrassing you?
No, never.
That's good.
- Let's play one round, then. - Okay.
- Let's do it. - Okay, let's get started.
Come here.
Is that rice for breakfast?
Yes.
You're always a huge help.
My goodness.
What is this?
You have to help...
me and Mother to be close.
Please give me information about her, too.
Do you understand what I mean?
Are you still doing something?
Let's go to sleep. I'm tired.
No, I'm done.
- Great job today. - Sure.
- Goodnight. - Goodnight.
She really is foxy.
She's very manipulative.
Great.
Don't get the card.
All right.
Okay, now.
You don't have enough cards,
and I'm on round three.
And this card means I get another double score.
Okay. I have the birds and blue flags.
I made a fortune!
This is great.
Tae Yang doesn't have any money. Stop it, Mum.
Why would I stop?
I'm on a roll.
Mother.
May I come in?
What? Well...
Give me a second. Hide it.
What are you all doing here?
What?
We were just...
chatting. What is it?
Do you have something to say?
I came to say goodnight.
Oh, I see.
Goodnight to you, too. Have a sweet dream.
Tae Yang. Aren't you going home?
Why do you care...
if he stays or goes?
Yes, exactly.
Tae Yang and I still have matters to discuss.
Don't worry about us...
and go sleep.
Goodnight.
- My gosh. - Hey.
Yes, Lawyer.
Hong Gi Pyo got bailed out.
He'll be released tomorrow.
Is this a hard fact?
I've met all the major shareholders.
Most of them are willing to help only if you come forward.
The only executive who can settle down the company...
is you.
If you can't come back because of me,
you can make your decision without thinking about me.
I'm asking you formally...
as the eldest daughter of Meesa Apparel.
Are you serious?
I am. You can trust me.
(From Hong Gi Pyo to Na Yun Shil)
(Penitentiary)
Bow.
- Hello, Sir. - Hello, Sir.
Thanks for coming to pick me up.
Congratulations.
You didn't have to make the trip. Thanks.
I'm not here for that.
I hope you don't make me regret...
paying to bail you out.
We want the same thing.
I don't have to say what, do I?
You don't.
I can't wait to get started. I have to go.
- Let's go. - Yes, Sir.
As you can see, your wife seems to have...
shacked up with her boss.
They love each other so much. They kiss and hug in public...
What's wrong with you?
How dare you talk about her like that?
Sorry, Boss.
You know that he tends to shoot off his mouth.
Don't take it to heart. Have some tofu.
Honey. Wife, can I come in?
Yes, come in.
- Did you sleep well? - Of course.
Did you sleep well?
You don't look like you slept well.
You didn't sleep a wink without me.
I did sleep well.
This won't do. I'll put you to bed from now on.
What if someone overhears?
Who cares? We'll be married soon.
You're so childish. Let's go.
I have to help Mother cook breakfast.
"Mother"?
She told me to call her that from now on.
Do you like it that much?
Of course I do. It feels like I finally have a family of my own.
I feel so happy.
What should I wear to work today?
Should I wear this?
What's this box?
I haven't seen this before?
Did she go shopping again? Let's see.
(Will)
What's this?
A will?
"First, on my last moment, Bae Sam Do should hold my hands..."
"and kiss on my forehead."
"At the same time, he should whisper in my ear that he loves me."
"After I die,"
"cremate me and leave my urn in Youngsung Remembrance Hall."
What is she up to?
Sun Nyeo, where are you?
Sun Nyeo.
What are you doing?
I just went to get tofu and beansprouts.
What's this?
How did you find that?
Give it back.
Fess up.
What are all these pictures and letters? Tell me now!
Tell me right now!
What happened now, Sam Do?
Sun Nyeo, what's wrong?
I'm...
dying.
What?
- You're dying? - What?
I went to see a doctor because I'd been having...
bad headaches and dizzy spells.
And?
He said it could be a brain tumour so I had some tests done.
What?
Did you get the results back?
What did they say?
Is it really a tumour?
The doctor said he has to tell me in person.
He told me to come by...
but I was too scared to.
I'm scared, Sam Do.
I don't want to die.
Stop saying such silly things. Who said you're going to die?
I've been thinking about it for a few days.
You'll help anyone and everyone get a loan...
and you're so clueless.
I can't bear the idea of leaving you alone.
I can't die like this.
Poor Sun Nyeo.
Medicine has advanced in leaps and bounds.
Let's go and talk to the doctor first.
- Yes, let's go. - Come with me.
No.
- I won't go. - Why not?
I'm too scared.
Even if you are, we need to see the doctor...
and discuss what kind of treatments are available.
I can't go.
I won't go.
I think she's having a headache.
Poor Sun Nyeo.
I know what I have.
It's terminal.
There's no hope.
Don't say that. You aren't a doctor!
He's right. I know you're scared, but let's go and see the doctor.
Let's hear what he has to say.
If the doctor confirms my suspicions...
I don't think I can last another day.
I can't go to the hospital.
Stop being so silly. You have to come with me.
I don't want to!
Get up. I won't let you die.
Tae Pyung, help me.
Yes, of course.
- Get up. We're going. - I'm not going!
- Come along. - Come with us.
I don't want to go.
We'll take her straight there.
Bring our coats and follow right away.
- Okay. - I said I'm not going!
Oh dear.
I don't want to go!
What took you so long? The results came out long ago.
Weren't you under a lot of stress?
I was, because of the terrible headaches.
The thought of hearing the results...
scared me too much.
We are...
ready to hear the news.
Tell us, Doctor.
How much longer...
will I live?
What do you mean?
I have cancer.
You don't.
After hearing your symptoms, I ran a medical checkup...
starting from blood panel to scans.
You don't have a tumor or brain haemorrhage.
- She doesn't? - I don't?
No, you don't.
Then why did I have all those headaches?
I thought my head was going to split in two.
The tests results show that you have a pressure headache...
caused by a leak of cerebrospinal fluid.
A pressure headache because of a leak?
What kind of illness is that?
Is that a threat to her life?
Not at all. You have nothing to worry about.
Let me explain exactly what you have.
There's water inside our head that protects our brain.
There's a hole somewhere in your body...
and that water is leaking.
A shortage of that water can cause excruciating headaches...
and nausea, all of which you suffered from.
Can you cure her with surgery?
We'll find a leak with a special scan.
Plugging that should solve the problem.
Doctor.
So I won't die?
What's taking them so long?
I have a bad feeling about this.
We should have gone in with them.
Maybe we should have.
Perhaps we should have told your parents before we left.
It's not too late to tell them once we're sure.
- Did you get the results? - Yes.
She has to get admitted right away.
Oh no...
I feel so sorry for you.
How could this be?
Don't drag it out. Tell them the truth.
I slightly...
overreacted.
- I don't have cancer. - What?
You don't?
Then why do they want to admit you?
They want her admitted...
to get a procedure done.
- A procedure? - A procedure?
You are going to shorten...
my life. Seriously.
I'm going to lose my mind.
I'm sorry, Sam Do.
Seriously.
Thank goodness.
Since you're all in the industry,
I'm sure you've heard of Tonelli of Italy.
Wolgyesu Tailor Shop...
will open Tonelli's first flagship store in Asia...
as their partner.
Good job.
We will not stop at being a branch for them.
We will create Wolgyesu-Tonelli,
a new brand,
which creates tailor-made suits.
Of course, in order to maintain consistency within the brand,
we will provide a joint training with Tonelli.
We'll establish a system in which a tailor who passes the training...
will become a master...
and will be able to participate in the manufacture process.
This is the union that I am trying to explain.
All of you...
have worked with my father,
Lee Man Sool,
and he personally recommended you.
So I'm sure you'll have plenty of influence.
Naturally.
Going back to business,
we will purchase all fabrics and materials...
to maintain consistent quality and market strength.
The database, which will include all patterns,
will be shared digitally.
Of course, the database...
will be shared with Tonelli as well.
Thus, we will be able to cooperate...
as partners with Tonelli,
the best in the world.
I'm touched.
People mocked us, calling us useless tailors.
I'm about to tear up.
Must we close the shops we currently run?
No. If you go through the training and are accepted...
as a master, as I mentioned,
you'll be given a license to use the Wolgyesu-Tonelli name.
After creating the suit at your shop.
You may mark it, using that license.
Then as a member,
we get training, participate in the manufacturing process...
and gain a joint brand label as well.
That's right. The reason for this unity is to raise...
profit and class.
Mr Lee, you have a very impressive son.
Thanks.
If we don't want banks to retrieve our loans,
we must announce the collaboration with Tonelli.
How many times must I tell you that?
We tried various routes to request a meeting with Mr Gianni,
but he said...
meeting Meesa Apparel is not in his agenda, and refused.
Even if we cannot work together with them,
we can't let them partner up with Wolgyesu.
So, get the planning team to figure out...
- what we need to do to stop it! - Yes, Sir.
If we can't eat it,
we make sure no one else does!
- That's my business rule! - Yes, Sir.
Hyo Won.
You didn't go to work?
- I'm off until today. - I see.
Hyo Won.
Let's shake off the bad feelings we have toward each other...
and get along.
We're family now.
Fine.
Since Tae Yang ask, too.
Let's get along.
- Why are you shaking hands? - It's nothing.
I'm going to Tae Yang's shoot.
You should go, too.
I'll just get kicked out again.
I won't bother.
Tell him to come home after the shoot...
and play cards with me.
You took all his money last night, and now you're hooked.
Forget it. Bye.
She cares more about Tae Yang than her own mom already.
Hi, Hee Sun.
It's been a while.
How have you been?
A rumour? What kind of a rumour?
I feel like the woman in the rumour...
sounds like your daughter-in-law.
I didn't know whether or not to tell you,
but I thought you should know.
I see.
My daughter-in-law is so cautious. I couldn't be about her.
Those are all lies by people who like to make stuff up.
Hey.
Send me that article.
I'll read it with my daughter-in-law.
Okay.
Thanks for your concern.
Send me the article first, okay?
Okay.
What is that about?
(Announcer C, the daughter-in-law of a top menswear company...)
"Announcer C, the daughter-in-law"...
"of a top menswear company..."
"dumped her long-term boyfriend since college..."
"and married a corporate heir."
"The past boyfriend who was traumatised swore revenge..."
"and recently debuted as a model."
"He is a rising star thanks to his make-up commercial."
What is all of this about?
I thought it'd be super comfortable living with Ji Yun,
and that I'd hate it,
but it's better than I expected.
- That's good. - In some ways,
I'm grateful to her.
If she hadn't betrayed you,
you wouldn't be mine now.
So I'm thankful.
You are the icon of optimism.
But you know,
I have a question.
I won't get angry, so you have to be honest with me.
Whom did you like more,
her or me?
I really won't get mad, so tell me the truth.
I won't get angry.
If I think about it now,
I feel like I never really liked your sister-in-law.
That's how much I love you.
Are you saying that to make me feel good?
I can swear it on everything that I have.
And I've never done anything I need to hide from you.
That's fine, then.
So don't be conscious of her...
and wear a hanbok and do stuff like that again.
I won't.
But...
say it one more time.
I love you.
Mr Lee Dong Jin? You have a package.
Thank you.
Yun Shil! Come down.
What is it?
Our invitations came.
It's so pretty.
(Lee Dong Jin and Na Yun Shil)
(Wolgyesu Tailor Shop)
Look at me.
There's a shiny sticker on Ms Shiny Eyes.
What are you doing? You are so childish.
Mr Pretty Eyes got a shiny sticker, too.
- Here. - What?
You said Mr Pretty Eyes got a shiny sticker.
I am Mr Pretty Eyes and you are Ms Shiny Eyes. Stick on me.
(The Gentlemen of Wolgyesu Tailor Shop)
I won't give up Yun Shil till I die.
How come Hong Gi Pyo came out already?
Is that you and Ji Yun?
It's not Tae Yang's fault. He's a victim.
You have to break up with him if Mum said so.
We don't need to discuss this. Break up with him.
- Wedding gift box for sale! - Wedding gift box for sale!
Are you going to wait and see?
We'll be a married couple after a few days.
I hope we can get married all right.
I hope we can do that without any incidents.