(Episode 44)
(Wolgyesu Tailor Shop)
(Lee Dong Jin, Na Yun Shil)
Thank you.
How did the meeting with Gianni go?
He liked everything about the proposal.
I'm good at my job.
There's nothing Mr Pretty Eyes can't do.
My wife's the only one who knows that.
Get in. We have somewhere to go.
- Where? - You'll find out.
They look so happy.
Let's see how long that lasts.
What do you think?
It's beautiful.
I knew you'd like it.
Aren't you glad you let me pick the location?
In just a few more days...
we'll be married in here.
It doesn't feel real yet.
Are we really getting married?
People who are about to get married...
get worked up and want to back out at the last minute.
Do you feel that way?
No. I'm so happy.
I surprise myself multiple times a day...
because I think it's a dream.
Me, too.
Just imagining how pretty you'll look...
walking towards me down the aisle...
in your wedding dress makes me happy.
My heart's pounding already.
You might be disappointed.
You were beautiful when we took our wedding photos out of the blue.
You'll be even more beautiful this time.
I learned so much from you.
You taught me that you should not...
hesitate to express the love you feel...
for someone or something.
Before you came along, I had no idea that...
hearing such words could make someone happy.
I didn't know I taught you that.
Thanks to you...
I think I'm becoming a better person.
- I'm grateful for that. - Me, too.
You made me...
want to become a better and cooler person.
If we both become better people,
we'll become a better couple.
Then one day, we'll become good parents.
Let's have...
as many children as possible.
I will try,
but I think three will be my limit.
Three?
Do you want that many kids?
I thought two kids were more than enough.
Ms Shiny Eyes...
never ceases to amaze me.
Will we be able to get married...
- without any difficulty? - Of course.
Do you really think there will be no problems?
Don't you worry.
Nothing will happen.
(Meesa Apparel)
Tell Mr Min Hyo Sang that Hong Gi Pyo's here.
Do you have an appointment?
I'm in no mood for wordplay.
Give him this message.
"Hong Gi Pyo is here to see you." Okay?
Our Meesa Apparel has the best distribution infrastructure...
and the best network in Korea.
I don't understand why Tonelli wants to go into...
a partnership with a mum and pop store like Wolgyesu.
Tailored suits are not meant to be mass-produced in a factory.
We at Tonelli see designers...
and artisan tailors as our most important assets.
He's being narrow-minded again.
Look. Meesa Apparel doesn't have the tailor management system...
to properly implement our fashion philosophy.
Tailored suits can't be factory-made like toys and televisions.
Well, I can assure you that...
we will quickly come up with a tailor management system...
that can meet Tonelli's standards, okay?
In the meanwhile, please take a look at this.
This is our proposal.
I can guarantee you. Look.
If you partner up with us, Tonelli is going to get the best support...
that it could possibly get in Korea.
Okay. I'll take a look.
Okay.
Excuse me.
- What is it? - A Mr Hong Gi Pyo...
is in the lobby insisting he sees you.
I'm in the middle of an important meeting.
Make up and send him away.
How did Hong Gi Pyo get out already?
"Announcer C, the daughter-in-law..."
"of a top menswear company..."
"dumped her long-term boyfriend since college..."
"and married a corporate heir."
"The past boyfriend who was traumatised swore revenge..."
"and recently debuted as a model."
"He is a rising star thanks to his make-up commercial."
This is unbelievable.
Wait.
Does this mean that Tae Yang...
once dated Ji Yun?
I've told you numerous times that I can't let Hyo Won and...
Tae Yang get married, not even over my dead body.
Look who's talking.
I cannot allow you and Pooper to get married...
for the life of me!
What's wrong with you two?
Why can't you allow each other to get married for the life of you?
Why? What's the reason?
So...
does that mean I was the only one...
who didn't know?
I'm home.
- You were out? - Yes.
I went out to get some groceries.
Ji Yun.
Have a seat here for a minute.
I got...
this text message from a friend earlier today.
(Announcer C, the daughter-in-law of a top menswear company...)
It looks like you're that announcer.
Is there anything you want to tell me?
People in the broadcasting industry love to gossip, you know.
There are so many groundless rumours like this.
So...
you're saying it's not true.
Of course not. Please don't let it concern you.
I'm relieved.
(Public Library, Study Room, Digital Reference Room)
Yes, Mother.
Are you...
with Hyo Won now?
Yes. Would you like to speak to her?
No. Let's meet.
- Don't say anything to Hyo Won. - You mean now?
Sure, okay.
See you in a bit, then.
Who was that?
A friend of mine wants to meet up out of the blue.
You promised you'll study with me here until late tonight.
I couldn't say no because it sounded like it's about something urgent.
I'm sorry, Hyo Won.
That friend of yours.
It's not a girl, is it?
No.
Then you can go.
My back and bottom have been aching...
from sitting down all day, so this is actually good.
I should go home and get some rest.
Is it hot?
- Isn't it good? - Yes.
Did I keep you waiting long?
No.
I just got here, too.
- Where's Hyo Won? - I just took her home.
Why are you looking at me like that, Mother?
(Announcer C, the daughter-in-law of a top menswear company...)
Those two people mentioned in that message.
It's you and Ji Yun, isn't it?
Yes.
It's very exaggerated,
but it's true that Ji Yun and I dated when we were in university.
My goodness.
How can you have the audacity to date Hyo Won?
Does Hyo Won know about it as well?
Yes, she does.
That foolish girl.
- Mother. - Don't call me like that.
Be honest with me. You must have...
approached Hyo Won intentionally to get back at Ji Yun.
No, that's not what happened. I swear.
Do you actually expect me to believe that?
How I feel about Hyo Won has nothing to do with this. I'm serious.
Even if that's the case, I can't allow the two of you to get married,
now that Hyo Sang and Ji Yun are married. I absolutely can't.
What I had with Ji Yun in the past shouldn't affect our relationship.
Now that I look back,
Ji Yun and I were more like friends who were there for each other...
Who's going to believe that? No one will believe you.
I mean, people are already gossiping about you two.
It must have surprised you, and you must be concerned about it.
But I'll be better to Hyo Won and prove myself to you.
You sure have a way with words.
This world isn't an easy place.
You seduced Hyo Won by sweet-talking like this...
just to toy with her emotions, didn't you?
What do you mean? That's not true at all.
I'm going to keep this short. Get out of Hyo Won's life.
I can't do that.
- What? - If I was going to give up,
I would've done so when I found out that Hyo Won is Hyo Sang's sister.
It's too late now. I cannot break up with her.
I didn't think you'd be like this.
I can't believe how shameless you are.
Hyo Won is a part of me now.
I can't even imagine a life without her.
If she's not in my life, I won't be able to breathe.
I won't be able to think at all, either.
Hyo Won is my everything.
How dare you try to trick me?
My quick wits are what got me to where I am now.
Do you think I'll be swayed by your sweet talks?
- Mother. - You'd better...
break up with Hyo Won immediately,
or I'll have to take drastic measures.
Is he still with his friend?
Break up with Tae Yang.
What are you talking about all of a sudden, Mum?
Did you not hear me?
Don't ask me why. Just break up with him immediately.
What's wrong, Mum?
Did my darling make a mistake or something?
I don't even want to hear you calling him Darling any more!
What's going on? You're scaring me.
All this time...
- Why did you fool me? - What do you mean?
I heard that Tae Yang and Ji Yun...
dated in the past.
- Mum, how did you know that? - That's not important.
Do you not have any pride?
I wouldn't say anything if it was someone else.
How can you want to marry a guy who used to be in love with Ji Yun?
Are you dumb? Are you an idiot?
It's all in the past. Why should it matter?
- What? - Tae Yang didn't do anything wrong.
Ji Yun dumped Tae Yang after she met Hyo Sang because Hyo Sang is rich.
You should pity him if anything.
Hyo Won.
It looks like you've lost your mind.
She's a bad person because she dumped him.
Why are you blaming Tae Yang when he's the one who was dumped?
He's the victim.
Shut it! Break up now unless you want to infuriate me more.
Don't disgrace our family.
I don't want to. I absolutely cannot break up with him.
You little... How dare you!
Mum.
I've never...
hit you before.
It shows how serious...
and desperate I am about this matter.
No means no.
Don't be so bullheaded.
End it with him completely.
No.
I can't do that.
Hyo Won.
Even if you beat me up to a pulp,
I can't.
I'll never give up on Tae Yang.
Hey. You!
You stop right there. Stop!
Stop right there...
You're home.
- Hey, did you have a good day? - Yes.
Hey, Hyo Won. Are you crying right now?
What's the matter with her?
Why are you sitting there looking all spaced out?
Read the newspaper or something.
I'm tired.
Shall I get herbal medicine made for you?
You seem to get tired easily.
Gok Ji,
why don't we use this comforter ourselves?
Let's not give it to Dong Jin and Yun Shil.
- What do you mean? - Dong Jin and Yun Shil...
have long years to live and they have great things ahead.
Why don't we enjoy some luxury ourselves?
Don't be too serious.
They'll use this comforter when they come back from honeymoon.
Why do you want to use this one?
I'd like to fall asleep in a nice comforter with you.
You're getting silly as you grow old.
Can you thread a needle for me?
My eyes are blurry. I can't see the eye of the needle.
Here you go.
What are you doing?
Can't you see this?
I see it.
What are you doing, then?
I guess I'm tired. My hands are shaking.
Let's go to the oriental medicine clinic tomorrow.
Mum, we're home.
Come in.
You must be tired.
I will do it, Mother.
She's so happy...
that you told her to call you Mother.
I'm so happy to have a daughter like Yun Shil.
Let's not have a silly conflict between us.
We'll be happy together.
Sure, Mother.
I'll do the sewing.
No, leave it to me.
This is my present for you and Dong Jin.
Your sewing skill might be better than mine,
but I'd like to finish this myself.
Why don't you thread this needle for me?
Sure I will, Mother.
(Restricted Area)
(Operating Theatre)
It's so distracting.
- Why don't you sit down, Sam Do? - Okay.
Do you think the operation is going all right?
It's not an operation. It's a treatment.
I see.
I hope there's no medical accident.
The doctor said not to worry.
Stay calm, Sam Do.
If something happens to Sun Nyeo,
I'll just go crazy. I can't never live alone.
You're too overreacting. Have a seat here.
Have a seat...
and calm down. Drink some water.
I'm such a bad guy.
A marriage between people in the same condition is safe.
You were so greedy...
to get married to someone like me.
That's why you always feel anxious and restless.
In a word, you're in a chronic mental breakdown.
People can even get tired of hearing compliments if they hear every day.
You always complain about money or a child.
Don't you have anything else to tell me?
Yes, I'm sick and tired.
The day seems like an eternity for me.
Now that you suggested divorce, I brought the paper cheerfully.
I'm so sick of you when you're acting like this.
I...
made too many mistakes to Sun Nyeo.
I have nothing...
but a fine figure and I bragged about it.
I was mean to my own wife.
It's a pity that I'm the only one watching this.
It's like you're shooting a drama.
Please calm down, Sam Do.
Honey,
if only you come out alive from the operating room,
if you come out alive, I would...
make up for everything I've done, honey.
Please.
What a virtuous husband!
Calm down. Here she comes.
(Operation Theatre)
Honey, honey.
Can you recognise me?
Sure I can.
I can recognise...
my one and only husband.
Thank you for coming back alive.
I appreciate that.
sbtitles ripped and synced by riri13
It must have been very hard for you, honey.
It was so painful...
but I endured it thinking about you.
You did a great job, honey.
I was...
going to kill myself if something happens to you.
Was you?
To think that I might live alone without you,
I felt hopeless and didn't want to live any more.
Don't cry.
Stop crying.
Are they filming a movie or what?
It's like they are shooting a movie.
That's what I'm saying. You can't see that without crying.
It must have been hard for you, Sun Nyeo.
Thank you, Dong Sook.
When I go home,
I'll cook spicy chicken stew for you.
It's nice that we can see you alive and eat spicy chicken stew.
- We'll move her to ward. - All right.
It's been a long time, Kyung Ja.
Look who's here!
Gi Pyo!
- It's my son Gi Pyo! - Mum!
Am I dreaming? Gi Pyo!
You finally came back to me.
Now you can have hot meal I made.
Are you that happy to see me come back?
Can't you imagine?
That hurts.
While you were staying there,
I couldn't get a sound sleep even for one night.
You're the only one who's been waiting for me.
- You're the only one, Mum. - You're making me dizzy.
Get me down.
Why didn't you cook any meat when I came back in a long time?
- It's all tofu dishes. - Stop talking.
Eat all these...
and never go near to the penitentiary again.
All right.
Here you go, my son.
Did you sometimes see Yun Shil?
Well, a few days ago,
she came with some meat and fruit, and asked to change your mind.
Have you met Yun Shil yet?
- No. - I thought you'd meet her...
right after you came out. That's strange.
Have you given up on her?
I don't know.
That's good.
She didn't like you and flirted with another man.
Just forget her...
and go away.
You don't need to have feeling for her. That's nonsense.
You made the right decision.
I will find better woman...
for you to be your wife,
someone much better than Yun Shil.
I can't give up on Yun Shil...
as long as I'm alive.
What?
Don't tell anyone I'm out for a while, Mum.
Even to Yun Shil. Do you get it?
This tastes amazing.
Now that he came out after all that, he would do his part.
Tae Yang.
What are you doing here? You didn't give me a call.
Mum hit me.
- What? - She found out...
what happened between you and Ji Yun.
So she told me to break up with you.
I told her I couldn't...
and she slapped me on the face.
Mother shouldn't have done that.
How could she hit you?
Come here.
- Did it hurt? - Yes.
It hurt so much.
The urgent appointment you said,
was it with Mum?
Did she tell you to break up with me?
Yes, she did.
So?
Do you have to ask that? I surely answered no.
I'm relieved.
Did my mum slap you as well?
She didn't, so don't worry.
I'll leave home right away.
I'll ask her to delete me from the family records.
I won't put up with violence.
She lashed out at you in surprise and anger.
Try to understand.
I can't. I'm going to leave home.
I'll move in with you.
There you go again.
Let me take you home.
My mum might scream and curse at you...
and she might even hit you.
If that scared me,
I wouldn't have dated you in the first place.
I understand how your mum feels.
The only thing I can do is persuade her...
by showing her how sincere I am.
You brats.
You deceived me...
and got married.
I can't believe my daughter-in-law...
used to date my son-in-law!
Since Hyo Sang and Ji Yun are already married,
I won't allow you two.
Break up.
Why should we break up because of them?
- No, I won't do that. - How dare you.
Tae Yang, it's up to you now.
Persuade her into leaving you.
As I told you before, I cannot do that, Mother.
Watch it.
You just do as she says. How dare you object!
Break up right now!
If one of us must break up,
then it should be you.
- There's no way it'll be us. - You aren't making any sense.
Your brother and I are already legally married.
You have no right to make any comments!
Don't be so stubborn. Tae Yang and Hyo Won...
must break up. That's the right thing to do.
I won't do that.
I'll move out if I must.
I won't leave Tae Yang.
Calm down, Hyo Won.
Does Tae Yang mean more to you...
than your own mum and brother?
My moving out will solve all the problems.
If I stop being your daughter and sister...
I won't have to break up with Tae Yang.
How could you...
How could you say such a thing?
- Mum. - Mother.
Are you okay?
Mum.
- Mother. - What's wrong?
What's wrong, Mum? Are you okay?
- Can you not talk, Mum? - Mother!
- Oh, no. - Mum.
I think she has aphasia.
- Aphasia? - Aphasia?
- Mum, try to relax and breathe. - Mum.
Mum.
Why is she suddenly unable to speak?
I'll need to run some tests to be sure,
but based on her condition, an immense shock...
caused her to lose her ability to speak.
So does she have aphasia?
Yes. Bring her to the hospital for a medical check up.
Is there a cure?
For severe cases, I recommend psychiatric treatment,
but it's best to discuss that once we have the test results.
Make sure she doesn't get stressed...
and keep her relaxed at all times.
Mum, I'm really sorry.
Say something.
Mum.
- I'm sorry, Mother. - How can you call her like that?
Not in front of the doctor, honey.
It's my fault.
I said I'd stop being her daughter.
That's why she got so upset.
Don't blame yourself.
She'll recover soon.
The doctor said she'll recover...
once she calms down.
Why is it so difficult?
Isn't it enough that we love each other?
Why is everyone so determined to break us up?
Cry all you want.
You're awake.
I must have fallen asleep.
Where are Dong Sook and Tae Pyung?
They went home.
You should've gone with them.
You should get a good sleep. You have to work tomorrow.
Don't be silly.
I can't work with you lying here.
What's the point in making suits when you're sick?
You've grown up.
You were begging for a divorce just a few days ago.
That was because I got infuriated...
because you kept acting up.
I'm sorry.
I had no idea you were so sick.
I'm a terrible husband.
Thinking about how sad and scared you must have felt...
all that while...
My heart breaks.
I deserve to die.
Don't blame yourself. It's my fault for not telling you.
I promise that from now on,
I'll treat you like how the prince treats the princess...
in a fairy story.
Don't you dare take that back.
I won't.
Your wife needs to rest.
Right.
Will she be okay, Doctor?
Yes. We located the right spot...
and the surgery went well. You don't need to worry about it.
You might have lingering headaches while your body replenishes...
the cerebrospinal fluid.
It would be best if you stay in bed.
You should recover in three days.
Make sure she drinks a lot of water.
Doctor.
If water leaks from my brain...
does that cause forgetfulness as well?
Ever since I had those headaches...
I've been forgetting things.
Headaches have many causes and so does forgetfulness.
In severe cases we'd suspect dementia,
but your tests results were clean so that's not a concern.
Good. Thank you.
- A marriage registration form? - I filled up my section.
Fill in your section and sign it.
Are we doing this already?
Do you want to register our marriage years later...
when you think I'm good enough?
Don't be silly.
Fill in your part, then.
(Na Yun Shil)
Your seal.
It's done.
You need to affix your seal one more time.
I think it's done.
What about the one here?
What are you doing?
You wanted me to seal your lips. Come here.
I'll get some extra red ink...
so my seal shows up nice and clear.
Not this. I want the other stamp.
Gosh, seriously.
Thank you.
Yes, Mother.
I'm just calling to let you know that the furniture just arrived.
There was no issue with the delivery, so don't worry.
It arrived already?
I should have been there to receive the delivery. Thank you.
It's no problem at all.
- Did you pick up the hanbok? - I just did.
Dong Jin and I will be there soon.
Okay.
Are you okay? It must have been scary.
I'm okay. What about you?
I'm fine. What is wrong with that driver, though?
It must be an inexperienced driver.
Still, he'll get himself into a big accident if he drives like that.
- The light changed. - What?
Oh, right.
We're back.
How does the hanbok look? Did it turn out well?
Yes. I must say,
Yun Shil is classically beautiful.
She looked so graceful and elegant in that dress.
How shall I say it? She looked like a true Asian beauty.
My goodness. You're so head over heels for her.
He brags about his future wife any second he gets.
I'm not bragging.
I'm just telling you the truth about what I witnessed with my own eyes.
When you see her in that dress later,
you'll say, "Oh, this is why Dong Jin said that earlier."
- Stop it already. - Okay.
- Is the wedding box coming today? - Yes.
Mr Lee and Ms Choi prepared all the gifts for the box, right?
Will they also act as your parents and receive...
- the box for you as well? - Yes.
I keep thinking...
that I'm so lucky to have such amazing parents-in-law.
They say, married couples resemble each other.
Yun Shil is starting to act like Mr Lee.
I know, right?
- Would you like some tea? - Yes, please.
- We have quince tea in the fridge. - Okay.
Oh, right. I just received...
a package for you.
- Package? - Yes.
Gosh, what's...
Here's quince tea for everyone.
Thanks.
There's something I have to do. I'll be back soon.
What do you have to do?
I forgot to take care of something.
I'll be back, everyone. It won't take long.
It's just a short-term liquidity shortage.
How can they start to collect the loan? That's just crazy.
No, listen.
I get that our stock price has fallen,
but everything will be resolved if the contract with Tonelli...
goes through.
So please don't worry and give us a bit more time.
Right, yes.
Let's meet tomorrow, then.
We can talk more in person. Yes.
All right.
- Excuse me. - Let go. I said, let go.
- What is going on? - I'm Hong Gi Pyo.
What do you say? Shall we talk in front of your employees?
You guys can leave. It's okay.
Look who's here.
Nice to see you.
When did you get released?
I was locked up in there because you neglected me.
But fortunately, someone else got me out which I'm thankful for.
What are you talking about? You're hurting my feelings here.
My attorney has been checking on your case on a regular basis.
Not to my knowledge. Anyway, give me the money you promised me.
I'm in a bit of a bind, so I don't have much patience now.
- Don't make me talk a lot. - Look, Gi Pyo.
You should have let me know that you were getting released...
so that I could prepare things for you, don't you think?
I said I'll give you one of our stores...
when you get released. Wasn't that our promise?
That's why I'm here now.
Right. Just give me a little bit of time.
It's not like I can open a new store in a day.
I don't need things like that any more. Give me cash instead.
As soon as possible.
Gi Pyo. Unfortunately,
you showed up when I'm having problems with my cash flow.
You've waited all this time, so wait just a little more.
All right. Fine. Here.
Take this.
Do you think I'm a beggar?
You can't get out of this with that meagre amount.
This is all I have right now.
Just take this for today and...
Okay, all right. Give me a little more time.
I'll give you the money.
If you don't keep your word the next time I see you,
there will be consequences. Got it?
All right.
Nothing is going my way.
Even that scum showed up and ruined my day!
Gosh, seriously.
How much did I spend on my hospital bills?
Thank goodness I had insurance. It would have been crazy otherwise.
(Hiring Collection Agents)
"Collection agents"?
Excuse me, Sir.
- Are you still hiring? - Yes.
It must be a job...
where you have to collect money from borrowers.
I'd like an application form.
- Oh, boy. - You must keep the balance.
You can't fall, okay?
Okay. Please don't worry, Mother.
Gosh, Mum.
We should just get the rice cake made.
Why do we have to make it at home?
It's seriously so much work.
It's not any rice cake.
It's for wishing Dong Jin and Yun Shil a happy marriage.
Of course I have to make it myself.
It's 100 percent sticky rice.
Make sure it doesn't get mixed with regular rice.
Watch it right in front of the machine the whole time, okay?
Okay, I will.
- Please don't worry, Mother. - All right.
She didn't do any of this for our wedding.
Don't you think this is too much?
You know how special Dong Jin is to her.
We should understand.
You're right. We should become successful to win her love.
I'll be back soon.
- Gosh, who's calling me now? - I'll get it for you.
- Yes, hurry up. - Okay.
Hello?
This is the gentleman of trot Tae Pyung's phone.
Hello, I'm calling from WN Entertainment.
Our CEO would like to speak with Tae Pyung regarding signing him.
- Is he available now? - Hold on, please.
My gosh, the CEO of WN entertainment...
wants to discuss signing you.
WN Entertainment?
(Visiting Application)
He has been released.
Already? From what I know, he hasn't served his sentence in full.
No, he didn't. He got bail.
Bail?
Yes.
Did everything go well?
Where are you now?
Now? I'm at the shop.
I'm on my way now. Stay right there, okay?
You can't leave the shop alone. You have to go home with me.
Okay, I'll wait for you.
By the way, is something going on?
No. I'll be there shortly, so don't go anywhere.
(Men's Suits)
Be careful.
Mum.
Tae Yang has been sitting like that for hours.
Don't you feel bad that he's been doing this for days?
Please, soften up and forgive him.
It wasn't my intention to hide it from you.
But it's clearly all my fault. I don't have a leg to stand on.
Mother,
I can promise you that I've never done anything...
to shame or dishonor you nor Hyo Won.
Also, my love for your daughter was truly sincere and pure.
Mum.
Mum. Mum.
Stand up.
Quickly.
Your legs feel numb, don't they?
Oh, dear.
Oh, gosh. They hurt a lot, don't they?
I'm all right.
It will only make Mother more upset. Why does he keep coming?
- Is the oriental medicine ready? - Yes, I warmed it up just right.
Oh, my. The smell of oriental medicine.
Mother.
She's cunning as a fox.
I've warmed up some medicine for you.
What's wrong, Mother?
(Did you really...)
(break up with Tae Yang...)
(for my son's money?)
"Did you really break up..."
"with Tae Yang for my son's money?"
How many times have I told you? That's not true.
It was Hyo Sang's ambitious...
and dignified features that made me fall in love with him.
I'm telling you the truth.
I did date Tae Yang for a long time,
but our relationship wasn't as serious as you think.
I can swear on my late parents.
Leave. Get out.
You want me to leave?
All right. I'll leave as you say.
I'm sorry.
There's no need for you to apologise.
I'm the one that should be sorry.
This is so frustrating.
The doctor said nothing's wrong.
I wonder why she still can't talk.
I sometimes feel like she's doing this on purpose.
Why say such a thing?
Why would she do this on purpose?
Your second exam is coming up.
I'm sure you're having trouble in concentrating because of Mum.
The exam isn't important...
because your mother can't speak any more.
I know.
This is so upsetting.
The doctor said it caused by shock.
As time passes, I'm sure she'll start to understand...
and eventually learn to speak again.
So don't get too upset.
I'll call you later.
Wait.
Yun Shil will be receiving her gifts from the groom today,
so I might not be able to answer your call.
Gifts from the groom?
You mean Dong Jin and Yun Shil are really getting married?
Did something happen this afternoon?
No, nothing happened.
I feel suspicious.
You told me to stay put at the tailor shop.
That was because although we were apart for a while,
I suddenly missed you so much.
That's why I told you to wait for me there.
Who told you to be so charming?
Let's go in.
Goodness.
Did you prepare this all by yourself?
I noticed people order everything nowadays.
This rice cake is made...
to prevent misfortune...
and brings the bride and groom closer together.
Therefore, mother must make it as it gives the best wishes.
Mum, why is there only one chestnut?
Chestnuts and jujubes symbolises...
giving birth to many sons and daughters.
The bride must eat this, so don't think of eating it.
Can I have a baby if I eat that?
You must be feeling better now that you're talking about babies.
You must be. You are you feeling?
My energy's back...
and my headache's gone. I feel good.
That's good news.
We shouldn't be wasting time here.
It's time for the groom to arrive. Let's hurry up.
- All right. - All right.
Let's go.
Why? Do I look weird?
What are you talking about? You look beautiful.
I was just amazed at how beautiful you are again.
The elders will hear you.
Wait.
Since the gifts are arriving today,
let's take a picture to remember this day.
Come and get the gifts!
They must have arrived.
The gifts are here!
- The gifts are here! - Come and get the gifts!
Come and get the gifts!
It's cold out there. Why don't you just go inside?
Look. The groom is empty-handed.
You have no manners.
I guess we'll just have to hit your soles until they're on fire.
Let me give you this on behalf of the groom.
Mr. Lee. You shouldn't have.
Wait. Let's see.
I think we can move to the front yard with this much of money.
Squid, move forward.
- Let's move forward. - To the front yard.
We can't be too nice.
Oh, gosh. We're moving all the way to the front yard.
- Come and get the gifts! - The gifts are here!
My father just paid you for them.
What are you talking about? That was to move to the front yard.
We'll surely need more to move from here to the bride's room.
Nonsense. I gave you more than enough.
Oh, my goodness.
Our carrier refuses to budge because we don't have...
enough labour money. What shall we do?
We're in a difficult situation here.
- Can I have some water, too? - The food is getting cold.
Hurry up and come inside.
They give me no choice. I'll have to use my good looks.
My good looks. My charm.
My good looks.
One step backwards.
- Why? - It's my turn, then.
Okay. You try.
Is our carrier feeling all right?
Three steps forward!
What are you talking about?
- My wife is just as sexy. - My husband is the best.
We'll be up until dawn.
Wrap it up and come inside. The food will get cold.
That won't be possible.
All right. Let me close the deal here and now.
Here. Will this do it, Sam Do?
- Yes. - What do you think?
Do you think you can go inside with this amount?
Okay.
Now...
the groom will break this.
May all the misfortune go away!
I'm going to break it now.
Yun Shil is not only our daughter-in-law but like a daughter.
So your mother and I prepared...
both gifts for the bride and groom.
She was like a daughter to us,
so it wasn't easy to come all this way.
Above all,
it must have been hard for both of you.
You went through all that...
and only good things will be ahead.
You don't have to say much.
Just have a married life like that of your parents.
That's the right answer.
Everyone, clap your hands!
Mum said...
you have to eat this, so I brought it.
You have to eat chestnut and jujube,
so that we can have a lot of children.
- You should eat too, Dong Jin. - The bride is supposed to eat it.
Eat it quickly.
Oh, can you give me the phone?
What are you going to do?
Let me see.
What are you doing?
I downloaded a location tracking application.
A location tracking application?
- Why do you need that? - Husband and wife are one.
We should know where the other is.
We're together at the tailor shop and home.
I don't understand why we need it.
- Is something wrong? - No, nothing is wrong.
Here you go. I wonder you want to keep a secret to me.
- No, I don't. - It's all right, then.
It must have been hard for you today.
Is everything all right?
Sure.
Finish eating now.
This is Hong Gi Pyo speaking.
Your wife received a wedding present box today.
Are you going to just wait and see?
Why don't you do anything after you came out of the prison?
Do you think I paid for all the bail...
for you to do nothing?
Don't order me to do anything.
I'll take care it myself.
Let's go!
Here we are.
- Goodness. It's so beautiful. - I agree.
I'd like to have a wedding again at such a nice place like here.
What are you talking about in front of your husband?
Do you want to have a wedding again?
I mean with you, not with another man. All right?
With me? You should have said that.
What a sight!
The groom is here.
You're here.
- Where are Mum and Dad? - They're coming in aunt's car.
They'll be here soon.
I see. Get inside. It's cold.
- All right. - Let's take a look.
It's beautiful.
Do you need to tell me something?
I really cherish this, but you can have it.
All right.
You're so silly.
You may need this, Dong Jin doesn't.
He needs this. Don't you see?
He's been just studying since he was young. He's not strong.
What's this?
This is the blue tablet the big shots take when they go climbing.
You keep this and use it when you need.
Neither Dong Jin nor I need that.
You know what,
I don't need it myself.
By the way, where's Yun Shil?
She's wearing the bridal makeup.
She'll come with Tae Yang.
Why don't you take just one?
He doesn't give up.
How come he keeps it in this pocket all the time?
Do I look all right? Isn't the makeup too heavy?
You're beautiful.
Dong Jin will love it.
- Are you all right, by the way? - What do you mean?
I heard that Madam Ko got very angry.
Don't worry. You're the bride today.
Don't mind my business. Just think about yourself.
Yun Shil.
I mean, aunt.
- I packed everything. - Thank you.
I'll bring the car.
- Wait for a minute. - All right.
- Let's go, Aunt. - All right.
Where is he? He's keeping the bride waiting.
I don't like this.
I left my bag packing your things.
- Stay here for a second. - All right.
You look stunning.
What are you doing here?
I came here to talk with you.
We have a lot of catching up to do.
Let me go!
Get off me!
Yun Shil!
Where is she?
Aunt!
Where's Yun Shil?
She was right here.
Didn't you see her when you were coming?
What do you mean?
Yun Shil!
- How are you? - How are you?
- Dad is inside. - Congratulations.
Thank you.
- Congratulations. - Thank you.
- Congratulations, Dong Jin. - Thank you.
It won't change anything.
Stop the car.
You wouldn't want to mess up your makeup.
Don't make a fuss and just go.
Hello. Where are you?
Yun Shil is missing.
What do you mean Yun Shil is missing?
What are you talking about?
(The Gentlemen of Wolgyesu Tailor Shop)
The bride is missing. What's going on?
We should report to the police.
What if she can't speak for the rest of her life?
What should I do?
I know it would be hard for you, but you should break up with Tae Yang.
If I break up with Hyo Won, it would be so painful for me.
I feel like my heart is empty.
What shall I do?
How can I watch my child suffer?
Stop playing house...
and come back to the place where you belong.