(The following content may not be suitable for viewers under 15.)
(Viewer discretion is advised.)
- Oh, my. - Hello.
What brings you here?
Could you please give this to Mother?
- Don't you mean Hyo Won? - No.
- I would appreciate your help. - All right.
Love is so hard.
(Episode 45)
Are preparations going well?
I just arrived at the church.
You're already there?
I just finished my makeup. I'll be getting my hair done now.
I'm sorry, but you'll have to wait a while. Is that okay?
I waited this long.
Just a few hours wouldn't be a problem.
Don't worry about me. Take your time.
By the way, did you sleep well last night?
No. I didn't get a wink of sleep. My eyes are bloodshot.
To be honest, I had a sleepless night myself.
I hope I don't doze off during the wedding ceremony.
If I notice you dozing,
I'll make sure to poke you in the side to wake you, so don't worry.
All right.
Yun Shil.
It was a long ride getting here.
Thank you for enduring the hard times...
and remaining by my side.
I want to thank you, too.
Thank you for being patient, Dong Jin.
While I'm at it, I can wait a few more hours, but don't be too late.
- I miss my bride. - I'll be there as soon as I'm done.
- I'll begin doing your hair. - All right.
See you in a bit, Dong Jin.
- Congratulations. - How are you?
Thank you for coming. Father is inside.
Hello. Thank you.
- Congratulations. - Thank you.
- Congratulations, Dong Jin. - Thank you.
You look stunning.
What are you doing here?
I came here to talk to you.
We have a lot of catching up to do.
Tae Yang, where are you?
Yun Shil is missing.
What do you mean Yun Shil is missing?
What are you talking about?
Da Jeong was with her while I went to get the car.
While Da Jeong went back up to get something, Yun Shil disappeared.
Okay. Hang up for now.
The phone has been turned off. Please leave a message.
This won't change anything.
Stop the car.
Don't make a fuss and just go.
The ceremony will start soon. Where's the bride?
I know. Maybe she's caught in traffic.
Yun Shil...
has gone missing.
- What do you mean she's missing? - What are you talking about?
Tae Yang says she disappeared while he went to get the car.
From the way I see it, I think it's that man's doing.
Who do you mean?
- Hong Gi Pyo. - Hong Gi Pyo?
You mean Hong Gi Pyo, Yun Shil's ex-husband?
No. He's not her ex-husband, is he?
Anyhow, you said he was in prison now.
He was released a few days ago.
You mean to say that scum actually got released?
I think he took Yun Shil...
to stop her from getting married.
Wait a minute. Then this means she's been kidnapped.
I've never seen such a scumbag.
Shouldn't we report this to the police first?
Sung Jun. Wait.
If we push things too far, you don't know what he'll do to Yun Shil.
Let's wait a bit longer.
Mr Lee and Ms Choi will be shocked if they hear this news.
How can something like this happen?
If I had known something would happen,
I wouldn't have left her side.
(Farm)
People will worry because I left without saying anything.
Please let me go, Gi Pyo.
My wedding was ruined, too.
His wedding should be ruined as well.
Go inside.
Please open this door.
Someone open the door, please.
Open it. I'm telling you to open the door!
Why on earth are you doing this?
What's your intention of doing this?
I just want to talk with you.
We have a lot to catch up on.
I don't have anything to say to you.
Yun Shil,
you're the first person I gave my heart to.
You're the only one I'll love until I die.
Yun Shil, you are the only woman in my life.
How could you think of...
leaving me to marry your boss?
What about me?
I never loved you.
Yes, you did.
You agreed to a wedding.
I told you, that was out of guilt.
Things happened that ruined the wedding that day,
but we had guests and we were all dressed up.
How could you pretend our wedding never happened?
The reason the detectives showed up was because...
I hoped to earn a fortune to make your life easier.
I ended up in prison and lost my wife to another man.
Don't you see why I'm so furious?
We would have never lived happily together...
even if you didn't go to prison.
I thought trying hard enough would make up for the lack of love.
I realised that effort alone isn't enough.
I said I love you! I love you!
Isn't that enough?
Change your mind.
We'll stay until you do, whether you take 10 days or a month.
Can I please make a phone call?
My in-laws will be worried. Please let me call them.
The bride's missing. What's going on?
At her first wedding the groom disappeared...
and this time she didn't show up.
Why is it always so hard for her to get married?
Mum.
Have you talked to her yet?
Her phone's still off.
Your mum's about to pass out.
What should we do about this?
Mr Lee, I think you should take Ms Choi home.
Dong Sook, take your parents' home.
Just us?
I think we should stay with Dong Jin and discuss what to do.
Take your parents' home.
Ask your aunt to drive them back.
What about me?
Go home. Look after them.
See you later.
Shouldn't we call the police?
Let's go inside and talk to Dong Jin first.
(Na Yun Shil)
Are you okay?
Thanks for coming.
I should've stayed with her.
If he hadn't taken her from outside the salon...
he'd have come here and ruined the wedding.
- You're right. - I saw him...
at their botched wedding because I was the wedding singer.
The look in his eyes were totally evil and frightening.
We can't wait here forever. What should we do?
I could be wrong. I'll wait here a little longer.
Sorry. I thought it's Yun Shil but it's Hyo Won.
Can I take the call outside?
Hi, Hyo Won. How's your mum?
Still no change.
We just got back from the hospital and...
the doctor said all we can do is help her relax.
I hope it doesn't last long.
What if she's never able to speak again?
What should I do then?
That won't ever happen.
It's temporary, not permanent. Try not to get too worked up.
I won't.
Is the wedding over?
There was no wedding.
There was no wedding? What do you mean?
Yun Shil disappeared. We're looking for her.
Yun Shil disappeared?
Do you mean the bride was a no-show?
Why did she disappear?
Does she not want to marry Dong Jin?
What happened?
I don't know.
We're looking for her now. I'll call you back.
Okay, bye.
Ware you talking about my ex-husband?
Yes. The bride didn't come to the wedding.
The bail wasn't a waste.
Bail? What do you mean?
It's a secret.
How do you feel?
You drank until early this morning.
Is your mum still sick?
How do you feel, Mum?
Are you sure you can't talk?
Are you just putting on a show...
to force Hyo Won to break up?
You're a great actress.
What's wrong with you?
Did you have to say that and upset her all over again?
Calm down, Mum. Try to relax.
It's okay.
It's okay, Mum.
Madam Ko, this came for you.
What's this?
I went out early this morning...
to get the milk and newspaper and met Tae Yang.
He asked me to give you this.
He said he couldn't visit because a friend's getting married.
I guess he wrote to you.
Shall I read it?
I'm writing this to apologise because I can't visit...
as I must attend a friend's wedding.
How shocked and upset must one be...
to lose one's ability to speak?
Thinking about it makes me feel guilty as if it's my fault.
Until you are free of the feeling that I betrayed you,
I will lie low and repent for what I've done.
Are you okay?
Splash.
If I must break up with Hyo Won because of this,
of course I will be hurt.
The thought of not being able to see you again...
leaves an empty hole in my heart.
The time we spent have become fond and special memories...
that I will cherish forever.
If I have one wish, it is that we can go back to...
how things were and be happy together.
Of course, I do understand your concerns.
I got over my past long ago.
Mum.
I want to tell you that I dated Hyo Won with a clear conscience.
"Falling in love with Hyo Won..."
"made me realise that my previous relationship was more about..."
"feeling pity for a friend who was there for me..."
"during my struggles and not love."
"I promise to act wisely so as to preserve everyone's happiness."
"I hope you will stop being angry."
"I will visit you tomorrow."
"Sincerely, Kang Tae Yang."
He writes such amazing letters.
He's never written me a letter yet.
You got a love letter from him before I did.
I'm jealous.
Mum.
(You and Kang Tae Yang)
"Can never..."
You and Kang Tae Yang can never date.
It's all in the past.
Hyo Sang and Ji Yun are happy.
Nothing will change how we feel about each other.
That hurts!
Okay, fine. I'll leave.
I knew this kind of thing would happen.
That's why I was opposed to Dong Jin and Yun Shil's marriage.
What shall I do?
I should never approved their marriage...
at all costs.
There's no point to say that.
This kind of thing happens from the day they get married.
What would happen after that is very obvious.
How can I bear to see my child suffers?
It's cold, Mum. Why don't we go inside and talk more?
Ms Choi, you might collapse if you stay here.
I'm sure that punk did this.
That punk...
must have kidnapped Yun Shil.
He's in penitentiary. How can he do such a thing?
I heard that Hong Gi Pyo came out of the prison.
- What? - What?
- Did he get out of the prison? - Yes, he did.
Sam Do heard about it from Dong Jin a while ago.
I was right.
That guy intended to ruin the wedding.
That's why he kidnapped Yun Shil.
- Where are you going, Sun Nyeo? - I need to see Hong Gi Pyo's mum.
His mum must know where her son is.
- I'll push her to get an answer. - I want to go, too.
Mum, you're not well. You should stay home.
- I'll go with her. - Let's go.
The world is so strange
We're in a strange world
Who is it?
My goodness. What are you doing?
Are you throwing a party?
Gosh, you're cooking fan cakes.
Don't touch. There are for my son.
Where's your son?
He went out for some business early in the morning.
Why are you looking for my son?
Mr Lee's family is troubled...
because of your son.
My brother's wedding was today.
However, Yun Shil did not show up at the wedding.
So the wedding was cancelled, and it was a mess.
How can a woman who has a husband get married again?
It's not a surprise to me the wedding was cancelled.
Don't you realise...
what kind of crime your son committed?
He kidnapped an innocent person. It's a kidnapping.
What are you saying? He brought his own wife himself.
I guess you don't know much about law...
as you're an old lady.
Have you ever heard of the additional punishment law?
- The additional punishment law? - He has a record...
and it's been just a few days since he was bailed out.
He can be subjected to harsher punishment.
If we report to the police,
your son will go to the prison...
and has to stay there until his hair gets all Gray.
- What? - So, contact your son quickly...
and tell him to bring Yun Shil back home.
Gi Pyo, where are you? Where are you now, Gi Pyo?
(Mum)
What shall I do? He left his cell phone at home.
Do you know what I wanted to do most at the jail?
I wanted to have instant noodle together with you.
When I first visited your house to receive private loan interest,
you were eating instant noodle in front of wood-burning stove.
It smelled so good. Remember what I said?
"If I can get a little of it,"
"I will deduct 100 dollars of the money I should collect today."
- Do you remember? - I don't remember that.
I erased everything about you in my head.
How can you forget all those memories?
Those things might be memories to you,
but they were nightmares to me.
Nightmares?
How could you be changed so much?
- Who changed you like this? - It's not that I'm changed.
I just couldn't say because I was scared back then.
Does it mean that you're not scared of me now?
Why?
Because I have someone I love.
Love?
How can you say love so easily in front of me?
I don't know how Lee Dong Jin seduced you.
However, you shouldn't say love...
to a thief who steals someone else's wife.
Yun Shil,
someone you should love is me, Hong Gi Pyo.
I don't want to listen to such things.
Family members must be worried.
Please let me make just one phone call.
They must be worried now.
I should tell them I'm all right.
Are you drinking now?
We just had some pork and soju.
- Would you like to drink? - I'm fine.
Bring her bag.
- Sure. Give me the bag. - Yes.
Here it is.
- Don't drink too much. - Yes, Sir.
(Mr Pretty Eyes)
Is Mr Pretty Eyes...
Lee Dong Jin?
Give me that.
Let's go, Dong Jin.
He's right.
Two hours have passed already.
I don't think Yun Shil would come here.
(Ms Shiny Eyes)
It's me, Yun Shil.
It's been a long time.
Let me talk to Yun Shil.
- I won't do that. - Get Yun Shil on the phone now,
or I'll report to the police.
You know what will happen next.
If a siren goes off, I cannot guarantee Yun Shil's safety.
Don't provoke me.
Let's talk face to face.
- Yun Shil is innocent. - Don't you get funny with me.
Who are you to get in between Yun Shil and me?
Hey.
- Hong Gi Pyo. - Yun Shil is my girl.
Why do you interfere when I want to talk to my wife?
If you don't provoke me,
I will have a long talk with Yun Shil,
resolve a misunderstanding and send her home myself.
So move out of my way.
Let me tell you again.
If you report to the police,
you'll never see Yun Shil again.
What does he say?
Is he with Yun Shil?
- Yes, he is. - Why did you hang up, then?
I installed a location tracking application on Yun Shil's phone.
A location tracking application?
You do possess the gift of foresight.
Where's Yun Shil now?
She's in a vineyard...
- in Anseong. - A vineyard?
- A vineyard? - A vineyard.
Hong Gi Pyo's mum works in Anseong.
- I've been there before. - That's good.
We need to go now.
Then we should go now.
- Sure we will. - Okay. Let's go.
I will throw some punches for friendship.
Hong Gi Pyo, you're so dead.
Lead the way!
That jerk.
This pork belly is awesome.
By the way, how long do we have to be on the guard here?
It's going to be cold after the sun goes down.
We should wait until Gi Pyo feels better.
Let's finish this.
- Cheers. - Cheers.
Please let me go.
Let me go home.
Just say that you would be with me again.
Then you can go to Seoul right now.
Don't be unreasonable.
I won't be with you again.
That's the last thing I want.
I beg of you.
Let's leave together.
I'm sick of being a mobster...
and I never felt honourable towards you.
I'll wash my hands of it all.
Give me one more chance.
I once escaped to an island to avoid getting caught...
and worked at sea for two months.
It's hard work, but it suited me well.
I'll quit the gang and work at sea.
Let's live a simple life together.
How many time must I say no?
I mean it this time. I'll change.
Forget about the past. Let's start over.
(Meesa Apparel)
Come in.
Sir, we have to repay the bank loans within 15 days.
Our current funds and...
this month's projected profits...
won't be enough to cover the amount.
You said we could manage somehow if we sold some land.
The economy is slow and no one is buying.
We might not even sell it at a give away price.
That bank president...
Do I have to meet that stubborn man again?
That's the only way, Sir.
Okay. Give him a call and set up a meeting.
Yes, Sir.
This is so annoying!
You've done business with us for years.
Why won't you give us an extension?
My Loan Screening Board reported that...
Meesa Apparel's business profits are decreasing and will likely...
end up in the red.
As a result, your stock prices are falling.
If I were to give you an extension...
my board could report me for breach of duty.
It's just a temporary crisis.
We have so many properties.
The report also mentioned that no one is willing to purchase them.
Your company was mentioned at this morning's board meeting.
How could you demand a perfectly sound company...
pay the debts so soon?
There is one solution.
I can extend your loans if you offer the majority shareholder's shares...
and your personal assets as collateral.
Show that much commitment and the investors will accept.
So...
you want me to risk my personal assets?
Where's Mum?
In her room.
Why are you home?
I have an urgent issue to discuss with her.
Mum, I'm coming in.
Mum.
Look.
Listen carefully to me and try not to be shocked.
The company's finances are an utter mess, okay?
I thought merging the warehouses...
and selling land would solve it,
but it didn't because the economy's so slow.
I offered the bank my, your and Hyo Won's...
shares, land and movable assets...
as collateral in exchange for...
an extension on the loans.
Are you crazy?
Who said you could do that?
Are you insane? Mad?
Mum. You can speak.
I can.
Congratulations.
Don't tell Hyo Won.
It's our secret.
What? Oh, okay.
Are you totally useless at running a company?
Why did you let things get this bad?
There's no need to get so upset.
It's because I spent too much on launching an outdoor line.
Once our profits go back up...
and we sell the land,
I'll repay the loans and get our collateral back.
The bank's just showing off and putting pressure on us.
Talk to the Legal Team and company lawyers.
Don't make the call yourself.
Don't you worry. I already looked into it.
It's the final and only option to maintain management.
Don't worry, Mum.
Don't you trust me?
Who am I?
I'm Min Hyo Sang, your son.
You have nothing to worry. Leave it to me.
Don't you think you should make up your mind?
How do you mean?
It's your fault that your mum lost the ability to speak.
Don't you think it's time to tell her that...
you'll break up with Tae Yang?
Your mum will feel much better...
and she'll be able to speak again.
Why is it my fault that she can't speak?
Whose fault is it if it isn't yours?
We'd have no problems if you hadn't married Hyo Sang.
What's done is done.
Stop being stubborn and do what's right.
I know it'll be hard...
but you should break up with Tae Yang.
That's the only way to heal your mum...
and set everything right within this household.
Why did you just laugh?
You're the root, the core, the beginning of this mess...
and you're slithering out of it like a mudfish.
As of today I'll change your nickname...
from Pooper to Mudfish.
I'm above her in rank. She should pretend to listen.
She has no manners at all.
It's so annoying.
The bank president met your brother.
In exchange for an extension he asked for...
the majority shareholder's shares, land and movable assets
Once the contract is signed,
inform Meesa's consortium partners...
of Meesa Apparel's current financial situation.
Also leak to the suppliers and construction companies...
that they might have difficulty getting paid.
Yes, I will do that.
You messed with me.
Now it's my turn.
Things will get back to normal if only Dong Jin were to come back.
Dong Jin. Stop playing house...
and come back to the place where you belong.
Is this it?
Are you sure this is it?
Yes. This is Gi Pyo's mother's vineyard.
Where is this rat?
Don't you smell something?
Why does a countryside farm smell so heavenly?
It smells like pork belly.
It is pork belly.
Let's follow the smell.
This way.
All that alcohol made me feel sleepy.
When do you think they'll be done talking?
They're taking longer than I thought.
Go inside and check.
What are we even doing here anyway?
Let me have one more shot.
Hey.
- Who are you? - Us?
We're the gentlemen of Wolgyesu Tailor Shop,
who came to save the abducted bride on her wedding day.
Where's Yun Shil?
She's in there, isn't she?
I thought you looked familiar. You're the tailor shop owner.
Answer me. Yun Shil is in there, isn't she?
She and our boss are talking, so don't make a ruckus, and leave.
What do you take me for?
- Move. - Hey, hey.
Step aside while we're being nice.
- Why you... - What? What?
- Look at them. - Forget this.
Good. I've been wanting to teach you a lesson anyway.
Today must be the day.
Hey!
Why you punk...
Are you okay?
Hey!
Our boss is... Hey!
- You punk. - Come on.
Watch where you put your foot.
You jerk.
- Are you okay? - You punks.
That's right. Good job.
Are you okay?
- Careful. - Darn it.
That's it. Good.
Good.
Careful.
How dare you steal our boss' wife?
It's cold out. Let's stop.
Dong Jin, go inside.
- Will you be okay? - We'll handle them. Go in.
Where do you think you're going?
Don't move. I got him!
Hold on. Stop it.
- Dong Jin! - Yun Shil.
What are you doing?
Don't come any closer.
Please, be rational, Hong Gi Pyo!
Rational?
How could someone who lost his wife be rational?
I wondered...
what would be the most fatal way to get revenge on the two of you.
I wondered if I should...
break your legs and make sure you never walk again...
or take Yun Shil somewhere no one would ever find her...
and separate her from the world,
but if I do,
you two would be that much more desperate for each other.
(Pesticide)
Making Yun Shil...
live with guilt for the rest of her life.
Making sure she can never smile again, even if she wants to.
That's the best revenge.
What are you talking about?
What are you doing?
- Hey! - Dong Jin.
Careful!
Don't come closer.
- What did you do to our boss? - It's okay.
Who's his guardian? Someone should come with him.
I'll go.
- What happened? - He's a trauma patient in his 30s.
The shelving fell and the items on it fell on him.
Okay.
Excuse me. Excuse me.
Can you hear me? Excuse me.
- Vitals. - His BP is 100 over 70.
Set up IV lines and execute a full drop.
Yes, doctor.
Are you his guardian?
Yes.
On first appearance, it looks like he's bleeding from the head...
and broke a few ribs,
so we'll need to run some tests.
We'll start examining him now.
Is it serious?
I suspect organ damage due to the external force,
but I can't say for sure until we run those tests.
Please push it...
so that he can get tested soon as a priority.
- Please take him. - Yes, doctor.
He'll be fine. Don't worry.
So, is he in critical condition?
We'll have to wait and see.
What a terrible man.
How could he do something so hideous and frightening?
I was in shock, too.
I still cringe at the thought.
What's Dong Jin doing?
Yun Shil is in shock,
so he's trying to calm her down.
How could a human being do such a thing?
I'm still in shock myself.
What is all of this?
(Temporarily Closed)
It's still closed.
I wonder if something's up.
Sun Nyeo.
How have you been?
You closed the bakery for days. Is something wrong?
My mother-in-law is sick, so I was with her.
Is she very sick?
Yes. She has stomach cancer.
Oh, my gosh.
My father-in-law passed away three years ago,
so she's been living alone.
I think I should go down and take care of her.
What about the bakery?
A friend will be running it for the time being.
We just became friends.
I'm so sad.
I know.
Poor Sam Do.
He'll be sick from a heart ache after losing his first love.
Stop calling me that.
What about you?
Me? I'd be sad but relieved.
More relieved or sadder?
Let's see.
I'd say sadness would be 4,
and relief would be 6.
Am I too honest?
That's your charm.
Come over before you leave. Let me cook for you.
I will.
Hyo Won.
Darling.
Were you waiting for me?
You should have called.
I knew you'd be too busy.
I refrained myself from causing you even more stress.
Aren't I so nice?
Yes.
That was considerate of you. I'm impressed.
Dong Jin must have been really upset.
Yes.
Dong Jin and Yun Shil both look miserable.
Love is so difficult.
Yes, indeed.
You haven't had dinner?
Why?
I feel like it's all my fault...
because Mum's lying in bed and unable to talk.
I couldn't possibly eat anything.
I told you she'll get better soon. Try to be patient.
You know how talkative my mother is.
Seeing someone so talkative with her mouth shut...
unable to say a word,
in a daze as if she's not all there,
my heart aches.
It's so painful.
It's all my fault.
I'll do my best to change her mind.
How is that your fault?
You've done nothing wrong.
Let's have dinner and then go see your mother.
If my mother sees you,
I'm sure she'll look at you disapprovingly and throw her pillow.
If that will make her feel better
and start to speak again, it'll be worth it.
Let's go.
Are you actually trying to provoke Mother?
How could you bring Kang Tae Yang here again?
- You're so selfish. - What did you say?
Why do you think my mother's sick?
Look at you blaming everything on Tae Yang...
and acting innocent like you had no part in it.
Excuse me?
Hyo Won. That's enough. Let's just go in to see your mother.
All right.
So Lawyer Choi, what you're saying is...
we won't be at risk even if we offer a security, right?
It doesn't mean there won't be any risks,
but I've made sure that management rights be maintained,
It'll work as a safety device.
I see.
I saw to it that mortgage set ups be cancelled when the loan is repaid.
So we should repay the loan after disposing real estate assets.
How on earth did the company end up like this?
I've come to see you, Mother.
Don't be like that, Mum.
Tae Yang brought some roasted chestnuts for you.
Try some while they're still warm.
What are you doing, Mum?
Calm down.
What's wrong? Calm down.
My goodness. What's going on?
Mother needs absolute rest,
so both of you leave this instant.
Quickly.
Tae Yang. Let's leave for now.
I'll return at a better time. I hope you can get some rest.
If you tell them not to come,
they should obey your order.
Are they trying to be rebellious?
I don't understand what their intention is by coming every day.
I'll tell Hyo Sang to tell them not to come,
so don't get too upset and have your herbal medicine.
Goodness!
What was that for, Mother?
You want me to leave as well?
All right, all right. I'm leaving.
I should have accepted Tae Yang as my son-in-law...
rather than letting that cunning girl join our family.
Oh, dear.
I've cut my own throat.
It's me, Dong Sook.
Hyo Joo.
No. Wait.
You're not my sister-in-law anymore.
You're hurting my feelings.
I heard Dong Jin's wedding was called off today.
That means our relationship is still valid.
Words sure spread quickly.
Where did you hear about Dong Jin's wedding from?
I heard about it by chance.
By the way, why did the bride run away?
She didn't run away. She was kidnapped.
She was kidnapped before she got to the wedding so it was cancelled.
I've never seen such chaos.
Wait. You called to ask that?
I called because I was worried about Mother and Father.
I'm sure they were shocked.
Why do I get the feeling that you're not all that worried?
Why do you always treat me with hostility?
Tell Mother and Father I'll be visiting them soon.
I'll let you get some rest.
Why be so coy when you only called to find out about the wedding?
How inconsiderate.
If you're done getting ready, let's get going. We might be late.
All right. Let's go.
By the way, Sung Jun...
You don't think this could be another fraud, do you?
I may have been swindled once but not twice.
Now, I can tell if it's a fraud or not.
Don't worry and just trust me.
All right.
Shall we go?
(Kim Seong Ho, WN Entertainment)
I'm Director of the Music Operation Team at WN Entertainment.
My name is Kim Seong Ho.
I see.
But why would a big agency like WN want to sign me?
Tae Pyung has taken an upturn in popularity these days,
so many agencies are contacting us to sign contracts with them.
So we should be careful not to act hastily in signing with anyone.
If you see what we're offering,
I'm sure there won't be much to worry about.
Mr. Oh. Please show them the contract.
(Contract)
(Exclusive Management Contract)
"Funds needed for not only producing albums..."
"but in pursuing a career will be fully provided by the agency."
I won't need to invest my own money when producing albums?
Our CEO...
promises his utmost support so that artists can pursue...
their career in the best environment possible.
We never demand investments.
Really?
Our CEO has strictly ordered that...
we fully support you with anything needed when producing an album...
including a vehicle, stylist and manager.
A strict order?
You must be hungry. Come help yourself.
It's been a long time since I brawled with bad guys.
I'm feeling hungry.
Those thugs must have been strong. You're amazing.
How did you knock out all of them...
and make a surprise attack at the warehouse...
and rescue Yun Shil?
I'm the terminator of Hyoja-dong, Bae Sam Do.
Those bullies are a piece of cake.
I just threw a punch...
and three of them went down on their knees.
Right.
There were also Dong Jin, Tae Pyung and Tae Yang.
Let's be honest. They're not fighters.
I fought against three or four of them by myself...
and rescued Yun Shil.
It's been a while since you put those muscles to good use.
By the way, Honey...
Young Eun is moving to Cheonan.
Is Young Eun moving?
Her mother-in-law is living alone and not well.
Young Eun is going to there to look after her.
Her friend will take care of the bakery in the meanwhile.
I see.
Why? Did you lose your appetite...
hearing that Young Eun is moving?
What? No way. This is delicious.
Would you like a drink?
No, thanks.
Your first love Young Eun is moving.
You need to drink some soju on a day like this.
Young Eun's moving...
has nothing to do with my drinking soju.
You must be upset...
at least by the slightest.
I'm not upset...
even by the slightest.
Really?
Still, why don't you have just one glass?
I'm feeling tipsy.
Look at you pretending to be cool with it.
She'll come back once her mother-in-law gets better.
Don't be too upset.
Who's upset?
I'm not upset at all.
Are you crying?
No, right?
That's good.
Would you like another drink?
Enjoy.
Eat up.
You haven't eaten anything all day.
I'm sorry, Dong Jin.
We should be in Jeju island...
with Mother and Father by now.
It's my fault.
It's not your fault, so don't be sorry.
Eat up.
You have to finish all of it.
That way, you can power through the rest of today.
Here you go.
I like it when you eat well.
(Sae Ma Eum Hospital)
After Hong Gi Pyo's mum gets here, you have to come home with me.
Would it be all right if I do so?
Of course.
It's not your fault. Don't feel guilty about it.
Gi Pyo. My son!
You witch!
You finally ruined my one and only son.
Stop it.
She did nothing wrong.
Of course she did.
My son gave her his kidney.
That alone is enraging.
Now, he's about to die because of her.
If something happens to Gi Pyo,
I'll kill you!
I said that's enough.
She's a foul witch.
But you're even worse to seduce someone else's wife.
What are you going to do about Gi Pyo?
Bring him back!
- What are you going to do? - Let go of him.
My goodness.
Mother.
Mother, wake up.
The patient went into shock...
due to sudden mental stress.
The test results show that it's nothing serious,
but she can fall into shock again...
if she does not get rest.
The guardian should stay with the patient.
Yes, I'll do so.
Lee Dong Jin and Na Yun Shil's wedding got cancelled.
Na Yun Shil is in the hospital with Hong Gi Pyo's mum.
Good work, Mr Hwang.
(Sae Ma Eum Hospital)
I don't think it's right for me to go back like this.
I told you it's not your fault.
You did everything you can do...
for two of them.
I also don't want to think that it wasn't my fault.
But, I can't deny that...
Gi Pyo lost a lot because of me.
That's the consequences he has to deal with.
You didn't want this to happen.
I can't begin to express...
how sorry I am.
If I go like this...
I wouldn't feel comfortable to be with you.
So,
do you want to stay here?
I'm really sorry.
I don't want hear that anymore.
So let's go home with me.
Today...
was our wedding day.
- Because of me... - I've told you it's not your fault.
Still you want to stay here. Does that mean...
that he's more important to you than me?
You know it's not like that. Why are you being unreasonable?
No, I don't know.
I want to think only about myself from now on.
Let's go home now.
Gi Pyo's mum collapsed. How can I ignore her?
The doctor told me to stay with her.
I'm saying I don't want you to.
Do you have to be so stubborn until the end?
I'm sorry.
(The Gentlemen of Wolgyesu Tailor Shop)
What do you mean she's in the hospital?
Is Yun Shil out of her mind?
Why is she staying at the hospital for him?
- She ran away from home? - Are they going to...
live together or something?
My credit card is suspended? That can't be.
Is this really Hong Gi Pyo's picture?
I'm begging you like this. Please save Gi Pyo.
What happened to Dong Jin and Yun Shil?
I wanted to be the most beautiful bride in the world...
for Dong Jin.
Na Yun Shil, do you get it now?
That's where you belong. Beside Hong Gi Pyo.