(The following content may not be suitable for viewers under 15.)
(Viewer discretion is advised.)
Today...
was our wedding day.
And you want to...
stay with Gi Pyo?
- Because of me... - I've told you it's not your fault.
Still you want to stay here. Does that mean...
that he's more important to you than me?
You know it's not like that. Why are you being unreasonable?
No. I don't know.
I want to think only about myself from now on.
Let's go home now.
Gi Pyo's mum collapsed. How can I ignore her?
The doctor told me to stay with her.
I'm saying I don't want you to.
Do you have to be so stubborn until the end?
I'm sorry.
(Operating Room)
(Episode 46)
You're still here.
I repaired the ruptured intestine.
Other than that,
we were concerned about the head trauma,
but fortunately, it wasn't deep.
Based on the CT scan,
the ruptured intestine was the only injury.
We'll keep him under observation.
Thank you, Doctor.
- Thank you. - Sure.
- Wait. - Yes?
Where are you taking him?
To the intensive care unit.
The intensive care unit?
Yes.
- Take him. - Okay.
Bye.
Where's Yun Shil?
Gi Pyo's mother fainted.
She's at the hospital.
Why should she care about them?
Why should Yun Shil stay and take care of them?
She can't just leave them both knowing that someone collapsed.
He got us in this mess...
and she wants to stay with him?
Has Yun Shil lost her mind?
- Sorry, Mum. - You don't have to apologise.
I gave my consent to the marriage knowing that this would happen.
I should be responsible.
He's been through a lot today. Don't berate him too much.
Let's go and get some rest. We can talk later.
- Have you eaten? - Yes.
This is such an embarrassment.
- I'm sorry, Dad. - Try to understand.
Yun Shil's kind-hearted and generous.
When she sees someone in need or trouble,
she just can't ignore them, that's why.
I try to understand...
but I keep getting angry.
The man who loved her for years is now in hospital...
and now his mother also fainted.
I'm sure that...
Yun Shil just can't turn away from them.
You can vent your anger at least,
but she has no one to turn to.
Do what you did until now...
and be a man and look out for her.
Comfort her.
(Lee Dong Jin and Na Yun Shil)
Are you asleep?
No.
Is this the new bed?
It's nice and bouncy.
Are you okay?
- Yes, of course. - You must feel downcast.
Come upstairs for a drink.
No thanks.
You can't enjoy your first night without your bride.
We'll comfort you with a few drinks.
- But... - Come along.
Just look at the colour. Isn't it great?
It's perfectly cooked.
Hello.
I invited myself.
I called our brothers in case Dong Jin was in a funk.
Thanks for helping out today.
I was too preoccupied to thank you earlier.
There's no need to thank us.
We're brothers, so forget about formalities.
- Let's all sit. - Sure.
Sit.
Here comes the stew.
Thanks.
Hi, Dong Jin.
You must've been really stressed.
You've lost weight in just a day.
Sorry, Dong Sook, Sun Nyeo.
Why should you apologise?
That was brazen of him.
How dare he even kidnap the bride on her wedding day?
Jerks like that should be left to suffer with really...
hard and bloody stools.
- Hard and bloody stools... - Sun Nyeo.
We're trying to eat here.
I just lost my appetite.
My bad. I got just a bit carried away.
Why isn't Yun Shil with you?
She's at the hospital.
The hospital? Why?
Is she at the hospital Gi Pyo was admitted to?
It was an emergency.
I don't care if it is.
Who cares if he lives or dies?
What business does she have with him?
Honey, don't get too excited.
How can I not get excited?
The wedding was in a mess because of them.
Why does she care whether he dies or not?
Does she still have feelings for him?
Gosh, seriously. What are you talking about now?
They say that hateful passion lasts longer than love.
Unlike how Yun Shil talks about him, she might actually...
- still have feelings for... - Stop.
Ladies, please leave.
- Sorry? - Pardon?
There's something we need...
to talk about man to man, so get up and leave, please.
What secret will you talk about behind our backs?
If I tell you, it's no longer a secret.
Please don't mind us and leave us alone.
Please, Honey. There's a bunch of things we need to talk about.
- Okay. - Okay.
- Thanks for the food. - No problem. Let's have a drink.
Guys, let's drink, too.
- Cheers. - Cheers.
It's a little embarrassing to compliment ourselves,
but the four of us were so amazing today.
It was almost like "Mission Impossible".
My flying kicks knocked those punks out like this.
I felt like I was Tom Cruise.
When did you do flying kicks?
I guess you didn't see it because I was too fast.
Following the flying kick, I gave them a double side kick...
and knocked them straight out.
That's what got them.
Dong Jin. You saw that, right?
Sorry? Well, I'm not sure.
Tae Pyung, you're a liar.
Liar? Watch yourself!
We can enjoy pork belly and soju like this because they were drunk.
If they weren't, we could've been the ones at the hospital now.
Gosh, that fool. He's such a downer.
He doesn't understand how men's world works.
He's ruining the taste of this soju.
- I'm sorry. - Anyhow, good work today, everyone.
Thanks to you guys, I could save Yun Shil.
How's that guy, Hong Gi Pyo?
I don't think he has gained his consciousness yet.
Gosh, love is so tough.
It makes so many people's lives difficult.
Are you all right?
- Why wouldn't I be? - You had...
a crazy fight with Sun Nyeo because of your first love.
To be exact, that wasn't really a fight. I almost...
died in Sun Nyeo's hands.
After meeting my first love again, I realised that no man...
should run into his first love again in his life.
Tae Pyung. You should be careful, too.
Don't worry. I'd never run into my first love again.
Tae Yang.
How's your love life going after dumping Da Jeong?
Not well. Hyo Won's mum threw roasted chestnuts at me today.
- Roasted chestnuts? - Roasted chestnuts?
She hasn't been in the greatest mood these days,
so I bought some roasted chestnuts for her to win some points,
but she threw them all at me.
I took a quick look at her the other day, and she was very charismatic.
I could tell that she has a bit of a temper.
Goodness, none of us has it easy.
It must hurt to have chestnuts thrown at you.
Were they peeled or not?
- They weren't peeled. - Goodness.
Let's drink up.
(Ms Shiny Eyes)
I know, right?
Let me fill your glass.
The customer you're calling is unavailable at the moment.
Please leave a message after the tone.
He must be really mad at me.
Are you all right?
Where's Gi Pyo?
Where is my son?
Gi Pyo!
Please calm down. You might faint again if you get worked up.
What? Calm down?
How can I calm down when my son is hovering between life and death?
Where is he?
Where is Gi Pyo now?
He was moved to the intensive care unit.
Intensive care unit?
Please calm down.
I have to see my son. Take me to the intensive care unit.
Lead the way!
(Intensive Care Unit)
You aren't allowed in here, Ma'am.
My son is in there. I'd like to see him.
You can only see him during designated visiting hours.
Please read the sign by the entrance and come back during the hours.
Please let me see him for a few seconds.
I fainted all of a sudden,
so I couldn't see my son.
I'm sorry. Please come back during the visiting hours.
The universe is just heartless.
He went through such a hard time in jail...
and got out just a few days ago.
Why does his life have to hang by a thread?
Gi Pyo, I'm going to die with you if you don't survive this.
The doctor said that you might faint again if you aren't careful.
Please calm down.
Gi Pyo. Gosh, Gi Pyo.
Gi Pyo...
Ma'am.
Are you okay?
Why did you let that happen to Gi Pyo? Where have you guys been?
You guys are so useless.
We were hungry, so we went to eat pork belly over some soju.
We're sorry.
It's all Yun Shil's fault.
If you go back to that jerk at the tailor shop after this,
both you and that jerk...
will die in our hands.
Do you understand?
Why are you doing this to me?
You had no idea what was happening to Gi Pyo and just got beaten up.
How dare you blabber away!
You punks love to look menacing,
but you're actually completely useless.
Just leave!
Please. You're being too harsh on us.
We've done our best to serve Gi Pyo over the years.
Then why is he bedridden like that right now? Tell me!
This is exactly why I told him to stay away from stupid guys like you.
Get lost.
- Guys, let's go. - Okay.
You stupid jerks. Goodness.
Yun Shil.
Those blokes must have been harassing you.
That's probably why you fell for the owner of the tailor shop.
Listen, Yun Shil.
Gi Pyo is different from those ignorant and rude jerks.
I mean, he's bedridden like that because he risked his life twice...
for the woman he loves.
I'm sorry, Mother.
Don't. Please don't apologise to me.
I beg you.
I promise I won't be mean to you.
I'll treat you like my own daughter, so please save Gi Pyo's life.
Even if he survives this, he'll strangle himself...
or drug himself to death if you tell him that you want to end it.
Please don't do this. This won't change anything.
If you leave Gi Pyo, he'll die.
If he dies, I'm going to die with him as well.
Two people's lives depend on you.
Hyo Won needs to wave the white flag.
Only then, I can put an end to acting like I have aphasia.
I'm worried about the company, too.
I can't really afford to be stuck at home like this now.
Mum, I'm coming in.
I want to sleep beside you tonight.
Repeat after me, okay?
A, b, c, d,
e, f and g.
I know it's hard, but you have to keep practising.
What if you really forget how to talk?
Repeat after me.
A, b, c, d,
e, f and g.
Mum, I'm so sorry...
I'm really sorry, Mum...
You can't even talk because of me.
My poor mum.
Mum, I'm so sorry.
Mum...
Mum.
What can I do to help you talk again?
What should I do to help you start talking again?
(Kang Tae Yang)
(Break up with Kang Tae Yang.)
Do you think you can speak again...
if I break up with Tae Yang?
I'm sorry, Mum.
I can do anything except this.
I can never do this.
I'm sorry, Mum.
It hurts, Mum.
Do you want me to get out?
I see.
I'll go. Calm down, Mum.
You're such a good actress.
You deserve the Academy Best Actress Award.
She is so stubborn.
Even when her mum can't speak for many days,
she doesn't say that she would break up with Kang Tae Yang.
Mum, Hyo Won wouldn't say such a thing.
Only you would keep feeling heavy and infuriated.
- You should stop acting now. - So why did you...
marry Choi Ji Yun and make this kind of trouble?
What are you talking about?
If only I had known earlier,
I would have separated you and Choi Ji Yun.
So do you mean...
it would have been better if you accepted Kang Tae Yang, not Ji Yun?
Do you mean that?
Frankly speaking,
I like Kang Tae Yang...
more than Ji Yun.
Wake up, Mum!
Kang Tae Yang is such a jerk.
He had a grudge against Ji Yun,
so he intentionally approached to Hyo Won.
My goodness.
How is the company now?
Will you bring that oriental medicine to Mum?
Right, Hyo Won.
Give it to me. I'll bring it to Mum.
She suffers so much for love.
You should have focused on suits.
Why did you launch outdoor look and make such a trouble?
Did I know that things will turn out this way?
Is that Mum's voice?
No, Mum.
As I promised some revenue to major shareholders,
I needed to make a new revenue model.
Mum agreed to it,
and told me to work with Hyo Won. Why are you doing this now?
Still, you should have done it within the range...
that the company can withstand.
Mum, when we launch a new line,
we need a full scale advertisement in the early stage...
to draw attention for the new brand.
It won't be helpful at all if we advertise...
in a small scale.
I'm doing my best myself.
I'm so tired.
It's not that I have many children.
I only have two children,
and they make me worry in turn.
Mum,
- you can speak well. - Well,
that's, Hyo Won...
Then,
have you been lying to me all along?
Well, that's...
it's not like that.
Listen to me.
Hyo Won.
I didn't know that. I was so worried.
Please.
Hyo Won.
Why did you keep talking to me and make this happen?
Why do you blame me every time something happens?
Hyo Won, Hyo Won!
Goodness.
What are you doing now?
I'm so disappointed with you.
It's natural that you got it wrong.
I just got to speak again right before you came.
After you came out of my room,
Hyo Sang came in and then I suddenly...
could speak again.
- It's a lie. - No, it isn't.
It's not a lie. It's true. You can ask Hyo Sang.
Do you know how much I was troubled all along?
How can you do this to me?
If only you said you would break up with Kang Tae Yang earlier,
things would not have turned out like this.
I can never break up with Tae Yang if you act like this.
- Where are you going? - It's none of your business.
- Are you going to Kang Tae Yang? - Never mind.
Hey, Min Hyo Won!
Stop right there!
Hyo Won, Hyo Won!
- Where are you going, Hyo Won? - Hold her so that she can't go out!
- Hold her now! - All right.
Hold her.
Get out of my way.
Mother is telling me to stop you.
- You can't go. - Can't you imagine...
why I even acted?
So, give up on Kang Tae Yang.
I said I would never give up on him.
Is Kang Tae Yang more important to you than your mum who gave...
birth to you and your own brother?
I'm not sure about that,
but I can't live if I break up with Tae Yang.
How can you say such a thing in front of Mother, Hyo Won?
All right.
You can go.
You'll realise how precious I am after having a hard time outside.
Just let her leave. Get her out of the house.
What if she shacks up with Kang Tae Yang, Mother?
Kang Tae Yang would never do such a thing.
He's an upright person.
He would never shack up without the consent from parents.
She favours Tae Yang so much.
By the way, she can speak now.
Congratulations, Mother!
I'm tired.
It was such a long day.
No, I shouldn't do this.
I should lie down on this bed with Ms Shiny Eyes.
My shoulder aches.
(Ms Shiny Eyes)
(Mr Pretty Eyes)
The phone has been turned off. Please leave a message.
it's me, Dong Jin.
Are you back home all right?
I wanted to be...
the most beautiful bride...
and be with you.
I'm sorry I couldn't do that.
You must have been troubled because of me.
I'm really sorry...
that I insisted staying here.
(Intensive Care Unit)
How is Hong Gi Pyo's condition?
Wait a minute.
(Intensive Care Unit)
He's not in a serious condition, but he still hasn't woken up yet.
His doctor says he will wait and see.
You can see him if you come on visiting hours.
I see.
It's not that there's a special reason.
My daughter-in-law...
was on her way from the beauty salon after her bridal make up...
and then she had a car accident.
No, no.
It was not a serious accident. It was just a little fender bender.
Of course.
She went to the hospital for treatment and came home.
All right.
You came all the way for us.
I'm sorry. All right.
Talk to you later.
What a shame.
It's not a shame.
They all think the bride got cold feet.
Dong Jin ended up looking like a fool.
All sorts of things happen to all sorts of people.
Don't take it too seriously.
You're so laid back.
I bet you'll live a very long time.
- Don't do that. - Can you stay still?
What's wrong?
You're tickling me.
You shouldn't move. Hold still.
- This is too much. - This is so annoying.
- Get the light. - Okay.
I know they're newlyweds but this is too much.
They aren't the only people here. They're so inconsiderate.
We were newlyweds once, too, you know.
I can't believe they get up to no good every night.
If they want to get some action, they should at least keep quiet.
I bet the whole neighbourhood knows what they're doing.
That's what I'm saying. It's infuriating.
Honey.
What?
Shall we get some action?
What action?
That action.
No. I'm tired.
You can't be that tired. You don't even work anymore.
Let's do our homework.
Shall we?
- Get the light. - Okay.
We haven't done this in a while.
I'm so happy.
Hold me tighter, Mr Sam Do.
Come here, Sun Nyeo.
Let's just sleep.
Why?
We haven't done this in so long that...
it feels awkward and weird.
Let's sleep.
Okay, then.
Sun Nyeo, can you scratch my back?
- Where? - Right there.
- Here? - A bit lower.
That feels so good.
Your scratching my back feels much better than doing homework.
That's enough, thanks.
Can you scratch my back now?
- I can't reach. - Where?
- Here? - Lower.
I'm so sleepy.
Scratch harder.
Put your hand inside.
Will she really move in with him?
No way.
I don't trust my daughter...
but Tae Yang would never do that.
Hello, Mother. Can you speak now?
A while ago... No.
A bit before a while ago...
I got my voice back.
That's great news. Congratulations.
Don't congratulate me. Put Hyo Won on.
Hyo Won?
- She isn't there? - No.
Where did she go?
She isn't at home?
She left home.
- She packed a suitcase and left. - She did what?
Hello, honey.
Hyo Won, did you leave home?
Is it my mum?
I won't come home until you let me date Tae Yang.
Aren't you being a bit too rash?
You crossed the line first.
How could you lie about not being able to speak?
Can't you come home first?
Let me explain.
You told me to leave.
Forget about it.
I won't go home...
- until you let me... - If you keep on being so bratty,
I will delete your name from the family registry!
I didn't know having a second house could be such a good thing.
I can leave home without a worry.
Even if your mum upset you,
you shouldn't have left. Go back right now.
- I don't want to. - Hyo Won.
How could a mum deceive her own daughter like that?
I had no idea.
You don't know how worried and scared I was.
For a short while,
a very short while,
I wondered if I really should break up with you.
Okay.
Don't force me to go home.
Whatever happens, I'll fight until she gives her consent.
(Saemaeum Hospital)
I said it's not your fault.
You did more than enough for those two.
I want to think it's not my fault, like you say,
but I can't deny that Gi Pyo lost a lot because of me.
That was his choice to make.
You didn't want any of that.
I wronged him in so many ways.
I don't know what to apologise for first.
I'm back.
I'm sorry, Dong Jin.
Hello.
Hello, Mother.
Come on inside.
I'm sorry for causing so much trouble.
You went through much more than we did.
Were you hurt?
No.
Mother, you must have been very shocked.
I was shocked beyond belief.
What upsets me even more is that you didn't come home...
to look after the fool who caused this mess.
Dong Jin said she had no choice...
because both mother and son were unconscious.
She had a long day and night. Let's not upset her even more.
I'm sorry.
I can do nothing but apologise to you both.
Listen carefully, Yun Shil.
If you go to the hospital once more,
I'll consider that you have turned against us.
I mean that.
Okay.
You had a long day. You can go.
I'm really sorry.
Are you off to work?
I was worried because you didn't answer your calls last night.
I'm not a concern of yours.
Why were you worried?
You can't say that.
You know how important and precious you are to me.
I thought I was, but yesterday made me rethink all that.
I'm sorry about that. Are you very angry?
You did something knowing I'd be angry,
so why bother apologising?
You don't care about me, so do whatever you want from now on.
Dong Jin.
I shouldn't have given in so easily...
knowing something like this would happen.
Why do you keep bringing up the past?
I can't stand it. It's so infuriating.
I'm glad to hear that no one got hurt,
but what's going to happen to Mr Lee and Yun Shil now?
They never had a wedding,
so they're technically not married.
Exactly. I'm wondering the same thing.
They're almost like a married couple,
but we can't say that they're married.
I wonder if they've done their homework yet.
Hey, Dong Jin.
- Hi, you're early today. - Yes.
Have you heard from Yun Shil?
I saw her getting home as I was heading out.
You should've waited for her to come with her.
Oh, right. She's probably not in the shape to come back to work yet.
I'm meeting with Gianni later today. I should go through the paperwork.
All right.
It looks like he's very angry.
I know. He's being so cold even to us.
Gosh, that fool.
(You have a new voicemail. Press the call button to listen to it.)
It's me, Dong Jin.
Did you get home safely?
Today,
I wanted to be the most beautiful bride in the world...
and be with you.
I'm sorry I couldn't do that.
I know how distressed you must have been because of me.
I'm so sorry that I was stubborn...
about staying here.
If I turn a blind eye to him...
and something happens to him,
I didn't think I could thoroughly enjoy our happiness together.
I did it for myself.
I'm going to run to you...
and apologise as soon as the sun comes up,
so I hope you don't get too upset about this.
Sweet dreams.
You must have been waiting for me because you knew I was coming.
You didn't even eat breakfast.
I bought toast for you.
Have a bite.
I asked them to fill it with special ingredients inside.
I don't have any appetite.
Come on. Just take a bite.
If you try a bite, it'll change your mind.
I have a lot of documents to go through. Let me focus on work.
Then eat while you get your work done.
(Fabric Inventory)
It must have been so scary for you.
- Did you get any injuries? - No, I'm fine.
Master Bae, thank you for yesterday.
I just did what I had to do. You don't need to thank me.
By the way, I think Dong Jin is mad.
He drank a lot last night.
I know. I understand why he's mad.
It's all my fault.
You're too nice for your own good.
Why do you even care about the guy who's been harassing you?
How can you ditch your husband to stay at the hospital for that jerk?
Gosh, you're seriously... I don't get you.
Since my darling doesn't seem to be in the greatest mood today,
I'm going to add an extra spoonful of sugar.
Who's your darling?
What do you think?
Mr Lee Dong Jin who's right beside me now.
Does the coffee taste good?
It's too sweet.
Sweet things make you feel better.
This'll help you come back to being my husband who has a heart...
that's as broad as the sky and as deep as the ocean,
so please drink all of it.
Who says that my heart is like the sky and ocean?
I'm not that broad-minded.
You are. My husband is...
very a broad-minded and understanding person.
I'm an extremely narrow-minded and jealous person.
I've been just putting on a show to impress you.
Do you see how I'm all mad at you now?
This is how I really am.
I just thought that you have...
forgiven me because you had...
the toast and coffee and you're talking to me like this now.
Are you still mad at me?
I'm not that easy.
Come on. Please go easy on me.
I'm always easy with you, you know.
Goodness.
You think you're easy?
Do you never listen to me and you're so bullheaded.
I'm sorry.
Gi Pyo's mum also collapsed yesterday,
so I had no choice.
I do understand,
but don't do that again.
Okay. I won't visit Gi Pyo...
without your permission.
No, I won't even bring up his name.
You're sure, right?
I thought about it all night,
and I think it's the right thing to do.
Here, promise me.
All right, we made a pinky promise.
We're even swearing on our rings.
If you break this promise,
I'll be so grumpy.
I'm going to be extremely difficult.
All right.
Good.
It's so sweet.
I wanted to have a meal with you.
I'm really sad that you have to move away so suddenly like this.
My mother-in-law's health is deteriorating, so I have no choice.
I feel bad that you have to go through this.
Honey, say something.
Seung Woo. You're a strong boy,
so you have to be good to your mum and grandma, okay?
- Okay. - Come here.
I'm going to be generous.
You have to say goodbye to your first love.
You should give her a big hug as a farewell.
What are you talking about now?
Just do it when I'm giving you a chance.
You'll regret it later otherwise.
Thanks for everything, Sam Do.
Feel free to call us whenever you feel down or stressed out.
Don't forget that both Sam Do and I are always on your side.
Thanks, Sun Nyeo.
The taxi is here.
- I'll get going first. - Sure.
- Bye. - Seung Woo, say goodbye.
- Goodbye. - All right, have a safe journey.
- I should get going now. - All right.
You can cry if you want to.
What are you talking about?
I feel bad for her.
She's still young, but she lost her husband,
and she now has to look after her ill mother-in-law.
She lost her parents at an early age...
and went through so much while growing up as an orphan.
I thought she could finally be happy with her husband, but...
Gosh, I feel so bad for her.
You're probably the only man in the entire Korea who cries...
in front of his wife because he feels bad about his first love.
Be grateful that you have such an understanding wife. Come here.
(Sung Tae Pyung)
Welcome to WN Entertainment.
You're our family now.
Thank you for allowing me to work under such favourable conditions.
We'd love to meet the CEO and thank him in person.
Our CEO is abroad at the moment due to a business trip.
We'll definitely arrange something soon.
Thank you.
- Shall we go now? - Shall we?
Goodbye.
I'd love to take you both out for soju when you're available.
That sounds good.
Please go ahead.
Why are you giving me this?
Shall I drive?
This is your car, Tae Pyung.
- Excuse me? - Excuse me?
This is my car?
Yes. This is your car.
Wasn't it in the contract? We said we'd provide you a car.
That didn't mean only on days when I have a schedule?
We told you.
Our CEO makes sure that his artists can work in the best environment.
He is the type that gives full support to his artists.
But still, he's doing so much for us.
We don't know how we should react to this.
This credit card has been suspended.
What do you mean suspended? That can't be possible.
- Please try it again. - All right.
It's not working.
One moment, please.
Hello?
Mum. Did you have my credit card suspended?
- Yes. - How could you do that?
How could you do that without telling me?
When you run away, that means you would cut off relations with me.
- Why would you use my money? - You're being so mean.
If you choose to act out like that, I'm going to do just the same.
An eye for an eye and a tooth for a tooth.
Okay. I understand you.
Also, exactly one hour from now,
I'll be taking away your car.
- Are you going to take my car, too? - Of course.
To be honest, I would even like to take all your clothes,
but I'm stopping myself.
Mum!
What!
Hyo Won. What's wrong?
Honey.
Mum had my credit card suspended.
She says she's also going to take away my car, too.
So stop acting stubborn and go back home.
No. I'm going to prove to Mum...
that I can do well on my own without her help.
Gosh. This war between mother and daughter is incredible.
By the way, did you do well on your second exam?
Yes.
Fortunately, it was a question I knew. I think I answered well.
Then does this mean you'll become a teacher soon?
It's too early to count the chickens before they're hatched.
We'll have wait and see.
I'll pay for these.
She's taken my credit card and now my car.
I'm penniless now.
(CEO Min Hyo Sang)
Yes?
- There's been a problem. - What is it this time?
The partners of our shopping complex have stopped all investments.
What are you talking about?
I'll know the details when the documents arrive.
They must have found out that you bet all your money...
as security to extend time for the loan repayment.
I think they have doubts on proceeding the project.
That deal can be closed...
as soon as we sell property.
How did they know? That's classified information between the bank and us.
I don't know, Sir.
Then go call the bank and find out.
Bring me the documents as soon as they get here.
Yes, Sir.
Gosh, it's like one obstacle after another.
Why is this all happening to me?
The consortium partners have suspended all investments?
What about the subcontractors?
Since Meesa Apparel is managing the business,
I heard they're all heading to Meesa to demand construction costs.
That's good news.
Let me know as soon as you get updates.
Let's just say you had a bad dream.
Just get over it and wake up, Gi Pyo.
I'm so worried about you. You're breaking my heart.
Oh goodness. Who is this?
What brings you here, Board President?
You must be very worried.
It's beyond words how worried I am.
I can't tell you how worried I am.
I can't imagine.
How unfair he must have thought?
I get so upset whenever I think about it.
How about your daughter-in-law?
Where is she while you're here looking after your son?
She was here last night,
but she left as soon as the sun came up.
But your daughter-in-law must look after him.
He can't express it,
but I'm sure he's waiting for her even if he's unconscious.
Do you think so, too?
Okay. Everything looks reasonable.
I'm glad you're satisfied with the contract.
Please let me know if there're any modifications you'd like to make...
before we finalise the contract.
Sure. Let's sign the final contract next week.
And also, I drew up the press releases myself.
That's great. Please also send me the Korean translations...
so I can confirm that it properly defines Tonelli's position as well.
Okay, I will. Thank you, Gianni.
Dong Jin. No, CEO Lee.
- The talk went well, right? - Yes, of course.
I'm looking forward to seeing you in action, Mr Bae.
What did he just say?
He said he has high expectations for you, Master Bae.
For me?
Are you crazy? No, wait.
I'm fine, thank you.
All right. I better get going. I've got an interview to do,
but let's stay in touch.
Okay. Let's go.
- Thank you. - Goodbye.
Then does this mean Wolgyesu Tailor Shop...
and Tonelli, the Italian company,
will be making suits together?
I think that's what's going to happen.
Our CEO is truly amazing.
His business acumen is unbelievable.
I agree. I think I met...
the perfect husband.
Did you just see her?
I thought Dong Jin was the fool,
but now that I see it, so is Yun Shil.
It might be because this car's so nice,
I just put my foot on the accelerator and it moves smoothly.
About the CEO...
I wonder how wealthy he his to be supporting you like this.
It might not be because he has a lot of money.
I'm sure it's because he likes my music.
We musicians have such thing as pure passion.
I see Dad over there.
Pull over, Sung Joon.
You're right. Okay.
Dad.
Dad. Dad.
I wonder what's wrong with Dad? He ignored me.
- Maybe he didn't see you. - I waved both hands.
Maybe he didn't notice because he was lost in his thoughts.
Father.
What brings you here?
Dong Sook and I were going for a drive when we noticed you.
How could you just go without noticing your daughter?
I'm sorry. I must have been thinking about something.
Tae Pyung signed a contract with an agency today.
They gave us a car to use for free.
Is that right?
We were just driving. Why don't you join us, Dad?
All right. Sounds great.
Let's go.
- Let's go, Dad. - Okay.
Hello?
Is this Bok Sun Nyeo speaking?
Yes. This is she speaking.
Did you apply for our job opening?
- Yes. - Congratulations.
You've been hired for the position.
- Oh, dear. - Please come tomorrow.
- Training will start from tomorrow. - Oh, gosh.
I got the job? Thank you.
Yes, Yes. Thank you.
Oh, my goodness.
Talks went so well with Tonelli.
Shouldn't we call it a day and go for a drink on a day like this?
It's all on me today.
I want to apologise for worrying everyone so much.
How could we...
All right. Then you pay for the first round.
The groom can pay for the second round.
Before we head for drinks and food, let me treat you all to tea.
How about we go to the new pork restaurant near the junction?
- Okay. - That sounds good.
You sure do like pork belly, don't you?
(Gi Pyo's Mother)
Aren't you even worried about Gi Pyo?
How could you leave like that and not even call?
If you have anything to say, say it to me.
Who is this?
You're the CEO of the tailor shop, aren't you?
You guys couldn't wait to be together, could you?
If you have nothing else to say, I'm hanging up.
Wait.
Tell Yun Shil that Gi Pyo...
has been moved from the intensive care unit to the general ward.
Does that mean his condition has gotten better?
Why?
Were you hoping he remains in the intensive care unit?
It's a relief to hear that he's better.
I'll pass the word on to Yun Shil.
Wait a minute!
I have an urgent business in Anseong,
so I have to go there now.
If Yun Shil comes, tell her to stay in the ward.
I'm asking her since I'm in such a hurry.
Tell her to come right away.
(Peace Gosiwon)
Hello.
- What? - Give me the key.
Do you really have to do this?
You left home since you didn't like me.
I don't want to give you my credit card and car.
All right. I'll give you since you're being cheap.
Mr Kim, what are you doing?
What's this?
Why do you ask? Of course these are your clothes and bags.
Why did you bring it here?
When you run out of money,
sell these and use the money.
Mum!
You're ignorant of the world. You should have a hard time...
and then you would appreciate your mum.
You would realise soon...
what a good daughter I was.
Mr Kim,
- let's go. - Yes, Madam Ko.
(Peace Gosiwon)
Bye, Sally.
You take advantage of subcontractors, Min Hyo Sang!
- You should apologise! - You should apologise!
Min Hyo Sang should apologise!
You take advantage of subcontractors, Min Hyo Sang!
- You should apologise! - You should apologise!
What are they doing in front of my house?
Excuse me.
What are you doing here?
We didn't get the construction payment...
due to the rumour of bankruptcy.
We came here to get the money from Min Hyo Sang.
A bankruptcy?
- Who's going bankrupt? - It's Meesa Apparel, of course.
Who's telling you such a nonsense?
Our Meesa Apparel would never go bankrupt!
Our Meesa Apparel?
How are you related to Min Hyo Sang?
Why are you saying my son's name thoughtlessly?
She must be Min Hyo Sang's mum.
Tell you son...
to pay for the delayed construction payment.
A vicious enterpriser Min Hyo Sang should...
- pay for the construction! - Pay for the construction!
- Pay for the construction! - Pay for the construction!
It is deafening.
What are they doing?
What's going on?
Mother!
Ji Yun.
She must be Min Hyo Sang's wife.
A vicious enterpriser Min Hyo Sang should...
- pay for the construction! - Pay for the construction!
- Pay for the construction! - Pay for the construction!
Who are all these people?
I have no idea...
what's going on.
- Pay for the construction! - Pay for the construction!
I'm sorry. I have a matter to take care of.
Let's have a nice get-together later.
All right. Let's go home early today.
See you tomorrow.
Bye.
Are you still angry at me?
You talked about a get-together nicely before.
And then you suddenly cancel it and don't even look at me.
You thought that you forgot your anger so early.
So you're being angry again, right?
Why are you treating a sane man as if he were moody?
It's not nothing like that, so you can go home first.
- Are you sure? - Trust me.
A friend asked to meet him...
since he got an urgent matter. Don't worry.
All right, then.
See you later at home.
(Wolgyesu Tailor Shop)
I'm home.
- Where's Dong Jin? - He has an urgent matter.
So I came home first.
Promise me you won't go near to the hospital.
Yes, Mother.
Go inside and have dinner. You must be hungry.
(Saemaeum Hospital)
- You can remove his respirator. - Yes.
I heard he got better.
Why can't he wake up yet?
It's not serious,
but his bleeding from head made him less immune...
and breathe unstably. That's why he couldn't wake up.
Now that his breathing is stable,
he would wake up soon.
The operation result for his enterorrhexis is also good.
He had his kidney donated before.
Wouldn't he have a problem...
for his injury this time?
He had his kidney donated?
I don't think so.
Can you hold this?
If he was a kidney donor,
he should have a wound around here.
When I saw his body before the operation,
he didn't have any surgical scar.
Have you run a test on his kidney?
Yes, I had a CT scan all over.
- Can I see it? - Are you his guardian?
- Yes, I am. - Follow me.
It's the kidney.
Can you see? Both kidney are...
in the right place.
Are you sure it's Hong Gi Pyo's picture?
Yes, this patient...
hadn't donated his kidney...
and hadn't had any surgery related to the kidney either.
What's this?
- Why are you here? - I appreciate...
that you woke up on time.
Where's Yun Shil?
Yun Shil! Na Yun Shil!
How can you look for Yun Shil?
You have deceived her all along.
What?
What are you talking about?
You've been emphasising your favour all along...
that you had your kidney donated to Yun Shil's dad.
What are you going to do?
I don't think that would work now.
What are you talking about?
I just checked on your CT pictures.
You have two kidneys right inside you.
You don't have any surgical scar on your stomach.
You are...
a small-time crook.
What?
(We thank Choi Ji Na for her special appearance.)
(The Gentlemen of Wolgyesu Tailor Shop)
Dong Jin. How did you know that?
How could she be fooled by a guy like that for over 10 years?
You didn't tell Yun Shil already, did you?
No, it's not that.
- Darn it. - Gosh, those love birds.
You can go ahead and live happily and be love birds like us then.
Go buy some eel. Ones that were freshly caught from the sea.
- Don't you need a part-timer? - You're going to work?
Leave things as they are? Nothing works out easily for you two.
You ruined Yun Shil's life with your dirty lies.
Even if Yun Shil finds out, nothing will change.
Yun Shil's my woman.