What's going on?
- Why are you here? - Thankfully,
you woke up on time.
Where's Yun Shil?
Yun Shil! Na Yun Shil!
You shouldn't look for Yun Shil.
You've been deceiving her for such a long time.
What?
What are you talking about?
You've taken credit to yourself that you donated your kidney...
to her late father all along. What a pity.
That's not going to work from now on.
What on earth are you talking about?
I just checked your CT scan.
You have two kidneys in their place.
You don't have any surgical scar on your stomach, either.
You're a small-time crook.
What?
It's been more than 10 years.
From all those years,
you've been ruining Yun Shil's life...
- with your dirty lies. - Yes, it was a lie.
But I lied because I love Yun Shil.
Don't you dare...
say that you love her.
What you're doing is obsession and abuse, not love.
You punk.
It's all over. Don't ever show your face...
to Yun Shil again.
Hey, stop right there! Stop!
I'm through if Yun Shil hears the truth.
(Patient Transport)
(Episode 47)
Wait.
Hey.
Lee Dong Jin. Stop right there!
Boss. When did you wake up? Are you all right?
Follow that car. Hurry and get in!
- Yes, Boss. - Get in!
- Chase him. Hurry! - Yes, Boss.
Lee Dong Jin. Pull over!
I'm telling you to pull over!
Try making me.
Why aren't those cars going?
Get out. Get out of way!
- Catch up with him. - Yes, Boss.
Gosh.
Lee Dong Jin.
Boss. Are you all right?
What would be the best and most fatal way...
to take revenge on you two?
I thought about making her life miserable by paralysing her legs.
Or maybe I should take her where no one can find her...
and isolate here from the world.
But I'm sure that'll only make your love grow stronger, right?
Yun Shil. Making you live in guilt...
and seeing that you don't smile for the rest of your life...
I guess that would be the best way to take revenge.
- Hello? - This is Saemaeum Hospital.
Are you Hong Gi Pyo's guardian?
Has his condition gotten worse?
No, that's not it. He's recovered his consciousness,
but he got in a car accident while he was outside of the hospital.
A car accident?
There was just a minor collision, so the patient wasn't hurt.
It's just that the patient seems to be extremely upset.
I'm calling because I think it would be best for the guardian to come.
I'm not his guardian.
I'll give you the patient's mother's phone number. Please contact her.
This afternoon, subcontractors were in front of the house in a group.
They held a demonstration demanding money.
There was a big commotion.
I know.
I simply asked for some headache pills. What's taking you so long?
I'm going, Mother.
How are you running the company? What did you do to make them...
come here and hold a demonstration? Are you out of your mind?
Don't make a fuss.
We're just temporarily short of cash.
I'll settle things in no time.
I overheard some of the things they were saying.
It didn't seem that simple.
We were able to disperse the group by calling the police,
but they didn't seem like the type that would give up easily.
Are you adding fuel to the fire?
It's not that, Mother. I'm just worried.
Relax, Stepmother.
Why are you taking it out on Ji Yun?
What do you think we should do?
Hyo Sang and I have all our assets...
held as security for the loan.
We have nothing at the moment.
You and Hyo Sang caused this mess,
so discuss this amongst yourselves and find a solution.
What would I know about the company?
That rude little brat.
Even if we end up on the streets,
I'll never ask for your help. You'll see.
We could actually end up on the streets?
Don't say such a thing. It'll bring bad luck!
Ji Yun.
I'm sorry.
My head hurts.
Seo Yun? This is Hyo Won.
It's been a while, hasn't it?
I'm doing well.
In fact, I called to ask you a favour.
Do you need a part-timer at your art studio by any chance?
I just thought you'd need a hand since it's time for practical exams.
What?
I have some extra time on my hands...
and I was thinking about the old days.
I thought I could do some work while I have the time.
I just want to make some pocket money. Don't worry about that.
You're back. Hi.
Yes.
All right. Thanks. Then I'll start working from tomorrow.
Okay. See you tomorrow.
Honey.
What do you mean you'll start working tomorrow?
My friend runs an art studio. I said I'd help out.
Mum took away my car and my credit card.
I should at least earn some pocket money now.
(Savings Account Passbook)
What is this?
It's the money I saved from shooting the advertisement.
Use this when you need it.
No, I can't. It's okay.
What do you mean it's okay? You've never worried about money.
I'm sure you're worried and upset.
It's not much, but try to live with this for the time being.
Thank you.
You don't need to thank me for something like this.
It's only natural that I help you when you're in need.
I sure did find an amazing man.
Then please listen to me.
Call your mother to apologize and reconcile with her.
I won't.
Unless she approves of you, I refuse to reconcile with her.
Hyo Won.
Oh, tangerines.
In fact, I've been wanting to eat tangerines.
You see?
We can read each other's minds.
I'll peel it for you.
I'm just kidding.
It's delicious, isn't it?
Why did you call?
I called to see how you were doing Mother.
Do you think I'd be well after what you did?
I suffered aphasia and in distress because of you.
There's not enough words to express how sorry I am.
Why did you call?
Mother. Please forgive Hyo Won and allow her back in the house.
It's all my fault. Hyo Won has nothing to blame.
She walked out on her own and cut all ties with me.
I have no intention of begging her to come back.
I can act as if I never had a daughter.
- Mother. - Who are you calling Mother?
Unless she breaks up with you,
I won't accept Hyo Won as my daughter.
Like mother, like daughter. They're both stubborn.
How will I resolve this problem?
Where is she?
Yun Shil, are you there?
- Yes. - May I come in?
Are you going to sleep here?
Yes. Why are you asking?
We have our room. Why do you want to sleep here?
Well, I've thought about that.
We didn't go down the aisle.
So I think it's not right that I sleep in that room.
Parents would think the same.
I don't agree with you.
All right. Let's register our marriage...
first thing in the morning.
Register marriage?
Once we register our marriage, you can stay in our room...
and feel comfortable about it. Then I would feel comfortable, too.
What do you think?
All right. Let's go and register our marriage tomorrow morning.
All right.
By the way, Yun Shil,
about Hong Gi Pyo.
He woke up, so you don't have to worry about him.
How do you know?
I called the hospital a while ago.
Actually, I received a call just now.
- Did Hong Gi Pyo call you? - No,
they asked me to come to the hospital...
since he was upset due to a minor accident.
However, I told them to contact his mother.
That's good. You don't have to worry...
now that he woke up and is recovering all right.
Well, it's your last night as a single girl.
You can snore and roll over as much as you want.
What are you talking about? I'm very gentle when I sleep.
I've seen you sleeping several times,
and you were always snoring and rolling over.
What are you talking about?
I always wake up in the morning right on the same position...
as the one I sleep the night before.
That's because you roll over here and there and come back.
Stop making fun of me.
I just want you to sleep comfortably.
- Good night. - Have a nice dream.
I'm leaving.
You punk. Where are you now?
Have you told Yun Shil already?
I guess you're scared.
Are you mocking me right now?
- I'll kill you. - Do you have nothing else to say?
I guess that's the best you can do.
I don't want to play words with you.
You think you had a good one today,
but nothing would change even if Yun Shil hears the truth.
I would never give up on Yun Shil. She's mine.
You are really...
a natural born bully.
Listen up.
You shouldn't be forgiven...
for the lies you told Yun Shil 10 years ago.
Also, what you've been doing to take control of Yun Shil...
- are all criminal acts. - Are trying to teach me right now?
No, I'm warning you.
If you ever show your face again,
I'll let you know how a criminal like you...
should be punished.
If you don't want to go back to prison after just several days,
don't you dare come around Yun Shil again.
Don't hang up on me.
Hey!
You've been deceived by a jerk like him for over 10 years.
What a pity.
Stop it.
They get on my nerves. What are they doing every night?
- That's what I'm saying. - My goodness.
They make me so mad. How irritating!
Get your mind off of it. Go back to sleep.
- Go to sleep. - I'm offended.
That tickles.
- Enough is enough. - I can't stand it.
Excuse me for a moment, Dong Sook.
What's the matter?
It's late at night.
You lack common sense. It's middle of the night,
but you two giggle and whisper all night long.
How can we go to sleep then?
I understand you're newlyweds, but it's too much.
Don't bother us and go to sleep.
How can we not bother? We can hear you as we lie down.
I fully understand that you're newlyweds,
but can't you keep quiet?
You can have quality time and keep quiet at the same time.
How can you keep quiet when you're having quality time?
That's nonsense, Sun Nyeo.
She's right. You can't keep quite when you have quality time.
If you feel offended, you two can have quality time...
as much as you want.
We'd like that, too.
- What's the problem then? - The problem is...
we don't have enough time,
we're aged and we have other reasons.
- What reasons do we have? - Well...
I mean, I have so much work to do at the tailor shop.
So I'm tired and I need some rest.
I know what you mean.
I understand,
but you shouldn't scold the newlyweds.
You two should solve the problem together.
I agree.
I'm sleepy.
I want to pillow my head on your arm.
Let's go inside, Dong Sook.
- Sweet dreams, Sam Do. - Sweet dreams, Sun Nyeo.
My pride has been hurt. I should take some medicine.
They look happy. I envy Dong Sook.
Do you envy her? Why do say that in front of me?
You're too sensitive. I was just talking to myself.
Tomorrow morning, go to the market...
and buy some good quality eels.
What's the racket? You didn't like to eat it when I cooked it for you.
Now you ask me to buy it.
I just feel like eating eels. I don't have any other reason.
I don't trust what he says.
Make sure you buy some good quality eels tomorrow.
What's wrong with him?
He wants me to buy eels for him.
(Gi Pyo's mother)
- Leave a message after the beep. - Blast it!
- How dare she ignores my call? - You've reached to voice mail.
See? It's Yun Shil's true self.
She's heartless.
She receives a call from hospital that someone is almost dying...
and she answers that she can't come as she's not the guardian.
I can't forgive her.
- I should... - Stop it, Mum.
Stop it.
Are you angry at me for speaking ill of Yun Shil?
I have a headache, so stop it and go home.
I came all the way from Anseong,
and you lose your temper because of a girl?
Mum, please.
All right, all right. I'm leaving.
It's no use to have a child.
I'm so unfortunate.
I'll take some rest at the lounge.
Yun Shil must have known the truth by now.
What shall I do?
- Mum, Dad, may we come inside? - Sure.
- Good morning. - Good morning.
We will register our marriage today.
What do you mean you register your marriage?
You mean you will register marriage when you didn't have the wedding?
We're as good as we're married.
The formality of a wedding isn't important.
If we really want to have a wedding,
we can do that later with just friends and family.
I'm sorry.
If you think that way, we should do so.
You're saying okay without even thinking about it?
But that's what they want.
Why can't anything ever happen easily with you guys?
I'm always nervous about you, like birds on a power line.
This is all my fault. I'm sorry.
The heart is what matters.
What's the big deal about a wedding?
Don't be upset, and let's give them our permission.
I'm not saying I won't let them.
I'm just upset, that's all.
Thank you, Mother.
Thank you.
Did you sleep well?
What do you think?
Hey. We're living together.
Can't you at least have...
a little etiquette towards us?
Come on. We're newlyweds.
I'm sure you were lovey-dovey when you first got married, too.
Not at all.
Why not?
My family caught me staying out all night with Sam Do,
so my mum and cousins practically beat him up,
and that's why we got married.
But you know,
Tae Pyung said he thinks Sam Do is going through menopause.
Men go through menopause, too?
Of course.
Doesn't he seem weak and unmotivated lately?
That's right.
You should be more attentive to him...
and try to get him to want to do things.
And don't wear sweats to sleep.
Wear something nice.
Where did you get that?
At a department store.
Is it expensive?
I spent a bit.
I went all out for the wedding.
Let me borrow it just once.
I'll wash it and give it back.
Seriously.
You can't borrow someone's nightgown.
Here.
It's sweet and sour. It tastes so good.
Tae Pyung will love this.
I'll give you some.
You want to swap cucumber salad with my nightgown?
I'll wear it just once.
Deal.
Seriously.
What the... What's wrong with you?
You look so much better lately.
Really? I guess.
Tae Pyung, I envy you more than anyone right now.
You've been lethargic and irritable lately.
Your muscles are shrinking, too.
What's gotten into you?
I know. I just feel depressed lately.
I get angry at the little things.
And I keep crying.
Good morning.
What brings you here so early?
I know.
We're going to register our marriage,
and we need witnesses, so we wanted you to sign it.
You're finally going to be a legally wedded couple.
Congratulations.
Thank you.
- Honey. - Yes?
Dong Jin and Yun Shil are registering their marriage.
They are? Congratulations.
When they go register their marriage,
let's go with them and register ours, too.
What? You haven't registered your marriage yet?
He just made his comeback.
If word gets out that he's married, it'll hinder his popularity.
We won't do it for the time being.
What if Tae Pyung leaves you later?
Don't you worry.
He'd never do that.
Still, it would be better to follow the procedure...
- according to the law. - Right?
Forget it. Once he wins the best artist of the year,
we can register our marriage then.
True, he may not have much, but he wouldn't change.
Should I sign here, where it says, "witness"?
Yes. Here.
- Okay. - There.
Sun Nyeo, you, too.
Okay. Gosh.
- "Witness one, Witness two." - Okay.
Sign anywhere?
- Here. - Okay.
We're finally a married couple now.
You're right. It still doesn't seem real.
It doesn't seem real, but we still need to commemorate,
so let's take a picture.
Here.
Here we go. One, two.
Okay.
Yun Shil.
Where's Yun Shil?
Are you back again?
Mr Lee and Yun Shil went to register their marriage.
What? Do what?
Register their marriage.
They're legally married now,
so don't bug her again and don't come here again, either.
That evil brat.
How dare she discard Gi Pyo like an old shoe?
Wait. I don't have time for this.
Good day.
Seriously. I wish I could stop seeing that woman.
My sentiments exactly.
I don't know if she'll back off so easily, though.
Gi Pyo. Gi Pyo. This is bad.
What now?
Yun Shil, that brat, registered her marriage...
with that tailor shop owner.
What?
Are... Are you okay?
Who said Yun Shil registered her marriage?
The tailor shop worker just told me.
When I said to register her marriage with you,
she made all sorts of excuses not to.
That wicked wench.
This isn't right! This isn't right!
Gi Pyo!
Gi Pyo! Gi Pyo! Goodness.
You and Yun Shil just weren't meant to be.
Let's hurt for now and forget it.
Please, Gi Pyo. Please cut her out of your life...
and let's finally live in peace.
I'm begging you. Please.
Please, Gi Pyo. My baby, Gi Pyo.
No.
Mum.
My poor baby.
We're back.
Did you register your marriage?
Yes.
Congratulations on becoming a married man and a married woman.
Thank you.
That woman came by again not long ago.
Hong Gi Pyo's mum.
She asked for you, so I told her that you registered your marriage.
Good. Thank you.
Are you okay?
Of course.
That's good, then.
I'm going to the bank.
Why?
We should get a loan if we're going to open the Wolgyesu-Tonelli shop.
Just a minute.
- What's this? - Come on.
I'm Wolgyesu's master tailor. I need to chip in.
It isn't much.
It's okay. Don't.
No. I just saved up my allowance that my wife had given me.
It isn't much. Please, you're embarrassing me.
You saved it for so long.
What if you lose it by investing in me?
I believe you are the safest investment in the world.
I'd go all in on you, too, if I had any money.
Wow. My husband is so well-trusted.
I'm the safest man in the world, Lee Dong Jin.
Thank you. I'll return this with a profit.
I feel like I saved face as Wolgyesu's master tailor.
Yes?
The bank issued an official refusal to pay.
What have you been doing?
Why isn't the real estate selling?
They are all warehouses,
so no one wants to purchase them in this down market.
Then will we go bankrupt? What?
The great Meesa Apparel, going bankrupt just because...
we don't have a few million dollars?
I put up my house and all my shares up as collateral!
I'm sorry.
I'm the guarantor on the company's loans, too.
If the company goes under,
are you saying I'll be kicked out with nothing to my name?
I'm going to the bank. Get the car.
Yes?
The bank just called Chairman Min Hyo Sang...
and issued an official refusal to pay.
It's as I expected.
I want you to make a public announcement...
- our promissory notes were refused. - Yes, Ma'am.
When all the remaining promissory notes get returned, he'll flip out.
- They abuse the subcontractors! - Ceasing payments?
- Repent! - Repent!
We have so much real estate. How can that be?
- Yes. - Contractors stuff themselves...
- Okay. - but starve the subcontractors!
- Repent! - Okay.
- Repent! - I need to talk to Hyo Sang.
Min Hyo Sang, who bleeds subcontractors dry must repent!
Repent!
(Hyo Sang)
- Repent! - The person you have reached...
- Repent! - What did he do?
How could he destroy a healthy company overnight?
Excuse me. Excuse me!
- Yes? - I need something for a headache.
Here.
Min Hyo Sang must step down!
- Step down! - Step down!
They're driving me crazy.
Call the police right now and tell them...
- to get rid of them. - Yes, Madam.
Min Hyo Sang must step down!
- Step down! - Step down!
What is going on?
How could this happen to me?
- Step down! - Step down!
Min Hyo Sang must step down!
- Will you be okay? - What?
You've never had a part time job before. Will you be okay?
It's just my friend's studio.
I'll be fine.
Why don't you just go with me to your mother?
- You should make up with her... - I told you.
I won't make up with her until she lets me be with you.
Imagine how desperate she was to make up such a lie.
Try to be understanding.
So? Will you break up with me?
I can never do that.
I'm saying we should work harder...
and make her feel reassured, so that she'll change her mind.
You can do that if you want, but I refuse.
Wait for me. Hyo Won!
- Wait for me. - No.
- Don't be mad. - Let go.
I was just thinking of you. Of you.
- You knew you'd hold my hand. - I will not.
Sorry. Okay.
Min Hyo Sang, who bleeds subcontractors dry must repent!
- Repent! - Repent!
Repent! Repent!
Contractors stuff themselves but starve the subcontractors!
- Repent! - Repent!
We're bleeding!
- We're bleeding! - We're bleeding!
There's Min Hyo Sang's mum!
Oh my gosh!
How could you steal our hard- earned money from construction...
and live in this huge mansion?
What cold blooded jerks.
What did you just say? Cold blooded jerks?
When are you going to pay us for the construction work?
Why are you asking me?
Ask the person who hired you.
Are you kidding me? That's your son, lady!
What? Lady?
- How dare you talk to me that way? - Whatever!
Give us our money!
I don't know anything, so ask elsewhere, before I call the cops!
Wow. What a dirty rat.
- What? A rat? - I know.
She needs to be taught a lesson.
- Give us our money! - Give us our money!
- Give us our money! - Excuse me.
- What are you doing? - Pay us!
Are you okay?
- Who is this jerk? - Get on my back. Hurry.
- What are you doing? - Where are you going?
- Where are you going? - Give us our money!
My shoe. I dropped a shoe.
- Excuse us. - What are they doing?
- She's insane. - What is she doing?
- Are you kidding? - What are you doing?
Hey!
What are they doing?
- Get them! - Get back here!
- Repent! - Repent!
Don't expect me...
to change my mind just because you're doing this.
I know.
But what's going on?
Right when we were about to launch the outdoor line,
the company fell apart.
We're suddenly in debt overnight.
Please calm down.
Don't expect me...
to change my mind just because you're doing this.
I don't expect...
your anger to subside that quickly.
I'll keep trying until it does.
Forget it.
Oh my gosh.
Are you okay?
I'm Bok Sun Nyeo.
I got a call that I was hired to be a bank correspondent.
You may go to the third floor.
Thank you.
It is necessary...
for a bank correspondent to always smile.
Please practice greeting...
with a big smile with me.
- Yes, Ma'am. - Yes, Ma'am.
Hello, Mr Cho.
- Hello, Mr Cho. - Hello, Mr Cho.
How may I help you?
- How may I help you? - How may I help you?
When they want to make a withdrawal,
fill out the blue withdrawal form.
Fill out their name and get their signature...
or seal.
Write the amount.
- In Korean. - Okay.
One.
Hold the cane lightly with one hand, as if you're shaking someone's hand.
Two.
Stand at attention and balance yourself.
Three.
Use your wrist, not arm,
to maintain a uniform distance.
Growing old...
may be a process in which you lose your bodily functions...
in exchange for gaining wisdom and experience.
Some lose hearing,
some lose the ability to walk,
and yet some others...
lose those experience and wisdom...
and are swept into the darkness of dementia.
Luckily, I am losing only my vision.
I still have strong legs,
ears to listen to the world...
and wisdom...
to accept myself as I am.
Let's be thankful.
Let's be thankful and even more thankful.
I am Choi Gok Ji's husband,
Dong Sook and Dong Jin's father,
and above all,
I am the tailor Lee Man Sool,
who is still standing tall on my own two feet.
Tae Pyung!
- Tae Pyung! - Yes?
What is it?
Someone's here from the company.
- I'm the CEO's assistant. - I see.
But what...
He asked me to bring this to you, his artist.
Here.
- The CEO? - Yes.
The car was nice enough. He didn't need to do this.
I know. He is so nice.
Anyway, I'd like to thank him.
Would you make an appointment for me?
He's still traveling abroad.
I'll let him know when he returns.
I'll get going now.
Would you...
like to come inside for some tea?
- Yes, do that. - No thanks.
I'll see you again.
- Bye. - I won't go too far.
Gosh. The CEO of your agency...
must really like you. Look at all this.
What's this?
It's a health supplement.
I'm home, Gok Ji.
Welcome home.
Did you have a baduk lesson?
Yes. Where's your mum?
She went to get groceries.
Father, have one of these.
What is this?
It's good for you. Drink it up.
It tastes good.
You don't look too well. You're not ill, are you?
I feel a bit under the weather. I'm okay, though.
(Woosung Bank)
It's just this one crisis. You know that.
Once I sell the land we own,
we can repay the loan in no time.
The Loan Screening Board made its decision.
There is nothing I can do for you.
Unless there's a huge shift in the market,
everyone has a dim outlook of Meesa Apparel's future.
What is it?
Let him right in.
I have another appointment. I need you to leave.
Come on in.
I came to thank you for helping me out with the loan.
- It's good to see you. - Hi.
Tonelli is a major player in the world fashion industry.
They selected Wolgyesu Tailor Shop as their Asia partner.
Of course, we had to help you.
I was shocked to hear you'd left Meesa.
Now I see you had greater plans.
(Woosung Bank)
It's me. I heard Tonelli chose Wolgyesu...
as their Asia partner. Find out if it's true.
That old raccoon of a president.
His sole purpose in life is to insult me in front of Dong Jin.
I hate my life.
- I'm home. - I'm home.
I hope the cold didn't bother you too much today.
I'll get dinner ready. Get changed.
Mum, just a moment.
We registered our marriage earlier today.
"Receipt of registration".
You're so happy you're grinning from ear to ear.
Mum.
Can we sleep in the same room from now on?
Of course you can.
Get your things.
What's the hurry? I'll pack my things later.
I can't wait another minute. Let's get your things right now.
- Wrong way. - It's this way.
Hurry.
This won't do.
What do you mean?
It's our first night together. Let's go to a hotel.
What for? This is our home.
It's our first night as a couple. It should be special.
Forget it. Don't make a fuss out of it.
Just get on with the packing.
We're consuming our marriage.
Do you want to spend it without any special events?
I feel uncomfortable in hotels. I can't sleep.
I prefer home.
I'm okay as long as I have you.
I was waiting for you to say that.
I'll do your bidding, then.
Does this go in here?
Yes, in there.
What this?
The first night is all about what you wear.
It must be from Dong Sook.
Give me that.
Let me see.
I should thank her profusely.
Put it on.
Have you lost your mind?
It's a gift from my sister. Don't take her generosity for granted.
If you're too shy, I won't watch the process.
Are you sure?
Will this do?
Don't you dare look.
I can't see.
Are you changing?
I'm off to shower.
What?
That's against the rules.
(Gi Pyo)
(Reject call)
The recipient refused the call.
Yun Shil, it's me.
I know you're angry and don't want to talk to me.
Please take my call.
Don't trust whatever he says.
Give me a chance to explain.
Why do you think...
I told such a lie?
(Hong Gi Pyo)
The recipient can't answer the call.
Please leave a message.
Is he avoiding me?
Who is it?
I wonder what brings you all the way to my room.
Your brother needs your help.
I just got a call from the lawyer.
The bank issued him an ultimatum.
He might go bankrupt.
- So what? - So what?
I need you to help us out.
- Why should I? - What?
I know you have a grudge against Hyo Sang and me.
I see why you do, but Hyo Joo.
Your own father put his whole life into building up Meesa.
We can't let it go bankrupt and watch it fall to pieces.
Whose fault is this?
Hyo Sang made a mess of the company...
and now you come to me for help?
This wouldn't have happened under Dong Jin.
I wouldn't have had to divorce him.
I'm sorry about that.
You're sorry?
You crushed my whole life...
and all you do is apologise?
What's the use of pointing fingers now?
We have to sort this out first.
Help us, Hyo Joo.
You two caused this mess. You two can clean it up.
I'll have nothing to do with it.
What should I do?
Do you want me to kneel and beg?
Don't you dare do that. I know you don't mean it.
Hyo Joo.
You made me hit rock bottom.
I want the same for you and Hyo Sang.
I lost what I cherished.
You two have to lose what you value.
I'll make you reap what you sowed.
Madam Ko's tonic is ready.
Do you think I'm in the mood to run errands?
You take it to her.
What if they really go bankrupt?
We only just got married.
Why am I so unfortunate?
I think dealing with the mob outside your house...
shocked your mum to the core.
Your support is what she needs the most.
You should go home.
Let's not talk about serious matters.
I used to follow you around all the time.
It's great to be able to work again.
I remember staying up all night to prepare for college.
I'm used to seeing your flashy side.
I'm not used to seeing you in an apron.
Are you the same Hyo Won?
One day, I want to draw you.
Will you model for me?
I'd like that.
You'll have to go nude.
Can't I pose in clothes?
Okay.
How long does it take to draw a nude?
I'm not sure.
From sketch to colouring...
At least three days.
That's how long you'll need to pose for.
- Three... Three days? - Is that a no?
If that's what you need, I'll do it.
I was kidding.
You're so cute.
You scared me.
Thank you.
Even when I ask for a daunting favour,
you always say yes first.
Having someone who's always on your side...
is something I should be very thankful for.
You sided with me first.
I should thank you.
That's so touching.
If you don't want to go home yet, at least call your mum.
She'll cheer up when she hears your voice.
She'll just yell at me.
I'm so confused and dazed. Thanks for being understanding.
- Hello? - It's me, Mum.
- Are you okay? - Why did you call?
Because I'm worried.
If you're that worried, come home and comfort me.
- How dare you just call. - Mum.
You evil brat.
Even in this dire situation,
I come second...
to Tae Yang.
If you accept us as a couple,
I'll come running home.
I'm hanging up.
My kids have failed me.
The company's about to go belly-up.
Ko Eun Sook's life is a total failure.
I wasted my life. I lived for nothing.
On a windy hillside
Where no one comes looking
Is a nameless weed
If you had so much as a flower
Then you'd be fragrant at least
You are a weed that has neither
Slow down. What if you get indigestion?
You're weird.
You used to shudder when I so much as mentioned eel.
What made you want some tonight?
I don't want to eat this. It's more of a medicine.
Time really changes people.
Who'd have thought you'd want to eat eel?
How could you? I didn't get to eat one piece.
I said it's not enjoyable.
It's more like a medicine at this point.
- At least there's no leftovers. - I feel so refreshed.
What did you have?
You're eating eel this late at night?
How dare you.
This is all your fault.
What is? I just stole one piece.
You make me look bad by getting busy every night.
I'm losing face here.
Aren't you too old to get jealous about things like that?
You brace yourselves for what's coming tonight.
You won't be getting any sleep.
He gets competitive about the odd things in life.
It won't be easy.
Honey.
How do I look?
Killer.
I knew you'd like it.
Let's do our homework...
and get a handsome son out of it.
The son's not our priority tonight.
Our goal is to crush the other couple.
Okay. I like that attitude.
Honey. Come here.
I haven't held you in a while.
I am so happy.
Hold me tighter.
I think I smell Tae Pyung on the robe you're wearing.
Stop talking nonsense and get back to work.
Sun Nyeo.
Do you have any more eel?
I bought four and you ate every piece of it.
Can you go and get six more tomorrow?
I don't feel virile enough.
Your battery's gone flat.
It's not that. My battery's fine.
Hardly. What a waste of biceps and triceps.
I'm really fine. Watch. One.
Don't waste your energy on things like this.
- I'm perfectly fine. - Look at all the dust.
Lie down. Let's go to sleep.
What's wrong with me?
Lie down.
I warmed your side of the bed, so you wouldn't feel cold.
Come on. Get in here.
I forgot the light.
Lie down. I'll get it.
No, don't turn it off.
See... If it's dark,
- I might not be able to sleep. - What?
Won't it be a bit embarrassing?
Okay, then.
Wait!
What is it now?
- The clock's ticking too loudly. - What?
The ticking's so loud I don't think I'll be able to sleep.
Will that do? Lie down.
I know you feel awkward.
- Try to go along with it. - Wait.
I think we should turn the light off.
It's too bright and I can't sleep.
This won't do.
Dong Jin.
Stay still.
The awkwardness and embarrassing feeling will go away soon.
- That tickles. - Don't scream.
- Don't do that. - Where is this?
- What was that sound? - I wonder.
- Dad! - Father!
I was coming out of the toilet and suddenly things went black.
I lost my balance.
Let's go to the hospital this instant.
It's no big deal.
This is just a slight scratch.
I'll bring the first-aid kit.
What's wrong with your father?
He fell on his way out of the toilet.
Goodness. You know your way around the house with your eyes shut.
How could you have fallen and hurt your forehead?
How could this have happened?
I must have been half asleep.
No matter what the reason was,
how could you have fallen and gotten hurt like this?
Father. This may hurt a bit, so please be patient.
Be patient.
Are you all right?
I'm all right. I'm all right.
Goodness. How could this have happened?
(Hangook University Hospital)
Your eyesight has gotten worse compared to the past, hasn't it?
Yes. When walking the streets, people suddenly
seem to appear out of nowhere, so I bump into them.
Sometimes, I can't notice steps,
so I end up falling down.
By looking at your test results,
about 10 degrees of your eyesight is remaining.
Doctor. Then how worse does that mean it has gotten?
As the visual field starts to contract, the eyesight weakens.
Normally, in the condition of 10 degrees,
patients become aware that their eyesight is weakening.
Like your father.
If it gets worse,
patients will start to feel discomfort and fear.
If in a place they're unfamiliar with,
it becomes difficult for the patient to walk on their own.
I see. Then you mean that it will only get worse, right?
Retinitis pigmentosa...
does not yet have a cure.
I don't know what more to tell you.
Please, don't give up though.
Make sure to take the adjuvant that I prescribed for you.
Also, try to eat green vegetables, dark-coloured fruits, nuts...
as well as fish with dark-coloured skin.
Yes. I understand.
(Wolgyesu Tailor Shop)
Yun Shil.
What are you doing here?
Let's talk. Please.
How many times have I told you. I have nothing to say to you.
Let's go somewhere quiet.
Where are you going to take me this time?
It's not like that.
If it makes you uncomfortable, we can talk here.
Please. I beg you.
(Wolgyesu Tailor Shop)
Keep it short. Say what you have to say and leave.
I heard you finished the marriage registration with Dong Jin.
You refused when my mother told you to register our marriage.
How could you?
I don't want to have to repeat my words.
If you're here to talk about that, leave.
Forgive me, Yun Shil.
I don't know what Dong Jin said to you,
but I truly would have given your father my kidney.
You were there. You saw me smiling as I entered the operating room.
At that moment, I was being sincere.
For the past 10 years, I wanted to tell you this myself.
I promised myself that I'd tell you the truth several times.
But I was worried you might leave me,
so I couldn't find the courage to tell you.
What are you talking about?
The fact that I wasn't able to give my kidney to your father...
Dong Jin...
didn't say anything to you?
So...
you didn't give your kidney...
to my father.
Is this what you're saying?
How...
could you do that?
How could you?
How could you lie about something like that?
(The Gentlemen of Wolgyesu Tailor Shop)
Mum. What should I do? Yun Shil will never see me again.
Why didn't you tell me?
Why didn't you tell me that Gi Pyo lied to me?
It's Dad.
Wait a minute, Dong Sook.
What is Dad doing right now?
Put the table away and spread the bedding.
Bae Sam Do is fully prepared.
- Are you declaring bankruptcy? - Bankruptcy?
You consider yourself the CEO?
Have you gone out of your mind?
My father worked so hard to build this company.
I can't just watch it go under.
Dong Jin. It's time for you to return. The company needs you.