Dramatorrent
(Episode 48)
Forgive me, Yun Shil.
I don't know what Dong Jin said to you,
but I truly would have given your father my kidney.
You were there. You saw me smiling as I entered the operating room.
At that moment, I was being sincere.
For the past 10 years,
I wanted to tell you this myself.
I promised myself that I'd tell you the truth several times.
But I was worried you might leave me,
so I couldn't find the courage to tell you.
What are you talking about?
The fact that I wasn't able to give my kidney to your father...
Dong Jin...
- didn't say anything to you? - So...
you didn't...
give your kidney to my father.
Is this what you're saying?
How...
could you do that?
How could you?
How could you lie about something like that?
I didn't mean to lie to you,
but I thought that was the only way I could make you stay with me.
I'm really sorry, Yun Shil.
Don't worry too much.
(Operating Room)
See you later.
They said they need...
to remove a tumour in his pancreas before the kidney transplant,
so your father went into the operating room first.
Then I also went into the OR and was about to go under anaesthesia...
Please request a pathology test on the tumour we just removed.
And let the donor know that we're done here. He should get ready.
Doctor, his vital signs are dropping.
Dr Choi. Epinephrine, please.
Dr Park. Get ready for CPR.
Dr Kim, let the donor know of the recipient's cardiac arrest.
Hello?
Doctor, the recipient went into cardiac arrest due to anaphylaxis.
We cannot do the transplant now.
Mr Hong, can you hear me?
Please open your eyes if you can hear me.
Is the surgery done?
The recipient went into cardiac arrest,
- so it has been put on hold. - Cardiac arrest?
Is he going to be okay?
We should wait and see what happens.
Please go to the recovery room and wait there...
Mr Hong, you have to be careful. It can be dangerous.
You should lie down.
I have an urgent matter. Don't bother me.
- Let me go. - Catch him!
Boss, are you done with your surgery already?
Cheong Man, take Yun Shil to somewhere else.
What?
Yun Shil should not meet the doctor. Take her to somewhere else.
How is everything?
We've prepared the funeral.
We're keeping our eyes on Yun Shil...
so that she doesn't meet your doctor.
Yun Shil should never find out that I didn't have the surgery.
If that happens, you and I are through.
Yes, Boss.
You thought your dad died during the transplant,
but actually, something went wrong right after removing the tumor,
and he died within an hour of being transferred...
to ICU from the operating room.
At the funeral,
you looked me in the eyes for the first time.
It seemed that I could never see your face again...
if I told you that I didn't donate my kidney to your dad.
It was because I loved you.
I didn't know that.
I've felt that I'm in debt to you for 10 years.
I wanted to run away,
but I've endured it all along.
Was it all because of your lie?
How could you...
make such a lie?
Sometimes it's better not to know something than to know it.
I did it for you.
It's all because of that Lee Dong Jin.
If only he didn't find it out, I could take the secret to the grave.
Did he know...
all about this?
Didn't you hear about this from him?
Didn't he really tell you anything?
I'm sorry, Yun Shil.
I didn't want to lose you because I loved you so much.
I couldn't help it.
I'll make it up to you.
(Wolgyesu Tailor Shop)
Big money is going to be in my hands soon.
I'll give you all of it.
That will be enough compensation.
Are you going to make up for my life...
with that money?
Do you think that can be a compensation for my life?
- Yun Shil. - Get out of here.
Get out of my sight!
(Wolgyesu Tailor Shop)
Goodness.
- Isn't he Hong Gi Pyo? - That's him.
- My goodness. Yun Shil! - Why was he here again?
We should tell Mum.
It would be better for her to know before your condition gets worse.
I think Mum should prepare her heart.
She exhausted herself...
preparing for Dong Sook's wedding and your wedding.
She's barely holding on now.
I'm not sure whether it's a good idea...
to tell her about my condition.
You have a point,
but your field of vision would gradually narrow down.
We should tell Mum quickly and plan some safety measures.
I will move more carefully and be cautious.
I think we should delay telling Gok Ji about this.
I'm getting trained about my condition. If I get more used to it,
things would be better, I suppose.
All right.
By then, be careful not to get hurt again.
I surely will.
I'm sorry I'm late.
You're here.
Where's Mr Lee?
I took him home.
By the way, where's Yun Shil?
She's totally exhausted, so I told her to take a rest.
What happened? Is she sick?
Hong Gi Pyo visited a while ago,
and made some trouble, so she was shocked.
What?
Hi.
Let's go to the hospital.
Why didn't you tell me?
You knew that Gi Pyo lied about his kidney donation to Dad.
You knew about it.
Why didn't you tell me anything?
I thought it would trouble you.
You're holding on already,
and you could blame yourself if you know the truth.
That's why I didn't tell you about it.
Even so, you should've told me.
I should have known even if the truth troubles me.
I was going to tell you once you become stable. I'm sorry.
I'm so furious and distressed.
I regret all those years of living in guilt because of his lie.
I'm angry about troubling you because of him.
It makes me so angry. I can't stand it.
How about thinking that you had a long nightmare?
You woke up from the bad dream, so forget about it.
You've been through so much.
You must have had a hard time enduring it alone.
You should go home and take a rest today.
I'm fine.
I'm giving an order as a CEO. You should go home and rest today.
Then I would be relieved.
By the way,
how is Father?
His field of vision is getting narrow quickly.
The doctor says it will get worse.
Are there any surgery or treatment for it?
Father is taking it calmly,
but I can't take it in well.
I'm not the only one who needs to be comforted.
I'm fine.
Let's go home now.
Why are you here at this time of the day?
Yun Shil seems to have a cold.
I heard that there's the flu going around.
Have you been to the hospital?
I took some medicine. I'm fine, Mother.
You don't look fine. Your face is so pale.
Take her inside and let her lie down.
All right.
You should go to the signing ceremony today.
It's all right. Don't worry about that and take some sleep.
I'm fine. Don't worry about me and go quickly.
You might be late.
Call me if you feel worse. I'll take you to the hospital.
All right. You should go now.
All right. I'm leaving.
- What are you doing now? - I'll show you my surgical wound.
It looks like you've forgotten how grateful you should be for me,
so I want to help you refresh your memory.
Is it going to rain later today? Where I got the surgery is hurting.
Does it hurt a lot?
A pain relieving patch and rest should make the pain go away.
I should go back in and rest.
(CEO of Wolgyesu Tailor Shop, Lee Dong Jin)
(Partnership Signing Ceremony)
If you give me a little more time,
I'll make sure to sort everything out.
- So please... - It's already bad as it is,
but it'll only get worse with all the promissory notes that are due.
You don't even have any measures as to how you'll pay them.
For any promissory notes that require payment,
- we'll have to issue a moratorium. - What are you saying?
- You'll dishonour them? - That's right.
We have no choice.
My personal assets are on it as collateral.
How can you think that I won't be able to sort it out?
I'm going to pay them. I'll pay everything off!
I've been fooled.
Had I known this would happen,
I wouldn't have agreed to use my personal assets as collateral.
We need to suggest a solution to the creditors before they act first.
Since the chairman's tenure,
Meesa Apparel was the most profitable when the company was...
run by the deputy CEO, Mr Lee. We need to let the creditors know.
Yes, Sir. I'll be in touch again soon.
- What's up? - I will...
cut to the chase.
Help me just this once, Hyo Joo.
I'm stuck at this foundation, so I have no power to help you.
Let me use your real estate properties as collateral for a loan.
I'll repay you for everything and more if this goes well.
You're trying to drag me into your mess.
I guess you don't want to die alone.
Help me just this once, please. The promissory notes are due today.
If I can't pay them, the company will have to declare bankruptcy.
Do you think anything will change by paying that promissory note?
Let's say I help you make the payment today. What will be next?
I'll figure out the rest after that,
so please help me out today. Hyo Joo,
Dad worked so hard to build this company. Isn't it important to you?
You're even bringing up our deceased dad.
You must be so desperate. But give up.
I do not want to help you.
Gosh, let's be honest. If the company goes under,
do you think your foundation won't be affected?
- I'm not attached to this place. - I won't be doomed alone.
If the company collapses, all of us will be doomed.
Your family will go bankrupt.
I have nothing to do with you people.
"You people"? Gosh, seriously.
I guess you don't think of us as a family at all.
Family?
Have you ever treated me like your family?
- I can't believe this. - You brought this upon yourself,
so you should take care of it yourself.
You'll regret this one day.
I'm going to make sure you regret doing this to me.
It's been a long time, Madam Sun.
I'm calling because...
there's a piece of land I want to buy in Gangwon Province.
I don't have enough cash on hand at the moment,
so I was wondering if you can lend me five big ones.
I'll pay you generous interest.
Rumours say your company might go bankrupt.
You must've put some money aside to buy land.
I guess you're quick-witted when it comes to those things.
Who's spreading such a groundless rumour?
Groundless rumour? Whatever.
There were a few newspaper articles about it, too.
Forget it. I don't want your money.
Are you trying to put a curse on our robust company or what?
I'm going to hang up.
- Are you there? Hello? - Yes, Ma'am.
Go bring me something to calm myself down.
Yes, Ma'am.
- Hello? - How did it go, Mum?
- Did you manage to get it? - You punk.
You've already taken so much money from me. How can you ask for more?
I've given you everything I have. I'm penniless now because of you!
- Gosh. - My goodness, my head is splitting.
The medicine.
- Gosh... - Here it is.
My goodness...
Gosh...
Hyo Won.
- Are you heading out for work? - Yes.
Have you decided to move back home?
No. I was just passing by.
It doesn't look like that's the case.
Stop being so stubborn and come back home.
Hyo Sang's company is in a bind,
so it's very tense at home.
Don't distress Mother even more...
just because of someone like Tae Yang. That's just not right.
You may feel like you can't live without him at the moment,
but it's just a fleeting emotion. Later on, you'll look back...
and wonder why you did this.
You'll come to realise it."I was so foolishly blinded by love."
Do you think I'm like you?
What? Why are you so rude to me?
Whatever.
Give these cupcakes to Mum. Tell her that you bought them.
I told her I was leaving for work. How can I give this to her now?
Tell her you thought of her and bought them on your way to work.
She probably hasn't been eating. Take these to her.
They're from her favourite cupcake place.
You take them to her.
My shift is starting shortly, so I have to go now.
How rude.
- Who is it? - It's me, Ji Yun.
I'm leaving a box of cupcakes in front of the door for Mother.
Sure. Shall I come get them now?
She's gone.
I'm sorry, Dad.
I shouldn't have believed him.
I was too foolish.
It must've hurt you tremendously.
I'm sorry.
Hey.
Hey, how are you feeling?
I'm fine now. I'm feeling much better.
Did the ceremony go well?
I left as soon as it ended because I was so worried about you.
I'll head home now. Meet me outside.
You're downhearted.
Let's skip work and go on a date instead.
Don't use me as an excuse to slack off.
I'm really okay.
I'll be perfectly fine after a little more rest.
Yes.
Okay. I'll see you in a bit.
- Hello, it's me. - Hi, Sun Nyeo.
- Do you need to make any deposits? - Yes.
- Hold on. Let me see. Here. - Thank you.
It looks like you had a great day yesterday.
At this rate, you'll own a building soon.
(Enter amount)
You're funny. Try this.
It almost tastes like ice cream.
It literally melts in your mouth.
- There you go. - Thank you.
Have another great day!
I'll close the window.
He reminds me of when...
I ran a fried chicken stall with Sam Do.
Can we have two chickens and a soda?
Sure. Just a moment.
Here you go. Enjoy.
- Sir. - Yes?
- Let me help you. - What?
I used to sell fried chicken in a Daejeon market...
until a while ago.
I'll fry the chicken while you serve the customers.
Thank you so much.
(The best-tasting crispy chicken)
I'll fry you a delicious chicken in no time.
Hello, I'm Tae Pyung, the gentleman of trot.
I'm Lee Dong Sook, his manager.
It's a pleasure to meet you.
It's been a while since Tae Pyung did a live radio show.
- He'll need a lot of help. - Thank you.
I've never met such a beautiful manager before.
If you don't mind me asking, how do you know each other?
I'm his cousin.
Standby, everyone.
Good luck, Tae Pyung.
- Thanks. - You, too.
You can watch us online.
It's the Four O'clock Live Cafe.
With us today is the singer of...
"My Brother Goes", a revolutionary trot masterpiece.
Let's meet Tae Pyung. Hello.
Hello, everyone.
I'm Tae Pyung, the gentleman of trot.
Your nickname is "the gentleman of trot"...
and it suits you because you look great in a suit.
Does it? Thank you.
Since we're talking about suits,
I get mine at a tailor shop in Hyoja-dong that boasts...
a very long history.
The shop is called W Tailor Shop.
Check out the shop's website and social media...
if you want to see the best suits available.
I think I really should as soon as this show's over.
Before we start, let's listen to everyone's favourite song.
Can you sing "My Brother Goes"?
Sure.
Have one each.
- You, too. - Thanks.
Thank you.
Take good care of Tae Pyung for me.
Is he really still single?
Of course he is.
I guess you could say he married his music.
Thanks for this.
Sure.
I'm crazy, crazy, crazy for you
What should I do?
When I'm asleep I think of you
Until the sun rises
- Look after him. - Sure.
I'm so lonely I get angry
I miss you so much
My brother goes, goes, goes
He goes at full speed
He is coming to you
Do not say a word
Just hold me tight
To you, right now, immediately
My brother goes
(Meesa Apparel)
Sir.
We got a call from the bank.
They will declare us bankrupt.
I got the call, too.
What will happen to Meesa?
The creditors are already meeting up...
to discuss legal management procedures.
Will you stop it?
I know all that. Leave me alone!
You can't just sit around and do nothing.
We should put out a statement...
The real issue is our liquid capital.
How did you sell off our assets and put us in this situation?
No company wants to buy our outdoor clothing brand...
and the price of our land is forecasted to drop further.
We can't sell our menswear line just to save the company.
We're a piece of meat left out for the wild beasts.
Do you get that?
Everyone's drooling, waiting to take a bite out of us.
They're waiting for us to give up.
Forget it. Leave.
Get out!
- Too bad. - She bragged so much.
The company went belly-up at last.
Hello.
Hi, Ji Yun.
- Here's your script. - Thanks.
- Are you okay? - What do you mean?
Have you not heard?
Heard about what?
You'll know when you read the script.
Okay.
(Meesa Apparel)
Bankruptcy finalised?
The last commercial's on.
Up next.
Menswear brand Meesa Apparel...
was unable to repay their loans...
and their bankruptcy was finalised today.
According to the financial and fashion industry,
Meesa should have repaid Woosung Bank before the 5th.
They owed the bank eight million and couldn't come up with the money.
This afternoon, their accounts were frozen...
and bankruptcy was announced.
The lengths are slightly different.
Se Ji, stop colouring in the face.
It's a bit too dark...
and her expression's too rigid.
Let's fix that.
(Darling, Honey, My Love)
Are you okay?
Are you in shock?
I didn't think they'd actually go bankrupt.
I should do something.
I should meet with Dong Jin.
What is it?
Meesa Apparel's bankruptcy was just finalised.
- What? - I need you back.
I can't. I have a lot to deal with at my own store.
Meesa's the only thing my father left behind.
I can't lose it to anyone else.
I left Meesa long ago.
You can deal with it.
I have no one left.
No one to trust.
It has to be you.
I'm a stranger now. Do you trust me?
We never got along as husband and wife...
but as a person you've never let me down.
I need you.
I can't answer right now. Give me time to think.
Dong Jin.
Help my family.
If you're talking about Meesa,
there's nothing I can do.
Don't say no just like that. Help them out.
Yes, please.
You're the only person who can help Meesa out.
It took a lot of courage to come to me, but I'm sorry.
The bankruptcy's finalised.
I can't help.
What now?
My dad made it what it is from nothing.
Do I have to watch it crumble?
Calm down, Hyo Won.
There's nothing I can do.
It's so upsetting.
Maybe...
this is a penalty.
Dong Jin was an important part of Meesa.
As soon as Dad died my mum and Hyo Sang...
took his CEO position and did a lot of bad things.
All her life, Mum was ridiculed for being a mistress.
Mum had bitterness in her heart,
and Dad always compared...
Hyo Sang to Dong Jin.
So Hyo Sang held a grudge against him.
I guess that's why he made a mistake.
His emotions kept for a long time exploded.
Even though what they did was wrong,
they are your mum and brother.
Other people might blame them,
but you shouldn't do so.
Mum is...
timid and easily moved to tears.
She must be very scared and upset by herself.
Then you should stay by her side.
I'll go back home.
I'm the only one who can protect Mum.
I'm glad you're here, Hyo Won.
How is Mum?
She's in her room. She is in shock,
so she's almost out of her mind.
Mum.
Mum!
Hyo Won.
Mum.
I was scared and exhausted.
Thank you for coming back.
Mum, I'm sorry.
It's my fault.
I even hit you.
I'm sorry.
It's my fault.
No, Mum. I'm sorry.
By the way, what shall I do?
Hyo Sang drove the company to ruin.
What shall I do?
Calm down, Mum. Everything will be fine.
I put in everything I have...
to pay off the debt.
What will become of us?
What if we are forced out onto the streets...
without any money?
Don't worry about it.
I'm doing a part-time job these days.
I can support you, so don't worry.
It's all right.
My goodness. What shall I do?
Dong Sook, you must be tired. I can drive.
You must be tired singing all day.
I should drive since I'm your manager.
I'm not tired.
By the way,
is it all right that we lie?
We're married couple, but we say that we're cousins.
That's no big deal.
We're not going to lie forever. It's just until you go into orbit.
It's going to be all right.
It's quite thrilling.
You're funny.
- It's Dad. - It is him.
Why is he going to the park when it's cold?
- I don't know. - Is he taking a walk?
There he is.
Wait a minute, Dong Sook.
Why?
It seems that he's carrying a cane.
Why is he carrying a cane?
What is he doing now?
I've been thinking that there's something strange.
I think Father has a problem with his eyes, Dong Sook.
What?
The cane...
looks like the ones for the visually handicapped.
That's impossible.
Dad.
Dad. It's me, Dong Sook.
It's me, Dong Sook.
I'm here. Can't you see me?
Dong Sook.
What are you doing here?
Dad.
What happened to you?
Father.
Don't be so surprised.
When people get old,
they get problems here or there.
In my case,
it was my eyes.
I didn't know that you were unwell.
I don't deserve to be your daughter.
- I'm sorry, Dad. - Don't say that.
You're such a sweet daughter to me.
Dad.
I'm sorry I didn't tell you earlier.
I thought you'd be less shocked...
once I get used to it myself.
I should have noticed.
I'm sorry, Father.
People have...
their own little inconveniences to some extent.
Don't complain about that.
That's life.
And...
I've seen my children make their own families.
I have no regrets.
What I'm sorry about is...
that I can't watch Da Jeong get married...
with my own eyes.
Also, I'm sorry...
that I can't care for Dong Jin's baby later.
My poor dad!
That's life.
It doesn't go as I planned.
Dad!
Stop crying.
- Why are you so drunk? - Stop it.
How can you drink in a situation like this?
Are you in a right mind or not?
I got drunk...
because I'm in a situation like this, Mum.
How can I stand it on a day like this if I don't drink?
How dare you answer back to me? You idiot!
Calm down, Mum.
Your dad devoted his lifetime to make the company grow.
You drove it to ruin in less than a year. I can't believe it.
I wanted to do well.
While Dad was alive...
he called me "Idiot!", "Fool!".
Those words...
pierced my heart.
I wanted to succeed...
and prove that Dad underestimated me.
Is this...
what you wanted to do?
I didn't know things would turn out this way.
It's driving me crazy.
Calm down, Hyo Sang.
- Take him upstairs. - You idiot.
You fool.
- You... - I'm Min Hyo Sang, the CEO!
He has no right to mope.
Your brother was never CEO material.
We should've let...
Dong Jin manage the company like your dad wanted.
I'm reaping what I sowed. This is all on me.
What now?
Now you get it?
You and Hyo Sang were out of your depth.
You brought this upon us.
You act like you don't care.
The company and our family's ruined.
How can you talk like that?
It's none of my business.
Hyo Joo, how can you say that?
What else should I say?
You're reaping what you sowed.
Accept the price and pay it.
That's all you can do.
How dare she.
She's a viper!
You evil brat!
Calm down before you faint again.
It's okay.
Poor me.
Then...
were you aware of Dad's condition?
I found out a while after he left home.
Why didn't you tell us until now?
You should have told me if not anyone else.
I'm sorry, Dong Sook,
but Dad told me not to.
Are you his son and I'm not his daughter?
How could you not tell me about this?
Dong Sook, calm down.
Your dad told him not to tell anyone.
Even so.
I'm his only daughter.
I had no idea he's going blind.
I whined about wanting to get married...
and grinned from ear to ear once I got married.
I'm the worst daughter a man could ever have.
I feel just as bad as you do.
I only found out before you did.
There's nothing...
I could do for him.
My poor dad.
I feel so sorry for him.
Stop crying. You cried so much in front of him earlier.
You'll drain yourself.
Is there a cure or treatment?
No.
Does your mum know?
She doesn't. I know it'll be hard, but pretend that...
nothing's wrong for now.
That's what Dad wants.
Okay.
I won't cry around him.
I'll hold it in.
Let me see.
Your fever's gone.
I'm fine now. How did the partnership signing go?
Very well, of course. But Yun Shil...
Dong Sook and Tae Pyung found out Dad's sick.
How?
They happened to see him in a park...
practicing how to use a walking stick.
Was Dong Sook very upset?
She cried a lot.
We agreed not to tell Mum for now. I thought you should know.
Okay.
I'll get dinner ready. You should shower.
Are you okay?
I just heard from Dong Jin.
Yun Shil.
How could this happen?
Dad was a tailor all his life.
He was happiest when he was making a suit.
What is he to do without his eyesight?
Are they still cooking?
Is dinner ready?
Yes, Mother, it's almost done.
What's wrong, Dong Sook?
Nothing's wrong. There's something in my eye...
and I just asked Yun Shil to blow it out.
Why are you even here?
Go and rest and leave dinner to us.
I'd like that.
Finally, I can relax while my daughter...
and daughter-in-law prepare my meals.
Dad's hungry, so move a bit faster.
We will.
What now?
You used to make up excuses to stay out of the kitchen.
Today, you volunteered to cook...
and are helping your dad eat.
What's the occasion?
Dong Sook's acting like the perfect daughter.
I'm sorry, Dad.
I was a useless daughter who only caused you trouble.
What's wrong with you?
Did you two fight?
No, Mother.
Now that she's married, I think she finally grew up.
It's high time she did, I guess.
Did you two argue about something?
What's going on?
Oh, right.
You weren't feeling too well. How are you now?
I feel better now.
I didn't know that.
I've felt that I'm in debt to you for 10 years.
I wanted to run away,
but I've endured it all along.
Was it all because of your lie?
How could you...
make such a lie?
Yun Shil.
You won't believe me,
but if it were to make you happy,
I could give you my heart, not just a kidney.
Are you trying to die?
You're drinking right after leaving the hospital?
Leave me alone. I don't mind dying.
I'd rather die than live without Yun Shil.
How could you say that to me?
She registered her marriage with someone else.
Why do you care about her?
Will you please get over her?
What should I do now?
She won't want to see me now.
But then,
if I were her, I wouldn't be able to forgive me.
I deceived her for over 10 years.
She must feel so angry and betrayed.
What are you talking about? How did you deceive her?
I should have told her.
I'm such an idiot. I'm a moron.
Stop it. What got into you? What are you doing?
Get a grip.
Why didn't he tell Yun Shil?
I thought he'd go straight to her.
What was he up to?
You aren't making any sense.
What are you talking about?
I can't give up. Not like this.
I'd rather die...
than let him take Yun Shil from me.
I don't care now.
You and I should both take our own lives.
You were still a student then.
Your dad's death alone was shocking enough.
Don't you ever blame yourself.
I won't let him control me like a child.
I wish that he suffers...
No, I wish he suffers more than I suffered.
- I... - I wish...
you wouldn't think like that.
Don't you hate him for what he did?
Why wouldn't I?
Just thinking of what he did to you...
still makes my blood boil.
Then why do you want me to forgive him?
If you spend your life hating him,
I think it'll only make your life difficult.
You know how there's the saying,
"The greatest revenge is indifference."
I wish you would take revenge the same way.
The two of you seem quiet tonight.
- I'm not in the mood. - Why? What's wrong?
No. It's nothing.
Did something happen?
Have they worn out already?
Bae Sam Do.
Get a hold of yourself. With a body like that,
you should be able to stand up to your wife.
I'll go take a cold shower,
and then I'll dance the night away with Sun Nyeo.
Put away the table and spread the bedding.
Not tonight. I have work to finish. You go ahead and sleep.
Bae Sam Do is fully prepared.
Let's dance the night away.
Enough with the nonsense.
Nonsense? Did you just say I'm talking nonsense?
Do you...
actually think I'd fall for your word three times?
Stop bothering me and just go to sleep.
Things were different then. Are you ignoring me?
Gosh.
If a lady says she doesn't want to be bothered,
a man should behave and listen. Why are you being so aggressive?
I wanted to spend some time with you, Honey.
I'm busy with work. You go to bed. I can't get anything done here.
Honey, wait. It's been a long time.
Has she gone crazy?
Is she rejecting me?
Hi.
Don't you have to go to work?
I have a program scheduled for this evening. I'll be leaving later.
Oh dear. My headaches.
Goodness.
Oh dear.
- Who is it this early? - Madam Ko,
People from the court are here.
They said it would be obstruction of justice if I don't open the door,
so I let them in.
People from the court?
We will proceed a provisional seizure of corporeal property.
What are you talking about? What gives you the right?
Woosung Bank has requested that we proceed a provisional seizure...
of the corporeal property Mr Min has secured. Let's begin.
- Yes, Sir. - Goodness.
What shall we do, Madam Ko? Oh dear. Oh dear.
Oh dear.
What should we do, Madam Ko? What shall we do?
(Seized Article)
Red stickers are everywhere. What's happening?
- Goodness gracious. - Mother.
- This can't be happening. - What should we do?
- They can't do this. - Excuse me. Please.
Goodness. Not the master bedroom.
The master bedroom? Not the master bedroom!
- Madam Ko. - Not the master bedroom!
- Oh goodness. - Not the bedroom. Please stop.
- Madam Ko. - What's happening?
Will we actually be evicted from this house?
You can't do this. You can't!
- You can't do this. Please stop! - If you continue,
you could be punished for obstruction of justice.
Mother. Please calm down.
Oh dear.
I worked so hard for all this.
This can't be happening.
I can't let them take this all away from me.
You can't. Please stop.
This can't be happening.
Please stop.
(Tonelli Signs Contract With Wolgyesu Tailor Shop)
Darn it.
- What is it, Ji Yun? - Something's happened.
- What is it this time? - Bailiffs from the court are here.
- There are stickers everywhere. - What?
I've succeeded, haven't I? My picture's in the papers.
I wonder who these men are. They sure are handsome.
- I agree. - CEO Lee.
- Can I keep this newspaper? - Of course.
I want to show this to my wife.
I get the feeling she's ignoring me and looking down on me these days.
I want to prove to her how successful I am.
Why would Sun Nyeo look down on you?
She has started working.
Now that she's earning money, she's started to walk all over me.
Mrs Bok wouldn't do that.
That's right. She's not that type.
No one would know until they see it.
I'm going to go show this to my wife and have lunch with her.
You do that, Sam Do.
Try this.
What do you think?
It just melts in your mouth.
The base of this sauce here was passed down from...
my great-grandmother.
- I added my specially-made sauce. - I see.
This was a hit at Daejeon Jungang Market.
I don't know what to say. I'm so grateful...
that I can learn such a valuable secret recipe.
If you're that grateful, you could entrust me with your bank work.
Of course I will.
Shall we open an account right away?
- Yes, indeed. - Thank you.
Have another drumstick.
You should have it. You worked so hard making this sauce.
I'm sure I heard that she works in this market.
Try it with this sauce.
Oh dear. You got some sauce on your cheek.
What is that woman doing over there?
I'm sorry. I got more sauce on your face.
You scum. What do you think you're doing?
How dare you hit on another man's wife?
Who are you, Mister?
What are you doing to my client?
You should just go on doing your job.
How dare you hit on my wife by feeding her chicken? You scum.
- Scum? - There's been a misunderstanding.
- He's a client at our bank. - What? A misunderstanding?
I saw everything over there.
How dare you hit on my wife with your cheesy moves?
- You won't get away with this. - Honey. Stop!
Come here, you scum. I'll teach you a lesson.
- You won't get away with this. - Oh dear. Oh dear.
You'll break my neck. Be careful. My head!
- My head, my head. Ouch! - My head, my head. Ouch!
- I told you to stop, didn't I? - Wait. Ouch.
- Wait! Let go! - Ouch!
Have you lost your mind?
In financial banking, gaining trust is essential. You made a scene.
The market is my workplace. What would they think of me?
Do you think they'd be able to trust me with their money?
Why did you feed a stranger chicken in the first place?
That was nothing. I was just doing my job.
You've changed.
After starting work, you've been pushing me away and ignoring me.
Before it's too late, you should go see a doctor.
Why? Did I get hurt? I don't see any blood.
You should go to a mental hospital.
I think you've come down with a severe case of delusional jealousy.
- What? - This is exactly why...
similar people should get married in order not to have any trouble.
You were way over your head.
You met such an amazing woman like me...
that you can't live a day without being anxious.
You're in a chronic and habitual state of mind.
You're late.
The janggi match lasted a while.
Did you bet over lunch?
As usual.
I'm tired.
Why are his shoes so dirty?
My goodness.
Was the janggi game that tiring?
He never used to take a nap.
He should hang up his coat.
Did he win money playing janggi?
Why is it so heavy?
My goodness.
It's a stick.
This looks like the one that blind people use.
(The Gentlemen of Wolgyesu Tailor Shop)
What is this? Why do you have it?
Did you have a drink?
People who work sometimes drink.
What's the problem?
I can't believe these stickers are in my own house.
Did the bank take all your assets as collateral?
- They called a board meeting. - How did it go?
Let's go to Anseong.
I wasted 10 years of my life,
but I decided to get over it and move on.
I'll see if there's a way to make up for the lost 10 years.