BioskopKeren
[Current Time 9:15]
I remembered that you were the onefrom the Namyeong Station accident.
Do you want to meet now?
I'll wait at Namyeong Station.
"Don't leave" is what she said.
I'm scared.
Don't leave.
I've disappeared, and I'm gone.
I don't know if this place is a dream.
Is this the world I live in?
Am I falling into time somewhere?
I do not know.
Strangely, what she said to me...
"Don't leave".
That is all I can recall.
[Tomorrow With You]
The customer's phone is turned off.
Did something happen to him?
Oh, my legs hurt.
Tonight, on subway line oneat Namyeong Station
an unidentified manwas found passed out.
The subway was stopped for 30 minutes,causing delays for passengers.
This is the next news item.
Due to increasing household debt
next year's consumption growth ratewill need to be lowered by 0.63 percent
the Korean Economy Research Centerhas concluded.
The Korean Economy Research Centerpresented these results...
Hello.
The hospital?
What happened?
Are you okay?
I asked if you're okay.
What did the hospital say?
Did they say you could just leave?
What's that look in your eyes?
Why are you looking at me like that?
I'm wondering if this is a dream.
Maybe I should have gotten hurt.
What did you say?
You look like youworried about me a lot.
But nothing's wrong with me.
How should I put it?
It's almost as ifI've done something wrong.
Is this hospitalmaking prank calls, or what?
You're fine, so why did they calllike something was really wrong?
Here.
Thank you so much,but I don't think it's right.
I'll be going now since you're fine.
Didn't you comebecause you were worried about me?
You look very pale.
You must've been startled.
Nothing happened, and you're okay.
So, let's just go our own way.
You asked to meet at Namyeong Station.
I just saw the text message.
You sure read it quickly.
You said you remember who I am.
We did survive death together.
Aren't you being too cold to me?
Yes... I remember it all.
You're the guy from the subwayseven years ago.
I was surprised and happy to find you.
So, I waited all day for you.
Do you know what I was thinkingwhile I waited?
The man that survived with me...
I had always been curious to knowif he was living well.
But, you are living so extremely well,so I thought it was a relief.
I was so thankful.
I guess we did end up meetingsince we're both alive.
Then I suddenly got a call that youwere in the emergency room.
According to the nurse
she said you got hurt in the subwaytunnel and I thought, "subway again?"
My insides just dropped.
What kind of joke is fate playing?
I wondered if you were very hurt.
I had been so relieved to knowyou were healthy and living well.
Then we should...
live together.
Of course, we should live for likea thousand years. What are you saying?
Do you really want to live with me?
I'll live even if you tell me not to.
You promised.
We're going to live together.
What do you mean by that?
Are you joking around again?
Yoo So Joon!
Oh, I'll get going now.
Take a taxi.
No, it's okay.
You don't have your wallet.Your bag is in my car.
Oh, right.
Do you need money for a ride home?Take this.
No, I can pay for it with my phone.
- Hey...- I'll call you.
Yoo So Joon.
Thanks for coming.
- What's wrong?- I'm hurt.
Where?
I was in the emergency room.
Oh no! Where's your car?
- I don't have my car.- You don't?
Why would I use his money?
Guys, I'm sorry,but I'm going to head home.
Ki Doong, can I borrow your card?
Yeah, sure.
Go home and rest.You're probably not feeling well.
But, you can't just leave like that.
Why were you passed out in the tunnel?Tell me that.
Come on. I just got out of the hospital.
- You look fine.- Ouch! I'm in pain.
I'm just so curious.
Hey, hey. He says he was drunk.
I was born in the same hospital as you,and I've seen all sides of you.
Despite that, there are two thingsI have not seen.
You alone with a girl,and you passed out drunk.
But I saw both today.
I date girls all the time,and I've been passed out drunk plenty.
You just haven't seen it.
I'm not that interested in your life.
Still, just tell me about the tunnel.I'm so curious, it'll keep me awake.
I'm sure So Joon had his reasons.
Yes, so what are his reasonsfor going into a subway tunnel?
- I'm curious. Aren't you?- No.
You're weird in my eyes too.
Hey, people can go inside subwaytunnels once in their lifetime.
I've done it, haven't you?
Does that make sense?Does that make sense to you?
Hey! Hey, Yoo So Joon!
What have you done all your life?You've never been in a subway tunnel?
Ask anyone on the street.They've all been in a subway tunnel.
Hurry up. Come on up.
I'm upset today.
Why do you twohave so many secrets from me?
What secrets?
Did you think I've never had suspicionsall this time?
After So Joon's parents passed away
I always thought it was strangehow he suddenly became rich.
Stocks?
Anyone would say that it's strange.
You're just as strange for accepting itas if it's normal.
You're right. It could appear that way.
Don't put on that fake act.
So Joon suddenly becomes rich.
You drop out of schoolto work for So Joon.
Hey, I'm just helping him.
To me, it looks like you putyour whole life on the line.
Even when So Joon was a teenagergoing through puberty
he didn't care at all if I wentinto his room or touched his stuff.
Now, he doesn't even let mecome near his house.
Don't ask me about it.
Even if I am living off of So Joonlike you say
I don't need to take care of himoutside of the company.
There is something going on with So Joonand you know that something.
There is nothing like that.
There's nothing?
There isn't.
Okay.
Why do I have his wallet?
You promised.
We're going to live together.
He sure has a way of talking.
Realtor needs to come with a warning.He's a dangerous guy.
I'll return your bag.How is 1:00 p.m?
Let's have lunch.
That would be rude of me.
You didn't by chance open my bagor anything, right?
Return my bag to me tomorrowin good condition.
I'll return your walletin good condition too.
Be careful of Realtor.
Song Ma Rin, Chiksa Girls' High School.
Okay. I'm confidentthat I can keep you well fed.
I'll be going now, Flower.
You have to say that.
Not Bap Soon, but Flower.
Do it for me.
Flower...
Flower.
Bap Soon. Yes.
You pass.
How can I help you?
Is there a restaurant here?
Whose name is the reservation under?
Yoo So Joon.
Follow me.
Why do you keep stealing glances?
It's creepy.
Why are you smiling?
I don't like it. Don't smile.
What are you looking at?
Stop it. What's wrong with you?
I can't smile, I can't glance.What am I supposed to do?
Should I just get lost?
No. Sorry.
What about my bag?
Is it ready?
And my wallet? Is it ready?
How are we supposed to eat all of this?
I wonder if we can do take-out.
You would be goodat running a household frugally.
But if you live with me,you won't need to be frugal.
We will be people with a duty to spend.
Did you say live together?
You promised to live with me.
So, the living togetheryou were referring to
it wasn't both of us staying alive?
It was the living togetherwhere you eat and sleep together?
Yes.
We haven't even held hands yet,and you want to move in together?
They say pigs are fed a deliciousmeal before they are slaughtered.
Are you feeding me this in orderto catch and eat me up?
Are you going to pay me, too?
I know second-generation rich kidsare so spoiled.
- I saw it on TV and movies...- Hold on.
I'm not a the second generationof a rich family.
- Third generation, then?- Forget all that.
Is the only way for a man and woman tolive in a house just moving in together?
Song Ma Rin, are you that one-minded?
I'm the type of woman who knowsten things if you teach me one.
I can see exactly what you're thinking.
Because of our past,I was being thoughtful of you.
Is this what I get in return?
I'm really disappointed in you.
What kind of person do you take me for?
A woman I want to marry.
What!
Not to date or just move in with.
But a woman I want to marry.
Marriage?
This isn't the best timing
but I feel like I'll waste awayif I wait any longer.
How do you feel about marrying me?
We could live in one house,intimately and lovey-dovey.
Crazy punk.
You should stick to asking meto move in with you.
Where are you going?
Hey. Song Ma Rin!
If marriage is too sudden,what do you think about dating?
Of course, with marriage in mind.
- What are you saying?- Wait.
Don't grab me.
Don't you dare touch me.
This isn't the way out.It's the restroom.
That's where I was headed.I need to wash my hands.
All right, I know. Let's go for now.
What do you know about me?
What do you really know about me?
Do you know anythingabout marriage, or women?
Do you know me?
I only asked the woman I want to marryto marry me.
Is getting a proposal from a mansomething to get so angry about?
What kind of proposal is so absurd,irrational, threatening?
This isn't is a proposal.It's some sort of ploy.
I know you may be taken aback.
This woman is the oneI'm supposed to marry.
I must marry this woman.
I have a clear conviction.
I have a feeling.
Don't try that with me.
Where are you even going?
Go away.
I'm not going to do anything to you.Don't get worked up.
Realtor! You scoundrel.
This is harassmentunder the pretext of marriage.
You could get in trouble.It's dangerous.
It's dangerous.
Why is this place so complicated?
He brought me into the thieves den.
I think we were meant to meet,and destined to be together.
A shared fate, if you will.
A shared fate or bad karma.
Seven years ago...
we wouldn't be here in this worldif we hadn't met on that subway.
You saved me, and I saved you.
Do you really think our fateis bad karma?
I think we are destined for each other.
You are just playing me.
I'm holding onto you like thisasking you to have a meal with me.
Come inside.
So, you're being sincere with me?
Yes.
Let me ask you one thing.
Do you love me?
I think I will die if I don't marry you.
So, give it some serious thought.
Flower.
Not Bap Soon, but Flower.
This...
is like a lump that's been in my heartall my life that is dissolving.
Is this ache an effect of that?
Are you not feeling well?
Flower.
Are you okay?
Flower...
[Driver]
Yes, Mister Hwang.I'm a little busy right now.
Chairman Yoo is with Bap Soon?
They are coming out togetherand leaving. Yes.
They are definitely not in anormal relationship.
The chairman has his armson Bap Soon's shoulder...
What? What? Her shoulder?
What about her shoulder?
He has it around her shoulder,and is holding her close.
Oh, Bap Soon is pushing him away.
Yes, now he is chasing after her.
Yes, he is.
Anyone can see that this is love.
It is passionate love.
Oh my. Yes, good job.
Oh my.
Customer, are you okay?
What? Yes.
Flower...
Flower?
Hey, Flower.
No, stop it.
- Flower.- Stop.
So, you can't ignore her?
Once she found out we were bothsurvivors of the accident
do you know what she said to me?
She says she's so thankfulthat I am alive.
She's so relieved.
How can I ignore a woman like that?
I know exactly what's going to happen.
So, you feel guilty leaving her to die.
Gosh, you sure talk in a distasteful way.
Be honest about it.
You believed me about telling youto have children.
Your heart started to beat faster,and you wanted to do it.
- You want to marry and have kids.- You're so childish.
What's their to hide between us?
How much do you think I trust you,in percentage?
About 120 percent.
At the most, being optimistic...
it's about two percent.
What's the reason for the remaining98 percent?
I told you that I just can't ignore her.
Yeah, it's natural to feel that heat.
We came to winter because youwanted cold noodles in winter.
You're making me feel hot.
Cold noodles are the best in winter.
This is something only we know,what else is there to time travel?
It's about finding the best places to eatand traveling to them.
That's the best part.
Yeah.
- Is it hard to chew?- I just took a big bite.
This place is known for their noodles.
You know if you really get married
the future you knowwill completely change.
A woman who wasn't in your fatehas suddenly come into your life.
A reset. You should expect a reset.
I suppose so.
Is that such a big deal?
What is it?
This is difficult for me to bring up.
Madam is asking me to dotoo many personal chores for her.
- Is that right?- Yes.
But, aren't they things you could do?
Well, if I could I would like to.
I would like to help her out.
It's just affecting my work.
Is she curious about Bap Soonand Chairman Yoo?
She wants you to lookinto their relationship?
She told me to keep it a secret from you.
Seriously?
It's so obvious. You need to grow up.
Even if Chairman Yoo is an idiot,would he date Bap Soon?
Just picture it. Think about it.
No, they really are dating.It was very extraordinary.
It must just be a fling,like young people do.
They're all like that.
Don't just stand there like that.You're making me nervous.
We're going to have to go a differentdirection with Sobeol district.
Why? LE Group isn'ttransferring their headquarters?
Because of legal issues,the transfer won't happen.
Look at the article.
Year 2019.
It's amazing every time I see it.
I've been curious for a while.
How come you don't bring anythingbeyond March, 2019?
Isn't it better for usto look further ahead?
Oh... it's just tiring.
It's so far to go there.
Sorry.
Should I come back?
No, no. Come in.
About today's management dinner...
I was thinking about doing itat my house.
- I actually have plans...- Oh, of course!
You went out of your way to invite us,so of course we should go.
Then I will expect you there.
- Yes.- Yes.
- See you later.- Okay.
Here. Drink this while you do it.
Why am I even doing this?
Friends are supposedto do these things for each other.
These are just the basics.
People would thinkwe are best friends, right?
Friend.
By any chance, are you dating anyonethese days?
No, why?
You aren't? Really?
What if I am?
Flower, where are you?Should we meet up tonight?
Well...
Yes. Go on.
Do you like being married?
How did you decide to marry Yong Jin?
Did someone ask to marry you?
Oh, they must be here. They're here.
Yes, I'm coming. Welcome.
- Hello.- Welcome.
- Welcome.- Thank you for inviting us.
- Hello.- Yes, hello.
Welcome.
Wow. This looks great.
Wow. This is a nice home.
- Come on in.- Hello.
The interior looks great.
Hello.
I really like your taste.
You have the same taste as I do.
Chairman, Chairman?
Please sit down.
- Sit down, Chairman.- Please sit.
Is this your first time here,Secretary Hwang?
No, I've been here before.
- I fixed the sink.- He fixed our sink.
Yes, I fixed it.
Do you have something to drink?
- Yes.- Do you have that schisandra drink?
Yes, I'll bring it out. Hold on.
You didn't say people would come now.
I didn't?
- I'm getting out of here.- Why?
Come here. Come on.
My friend here helped me a lot today.
I didn't prepare much,but please enjoy the food.
Thank you for the food.
Please enjoy your night.I'll be going now.
You should stay and eat with us.
Yes, you should.
Oh, I don't think so.
Have fun.
You're really leaving?
She's leaving? Really?
One moment.
Why are you sitting on the cornerlike that?
I'm comfortable here.
The food is good.
Just like your name, Bap Soon.
Look how much you enjoy your rice.
Don't you all think she looks familiar?
You do looklike I've seen you somewhere.
She's Bap Soon.
"Give me rice", Bap Soon.
You all know, right?
She still makes an appearance onlineevery now and then.
Oh, "Tomorrow's Morning".You're that Bap Soon.
- "Give me rice", Bap Soon.- Yes.
I really liked Bap Soon.
Thanks to you, Gun Sook,I get to see Bap Soon eat rice.
It's an honor.
Do you want an autograph?
Yes, yes. Right here, please.
Seeing the two of you living here,I want to get married too.
- Really?- Yes.
Yes, don't you have anyoneto introduce to him?
We should get Secretary Hwangmarried first.
What? Me?
Mister Hwang? What do you thinkof our Bap Soon?
I've thought you two wereperfect for each other for a long time.
I'm actually a pretty popular guy...
You two suit one another.
- You do suit each other.- Gun Sook.
Can you get me some water?
You can get it yourself.
It's over there.
Eat up.
Yes. Thank you.
Cheers.
Cheers!
What do you think, Chairman?
About Secretary Hwang and my friend?
Aren't they perfect?
- I don't know.- Why?
I know the gossip online isn't good,but she really isn't that bad.
She suffers so much because ofpeople's preconceptions.
She can't even get a job.
Maybe I was being too greedybecause she's my friend.
Honestly, Mister Hwang would bea little too good for her.
- A little?- A little bit.
What was that?
This was so expensive.
You did it on purpose, didn't you?
Yes, so that you would shut up.
I pitied you for being an outcast
so I hung out with you,and what do you do?
I don't thinkI can be your friend anymore.
Let go.
Clean it up.
Should we fight like dogs?Who has more to lose?
Go ahead if you think you can.
Why are you always trying so hardto drag me down?
That's the state you're in.Who are you blaming?
You should know your place.
You crazy...
You're ignorant with nothingbut strength.
You are more ignorant than I am.
Don't pretend to be cultured.I know your past, you wench.
Why don't you screamso everyone outside can hear?
- Are you all right?- Yes, yes.
Are you okay?
Keep eating. I'm fine.
I think you're drunk.
I have many courses.
How many have I had?
Do you think I've been your friendwithout knowing you look down on me?
Still, it seemed like youdepended on me. I pitied you.
See, you don't even know your place.
I just find you an easy personto keep around.
What?
Didn't you know?
Don't you know how easyand foolish you are?
So...
even if it's not me,if someone is a little good to you
don't get delusional.
Why don't you both stop?
Okay. Thanks for letting me know.
You think I'm an easy fool,and I hate you.
Let's not deal with each other anymore.
It's our problem.
I'd like it if you pretendednot to notice...
- Gosh, this makes me angry.- Excuse me?
Trying to stand out by poking peoplewhere you know it hurts...
I will remember youas that kind of person.
Let's see each other oftenfrom now on.
Oh.
The four of us can meet together.
With Song Ma Rin.
I was crazy.I should know what reality is like.
Look at you now. Look at you.
I'm not picking up. I'm not going to!
I'm dying of embarrassment,so stop calling.
Hey, who are you?
I think I've seen you here before.
You got my daughter, Ma Rin, drunk.It's you, right?
Oh, yes. Hello.
Why are you followingmy daughter around?
We are a very conservative family.Why are you here so late at night?
I haven't introduced myself yet.
My name is Yoo So Joon.
What is this English part? Ceo?
You're the ceo?
I'm the CEO.
- I'd like to buy you a meal...- Don't follow Ma Rin.
Look at the time.
CEO? What is that? How funny.
I told her to date a senior manager,at the very least.
- Mother.- How annoying.
Hey. You're really not eating?
I bought it for both of us.
I'm going to sleep.
My goodness.
You know that guy you came homedrunk with before?
- What?- Never mind. Forget it.
Oh, it's so good and chewy.
Hey, what does a CEO do?
It sounds very unstable,just by the sounds of it.
It's the chairman of the company.
- Huh?- I'm tired.
So, the chairman?
What are you doing?
I'm going to eat it.
I'll become a ghost who ate and died.
No! You'll gain weight.
Only I can eat it.
Seriously, your personality...
Oh, my word. Oh dear.
This place.
What is this place?
Oh my goodness.
Oh my.
Oh my goodness!
Excuse me. Excuse me, sir.
Excuse me.
Sorry to bother you,but I have a question.
Is there a companycalled "Myreits" here?
It's right upstairs.
So, it is here.
I received this business cardfrom the CEO here.
Is this Yoo So Joon the CEO here?
Yes, he is.Should I contact his office for you?
Oh, no.
It's good enough to know he is.
You look good in that suit.
You should lengthen the sleeves.
I just sent you an email.Please read it.
Bye.
I have a bad feeling.
Thank you for everything.
Realtor.
I wanted to call you that one last time.
I just don't think we suit one another.
I am lacking in so many ways.
I am not enough.
I'll keep this short.
"I really hope you don't get hurt".
"I want to remain a beautifulmemory to you".
"No, even that is selfish of me".
"I am a selfish woman andI will be like dust in your life".
What is this?Why is she going so overboard?
Why is it so long?
This would be like ten pages long.
Is she asking to break up,or is she holding onto me?
Does she expect me to read it all?
Why is she acting like that?Is she drunk?
Gun Sook is really awful.
I better tell all the girlsabout what you went through.
You shouldn't hang out with her either.
Of course. We only did because of you.
You're all I have, So Ri.
Realtor is really annoying too.
What about him?
He even asked to marry you.Why did he just watch you suffer?
He's the chairman and Gun Sook'shusband is the director, so why?
I told him to actlike he doesn't know me.
Still, if he likes you,he should say it.
Or he should've flipped the table over.
Don't insult Realtor.
You don't know anything.
He wasn't sincere to you at all.
He was just having some fun.
Isn't that obvious?
There's no reason Realtorwould be sincere with me.
Even if he was sincere,reality probably kicked in at Gun Sook's.
I really don't suit him.
Realtor, that punk, is not going to do.
Hey, the worst kind of man in the world
is a man who makes a womanfeel shabby.
I don't care how great he is.
If he makes the girl feel shabby,I will rip him apart.
It's my fault, my fault.It's my self-condemnation .
It's the fault of the guy who makesyou feel that way.
Hey, say no even if he offers.
Don't meet him.
I'm not going to.I already told him I'm not.
Good. My friend is smart.
Still, don't insult Realtor.He's a good person.
Also...
he called me "Flower."
Why are you eating chestnuts?
These are dates, not chestnuts.You're so ignorant.
These are dates?
Oh, I'm an urban man, so I don't knowmuch about agricultural goods.
Like fruits, vegetables, and fish.
What?
Mom, what are you doing?You must be crazy.
Where are you now?
Why would you meet Yoo So Joon?
I'm telling you,he suggested dinner first.
When I called Yoo So Joon,he said he'd come right away.
He said, "Yes, Mother".
How did you find that a guy like that?Really?
I'll meet him todayand take care of everything.
You pretend not to know anything,okay?
How did you even know his number?
We are not evenin any sort of relationship.
Mom, don't do this.
Don't you dare meet him.
I won't speak to you again.
Yoo So Joon.
Yoo So Joon!
Why are you here?
My mom made a mistake, so leave.
That wouldn't be polite.
Why would you need to be polite tomy mom?
My mom was mistaken about us...
Still, she called me.I can't just leave.
Wait, wait.
Hold on.
Didn't you read my email?
I didn't read it yet.
Well, this isn't right.
I have an important meeting today.I'll talk to you later.
Okay.
I don't want to be exposed to youmore than I already am.
It was a time in my lifewhen everyone adored me.
I was my family's hope back then.
However, the people who liked meturned on me in one quick moment.
"She won't do. We're tired of her."
"She's over with."
I spent my teenage yearsfacing all that rejection.
My dad left during that time.
I became my mom's pawnto find suitable husbands.
Like all those peoplewho once loved Bap Soon
your feelings you profess for mefeel like a fleeting bubble to me.
So, I'm afraid,and I have no confidence.
It may be my fault for that.
Unfortunately, that's just me.
You should leave.
Huh? Leave?
You want me to leave?
I said leave.
It's hard to even look at you.
But, what are we going to do?
In my eyes...
I see you telling me not to leave.
My mom is here.
I'll just say hello and come out.Wait for me.
Oh yeah.
I don't know.We'll break up next time.
[Cancel Email Delivery]
Let's go.
You got out already?
I said I was going on a date with you,and she told me to go.
Date?
Let's go to my place.
Beer?
Come in.
Wow.
You can wear these.
My place is kind of messy, right?
No, it's really nice.
You can sit here.
Ah, you can't go upstairs.
Why?
Privacy. Sit down.
Oh no. What do I do?I'm all out of beer.
I don't have a single can of beer.
I guess today is not a day for drinking.
Oh, that scared me.
Shouldn't we goto the convenience store then?
Let's just drink next time.You're okay with juice, right?
I suppose there's no choice.
We could go to the convenience store.
How can I act like things are normalwhile sober?
What is this?
Is this from the 90's?
Does he like this tacky style?
What's wrong?
What is this thing?
Hey, what... why are youputting on my shoes?
It just wrapped itselfaround my foot on its own.
- What is it?- Hey, take it off.
Wait a minute.
Take it off.
Hey, you can't justput these on like that.
I've never evengone outside with these things.
You didn't take pictures of these,did you?
There will be trouble if you takepictures and put them online.
People will come for you.There will be chaos.
- I'll just leave.- Why? Already?
Well, I wanted to see your place,and you're only showing me half.
And you're making me feel really awkwardover some shoes.
Sorry, sorry. I was wrong.Come back.
No, there's no beer either.
Your family will probablybe home soon anyway.
I don't have family.
My parents... died in a car accident.
So, come on in. It's okay.
I lost my parents early in life,but moved up in the world.
I suppose I'm someonepeople respect a lot.
Then what about beingan heir to a rich family?
Oh...
And I thought...
It does seem less complex.
I don't have any family,so I have a very free life.
There is no one who would meddlein my life.
Must be lonely.
Having no one to depend on,isn't it the same for you?
The great Song Ma Rin, is the sizeof all this too much for you?
This is enough to cover for you, right?
All I want is...
someone who likes me the way I am.
I want to be able to do somethingfor that person.
Someone who is comfortableand fun to be with.
I don't need anything great.That's the kind of person I like.
Nothing great?
You didn't expect anything great.
But, you did get something great.
You'd be perfect if you wouldstop talking about marriage.
Do you not have a midpointwith your personality?
You make itso that I can't have a midpoint.
What did I do?
What did I doto make you act so extreme?
I feel nervous leaving you alone.
I feel like something will happen.
I keep worrying.
I usually don’t worryabout other people.
Strangely, I really want to be involvedin your life.
I think that would be right.
- Right?- Yes.
Rather than being apart...
I think we should be together.
I don't think we shouldignore each other.
We should overcome everything together.
I think that is the right thing.
So, stay by my side.
So that I can protect you.
Put your future in my hands.
Future...
Just don't bring up marriage.
That makes you seem weird.
Well, if you leave out marriage...
I guess I can date you once.
Hey, then are we dating now?
Depends on how you do.
We're really dating, right?
Why are you coming so close?
Huh? It's just...
I want to confirm it.
Are we really dating?
Oh, by the way...
You have really pretty hands.
You have a pretty nose.
- Ma Rin.- Yes?
Should we go?
Okay.
Can we do this?
Yes.
This soon?
- So Joon.- Yes?
I love you.
Me too.
I'm getting married.
- What, girl!- Wow.
- Congratulations.- Thank you.
- I'm getting married.- You're finally getting married.
Congratulations, really.
She's so pretty, isn't she?
Calm down, would you?
The invitations came out.You have to come.
- Congratulations!- Congratulations!
- Here you go!- Here.
Congratulations!
- Are you that happy?- Yes, so happy!
Yay!
Kiss, kiss, kiss.
Ma Rin, you have to do it.
Mother, please let me marry Ma Rin.
I will take good care of her.
Mother, please.
What now? Oh my.
What, what?
Are we getting married?
Taking the picture now.One, two, three.
That's great.
Lower the heart a little.
Just a little bit. We'll go again.
One, two, three. That was great.
Can the bride smile a little bit more?That's good.
Okay. One, two, three.
Let's go. One, two, three.
Se Young, let's leave early today.
We need to get readyfor So Joon's wedding tomorrow.
It's already tomorrow?
Get ready to leave.
How many days are you goingto stay up working late for?
So Joon's getting married.Why do I need to get ready?
I'm not the bride.
We have to take pictures tomorrowand so on.
I'll go to the store.Do you want something to drink?
Get me some cigarettes.
I said drink.
That jerk.
He never dated anyone.
Why is he in such a hurry?
[So Joon]
I'm in a meeting.See you at the wedding tomorrow.
Hey, Shin Se Young.
Is she busy?
Is she mad at me about something?
She won't even show me her face.It's kind of hurtful.
She's been working really hard lately.
Still, I'm getting married tomorrow.
You know that's how Se Young is,and we don't have time for dinner.
How do you planon moving all this today?
Where is your new apartment?
Me? I'm moving to yours.
What?
I'm moving to your place.Isn't that the obvious thing to do?
Crazy punk... crazy.Hey, no you can't.
I have my personal life too.You didn't even ask me.
It's so nice moving in here.
I just feel a bit guilty.
For what?
It feels like you have two homes.
Are you really not going to tellMa Rin about the other world?
She is your family now,so shouldn't you be honest?
Even if I tell her the truth,I can't be honest about everything.
What else are you hiding?
Nothing. I'll tell you everything later.
Hey.
What do you think marriage is?
A housemate with a lifelong contract.
Gosh.
I guess that's not wrong.
I don't know why people put so muchmeaning into marriage.
You can just live the way you didwhile respecting each other's style.
You can live comfortably like that.Don't you think?
Maybe not.
I'm getting married tomorrow.
To that man I met on the subway.
I'll live a good life.
Let's go!
It's a rain shower.
Bride and groom, enter.
Even on a daywhen rain falls from a clear sky
there will be many days in lifewhen it will rain.
When it does, these two peoplewill join hands tightly.
They will be each other's umbrellas.
They have promised toprotect each other with love's umbrella.
Kiss, kiss, kiss, kiss, kiss!
It's really amazing.
What is?
You said it seemedlike it would rain today.
You told me we shouldn't doan outdoor wedding.
You trusted the weather forecastover my senses.
That's the strange part.
How are you alwaysmore precise than the forecast?
Here we go.
Look here and smile.
Yes, that looks good.
One, two, three.
That looks good. Everything's great.
Now, face each other lovingly.
Good. Don't move. Just like that.
Okay. One, two, three.
Mine... my husband.
He is really handsome.
Is he dead?
He's alive.
He is alive!
He's my husband from here,and he's my husband from over here.
See you later, mine.
Wait a minute.Where did mine go?
Here he is!
Hold on now.Where did mine go?
There he is!
Mine, mine... where are you?
There he is.
Why are you coming out?You should go in.
It's your first day at worksince we got married.
I've always wanted to do this.
What a strange thing to want to do.I'll be going now.
Honey!
Have a nice day.
My husband.
Come home early.
Go on inside.
That man and I...
That woman and I...
- got married.- got married.
BioskopKeren.CO