Mr Lee, your retirement
ceremony today was so glorious.
I shed tears since it was so touching.
All the suits Mr Lee has made...
for 50 years were there to see.
That's right, Mother. Our
customers gathered in suits...
that were popular over time.
It felt like I was watching a fashion show.
It must have been amazing.
I wish I were there to see it if
only I haven't had work today.
Why didn't you go there, Grandma?
I didn't go there since I didn't
want to spoil the mood...
by crying on such a good occasion.
You deserved it.
How do you feel?
My sight is better maybe
because I feel good.
Anyway, Yun Shil,
you went through a lot of trouble.
It was nothing.
What do you mean it was nothing?
You planned the retirement ceremony
and prepared food all by yourself.
You're such a dullard to brag
about your wife all the time.
I'm not bragging.
I'm just stating the fact.
Shall I stop?
I'll stop now. That's what she says.
- Goodness.
- He obeys his wife so well.
I've been a tailor for all of my life.
I was a diligent tailor to my customers.
However, I was lazy...
taking care of only one person, Gok Ji.
There's a saying that the beacon
does not shine on its own base.
I thought she would always be there for me.
I've delayed viewing flowers,
viewing autumn colours and snow
for next year all the time.
I kept saying "next year".
And then here I am now.
I decided to spend the
last days of my life...
entirely for your mum.
However, I'm worried that your
mum might have a hard time...
taking care of my eyes,
opposite to what I wanted.
That's how I feel now.
The suits were your priority all along,
and now I am number one to you.
I'm not sorry about that.
I'm glad that I am treated well.
Here's another dullard, I may say.
He's right.
To keep the good mood,
let's hear a song from Father!
- What?
- What did he say?
- A song?
- Right.
You're right. I should sing
a song on such a good day.
I give this song...
to my love, Gok Ji.
Besame
Besame Mucho
On a silent night when the
Lila flowers were falling
Besame Besame Mucho
Send me the scent of Lila flowers
Besame Mucho
A pretty young lady like a Lila flower
You're a lonely Santa Maria
Besame Besame Mucho
Send me the scent of Lila flowers
- Encore!
The person you're calling is not answering.
Leave a message after the beep.
Everyone is ignoring my calls as if
they've signed a pact or something.
I can't believe this.
Have you found a place to move yet?
Can't you see that I'm calling
everyone I know to borrow money?
Why are you even asking?
To make my blood boil?
Why are you taking it out on me?
How much do you need?
- Shall I lend you some money?
- You're so heartless.
How many flats do you own...
in Gangnam and Gangbuk?
You can obviously see that your
brother and I are going crazy...
because we're about to be out
on the street. And what?
"How much do you need? Shall
I lend you some money?"
Are you expecting me to rent one
of the flats out to you for free?
Do you think I'm a beggar?
I'm going to say no even if you offer.
I don't want your flat!
Why are the two of you being like this?
Please calm down.
I was going to think about it if you
implored me. I shouldn't bother.
Are you pouring oil on the flames now?
Are you loving the fact that
I'm completely broke now?
That's enough, Mother.
You're being childish.
Childish?
Whose side are you on?
Be honest with me.
Are you on my side or on Hyo Joo's side?
Talking about things like that
won't help us in any way.
You should try to get on Hyo Joo's
good side to get a place to live.
Nothing good will come out of
losing your temper like that.
Do you have no pride or what?
Why should pride even
matter in this situation?
You frustrate me so much.
What?
That must be Hyo Sang.
"You frustrate me so much"?
How can she talk like that
to her mother-in-law?
Gosh, my pride has been shattered.
People are so ungenerous and ungiving.
I'm the one who helped them
get to where they are now.
Even my relatives are avoiding my calls.
We were too naive.
Well...
You have a stable job.
Can you take out a loan?
I already told you.
I already borrowed the
maximum amount allowed...
because you asked me for
money as a wedding gift.
Gosh.
People will think that I asked
you for a huge fortune.
My gosh, I'm so upset.
I'm tired. I'm going to get some rest.
- She's acting strange.
- In what way?
Ever since we went bankrupt,
she's been rude to me. She
talks back to me, too.
She's gotten so cheeky.
She's a sensitive person.
Try to be more understanding.
My goodness...
Honey.
Gosh, it's so cold.
You should've waited inside.
I'm all right. But I need you...
- to go somewhere with me.
- Where?
You'll find out.
Oh, that guy...
It's you.
I shot that commercial a little while ago.
I didn't know it'd be out already.
Why didn't you tell me?
Handling everything alone
must've been stressful.
You've been stressed out
with your family matters.
Still, I should've been on set
to take care of things for you.
You look even more dashing in it.
What if you really become
globally famous...
like my mum said?
Fame doesn't come that easy.
I shot it thinking it'd be...
my last commercial because I'd
be assigned to a school soon.
It's already over.
Honey, you're so awesome.
What is this?
A long-term lease agreement for this house.
You've been having such a hard time...
trying to find a place to live.
I signed a long-term lease for
this house with the money...
I earned with the commercial.
- Tae Yang.
- It's small and shabby,
but it can be a shelter for
your family for the time being.
What do you think?
That's crazy. I can't accept this.
- What's the matter?
- You even lent me money.
I don't want to be more indebted to you.
I don't want you to feel indebted.
Put yourself in my shoes. If I'm in a bind,
will you turn a blind eye?
I know that you won't.
The same goes for me.
- But still...
- Also, if we break the lease,
I won't be able to get the deposit back.
That will be a waste.
The lease is for two years.
If your family moves out because
the situation improves,
I can take over the lease.
There's no need to feel indebted.
It took me a whole week to find this house.
Please accept my sincere gesture...
and live here with your mum.
I'm so happy and grateful to be
able to do something for you,
so don't take my happiness away from me.
Tae Yang.
Don't tell your mum that I got this lease.
I'm worried it might
make her uncomfortable.
I'm grateful...
and sorry.
I do need to wait until I
get assigned to a school,
but I passed the exam,
so don't worry about me.
I need to establish my career
as soon as possible...
so that I can take great care of you.
How did I meet such a
wonderful guy like you?
I must've saved the world at
least 10 times in my past life.
Then I must've saved the
world at least 100 times.
You even have a way with words.
You're honestly so sweet.
Thanks...
for accepting it.
I should thank you.
I'll be grateful for the rest of my life.
Mr Lee's retirement ceremony
made me think of this.
I'd also love to have...
a retirement ceremony when I'm
older and wiser in about 30 years.
Thinking about it got me emotional.
I hear you.
When I first heard that Mr Lee
wants to move to Gangneung,
my heart ached so much as
if it's been punctured.
But then I thought about it...
and realised that he'll
really enjoy his time there.
He will.
Couples must have...
each other's backs especially
when they're older.
Let's try to be more caring
toward each other...
and love each other more
passionately, okay?
All right.
By the way,
isn't today that day?
I told you.
I gave up on having a baby. I
won't stress you out about it.
They say that age is nothing but a number.
That's so not true.
Every year, I feel the difference.
Our batteries have been depleted.
Both of us...
are still too young to feel depleted.
My battery is still at its fullest.
Goodness, whatever.
Move over. Gosh.
Are you going to bed already?
I'm tired.
Gosh, where's the blanket?
Why are you tired, Honey?
Go away. Stop coming on to me.
Gosh, seriously.
Sun Nyeo, please.
It's so nice to lie down next to you.
- Sun Nyeo...
- I'm exhausted.
I'm not even in the mood for it.
What are you talking about?
You don't understand romance.
Romance doesn't give you food.
Let's give up on having a baby
because it just won't happen.
I'm going to focus on
preparing for retirement.
If I try a little harder,
I'll be awarded for my
performance in this quarter.
Gosh, stop going on about it.
The prize is 40g of gold.
I'll make sure I get it
no matter what happens.
You're a gold-grubber.
How can you think that 40g of gold...
is more important than your husband?
I'm speechless.
I want that 40g of gold.
I'm so exhausted.
It was a long day, wasn't it?
It was pretty hectic,
but it felt rewarding and I'm
proud of myself. It feels good.
You did really well today.
Come sit here.
Since you worked so hard today,
I'll give you a foot massage.
You don't have to.
You shouldn't resist when I
offer something like this.
How does it feel getting a foot
massage from your husband?
It feels so refreshing.
It does, doesn't it? You'll feel
even more refreshed in the morning.
You can count on it.
I'm all done.
- Thank you, Yun Shil.
- For what?
For doing so much for my
dad's retirement ceremony.
Thanks to you, Dad's
last day as a tailor...
will be more memorable.
I don't know if I can be even half
as good as he was as a tailor.
I still have a long way to go.
Once we get the time,
let's put our heads
together and think about...
how you can become a better tailor.
- What's this?
- It's Yun Shil's diary.
When I moved into this house,
Yun Shil was in such a hurry to
leave that she left this behind.
I was curious so I read
through a few pages.
I'm giving you this because I thought
this might help you move on.
I barely escaped and ran away to Seoul.
I'm a stranger here and I
have no one to rely on.
But knowing that he's not here,
I feel like I can finally breathe now.
I've come this far,
but what if he finds me?
I'm scared he might find me again.
He ended up finding where I was.
No matter how far I run away...
or work to pay back the money
I owe, it's was no use.
If I could, I would give him my kidney...
in order to end this ill-fated
relationship with Gi Pyo.
But there's nothing I can do.
I feel so suffocated.
Stop trying to run away!
Tomorrow is the day I marry Gi Pyo.
I've come this far for I
have nowhere to run away to.
I've tried telling myself to
marry him out of gratitude.
But I can't help feeling
like I'm entering a dark...
prison where there's no
exit nor a beam of hope.
Will I be able to do this?
I'm scared and I feel hopeless.
Gi Pyo. You're my son,
but you should have at least a
little bit of conscious in you.
Since she was in the peak of her youth...
up until now, you kept her
by your side with that lie.
It's not too late now to let her
go and live her life in happiness.
You've tortured her enough.
So wish her happiness with a good heart.
Please come back to Anseong with me.
You'll have to pay for your
sins if you go on like this.
Are you crying?
Why shed tears so early in the morning?
To think that you and Father won't
be sitting here at the table...
with us from tonight, makes me cry.
If Mother and Father leave,
I'll be so sad and things won't
be the same around here.
If your mother-in-law isn't here,
you'll be happy there's no
one here to nag at you.
Don't say such a thing. I've
never thought like that.
I'm just kidding. It's a joke.
Oh dear.
If I'm not here, you're
the lady of the house.
You can't be so weak hearted.
Mum. Why is Yun Shil crying?
It's a secret between us two.
Stop crying now.
In order to give birth to a
child, you must have larger hips.
How do you expect to have
a child with those hips?
Mother. You're embarrassing me.
- Let me see.
- What?
In order to have at least three children,
your hips should be this
large, don't you think?
Stop it. That's absurd.
I'll take good care of the family.
Don't worry about us here.
Just enjoy your newlywed life.
If there's anything you'd like
to eat or you need, let me know.
I'll deliver it to you
as fast as lightening.
Next year,
I'm hoping you'll have a baby in your arms.
We've agreed not to get too
stressed out about that.
It's our turn next.
Please accept our bows.
Please take good care of Da Jeong
as if she were your own daughter.
Of course, Father. Please don't worry.
I'll make sure to visit
you often on my days off.
If you come too often, you'll be
interfering our newlywed life.
Once a month will be enough.
Yes, Grandfather.
Tae Pyung's new song
ranked 12th on the chart.
We only have his success
to look forward to now.
Don't worry about us now. Just
focus on enjoying your lives.
If the song ranked 12th,
and if you move up one each month,
by the time we move back, you'll
be on the top of the chart.
Goodness, Mum.
I'm sure no one can think the way you do.
Whether you choose to remain
at Wolgyesu Tailor Shop...
or decide to return to Meesa Apparel,
I leave that to you to decide.
We have Sam Do and Ms Geum
to run Wolgyesu Tailor Shop,
so don't worry and discuss
things with Yun Shil.
I hope you'll make a wise decision.
I will, Dad.
You're the lady of the house from now on.
Do your best managing the household...
and take good care of the family.
I will, Mother.
I think that will be
enough for our farewells.
Why don't we all go to the front
yard and take a family picture?
- Let's do that.
- That sounds good.
It looks perfect.
Everyone's in perfect position.
Sam Do. Stand closer to Sun Nyeo.
There you go. That's perfect.
Dong Jin and Yun Shil. You
two seem stuck together.
You two are too close. Move away a bit.
Let's see now. Mother and Father.
It will look nice if you hold hands.
Now, now. I know you're newlyweds,
but if you could restrain yourselves
a little, I'd appreciate it.
I thought you told me to hold
her hands with both my hands.
Everyone seems to be in position
and you all look very nice.
This is looking good.
Everyone say, "Kimchi".
- Kimchi.
Say, "Cheese".
- Cheese.
Everyone say, "Wolgyesu".
- Wolgyesu.
I never imagined we'd be
thrown out of this house.
My goodness. This can't be happening.
How did I end up like this?
I've always been able to
live off my tactfulness.
How could I have shot myself in the foot?
Calm down, Mum.
That's enough now. Our
cab is waiting outside.
Take care, Madam Ko.
Thank you for everything.
Here's this month's salary...
and some consolatory payment.
You don't have to give
me consolatory payment.
We should evacuate before
the new owner comes.
Haven't you finished packing?
I don't have much to pack. You can leave.
Goodbye, Stepmother.
So, are you going to
Cheongdam-dong or Seongbuk-dong?
- I haven't decided yet.
- Anyway,
whether you go to Cheongdam-dong
or Seongbuk-dong,
take good care of yourself
and keep in touch.
All right.
Goodbye, Hyo Won.
I guess you didn't like me,
but I liked you a lot.
I feel sorrier about parting with you...
without getting more closer,
than leaving this house.
I don't hold any grudges against you.
I guess you wouldn't need it,
but let me know if you
need my help at any time.
I'll be there for you right away.
All right.
Goodbye, Ji Yun.
I think our cab is here.
All right.
We're leaving. Take care.
Don't drink too much.
Take...
Goodbye.
You should start packing...
before the new owner comes.
- Remove all the distraint tags.
- What?
I'm the new owner of this house.
- I won the auction.
- What?
So...
- Then why...
- This house was my late mum's,
and mine.
I didn't have any other way
to get rid of lodgers.
You can stay.
She's so scary.
Watch your step.
Be careful.
Why are you standing still?
You can leave.
I'll be staying at a
friend's house for a while.
Ji Yun!
Does it mean...
that you'll separate with Hyo Sang?
It's not a separation.
I need some time to think.
What do you need to think about?
Are you going to think about
breaking up with Hyo Sang...
now that we're broke?
It's not like that.
I've been stressed out
and troubled these days.
I need to straighten up my thoughts alone.
Are you holding a candle to the sun?
Do you think you're more
stressed out than Hyo Sang?
Are you more troubled than Hyo Sang?
You don't console and encourage...
your husband in trouble.
You think of running away.
I'm not running away.
I need some time to accept this situation.
Are you yelling at me now?
Calm down, Mum.
She can think that way in her position.
Does Hyo Sang know about this?
Yes. I talked to him on the phone just now.
Let's go, Mum.
You shouldn't live like that.
Stop it, Mum.
Come back after you take some rest.
I'll text you the new address.
I'm sorry, Hyo Won.
You!
You must've married Hyo Sang for money.
If not, you can't do this.
Stop it.
Let's go.
What on earth is this?
What shall I do now?
It seems to be...
Dong Jin's neighborhood.
Well, it happened to be near his house.
Do you like it, Mum?
My goodness.
How could this happen to me?
My late mum said,
you can deceive a tiger
approaching from the back,
but you can't deceive your destiny
approaching from the front.
My goodness.
Even a tiger wouldn't want my destiny.
What's the matter with you, Mum?
People might see. It's embarrassing.
There was such a lot of fortune.
Neither have I spent it
nor even touched it.
What a state I am in!
How could my destiny...
turn out this way?
What should Hyo Sang and I do
if you keep acting like this?
You should muster up your courage.
How can I have courage in this situation?
It's a good thing that I
don't dive into Han River.
All right. Cry as much as you want.
You can cry if that makes you feel better.
It's all right, Mum.
You're here.
You're here, Mother.
What are you doing here, Tae Yang?
Well, Tae Yang...
and I looked for a place to live.
We looked hard to find this place.
I came first and looked around the house.
Mother, it's very warm inside since
the house gets a lot of sunlight.
Let's get inside, Mum.
I can't walk.
I feel like being dragged
to a slaughterhouse.
Why is it a slaughterhouse?
The four of us will live
happily in this house.
I can't walk.
It's cold, Mum.
Let's go inside.
Ride on my back, Mother.
Goodness.
- Watch out for your head.
- Be careful.
Honey!
Be careful.
It's cozy.
I cleaned up and wiped
the floor this morning.
You can unpack.
Do you like it, Mum?
All four of us...
have to live in here?
You and I share a room,
and Hyo Sang and Ji Yun
can stay in another room.
My goodness.
Is that all?
Even if I add two rooms, a
bathroom and a living room,
it's smaller than the living
room at our former house.
What's the use of having
a big and empty house?
It's a house for four of us,
and it's just right for us.
What's wrong, Mother? Are you all right?
This house is so small...
that I feel it lacks oxygen.
- I can't breathe.
- Mum, you're overreacting.
That's nonsense.
I'm serious.
I can't breathe.
Mother, follow what I do.
Inhale...
and exhale.
You're really something, aren't you?
I wondered...
who on earth won my house at the auction.
It was you!
So...
you put on a show because you wanted...
to kick me, Hyo Won and
Mum out of this house.
This is my house where I used to
live with my deceased mother.
You're the ones who barged
in and took over the house.
So?
Have you been sharpening your blade
for revenge for the last 20 years...
so that you can slash us off in one blow?
You kicked my family out of the house...
and ousted me from the company.
Was this your plan from the get-go?
None of this would've happened if
you and your mum hadn't acted up.
If you let Dong Jin become the CEO,
you wouldn't be in this mess now.
Let me make it clear to you once again.
I absolutely cannot give the
CEO position to Dong Jin.
Mum, Hyo Won and I risked...
everything we own to protect
our control over the company.
I'll utilise every legal rule
that exists to keep our control.
The board already made the decision.
Don't complicate things. Just
take your hands off the company.
Hyo Joo, please come to your senses.
Dong Jin is happy with
that employee of his,
and they have even registered
themselves as married.
You're wasting your time and energy
if you're doing all of this for him!
Shut it.
I'm going to do everything
in my power to make sure...
he returns to where he should be.
I will not let him take
the CEO position from me.
You just watch.
(Min Hyo Joo)
Yes, go ahead.
I asked you meet me at my office.
What's taking you so long?
I just got out of jail, you know.
I have a lot to catch up on.
You talked as if you'd...
be able to change Yun Shil's mind
right away if I help you get out.
What on earth is going on?
Things don't always work out the
way you want them to, you know.
What do you mean by that?
Are you giving up on your wife?
I'm not sure.
I don't know how I feel about all this.
I need time to think.
Wolgyesu Custom Suit Cooperative...
is a cooperative union of top-notch
tailors gathered with a goal...
of consistently producing the
highest-quality bespoke suits.
Our cooperative's official address...
will be here, Wolgyesu Tailor Shop...
located in Hyoja-dong, Seoul.
From now on, the members will co-own...
all orders and production. Selling
will also be done cooperatively.
I'm honoured to work with the
best tailors in the country.
This is our master tailor, Bae Sam Do.
This is our human sewing machine.
Last but not least, this
beautiful tailor here...
is my wife.
She's so beautiful.
My gosh, she's very pretty.
Have a seat.
You did such a great job.
That feels so nice.
You even give good massages.
Goodness. What an eyesore.
At home, Dong Sook and Tae Pyung
are lovey-dovey all the time.
And I have to put up with you
two when I'm at work. Gosh.
I want to live in a world
without newlyweds.
By the way, how are Mr Lee and Ms Choi?
I just spoke to Dong Sook on the phone.
They got there safe and sound. She
and Tae Pyung are on their way back.
Are Mum and Dad both okay?
Yes. She said the house is
actually very clean and cosy...
and that they'd be pretty
comfortable there.
I see. I'm glad to hear that,
but it still worries me
that they're there alone.
I'm thinking about visiting
them on my day off.
We'll announce the Employee of the Month.
It's Bok Sun Nyeo. Please come forward.
Gosh, me?
(Employee of the Month Award Ceremony)
Employee of the Month, Bok Sun Nyeo.
This person has been carrying out
all of her given tasks efficiently,
and her strong work ethic has set
an example for her co-workers.
Hence, she has been chosen as
the Employee of the Month.
Thank you.
The Employee of the Month, Bok Sun Nyeo,
will receive cash prize as
well as 40g of pure gold.
I'll work harder from now on.
I can do it!
This is the schedule for this week.
My gosh.
He's booked back to back with TV shows.
Tae Pyung's song is so popular
these days, you know.
We actually tried to cut down.
Is it still too much?
No, don't worry. I should be
grateful for the opportunities.
By the way, is the CEO still abroad?
I'd love to meet him so that
I can thank him in person.
My boss arrived yesterday. You
two should be able to meet soon.
What's he like?
There's no photo of him on your website.
I'm just curious.
Is he broad-minded and fun?
Or is he more of the intellectual type?
Is he older?
My boss is a woman.
- A woman?
Yes.
Lee Yeon Jun is a masculine name.
I thought it was a man.
Me, too.
My goodness...
Stop crying, Mum.
I'm worried that you might faint.
I shouldn't have listened to Hyo Sang.
We lost everything we had.
What a disaster...
He meant well.
Don't be so upset. Lie down, Mum.
I need a bed. I can't
lie down on the floor.
It hurts my back!
We should buy a bed first thing tomorrow.
All right. I'll buy you a bed tomorrow.
Mother, I'm coming in.
Come in.
I changed the door knob and
also fixed all the lights.
Thanks.
Tae Yang, are you looking down on me...
- because I'm penniless now?
- Pardon?
Who told you that you can change
our door knob and light bulbs?
Please, Mum. He did all the work.
Why are you being mean to him?
You're hugely mistaken if you
think that you can go ahead...
and marry Hyo Won just because
our family went bankrupt.
My opinion of you has not
changed even by one bit.
I should get going now.
I know how distressed you are,
but please don't skip meals.
Please cheer up.
You don't need to see me out.
Stay with your mum.
Why are you taking things out on Tae Yang?
He made such a big
sacrifice for our family.
He made a sacrifice for us?
What do you mean by that?
Never mind. It's nothing.
I'm going to say goodbye to him
and head out for my shift.
What's she saying?
I hope your mum pulls herself
together soon. I'm worried.
She's just shocked by what happened.
She'll get better soon.
She's really good at adapting
to new surroundings.
Why are you looking at me like that?
I thought you were the spoiled
youngest one of the family,
but I'm realising how mature you are.
To be honest, I never thought that
you'd handle this so maturely.
Everyone is extremely stressed out,
so I thought I should try to
be an anchor for my family.
I'm quite great, aren't I?
"Great" isn't enough.
You're amazing.
Thanks for the compliment.
Where's Hyo Sang by the way?
I'm not sure.
Ji Yun left to stay with her friend,
saying that she needs some time to think.
Why does she need time to think?
I don't really know.
I guess she has a lot on her mind
because of my family's situation.
Hello.
Hey, Tae Yang.
I heard you passed the exam. I'm
so impressed. Congratulations.
Congratulations, Tae Yang.
Congratulations.
Thank you.
I'm so proud of you.
Hold on a second. Then what will
happen to your modelling career?
Wouldn't you regret letting it go?
I thought of it as a short-term
thing, so I won't regret it.
Do you want a cup of tea?
Yes. Thanks.
Have a seat.
Gosh, why are you looking so tired?
Did you do some sort of manual labour?
Hyo Won's family moved today,
so I helped them unpack. I
must look pretty rough now.
Where did they move to?
It's close to your place.
What? Are you saying Eun Sook
moved to this neighbourhood?
The house is a lot smaller compared
to where they used to live.
She's having a hard time adjusting.
She always talked about
how much she hates...
Hyoja-dong and this shop.
It's so ironic that she's back here now.
You're right.
She used to live in this neighbourhood?
Yes, she used to work as a
bookkeeper at our shop.
I had no idea.
Look at this.
(Wolgyesu Tailor Shop)
How is Hyo Won?
She pretends to be okay.
She'll get used to it.
She's cheerful and positive.
Are you feeling better?
I'm trying to forget about it all.
I'm angry that...
I wasted 10 years of my life,
but at least now I know the truth.
I think it's a relief.
Yes. Now you have Dong Jin,
- focus on happy thoughts.
- I will.
Is Dong Jin very busy?
He's working on the Tonelli deal,
and Meesa Apparel wants him to return.
He has a lot to think about.
- Do you mind?
- How do you mean?
It would be weird for him
to go back to Meesa.
Isn't his ex-wife an executive?
I'm not that shallow or jealous.
I trust Dong Jin completely,
in any situation.
I don't mind.
Gianni.
How do you feel about my
returning to Meesa Apparel?
Well, I heard that Meesa
Apparel was going bankrupt,
but honestly, I'm surprised to hear that...
you're going back to Meesa Apparel.
I want to grow our Wolgyesu
Tonelli brand beyond Korea.
And make it the top suit
brand in Asia and the world,
with you, Dong Jin.
What's going to happen to our project?
I will be in charge of the
Wolgyesu Tonelli project...
until it will be stable.
If you're going to take on Meesa Apparel,
what's going to happen to Tonelli?
Tonelli won't accept any changes
that threaten the brand.
Will Mr Bae manage production?
Yes, he will, but don't worry, Gianni.
Everything's going to
be fine, as we planned.
Who's going to replace you?
I have someone in mind.
I trust your judgement, Dong Jin.
Okay, thanks.
Were you carsick?
How is your new house?
I see, that's great.
Sun Nyeo and I...
will visit you this weekend.
Try to make do until then.
I'll fix everything for you.
Sure. Goodnight.
Oh dear.
Did you go drinking again?
I was in a good mood,
so I bought a few rounds.
Look at this.
Sam Do.
I bet you've never seen anything like this.
What's this? "Employee of the Month"?
The branch manager said...
I'm his best employee so far...
because I made a record profit...
in a record-breaking short
period and he complimented me.
He just said that to make you feel good.
Is this gold?
That's 40g of 24k pure gold.
Let me see.
- It's real gold.
- It is, isn't it?
This is what your wife is capable of.
Do not belittle me.
When did I belittle you? I never did.
I've never seen such a huge chunk of gold.
Me, neither.
Is Dong Jin very busy?
Yes, with the tailor union...
and the Tonelli project.
I heard about Meesa Apparel.
He's focusing on Wolgyesu.
Does that mean he isn't interested
in going back to Meesa?
He's still thinking.
Don't you mind that he might go back?
If he works there,
he'll have to deal with his ex-wife.
It can't be helped if it's about business.
I don't mind.
Pour me one.
Can I have a soju, please?
What are you doing?
I'm joining so you don't look so pathetic.
Here.
Is this a joke?
Sorry.
This is a public area. Calm down.
How can I calm down? Get out of my face.
Why you...
How's Yun Shil?
Is she okay?
What do you think?
Does she blame and hate me?
Rather than that,
she's trying her best to forget about it.
Yun Shil...
will forget all about you.
She lost 10 years of her
life and that's enough.
I have a question.
Why didn't you tell her I
didn't donate a kidney?
I wanted to...
give you a chance to tell her yourself.
Rather than she hear it
from somewhere else,
I thought you should tell her
and ask for forgiveness.
That would make it easier for her.
What a joke.
You knew I'd go to her so you waited.
It was to mess with me.
- Am I right?
- You said you loved her.
I believe it.
In the warehouse,
I saw you subconsciously
go to save her first.
I saw the love you talked
about wasn't all a lie.
I acknowledged that.
I didn't save her to gain
your acknowledgement.
That's not love.
Love...
is not fitting a person into what you want.
It's changing yourself to conform
with what the other wants.
Are you lecturing me?
Yun Shil...
was never on the same wavelength as you.
That's not love.
It's just an obsession.
So what?
- Did you do what she wanted?
- No.
I'm still trying.
I think and wonder every single day...
how to make her happy.
Because that makes me happy.
So...
if you sincerely loved her...
and feel bad for what you did,
I say it's best that you try
to think what you can do...
to make her happy.
- Did you have a drink?
- Do I smell?
I had just two shots.
Let's go inside, it's cold.
I talked to Mother earlier today.
They went for a walk on the beach.
Did they? Are they okay?
Yes. Your aunt...
renovated the house not so long ago.
It's clean and cozy.
She said Father will have no
trouble memorising the layout.
There will still be a lot
to do around the house.
They'll need bars on the
walls and safety measures.
I said we'd visit on our day off.
- Good.
- Is something wrong?
You look downcast.
I guess I'm just tired.
- Have you eaten?
- I'm not hungry.
You eat when it's time,
not because you want to.
That's what my mum said.
I learned it from her.
Come out in a bit. I'll set the table.
- Sorry, Mum.
- What now?
Why are you apologising
as soon as you come in?
What on earth is going on?
Can you please not shout?
I've been arguing all day.
I'm exhausted as it is.
Whose fault is this? It's yours.
- How dare you shout at me.
- I didn't think this would happen!
I'm just as upset as you are!
What on earth...
have you decided to do with your wife?
Are you splitting up?
Why would we split up?
She just needs time to think.
To think about what?
Of a way to run away,
- now that we're bankrupt?
- Mum!
Get a grip.
I'm positive that Ji Yun
married you for our money.
Can't you tell? She left as
soon as we went bankrupt.
It's not like that! Why
do you keep saying that?
You're so mean.
We're done for. We're ruined.
- We're all ruined.
- I'm home.
Mum.
I don't think I have much long to live.
I'm practically penniless.
What's the point in living?
You can't say that.
Things are bad now, but they'll get better.
How can it get better
when we lost everything?
You're so positive. Who do you take after?
Tae Yang said that's
what he likes about me.
I was wondering why you
didn't mention him already.
Was the house this big?
It's not a nice thing to say,
but I'm a bit scared.
What do you mean?
The huge house suddenly
feels so cold and empty.
It's borderline scary if you ask me.
I keep having bad thoughts.
Turnip soup?
I made some because
Mother said you like it.
Let's see.
Gosh, it tastes great.
I'm sure it does. I
followed Mother's recipe.
Why are you looking at me?
Looking at you makes me happy.
Do you know you say corny things
as if it's nothing at all?
That's the kind of sweet person I am.
Just watching you eat makes me feel full.
You can be just as corny.
We're a corny couple.
Are you happy?
I wonder if I'm making you happy.
I always do.
Of course.
I've never been this happy my whole life.
Thanks to you, I now have a family...
and thanks to them, I was able...
to overcome a rough patch.
To be honest, when I'm
with you and your family,
I don't feel so bad or angry about...
the 10 years I lost because of Gi Pyo.
Actually, because I fled to
Seoul to get away from him,
I got a job at Wolgyesu,
I met your parents,
and then I met you.
You are so positive.
I'm so proud of you.
I want you to be proud of me,
so I'll be more cheerful and positive.
Thanks for making me want
to become a better person.
I feel the same.
Yun Shil was never on the
same wavelength as you.
That's not love. It's just an obsession.
Yun Shil.
What should I do to make you happy?
Can Dong Jin...
really make you happy?
Hello.
Sorry.
Dong Jin.
Why are you here?
How are you?
It's been a while.
Congratulations on your marriage.
It's only right that I wish you well.
Thank you. I'll make you some tea.
I came to ask for a favour.
Please sit.
Do you know the situation Meesa's in?
- Yes.
- And...
you won't do anything about it?
Meesa Apparel...
was my husband's pride and joy
and lifetime achievement.
You served and worked closely with him.
You must know that.
I know that...
you think it's shameless
of me and it's silly,
but I want you to take over the company.
Meesa was my husband's other half.
It might get broken up...
or sold to someone who
knows nothing about suits.
All this seems like my fault.
When I die,
I don't dare face him like this.
Please, Dong Jin.
Do it for him.
Please save Meesa Apparel from this mess.
I have...
- a condition.
- A condition?
Send Hyo Sang...
to work at Wolgyesu Tailor Shop.
What?
This is the best place where he
can learn about the philosophy...
of suit making that the late
chairman always talked about.
It will take time,
but once he learns the basics,
I'll call him back to Meesa Apparel.
Where have you been all this while?
- I met with a lawyer.
- What for?
The board's going to sue
me for compensation.
I'll take legal action.
Will you please stop?
Hand over your title...
- to Dong Jin.
- Mum!
If you don't, the creditors will sell.
They'll split Meesa up.
I'd rather see that happen...
than let Dong Jin take over.
- What?
- I can't give in to him.
Your late dad put his whole life
into making Meesa what it is.
How can you say you'd
rather see it get split up?
I will not lose to Dong Jin.
I'd rather die...
than let him take my CEO title.
How dare you come into my
office without knocking.
Did you do as I said?
I switched the labels and
handed over the goods.
And the payment?
They'll bring cash to an agreed location.
Isn't that your voice?
Yes, it's your son's voice.
What's that?
If I release this, you'll go to prison.
What are you doing? Are you crazy?
You never paid me,
and I lost my wife while
doing time for you.
Of course I'm crazy.
What do you want?
The CEO title.
Hand it over to Dong Jin.
What?
- Why are you here?
- To give you some advice.
Advice?
Just when I was getting
somewhere with this song.
This is Tae Pyung, the gentleman of trot.
It's Kim Sung Oh from WN Entertainment.
Oh, yes, hello.
Our CEO wishes to see you. Are you free?
Right now? Of course.
She wants to see you alone,
without your manager.
Alone?
(So and You)
(Urology)
Urology.
How did the meeting with
Mr Lee Dong Jin go?
We haven't heard from him yet.
Does this mean we must sell the company?
I heard that BS Fashion offered
our creditors a decent deal.
Has Mr Lee given up on Meesa Apparel?
(Meesa Apparel's 26th Board Meeting)
I'm a bit late. I apologise.
The blood test results show
your hormone levels are low...
and out of balance.
To put it easily,
you have the male equivalent of menopause.
What will happen to me, then?
Is my life as a man...
Pack your things...
- and move in with Hyo Won.
- What?
If you're up to something...
because they lost everything,
it means you married Hyo
Sang for his money.
Tae Yang,
what gives you the right to lecture me?
Choi Ji Yun!
Unless you want to become trash,
go back to where you belong.
Has it been 15 years?
I missed you a lot, Jun...
Should I call you Tae Pyung now?
Yeon Hee.
Why are you here?
I'm Lee Yeon Jun, the CEO
of WN Entertainment.
- What?
- Yeon Hee and Sung Jun.
Yeon Jun.
We requested you return
as Meesa Apparel's CEO.
May we assume you accepted the offer?
I had to think long and hard about it.
That's why I'm late.
I shall...
accept your offer.
(The Gentlemen of Wolgyesu Tailor Shop)
The rightful owner is back.
Everything's back in its place.
Don't think you can make me change my mind.
It's my dad's death anniversary.
If you don't come, I'll take it
to mean you want to leave me.
To overcome my male menopause?
What kind of exercise have you been doing?
I'll be direct.
Are you two dating?
Don't do anything to upset my wife.
Stop coming by whenever
you want and get out.
Stop before you make a fool of yourself.
Leave my husband alone.