(The following content may not be suitable for viewers under 15.)
(Viewer discretion is advised.)
I'm glad to see you again.
From this day forward,
I'll be responsible for the revival of...
Meesa Apparel.
Meesa Apparel is passing through...
the most critical stage in its history. However,
we can make a change.
Meesa Apparel has overcome...
such crises before.
We have experiences and knowledge.
I don't think we're facing this crisis...
due to your lack of capabilities.
The management did not understand the market situation...
and made a wrong decision.
Therefore,
I will not hold you accountable for the crisis.
The former CEO Min Hyo Sang...
made a mistake of aggressively expanding growth...
with his youthful vigor.
However,
he offered his private fortune to revive the company.
He did his best as a CEO.
So, we should not...
point fingers at each other.
Here are my plans.
First,
I will reduce costs by reducing unprofitable...
business departments in the company.
Second,
I will operate an integrated distribution center.
We will sell the remaining real estate and obtain funds.
Third.
We will promote our technique for manufacturing off-the-shelf suits...
and increase long-term profit.
I am confident that we, Meesa Apparel can use this challenge...
to improve upon ourselves.
And at the core will be...
all of you.
(Identification Card, Design Department, Min Hyo Won)
(Design Team 1)
- Oh my gosh. Ms Min. - Ms Min!
How have you all been?
We've been well. We're glad to have you back.
Welcome back.
Thank you.
I'll work extra hard to make up for the time I've been away,
so I'll need your help.
Let's work hard.
- Okay. - Okay.
Dong Jin.
I mean, Mr Lee.
How's your mother?
Whining, of course.
But thanks to your generosity,
I'm back at work...
and Hyo Sang is able to avoid being unemployed,
so she's very grateful.
I'm sincerely grateful as well.
How does it feel to be back after so long?
I feel motivated and like I can do anything.
You won't end up being an outcast like before, will you?
That will not happen.
I've become a completely different person since I met Tae Yang.
I'm not the Min Hyo Won of old.
Sure. You do seem to have matured a lot since you met him.
I want to work hard...
and help you and the company.
I hope that determination doesn't fade and you work hard,
Ms Min Hyo Won.
Yes, Mr Lee Dong Jin.
I'm burning up inside. I can't stand it.
Hello?
Hi, Mum.
What now?
I really can't do this.
How could I, Min Hyo Sang,
be sewing in a tiny tailor shop?
This is a slapstick comedy, Mum.
This is impossible in real-life.
Stop whining.
Dong Jin did it, too.
That's because he grew up with a father who ran a tailor shop.
I'm the founder of Meesa Apparel's only son.
We're not the same. You can't compare us!
That's right. You ran the company to the ground...
within a year of becoming CEO.
- How could you dare compare? - Mum!
Wake up and smell the coffee. Crawl on your hands and feet...
- and do as Dong Jin says. - Come on.
I feel like I can't breathe.
Dong Jin promised to bring you back to headquarters...
if you learn how to make suits there.
So just be patient.
Look, I can handle anything else,
but there's a freak tailor here named Bae Sam Do.
That jerk is a total freak. He talks so much.
He never stops nagging me. I'm going to lose my mind.
He treats me like I'm his subordinate or something.
Yes, Sir. I'll look into it and get back to you. Okay.
What are you doing?
Whenever you get a chance,
you're on the phone or the computer.
Will you keep slacking off?
Why you...
You keep nagging and ordering me around.
- Am I your assistant? - I'm glad you brought that up.
Yes, you are my assistant.
Hyo Sang is an assistant. Sam Do is your boss.
You realise how strict hierarchy is in this industry, right?
If you don't want to get fired, get back to work.
And stop drinking so much coffee. Or buy it yourself.
I'm going to lose my mind.
I'll test your sewing skills an hour from now, so be ready.
Who are you to test me?
What? I guess you don't want to return to headquarters.
I'll combine your work attitude and sewing test score...
and send it to Mr Lee Dong Jin on a daily basis.
If it's below 60, you fail.
I'm speechless.
Look, guy.
Things kind of happened and I ended up here,
so you must be mistaken, thinking you and I are in similar situations,
but listen. You and I are on completely different levels!
I'm Meesa Apparel's founder's son!
- Is that right? - That's right!
- You're the founder's son? - That's right!
Is that what you expected, you punk?
Stop barking like a mad dog.
Wake up, unless you want a beating.
Have some hot tea and let it go.
Goodness. Thank you.
It's so hard to get treated like a human being here.
It's hot.
Who is it?
It's Tae Yang.
What are you doing here?
My training started today, and I picked up short rib soup...
on my way back.
Do you think I could eat right now?
I want to just hang myself.
Stop saying things like that.
I tried it on my way back with my coworkers,
and the soup tastes awesome.
Why is the fan...
I needed some air.
You'll catch a cold. You need to stay warm and eat nourishing foods.
Please try some.
I have no appetite.
You should eat before it gets cold.
Here.
Please calm down.
Life is so cruel.
How did this happen to me?
I'm always crying in front of you.
You think I'm pathetic, don't you?
Definitely not.
Every time you cry, I feel my heart break.
Are you kissing up to me?
I am not. I mean it.
Don't expect me...
to change my mind just because you're doing this.
I know.
Please eat before it gets cold.
- Put some rice in it. - Okay.
Sir, Ms Min Hyo Joo is coming in.
Congratulations on your first day as CEO, Mr Lee Dong Jin.
Thanks.
Finally, the rightful owner is back in the room.
Now that you're back,
it feels like everything is back to where it belongs.
I need to make something clear to you.
I returned to Meesa Apparel only because I thought...
things were over for good between us.
I felt bad toward my wife...
for returning to the company where you were,
but I did it because she has complete faith in me.
What do you want to say?
Just in case,
don't do anything that may cause my wife any misunderstandings.
I'm saying this in case you have any misconceptions or hope.
We won't meet other than for work,
so don't come here unless you have a business matter to discuss.
Must you be so cold?
I don't want my wife to be hurt because of you.
Stop saying, "my wife" this, "my wife" that.
Are you doing that on purpose?
Don't you see that I'm hurt because of you?
It isn't because of me,
but because you won't let go.
So let go of me. Stop clinging on.
I got what you mean.
There's no need to repeat yourself.
Hearing it over and over again...
only makes it worse.
It's me.
Are you okay?
You sound a bit tired.
I had a meeting as soon as I got here,
and another one at lunchtime.
I still have more left.
It looks like I'll be in meetings all day today.
Did you eat lunch?
I had a sandwich.
Continuous meetings are tiring even on a full stomach.
You should've had more than a sandwich.
Forget about food.
I can't seem to recharge...
because you aren't around.
We were together all day at the store...
and that kept me going.
I think my battery's almost flat.
Now that you don't work here anymore,
I feel lonely and a bit down.
I can't seem to settle in at work.
Being apart made you...
a bit more aggressive in showing your love.
Sir, it's time for you to attend the board meeting.
I have another meeting.
- Okay, go ahead. - Just a moment.
Being apart isn't working for either of us.
How about I got back to the store?
Don't say that.
I was just kidding.
I'll be completely exhausted when I get home tonight.
You'd better charge me up.
I will. Go to your meeting.
I will. Cheer up yourself.
Didn't I tell you to use the thimble?
That thing is so uncomfortable.
It makes my fingers stiff...
and harder to sew.
Even if your fingers lock up,
we use it to work safely.
I use one!
Are you an expert. Are you better than me?
Why won't you use it?
How dare the ex-CEO of a company...
not even have the right attitude?
You lack all the basics. Now put it on.
How can someone nag so much?
He's like a middle-aged woman.
What did you just say?
Nothing at all.
You're infuriating. Watch.
This is called hemming.
It's used...
to hem pant bottoms, sleeves or seams.
You go down and up like this.
Bottom first.
Then you come up.
Bottom first then up. You do it.
If you stick the needle so deep, the thread will show.
It shouldn't show on the other side.
I'd rather teach an ox how to sew.
You lack the basic knowledge.
He never had to...
pick up a needle in his whole life.
Teach him nice and slowly.
Yes, Master. Calm down.
I knew what he's made of when he stole my suit...
during the competition.
He's the worst kind of human being ever.
I can't do this!
Please throw that. Please do.
The second you do, I'll call Dong Jin.
Then you're out. Throw that right now.
You're infuriating.
He's been getting annoyed really easily.
Something seems to be bothering him.
Is something going on?
I don't really know.
Wear it properly, okay?
Hello!
- Hello. - You seem busy.
- Have a nice day. - You, too.
That view seems oddly familiar.
Who's this?
You're the oil lady.
Sun Nyeo.
Why are you here?
Why do you think I'm here?
I'm here for you, the woman who took my money.
There's a huge misunderstanding.
A misunderstanding? Whatever.
I'll get you today.
- Let go of me. - Hey!
- Stop right there! - No way!
Stop that thief!
She took my money! Stop her!
Stop that thief! Stop her!
Get her!
- Save me! - She's a thief!
Get out of the way! A mad woman's after me.
Make way.
Stop thief!
Stop that thief!
Move, move.
That thief.
Sorry. Sorry.
Will you move?
Get out of the way.
Oil lady.
Oil lady!
Oil lady...
I just wasted a great opportunity. Just my luck.
Oil lady!
Your CEO asked to see me.
I'm Lee Dong Sook, Sung Tae Pyung's manager.
- Just a moment, please. - Sure.
Why does she want to see me?
(Sung Tae Pyung)
(Lee Yeon Jun, CEO)
Hello, Ma'am.
Welcome.
Does Jun... Sorry, Tae Pyung know you're here?
You told me not to tell him, so I didn't.
Well done.
- Have a seat. - Thanks.
I wanted to meet you to ask some questions.
Okay.
I'll be direct.
You and Tae Pyung.
- Are you dating? - What?
I think I should know, as the CEO.
My staff say you live under the same roof.
Are you two...
Don't even imply such a thing.
No, we aren't dating at all.
It is true that Tae Pyung lives on the second floor,
but that's because we're cousins.
He's my older cousin.
Oh, I see.
I thought you were dating...
and that bothered me so much.
You're cousins.
Tae Pyung's working again and trying to...
get people to notice him.
Any strange rumours can...
ruin someone's career.
Of course.
You don't have to worry about that.
- Is he dating anyone, then? - What?
Tae Pyung, I mean.
Does he have a crush on someone?
I'm not sure.
I wouldn't know.
I believe he doesn't at the moment.
What a relief.
That is such good news.
Why do you think...
he isn't dating anyone?
Do you think it's because of the trauma of a past love?
The trauma of a past love?
For example,
he closed up because his first love went tragically wrong...
and he never fell in love again.
Some men are like that.
I'm wondering if he's like that.
He was never married and is still single.
I don't know.
His debut single was "Susanna's Handkerchief".
It's about missing a first love.
As the singer,
I bet he's still wallowing in the past.
He closed himself up...
and cut himself from the outside world.
Like the men in "Architecture 101"...
or "The Best of Me".
He never got over his first love from 15 years ago...
and is still unable to fall in love.
That is so cruel.
And so romantic.
Is she crying because she talked about movies?
She doesn't look like it, but she's quite silly.
Why are you here?
I was headed to the store...
but came here instead, thinking you'd be off work.
Is no one at home?
Neither me...
or my in-laws want to talk to you, so please go away.
I'm sorry for everything.
I know an apology is hardly enough,
but I'd feel so bad if I didn't even apologise.
I came here on purpose.
I also bought this.
1.2kg of meat.
Make some soup for your family.
No thanks. Take it and leave.
You can ignore my apology,
but take the meat and eat it.
I will take Gi Pyo...
back to Anseong with me.
Don't you worry.
I'm sorry for being so rude...
in the name of being an in-law.
I hope you forget about it...
and live happily ever after.
I'll find Gi Pyo...
a nice young woman...
and marry him off soon.
I'm off. Take care.
Tell me the truth.
Are you really okay with my returning to Meesa Appareal?
If you're even the slightest bit upset or bothered by it,
I won't go.
Didn't you decide to go?
I just feel like it would bother you.
My calling with respect to Meesa is important too,
but you are much more important to me.
I'm fine, so it's okay.
Do you mean it?
But what if Min Hyo Sang makes life difficult for you?
I'm worried that he'll hold a grudge and take it out on you.
Look. Yun Shil.
Hong Gi Pyo went to see Hyo Sang.
He said if he didn't reinstate me as CEO,
he'd play the recording of Hyo Sang regarding the fake label incident...
at the shareholders meeting.
Why would he do that?
I think he wanted to help me become CEO...
and in a way, make up to you for his wrongdoings.
Hi, Dong Jin.
I have too many documents to look over.
I'm going to have to work late.
I won't be able to have dinner with you. Sorry.
It's okay.
Have you had dinner yet?
You didn't have a proper lunch, either.
I can eat something quick when I get a chance. Don't worry.
Don't skip dinner because I'm not there. Eat a full meal, okay?
Okay, I will. Good luck with your work.
I'm here to see Mr Lee Dong Jin.
Do you have an appointment?
No. I'm his wife.
I wanted to bring him some food.
You're his wife? Hello, Madam.
Hello.
Please give me a minute. I'll call his office.
Thank you.
What are you doing here at this hour?
I came to see Dong Jin.
I guess you wanted to hear the workers call you "Madam".
What did you just say?
The office is not your playground.
You're distracting him from his work, so don't stop by as you wish,
trying to play house, and just go home.
I'm Lee Dong Jin's wife.
You are nothing to him now, so I don't need to take that from you.
Why am I nothing?
Dong Jin and I...
You know nothing about Dong Jin and me.
We share many things that you know nothing about.
You should stop before you look any more pathetic.
What?
Dong Jin has no feelings toward you,
so leave my man alone.
"My man"?
Sure.
Yun Shil.
Honey.
Why did you come all the way here?
It sounded like you were too busy to have dinner,
so I brought you some food.
Wow. My wife is the best.
Sorry, but you'll have to eat without me.
My wife brought me food.
Is she your wife?
- Hello. - Hello.
I wondered why Mr Lee looked so happy.
It was because you have a wife who brings you food.
Yes, that's right.
Did you have dinner plans with them?
No, no.
We just finished our meeting and were going to grab dinner,
but I think we should go home and eat with our wives tonight.
Sure. Please enjoy your dinner, Mr Lee.
- Thank you. I'll see you tomorrow. - Okay.
Wow. This is a total feast.
You brought me dinner because I'm working late. I'm so touched.
You must be hungry. Go on and eat.
Okay.
But earlier, in the lobby...
I yelled at Min Hyo Joo to stay away from you...
because you're my man now.
Did you really say that?
Yes. I didn't mean to say something like that,
but I got angry.
Wow. My girl is getting bolder and braver.
I told you. I won't be a fool and just take it...
any longer.
Good. You did well.
You should always be bold and say what you want.
But Dong Jin,
I want to become someone who is a good match for you.
What do you mean?
I'm not educated and don't have much to offer.
I'm afraid I'll end up embarrassing you.
That's absurd.
I'm so proud to have you as my wife.
Don't ever think that.
If only I hadn't wasted 10 years because of Gi Pyo,
I would've been better than I am now.
That thought keeps crossing my mind,
so I keep getting upset, and feel like it was such a waste.
What upsets you the most?
Not going to school.
I liked studying and got good grades.
But back then, my situation made it impossible...
for me to go to college.
You can always go back to school now.
It's too late to go back to school now.
The soup will get cold. You should eat.
I'm saying this...
because I'm really worried.
Dong Jin is a married man. He is legally married to someone else.
subtitles ripped and synced by riri13
He isn't your husband anymore.
I know that.
Then why are you doing this?
I understand it's out of your control,
but you have to let go of him.
Are you lecturing me?
I'm not lecturing you.
I'm just worried, that's all. Sorry, if I offended you.
True.
You saw me get insulted by my ex-husband's new wife,
so you must think I'm pathetic.
I do not. You're not pathetic at all.
I'm upset because I understand how you feel,
and it breaks my heart.
You were always like that.
You said you understood me,
and stuck next to me although I told you to go.
What could a little kid like you know?
That's because I really did understand how you feel.
And I still do.
Don't you resent me...
for kicking out your family?
Seeing Mum suffer in the tiny house,
I did resent you for a moment.
But...
you were hurt and suffered ever since you were little...
because of us.
Even if I were in your situation,
I probably would've hated my family, too.
That's why I always...
feel sorry toward you.
That's why I was even meaner to you.
If you had fought back like Hyo Sang,
I would've just ignored you.
I really...
sorry toward you...
and I sincerely like you.
Is your mum still having a tough time?
It's because she can't adapt to the situation,
but she'll get better soon.
How about you?
I'm neither well nor bad.
I thought I'd feel relieved once your family left,
but I was wrong.
I'm glad.
If you said it was nice and comfortable...
because we were gone,
I think I would've been upset and hurt.
Do you know how long I've been looking for you?
After I practically abandoned you in the US...
and came to Korea alone,
I was struggling so much with the guilt.
I've forgotten the past, so you don't need to bring it up.
I suffered a lot from a panic disorder after that.
I'm still on medication.
My father finally gave in, after seeing me...
unable to get my life together.
That's why he started the company for me.
Let's start over.
- What? - I was too young back then.
I won't betray you this time. I swear.
I won't give up this time. I'm confident.
So please give me a chance.
She abandoned me...
and now, she says...
nothing has changed?
She is just as thoughtless as she used to be.
Where were you? I couldn't reach you.
The thing is...
I just met with a friend.
Honey, I'm home.
Do you know what happened...
Do you feel sick?
No, I'm fine.
You are not fine.
Were you crying?
No.
Did something happen?
No, nothing.
- Then what is it? - Just.
Life is just so meaningless.
Why is life meaningless?
Look at me.
Did you cause trouble again?
Did you get a notice to pay back a loan you guaranteed again?
No. I told you, it's nothing.
Then why are you like this?
I received...
a death sentence.
A death sentence?
Bae Sam Do received a death sentence as a man.
I've hit menopause.
My testosterone level had dropped substantially.
Is that all?
You're not the only one hitting menopause! So am I.
I'm always getting hot flashes...
and sweating.
Does everything annoy you to no end?
That's right.
It isn't just you, so don't be down.
Goodness. My honey.
Goodness. Menopause...
is nothing, so don't let it get you down.
What a waste of your looks.
Had I known,
I would've worked hard on our homework when you asked.
It isn't too late yet.
Be confident, Mr Bae Sam Do.
No.
It's too late for me now.
Rivers are meant to be crossed,
and menopause is meant to be overcome.
Let's start our "overcome menopause project" tomorrow.
Overcome menopause project?
Go, go!
Honey.
Did you have a good day?
Did you wait long?
No.
You did, too.
Your cheeks are frozen.
- Should I not wait any more? - No.
I love having you pick me up at the bus stop.
How was your first day back?
It was good.
Memories of when we first met...
and our working together kept coming back to me.
You're right. I'm reminded of those times, too.
What was your first impression of me...
when we met?
Ms Min.
He's a new hire.
He was assigned to your team, so I wanted to introduce him.
A new hire?
What?
Why is that man here?
I just told you.
He's a new hire who was assigned to your team.
Hello, I'm Kang Tae Yang.
You were very frightening.
What?
Just kidding.
But...
isn't it hard commuting by mass transportation?
No.
I like taking the bus. I get to exercise.
Don't worry.
It'll be hard, commuting by bus...
when it gets packed.
I'd better make money quickly and buy you a car.
Your thoughtfulness alone is making me happy.
I'll do it, so just wait.
But Hyo Won...
I think you should take special care of your mother.
I stopped by earlier to see her,
and she wasn't eating...
and was chewing on ice.
It's probably because she's frustrated.
It'll hurt her teeth and her health.
I know you'll be tired too,
but I think you should pay special attention to her.
Okay, I will.
Did Ji Yun move in yet?
No, not yet.
I understand it's frustrating for her,
but I'm worried that she'll abandon my brother...
and never come back.
She'll be back soon, so don't worry.
I'm home.
Mum. You'll make yourself sick.
I'm burning up inside. I can't stand it. Give it back.
No. Tae Yang said...
to make sure you don't chew on ice.
Who is he to say anything?
He said if you chew on ice on an empty stomach,
you'll get a stomachache and damage your teeth.
Do you know how much he worries about you?
If he's so worried,
tell him to break up with you.
- Mum! - Oh my gosh.
How dare you yell at me?
Don't be like that to him You can't do that.
Don't be like what?
What does that punk have to offer?
This house...
Tae Yang paid for it.
What?
Tae Yang used the money he got from shooting that commercial...
and got us this place...
and told me not to tell you.
He said you'd feel bad and refuse.
He is so thoughtful of you.
What's wrong with you?
I can't believe this.
I'm getting handouts from my daughter's boyfriend.
Ko Eun Sook,
your life has hit rock bottom.
Mum. Why are you saying that?
Your future son-in-law helped his wife's family.
Just be grateful and pay him back later.
He's not my future son-in-law.
Oh my goodness.
What's the use in living like this?
Please, take me away...
from this life.
I can't live like this.
I'm burning up.
Goodness.
Stop it already.
Miss.
You didn't forget...
that I need to go down to visit my family...
for a few days, did you?
Is that tomorrow?
Yes. I'm leaving early in the morning.
I already bought my tickets.
- Okay. - Thank you.
Wow. My wife is the best.
Sorry, but you'll have to eat without me.
My wife brought me food.
We're home.
Oh.
The house feels so empty...
without Mum and Dad.
You can go to Gangneung this weekend, right?
The company is in a state of emergency,
so I'm not sure.
If you're too busy, I'll just go by myself.
I'm worried...
and feel too uneasy.
I will make some time.
Go inside. I should make a phone call to Dad.
All right.
Hello.
Hello. How are you?
I'm fine.
It's not so cold, so I'm taking a walk in the yard.
Is everyone doing all right?
Sure. Don't worry about us.
The sea breeze is cold at night, so don't stay outside for long.
It's warmer here than Seoul. Don't worry.
- How is Mum? - She's sleeping like a log.
She was following me all day.
She must be tired.
You are not familiar with the surroundings yet.
Make sure you go out with Mum.
I talked about a newly wedded life and it became true.
Your mum wouldn't stay away from me.
I'm so glad that you are together.
It was my first day at Meesa Apparel.
Good for you.
It must not be easy. Brace yourself.
- Dong Jin. - Yes.
I'm sure you'll do all right,
but make sure not to hurt anyone's feelings.
Sure. I learned that from you while I worked at the tailor shop...
that it's all about people whether I work at the shop or in the company.
Don't worry about it.
The guild with Tonelli...
is going along nicely.
They are all your acquaintances,
so I will do my best not to cause you any trouble.
All right. I trust you.
You must be tired after your first day. Take a rest.
All right. You take a rest, too, Dad.
Enjoy your newlywed life.
I will. Bye.
I'll be 80 years old soon.
I'm having a newlywed life in such an old age.
It won't be as sweet as before when we were young,
but I'm so thankful...
for the quiet and warm days.
As the lamp shines at the dark night,
the life is both sad and happy.
I should appreciate that I can grow old with my good wife.
Why do we have to come to the park in such an early morning?
I told you.
We'll start the project to overcome menopause.
I'm the assistant instructor, and you're the recruit.
We should harden our heart and overcome menopause.
Was that why we're here? I'll go back home.
Why are you doing this?
People live up to 100 years these days. They say 9988234.
We should live youthfully until 99 years old,
and suffer 2 or 3 days and die.
Do you want to stagger when you're only 50 years old?
Well, I don't.
Then we should make an excruciating effort...
to overcome this.
Repeat after me. I can do it!
- I can do it. - Good.
Let's start with walking up the stairs.
Shall I walk up that stairs?
- Go! - All right.
Go.
By the way, you're also menopausal. Why am I the only one doing this?
I usually walk around 20,000 steps a day...
receiving deposits on dispatch.
I don't need more exercise. Run, Bae Sam Do!
That hurts my ears. All right. Wait a second.
When I run...
All right, I'm ready.
You're handsome.
Let's go with all your might!
Go! Go!
- Honey, take this! - All right.
- You can do it! - I can do it!
I can do it!
Let's go!
Again!
One, two!
How was it?
Rather than dwelling on your own misfortune,
exercising outside must make you feel much better.
I feel better, but I can't breathe.
- You can do it! - I can do it.
Good.
What's going on? Did you do morning exercise?
It was rather a training than an exercise.
A training? What do you mean?
Don't ask in detail. Curiosity kills the cat.
- Go inside and have breakfast. - Can we?
The house feels empty without Mum and Dad.
Let's get together and have meals together.
Let's eat together starting today.
Then we should take turns cooking.
- Sam Do. - Yes.
What kind of exercise did you do? It seems that your legs are rubbery.
It was not an exercise. It was a training.
You don't catch my drift.
A training?
He's funny.
Are we that poor? I don't like the side dishes.
Stop being childish.
You're not in a position to complain about the food.
All right. You scold me whenever I say something.
All right.
Is this bean sprout soup or salt soup?
It's so salty.
You put too much salt.
I didn't put that much salt.
I let the housekeeper take charge of the kitchen all along.
I haven't cooked for a long time.
I must have lost the sense of cooking.
You never had the touch.
You don't have a natural sense.
You're not supposed to complain about me.
Why are we having such a hard time in this house?
Mum. Stop it.
Why are you yelling in the morning?
Do you know...
it's the anniversary of Dad's death?
Is it the anniversary of Dad's death?
My goodness. I forgot as I was so busy nowadays.
What are you going to do with Ji Yun on such a day?
It's the first time for her to commemorate her father-in-law.
If she won't come, does it mean that she would break up with you?
- I'll call her. - She's so mean.
She should stay by her husband when he's having a hard time.
How could she run away?
She lacks common sense.
Aren't you...
finishing your meal?
I had enough.
- Goodness. - Stop it, Mum.
Do you have to say that when he's already distressed?
I shouldn't have let him marry Ji Yun.
I should have disapproved that marriage.
How unfortunate I am!
I'm so upset.
I came to see whether you're doing fine.
How is everything?
I'm sorry.
You don't have to be sorry.
It's all my fault.
Life is so turbulent.
I don't know what to do.
I don't feel calm.
I'm such a bad woman.
What are you talking about?
I can understand your situation.
Have you really decided to work in the tailor shop?
Well, it turned out that way.
That's nonsense.
That's too harsh.
I appointed Dong Jin to the warehouse to dismiss him,
and finally made him work in the tailor shop.
But you don't have any experience doing such work.
Is he taking revenge on you? That's too much.
Dong Jin wouldn't do such a thing.
I'm reaping the fruits of my actions.
Don't you have any other choice?
I have nothing to do except wishing that Doing Jin would...
bring the company back to normal, and work in the tailor shop.
If Dong Jin fails,
there's no other hope.
It's the anniversary of Dad's death today.
I don't mean to pressure you.
But if you have any thought of being with me,
I want you to come for the anniversary today.
If you don't show up,
I'll take it to mean we're separating.
Hyo Sang.
Whatever you decide,
I will respect your decision.
Did you curse me a lot on the inside?
As you know, I'm mean and have a horrid temper.
You're the only person I open up to...
and manage to understand.
I know it's hard on you, so don't worry.
I have to go.
All right.
Here you go.
- Have a great day. - Thanks.
One more thing.
This is our new fire insurance.
- Have a look. - Okay.
- See you tomorrow. - Bye.
Can't you give me a two-dollar discount?
I don't have that much cash.
- Who's that? - Give me a discount.
I already took three dollars off.
You can't ask for more than that.
- Why are you so stingy? - Lady.
I don't make much as it is.
How can an octopus cost as much as 50 dollars?
- Take two dollars more off. - Then take the small one.
It's for my husband's death anniversary service.
Can you take two dollars off?
- My goodness. - No?
- Madam Ko. - Gosh.
Hey.
- It's been a while. - It has.
I'd heard you'd moved to the neighbourhood,
but I was too busy to visit.
How do you feel?
Much better now.
Why are you tutting?
You used to be so elegant and haughty.
Who'd have thought you'd end up crouching in a market like this...
haggling over the price of an octopus?
Lives change in the blink of an eye.
Will you buy it or not?
I will if you give me two more dollars off.
- What? - No?
- I can't. - I'll give you the two dollars.
Buy the octopus.
It's fine.
It's not fine.
You don't have to feel bad.
- Can you wash it, please? - Goodness.
I wouldn't feel bad over just two dollars.
- You take it. - Thank you.
Unbelievable.
This is the 2017 fall season collection suit.
- What do you think? - This is amazing.
It's like looking at a manica camicia textbook.
He really likes it.
Asians have smaller shoulders compared to westerners.
A slim fit poses no problems,
but our shoulders are more rounded.
Instead of using shoulder pads,
we used a thicker lining...
for a more active fit.
The details are extremely creative.
Good job.
Thank you, thank you.
You know, with your skill,
I'm sure the proud tailors at Tonelli studios...
will have nothing to complain about.
Hey, you, come here.
Does "good job" mean something nice?
Yes, it does.
It's a huge compliment.
The design team from Headquarters will be visiting soon...
to see the new collection and the tailor training.
But I'm sure there won't be anything to worry about.
Mr Intern.
Do you have anything to say to him?
Well, yes.
Our tailors will be forwarded with the details...
and the information about the suits,
and we'll make sure to make at least...
one prototype for each design so the...
designers at Tonelli can, you know, thoroughly supervise them.
So, from now on, Mr Lee will be leading the company...
at Meesa Apparel...
and Mr Min will be managing the Wolgyesu-Tonelli store?
Yes, he's going to be coming back and forth...
until I master the technical parts,
and once I do, I'm going to take charge.
And Mr Bae will be with me by my side,
so there's really nothing to worry about.
President.
Master Tailor.
Intern.
We will teach him the skills.
Starting with how to sew.
And he's his translator.
Yes.
Hello.
How are you?
Don't pretend we're chummy. It's awkward.
Can't you be nice?
Why are you here?
It's Dad's death anniversary.
Mum's preparing the service.
Come to our place if you can.
Why should I?
Just come.
Dad will want to see the whole family together.
I'll text you our address. I hope you'll come.
I'll wait.
You must come.
Promise.
I know I was preoccupied,
but how did I forget that?
It's me.
It's my dad's death anniversary...
- and we should prepare... - Ms Min.
I told you I'd be visiting my hometown.
Right. You did.
Sorry.
- Come with me. - Where to?
You'll find out.
Sorry to surprise you. Gi Pyo's...
- leaving Seoul today. - So what?
He asked me to let him see you one last time.
- Go and talk to him. - No.
I'm not saying you should forgive him.
I can't, either.
But I think you need to end things properly...
if you're to move on...
with a clear conscience.
Go on.
I'll stand guard from here.
It's been a while.
I'm leaving Seoul today.
What does that have to do with me?
Nothing, I know.
But I wanted to see you one last time,
so I asked Dong Jin for an incredulous favour.
We'll never meet again. Don't look at me like that.
I don't know what you said that made Dong Jin bring me here,
but never do it again.
I don't want to see you again, even by chance.
I thought...
I should return this to you.
It's your diary.
I read a few pages. Sorry.
Thanks for letting me see your face before I go.
I'm really sorry for everything.
I should go.
Be happy, Yun Shil.
Thanks for letting me see her.
It's to help her get over you.
I know.
Keep putting her first.
Take...
good care of her.
Make her happy.
You don't need to worry about her.
Stay out of trouble and live an honest life.
That's the only way you can ever repay her.
You're horrid to the end.
Bye.
Yun Shil.
It was horrific for you...
but I was happy that I was able to love you.
Everything I say will only sound like an excuse,
but the love I had for you was pure.
A few days ago,
I went to a temple to ask for your dad's forgiveness.
That was the only thing I could do.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, Father.
I decided to go far away.
I will go to sea.
The lies I told to keep you close...
ended up driving you away,
but I doubt I'll ever be able to forget you.
That doesn't mean you'll see me again, so don't worry.
If time passes and you still can't forgive me,
then forget about me.
I don't want you to remember me as a scoundrel.
Please be happy, Yun Shil.
Are you okay?
Finally, it's all over.
Well done.
Do you call that a line? That'll make a terrible suit.
Draw as if you're...
- drawing on your soul. - Master.
What?
- You have a visitor. - Who is it?
I don't think he wants a suit, but he asked to see you.
I wonder who it is. Ms Geum, if he slacks off, hit him with this.
Okay. Gosh, this thing...
Please save me.
What? Master!
Please don't. Okay, I'll do it.
- I will. - Get to work.
- I don't want to hit you. - Don't.
- I can do this. - Do it, then.
Do it properly.
Just draw.
Yong Suk.
Are you Yong Suk?
Sam Do.
Hey, how long has it been?
Sorry, Sam Do.
How is your health?
I should've called you.
After I went bankrupt, avoiding creditors was my priority.
Did you hate me?
No, I just assumed you had your reasons.
I didn't hate you. I just cursed you a few times.
I never thought you'd disappear leaving me with your debt.
Thanks, Sam Do.
Take this.
What's this?
Now that the worst is over,
I came by to repay you what I owe.
I never thought...
I'd ever see this money again.
Thanks so much.
Thank you.
"A Stroll With Music",
"Show Music Zone", "Dating Garden",
"Music Melon", "Sound From the Heart".
"Icheon Rice Festival"? I can't make this.
This is tough.
(CEO)
This is becoming an issue.
Should I have said I'm married?
What should I do?
Dad, come down for dinner.
Da Jeong.
We have meat, your favourite.
- Hurry up. - Really?
Okay, let's hurry.
Is it a special day? Why are we eating meat?
This is our treat.
Do you have good news to share?
Today, I found some money.
Do you remember how...
we had to repay 50,000 dollars of his friend's debt?
That friend came by today and gave it back.
That's great news. Congratulations.
I guess there's always a way out.
I never imagined I'd get it back.
What will you do with that money?
We'll figure something out.
That is such a happy problem to have.
Hello? Is anyone home?
- Is someone at the door? - Who's that?
Who is it? Eat up.
It's delicious.
What brings you here, Ms Lee?
I'm here to see Tae Pyung. Is he in?
Why do you want to see him?
Just a moment.
Tae Pyung. Tae Pyung.
Your CEO's here.
The CEO of your agency?
What would someone like her be doing here?
This is just crazy.
What's wrong?
Let's go and watch.
Tae Pyung.
Why are you here, Ms Lee?
I finally got permission to marry.
Permission to marry?
Are you getting married?
Isn't it unbelievable?
Mum and Dad finally gave in.
They want to see you tomorrow for an official meeting.
What is she talking about?
Well, the thing is...
What the CEO is saying is...
you're going to marry Tae Pyung?
Is that it?
Yes. Tae Pyung promised to marry each other 15 years ago.
I was immature and I left him then,
but fate brought us together again, so this time I'm marrying him.
Mum.
Let's not waste time. Let's get married next week.
What do you mean?
Who is marrying whom? Tae Pyung is my husband.
What? What do you mean? You said you're cousins.
Yeon Hee, let me explain.
I don't care if you aren't cousins.
I'm going to marry you.
You are mine, Jun.
- This can't be happening. - Let go.
- Honey. - Isn't this pretty?
Stop it.
- Honey! - Let go!
(The Gentlemen of Wolgyesu Tailor Shop)
Why do all the women here start by grabbing someone's hair?
Why are you venting at us?
It's her fault for hitting on a married man.
Fire your manager...
or cancel your contract with us. It's one or the other.
Do you look down on us now that we're poor?
You're using the apartment you got as leverage on Hyo Won.
Congratulations.
Why do I feel so little?
I think you did something wrong.
- What's this? - Sorry for making you wait.
Will you marry me?