(The following content may not be suitable for viewers under 15.)
(Viewer discretion is advised.)
(Episode 52)
Look, strictly speaking,
that CEO lady is not to blame.
Dong Sook insisted...
on Tae Pyung pretending to be single until he becomes a top singer.
That's why he couldn't tell her he's married.
Isn't that right?
What you said is true.
What on the earth are you talking about?
Had Dong Sook known...
that there used to be something between Tae Pyung and her,
would Dong Sook have done the same thing?
Dong Sook, if you had known their relationship,
would you have let Tae Pyung pretend to be single?
I must be crazy if I did that.
She says she wouldn't.
Well, there was a misunderstanding,
but it was rude to grab her by the hair.
It's her who was rude.
Dong Sook told her Tae Pyung was her husband.
But still, Ms Lee insisted on marrying Tae Pyung.
Even so, you could've talked to her instead of grabbing her by the hair.
Are you taking her side, not your sister's?
I'm not taking anyone's side.
If Tae Pyung hadn't apologised, we may have been taken...
to the police station.
I agree. Why are you women so daring?
Why are you scolding us? We didn't do anything wrong.
It's her fault for trying to take someone else's man.
How many times do I have to tell you?
She thought that Dong Sook was Tae Pyung's cousin.
I told her I was not his cousin.
Yeon Hee tends to not listen to others...
when she wants something.
Yeon Hee? Are taking her side now?
I'm not taking her side.
He's just telling the fact.
What is the fact?
It was her who started an argument.
Yun Shil, calm down.
Why do I have to calm down? I'm also a member of this family.
What I meant was...
Anyway,
Let's call Ms Lee tomorrow and apologise to her, Dong Sook.
Why do I have to tell her I'm sorry?
Does it hurt your feelings...
that your first love was seized by the hair?
I don't mean that...
The first love always makes a trouble.
I'm sick and tired of the first love.
Why is the first love...
so important to the men in this house?
Why do the women in this house always try to pick a fight...
whenever something happens?
This time,
I'll make sure they never think about their first love again.
I will make sure the women in this house...
never use violence again.
I'm not going...
to let it slide this time.
Are you saying that what happened today is all my fault?
That's nonsense, Dong Sook.
Be quiet, Dong Jin.
After Mr Lee left this house,
the hierarchy of the household is completely disrupted.
- I can't stand it. - Look who's talking!
As Ms Choi is not at home,
the husbands are not afraid of their wives.
I'm taking this opportunity...
to make you realise how precious your wives are.
From this moment on, the women in this house...
announce a strike. We won't do any household chores.
House chores are not a big deal.
Men can do that without any problem.
All right. Then there's no need to worry.
Ladies, stand up.
From now on, women will eat and sleep by ourselves.
Men can live among yourselves.
Cooking is not a big deal.
Do as you wish.
Why are you still sitting here? Stand up!
- Follow me. - We...
Come here. Let's go inside.
- Come in. - Where are you going?
There...
Then, you also...
stand up.
Goodness. Why are they doing this?
Are you saying that we should sleep in separate bedrooms, Sam Do?
You saw them grabbing her hair a while ago.
Women in this house are so bossy.
We should break their spirits.
Still, I don't think sleeping separately is a good idea.
In addition,
I'm a newlywed.
- I don't want to do that. - Hey.
Dong Jin, you're the one who has a problem.
From what I heard her say earlier, you should really be careful.
He's right.
"Be quiet, Dong Jin."
Yun Shil is feistier than what I previously thought.
From the start, we should make things right.
Unless we make it as their fault, we're all dead meat.
Right. It will be the end for us. We should do that.
- Do as what he says. - Goodness.
Goodness.
My goodness.
What can I do with it?
Are you all right, Mother?
Goodness.
That thing...
Can you do something about that thing?
What can I do?
Are you all right?
I was scared to death.
By the way,
how did you get in here?
The gate was open, so I came in to see whether everything's fine.
I see.
I'm out of my mind these days.
I must have forgotten to lock the gate.
- Are you going to boil the octopus? - Yes.
I'd like to put it on the table for the memorial ceremony.
Hyo Won's dad used to like it.
Good thing you came. I actually wanted to talk to you.
I heard that you rented this house...
- and gave it to Hyo Won. - Right.
As we're broke and the situation reversed,
you probably wanted to show off your money.
It's a misunderstanding.
Whether I got it wrong or not,
I will do anything...
to pay off the rent for this house soon.
Don't ever think of looking down on me.
What are you talking about? I will never do that.
How can I look down on you?
I will cook the octopus.
You can go inside and take some rest, Mother.
What can you do?
I can cook seafood well. I used to live by the coast.
I see.
That's gross.
- I'm home. - Hi.
- Tae Yang. - Hi.
What are you doing here?
Well,
- he's preparing the octopus. - Why is he doing that?
To put it on the table for the memorial ceremony.
Father would enjoy the food since his son-in-law prepared it.
Who is the son-in-law?
You're so tricky.
You've already decided in your mind.
What are you talking about?
Do you want me to help you?
First, wash your hands.
Mother, Hyo Won and I can do the work here.
You can go inside and take a rest.
How can I trust you and let you prepare the food?
He's been living alone for many years.
He's a much better cook than you are, Mum.
I've prepared food with Mum for Dad's memorial before.
I can cook most things.
I'll ask you if I'm not sure.
All right.
I was shocked because of the octopus. I need to calm down.
Don't ruin the expensive ingredients.
Don't hesitate to ask me if you're not sure.
By the way,
do you really know how to prepare these food?
Of course.
There's nothing you can't do.
They seem to be so happy.
Ji Yun.
I hope I'm not late.
You're not. You came just on time.
I thought you wouldn't come back.
I...
won't leave you.
I won't do that...
although people expect I would.
I know that people think I married you because of money.
I'm going to show them that they were wrong.
Are you...
doing this just to prove them wrong?
No, I'm not.
I'm doing this for love.
It's true...
that I was attracted to your wealth at the beginning.
You looked like you had everything,
and I felt that I could risk my everything for a man like you.
But you protected me even after seeing all of my ugly sides...
and defended me against your mum saying you have to be with me.
Seeing that made me realise how much you love me.
Now, it's my turn to be there for you.
I'm so sorry for putting you through such a hard time.
Thank you.
We're here, Mum.
Ji Yun.
- Thanks for coming. - Have you been well?
Of course.
Mum, Ji Yun is here.
I'm sorry, Mother.
It's all my fault, Mum.
Don't be angry at Ji Yun.
Please forgive her.
You didn't even apologise after making the company go under.
I can't believe you're saying sorry just to defend your wife.
This is why people say that sons are useless.
Mother, I know that I'm at fault.
I'm really sorry.
She's apologising sincerely. Forgive her, Mum.
Hyo Won is right.
Try putting yourself in Ji Yun's shoes.
I know for a fact that you won't bother coming back.
What kind of person do you think I am?
Gosh, that hurt. I'm just asking you...
to understand her since you're so generous.
Please calm down.
Listen.
If you leave as you please once again,
you will not be able to come back.
I'll cut you some slack this time, but that's it.
Okay. I'll never do it again.
Mother, what can I do to give you a hand?
Can't you see?
Go to the kitchen and bring out the food.
Okay.
Coming back like this must've been a tough decision to make.
Don't be so harsh on her, Mum.
You always have to take her side, don't you?
Anyhow,
your dad will be glad to see...
that his one and only daughter-in-law is back.
What are you doing here?
Tae Yang made all of the dishes.
It's for Father's memorial ceremony. Why is he making the food?
He's not even our family.
You should be thanking him for preparing all the food...
in your place. What are you even saying now?
I never asked for help. Does he want me to give him credit or what?
I don't want any credit for this.
I'll let you take care of the rest.
I'll get going, Hyo Won.
Why? Stay for the ceremony...
and eat with us after.
I shouldn't be here.
You little...
What's going on?
Tae Yang, why are you coming out of the kitchen?
He made all the dishes for Dad's memorial ceremony.
You and your wife showed up after he took care of all the preparation.
Shouldn't you be thanking him? How rude.
That's my point. Why did he make food for Dad's memorial ceremony?
I should go.
You want to leave now?
Stay for the ceremony and have dinner with us.
Why should he stay for the ceremony?
Have you lost your mind, Mum?
I'll visit again soon.
Gosh, you're so mean!
I'll see him out.
I can't believe he's expecting us to thank him for making a few dishes.
This house.
He got it for us.
- What? - He signed the lease...
with the money he earned from the TV commercial.
Don't be so disrespectful to him.
Gosh, is it almsgiving or what? Does he look down on us now?
I have to go teach that guy a lesson.
- Where's Hyo Sang going? - What?
Just go help Ji Yun with setting the table.
You, Kang Tae Yang.
Do you think my family is a big joke now that our company...
has gone bankrupt?
What are you talking about?
You probably got this shabby house for us...
so that you can visit us anytime...
to belittle us as much as you want.
- That's not why I got it. - Don't lie to my face.
You got this house for us because we've become homeless.
I know you did it so that you can approach Hyo Won more easily.
Why are you so twisted?
- What? - I got this house...
because of Hyo Won.
I love her, and I didn't want to see her family having to suffer.
I just wanted to help.
Do you expect me to believe that?
She was distressed thinking she couldn't help her family,
so I wanted to take a load off of her chest. That's why I got it.
Are you sure there were no other reasons?
My heart is aching because I can't do more for her,
and I'm upset as I don't have much to offer.
So please don't get any wrong ideas and just make yourself at home.
That fool. He irks me.
Gosh, I've been thinking hard.
I think sleeping separately is pushing it too far.
I agree with Dong Jin, Sam Do.
How about we go back to our rooms?
My gosh, seriously.
I've been living like this for over two decades,
so I have no problem with continuing on like this.
However, I cannot bear to watch my beloved brothers living like me.
You know how overbearing and bullheaded those women are.
If we fail to turn the tables this time, we'll have no future.
You'll spend the rest of your life in agony.
That's how Sun Nyeo and Dong Sook are.
Yun Shil would never become like them.
I'm doing this for you guys. Just trust me and follow my lead.
It's okay for you as you're going through a midlife crisis.
- But Dong Jin and I are newlyweds. - Exactly.
Gosh, cut it out. You're at it again.
Shut it and go back to bed. Just sleep!
I feel as if I'm back in the army.
- Gosh, I'm tired. - What on earth are we doing now?
I think I overreacted.
Tae Pyung didn't do anything wrong.
You're too nice.
I'm the one who told him to act like he's single.
The problem is that he didn't say anything to you...
after meeting his first love.
What's wrong with telling you that he ran into his first love?
He definitely should've told you.
It's obvious that he kept it from you intentionally.
Nothing good would've come out of her knowing about it from...
Stop blabbing away. Just get some sleep.
Sweet dreams.
(Tae Pyung)
I'm realising that I should've been more thoughtful.
I should've been honest with you from the get-go.
Can you meet me in the front yard?
I would've been very angry if I were in your position.
I'm sorry.
I don't think she's over you yet, though.
We ended everything 15 years ago.
My immature act haunted me...
for a long enough time,
and there's no reason for me to have feelings for her again now.
I didn't want to worry you for no reason.
That's why I didn't tell you.
Please believe me.
I'm sorry about earlier, too.
Gosh, I'm cold. What time is it now?
It's 3am.
It's so cold in here.
Don't skip the exercise tomorrow morning.
I know that we're fighting,
but the project must go on.
I probably won't be able to get up that early.
I'll give you a wake-up all.
My phone is on vibrate. What if I can't hear it?
Do you have hearing problems or what?
Then let's sleep together if you want.
Then shall we?
Goodness.
Didn't you say you were going on a strike?
Even though I'm on a strike,
I can't stop helping you overcome your menopause, can I?
Here you go.
Thanks.
Well done.
To be honest, you were a bit excessive.
How could you let them see you...
grappling me, especially in front of the females?
Like I said,
whoever lusts over another women's husband should know what to expect.
By the way,
how should we spend the 50,000 dollars?
First, let's go to the bank tomorrow and deposit the money.
Afterward, we can think carefully about how we should use it.
Now that I think of it,
the lucky dream I dreamt before...
must have been hinting that we'd get out 50,000 dollars back.
This still feels like a dream.
Honey.
You see...
- That menopause project... - Yes?
I think it's actually taking effect already.
That doesn't make sense.
It's only been a few days. How could the training take effect already?
You really think so?
Yes.
Then let's turn off the lights and go to bed.
It's been a while since we've been together like this.
Oh dear. Sam Do. You're hugging me too tightly.
It's Hyo Joo.
Has she lost her mind?
Why is she here?
Hello. Welcome, Hyo Joo.
What brings such a noble person...
to such a humble place like this?
You're right.
It does seem a bit humble.
subtitles ripped and synced by riri13
Are you happy now that you...
threw us all out and have that big house to yourself now?
Do you find yourself smiling for no reason...
and feel full without even eating?
Mum. That's enough.
You selfish brat.
Why are you here?
Did you want to see for yourself how we're living?
I came because if we hold a memorial ceremony in two places,
I thought Dad would get confused. Calm down.
I'm going to bow and then I'll leave right away.
Honey. It's only been a year...
since you passed away.
But it feels like 10 years.
No, it feels like it's been more than 100 years since you left.
Who could that be?
We're not expecting anyone else.
It's Lawyer Choi.
What?
Why would he come here?
How have you been, Madam?
- How does it look like I've been? - What...
brings you here, Lawyer Choi?
I'm here to administer Chairman Min's final will.
What do you mean by his final will? There's more to his will?
On the day of the first-year anniversary, Chairman Min...
left a message for me to deliver to the family.
I hope you are all doing well.
It's really your father's voice.
Honey.
Darling.
Please don't cry and listen to me carefully.
Dad says you shouldn't cry,
so don't cry, all right?
If I had a clear mind and a sound body,
I would've like to have written a letter...
to each and every one of you.
Unfortunately, you all know the condition I'm in.
So I'm recording my voice when I still can.
First of all,
this is for my dear eldest daughter, Hyo Joo.
I still don't quite know whether...
it's right for me to tell you this or not.
But I think it's about time I am honest with you.
When your mother was sick but still alive,
I brought your stepmother home.
I'm well aware how much that hurt you...
at such a young age.
But Hyo Joo,
I did that...
because it was your mother's wish.
That doesn't make sense.
Your mother...
didn't want you to feel lonely because of her absence.
So when she knew her time had almost come,
she had your stepmother move in.
I'm sure she made that decision...
because she didn't want her only daughter...
to feel lonely.
I didn't know you would be so heartbroken...
and close your heart towards your stepmother and your siblings.
At the time, I thought it would be best for everyone.
I know it's too late saying this,
but I'm truly sorry.
He's lying. That's a lie.
Say something, Mum.
Lawyer Choi.
Please turn off the recorder and give us some time to ourselves.
I'll be outside.
I'm sure you don't want to believe it,
but what your dad said is all true.
Don't lie to me.
You chased my father when my mum was alive.
That's right.
When your mum was alive,
I met your dad, fell in love and gave birth to Hyo Sang.
That's my sin.
I won't make excuses. I know I'll have to pay for my sins.
But I had no desire to take over your mum's place.
It was obvious...
that people would talk behind my back that I kicked out...
the wife and took over the household.
Why on earth would I put myself in that sort of situation voluntarily?
Your mum...
asked me to come to the hospital.
She said she wouldn't be able to...
close her eyes thinking that you...
would be crying alone in an empty room.
So...
she asked that I take her place,
so I could look after your dad...
and act as a mother to you.
I was the woman that had an affair with her husband,
yet she entreated me holding my hands.
I couldn't possibly say no to her.
You're lying. That's a lie!
After all this time,
it may be useless to say such a thing.
I took over the household,
but failed in becoming a good mother to you. I'm sorry.
I...
truly mean this.
This can't be true.
What's happening?
Honey.
Hyo Won.
Tae Yang.
It's dangerous for you to come here alone this late at night.
What the matter? Is something wrong?
It would be great if your mother and sister clear up...
all their misunderstandings and reconcile with each other.
They've been on bad terms for so long.
I don't think it'll be easy.
But I'm sure things will be better than before.
Of course. They're family.
Thank you, Tae Yang.
Thanks to you,
I'm sure Dad...
was pleased and enjoyed his meal.
I hope the food suited his taste.
I'm sure your father would've been happy because...
your sister-in-law has returned and your sister came today.
Dad...
would've been happy.
Next year, I hope you could be there...
at my dad's memorial ceremony.
I'll try hard to make that happen.
Really?
Does that mean we'll get married soon?
We must win your mother's approval first.
I wonder how nice it would be...
if you were the first person I see when I open my eyes in the morning.
I'll make you breakfast.
Then I'll cook dinner.
No. I can't cook.
I'll do the dishes.
Don't even do the dishes.
I can't bear looking at you, let alone make you do chores.
I'll do everything.
My married life will be so amazing.
Hang in there for me. I'm almost there.
However much...
Tae Yang loves Hyo Won,
how dare he prepare the food for my dad's memorial.
Tae Yang can be sweet and thoughtful.
Wait.
Are you taking his side?
After I'd moved out of your house,
- he came to see me. - Did he?
He said I'd be trash...
if I didn't go back to you.
My heart sunk...
as I realised how selfish I'd been.
What gives him the right to say that to my wife?
I think he loves your sister very much.
Can't we help them out?
- What? - Did you get home safely?
That's why I'm picking up.
Why do you suddenly care?
You're still just as nasty.
Are you okay?
Why wouldn't I be?
How do you feel?
I'm okay.
I acted out because I got a bit emotional.
I'm fine now.
- That's a relief. - Yes.
I'm saying this only because I have liquid courage.
I'm sorry, Hyo Joo.
I mean it.
I wronged you in many ways.
I guess...
it's only natural for you to act this way.
You're drunk.
Stop drinking and go to bed.
Why is the house so cold and empty?
Where did the other two go?
So,
you could've married into a rich and powerful family.
Doesn't that upset you?
Rather than be son-in-law to a rich man, I want to be...
your husband and Da Jeong's dad.
I'm a bit worried.
Your CEO will be really angry.
What are you doing here?
Tae Pyung suggested we have some wine.
What? Where's Sam Do?
I think he's in bed with Sun Nyeo.
How could you do this?
We said men with men and women with women.
Yes, we did. That was the original plan,
but some things can't be controlled.
A married couple's fight never really goes on.
We're still newlyweds.
What about me? Aren't I a newlywed?
Silly.
Dong Jin.
Hi.
You can't come in here. This is the women's room.
It's no longer the women's room.
- The others are with their spouses. - What?
You're so silly not to even notice.
How could you sleep so deep you didn't notice them leave?
I can't believe you're so imperceptive.
What?
I felt so alone without you. I couldn't sleep.
Seeing you sleep so well made me feel bad.
Don't even talk about it. I'd tossed and turned...
and had only just fallen asleep.
That's a lie. You need just one minute.
One minute?
You fall asleep a minute after your head hits the pillow.
What?
Mum called earlier today.
Why? Is something wrong?
No. She went for a stroll with Dad along the beach...
and saw a little baby.
She said the baby looked so cute.
She wants us to have a child soon.
We only just got married.
Let's...
do this for them.
Let's give them a grandchild to hold.
Stop it.
Why not? I can't wait to have a daughter that looks like you.
Don't you?
Not me. I want to have a son that looks like you.
Who cares if it's a boy or a girl?
Let's have it first.
It's what my parents want.
Shall we?
Come on.
Stop it.
No way. Be still.
Things got almost brutal last night when you...
decided to go men versus women.
Why is everyone grinning this morning?
Da Jeong, fights between a married couple...
never really last.
Are you okay?
I'm okay.
Let's all eat.
Just so you all know, I cooked breakfast this morning.
- Thank you. - Thank you.
- Thanks for cooking. - Sure.
The soup's nice.
I wonder if Father and Mother are eating properly.
Shall we video-call them?
Can your grandpa do that?
You bet.
I taught him all that before he left for Gangneung.
He's smart.
Look over here.
- Hey. - You're sophisticated, Dad.
Did you sleep well, Mr Lee?
- Good morning. - Good morning.
I'm doing very well, thanks to you all.
What were you doing, Dad?
Your mum followed me all day to look after me,
and she's sleeping in because she's tired.
I'm cooking breakfast instead.
Are you preparing breakfast?
It's very simple. Some bread, milk and fruit.
Be careful with fire and knives, Father.
I have no problem with those yet.
Are you enjoying your newlywed life?
- Yes. - This weekend,
I'll visit you with my uncle and aunt. See you then.
Sure. Don't you worry about me.
Look after yourselves. Out.
- Goodbye. - Bye.
He hung up.
(Grand Opening)
Is she Mr Lee Dong Jin's wife?
Yes. She works at Wolgyesu Tailor Shop...
and supports her husband well, I heard.
I think Mr Lee found himself a great wife.
What a lovely couple. They suit each other.
Thank you for taking time out of your busy schedules...
to attend the opening of the Tonelli-Wolgyesu store.
As you know, Tonelli...
is a famous brand that boasts great skill and technology.
Wolgyesu has a history that goes back 100 years,
making it Korea's best tailor store.
The launching of the Tonelli-Wolgyesu brand...
means that...
our skill and tradition has been accepted overseas.
We will upgrade the domestic bespoke suit market...
that caters to Asian body types...
as we aim to become a major player in the Asian fashion market.
We will do our best. Thank you.
- About the emblem. - It's great.
I am Bae Sam Do, the Master Tailor.
Standing next to me is Min Hyo Sang.
He worked at Meesa Apparel and is currently our intern.
- Please feel free to look around. - Thank you.
Gianni.
It's a pleasure to meet you. I'm Min Hyo Joo,
the director of Meesa Cultural Foundation.
It's a pleasure to meet you as well.
I'm looking forward to seeing...
the future of Wolgyesu-Tonelli collaboration.
Please know that Meesa Cultural Foundation...
will be giving our full support.
And even though Mr Lee and I...
are now separated as you know,
we're professionally on excellent terms.
Congratulations, Dong Jin.
Thanks.
Are you the director of Meesa Cultural Foundation, Ms Min Hyo Joo?
- Mr Lee's ex-wife. - Yes, I am.
What made you decide to attend this occasion?
We got divorced due to various circumstances,
but we're still good friends...
who are rooting for each other.
Marriage as a system...
isn't that important for people like us.
- Thank you. - Thank you for coming.
Hello. You're Mr Lee's wife, right?
Pardon?
Oh, yes.
I heard that you work as a tailor at Wolgyesu Tailor Shop.
Did you join the shop for your husband?
I want to know more about your love story.
That's not what happened. I'm...
From what I know,
Ms Na worked a bunch of odd jobs after graduating high school...
before getting her first job at the shop.
She started out as an errand runner. Aren't I right?
Even though she didn't go to college,
she's working hard to become the best female tailor...
in the country.
That was petty.
- What do you mean? - You've been...
stomping all over Yun Shil on purpose.
She got all flustered and couldn't answer,
so I just helped her out a little.
Don't be like that to her.
I've been working with her closely,
so I know that she's a nice, good-hearted person.
Stop being so mean to her.
Don't lecture me. Sort out your own mess first.
That temper of hers.
How vicious. That's obviously why...
Dong Jin fell head over heels for Yun Shil who's kind-hearted.
Hey, you. Why are you just standing here?
You should be walking around to check if the guests need anything...
- Hands out of your pockets now. - Gosh, I'm so sick...
and tired of your nagging.
I need to retrieve my job so that I won't have to put up with this.
It won't be easy.
You need to learn how to sew.
After that, you have to learn how to iron and use the sewing machine.
Then taking measurements.
Thank you for coming.
- Are you looking for someone? - Have you seen Yun Shil?
I think I saw her here.
I think she stepped out.
- She stepped out? - Yes.
Hello.
There you are, Mr Lee.
- Congratulations. - It's nice to see you.
- Thank you for coming. - My pleasure.
- Feel free to browse around. - Thank you.
Why do I feel so pathetic?
My gosh.
Why are you back so early?
- Did something happen? - No.
I'm just not feeling well.
Please either fire Ms Lee Dong Sook...
or annul the contract with us.
The choice is yours.
Gosh, Ms Lee.
I understand that you're angry, but the contract can't be annulled.
Please don't let your personal feelings affect your work.
Shut it, lady.
What are you going to do?
Will you let her go?
Or shall we annul the contract?
It's a great opportunity for you.
Just tell her that you'll fire me.
My choice is obvious.
Of course...
Of course, I'll...
choose Dong Sook.
Let's annul the contract.
Tae Pyung.
Well, if that's your decision,
you'll have to return the car...
and work without a stylist.
You'll also have to do all the legwork yourself...
to book TV shows and events.
I'll figure something out.
It should be fine.
Tae Pyung.
Don't worry, Dong Sook.
We can offer 3,000 dollars for this purse.
That is crazy.
Do you know much I paid for this baby? 3,000 won't cut it.
I bought it last year and only used it a few times.
I should take it elsewhere.
That's the going rate. You won't get more even if you go elsewhere.
I know that it's a second-hand,
but I should get at least half of what I paid. This is so crazy.
How about just 200 more?
I'm afraid I can't do that.
Don't be so difficult.
I want 200 more. This is...
a limited-edition purse from the brand's SS collection last year.
This baby is very special.
I'm sorry.
You know who I am, right?
I've seen you on TV.
You're an announcer, right?
Yes, I am.
My mother-in-law...
has so many purses and jewellery pieces.
She wants to get rid of the things that she doesn't really use,
so please give her a good deal.
Would you like my autograph?
You're...
one of my favourite announcers.
I'll take good care of her.
- Just a moment, please. - Thank you.
You impressed me there.
You're selling your beloved purses and jewellery pieces.
This is the least I can do as your daughter-in-law.
Tae Yang!
I came to tell you good news.
Good news? What is it?
(Certificate of Appointment, Kang Tae Yang)
"Certificate of Appointment, Kang Tae Yang".
"Certified to teach at secondary schools."
"Appointed to a teaching post at Hyohwa High School."
"February 17, 2017."
"Commissioner of Seoul Metropolitan Office of Education."
You got a post?
I'm so happy for you. Congratulations, Tae Yang.
Well...
There's one more.
What is this?
(Certificate of Appointment, Min Hyo Won)
"Certificate of Appointment, Min Hyo Won".
"Despite all the difficulties and hardships,"
"your optimism and passion..."
"have allowed you to continue loving and trusting me, Kang Tae Yang."
"Hence, I'd like to appoint you as my lifetime partner."
"February 17, 2017."
"From Kang Tae Yang."
Kang Tae Yang.
Would you marry me?
Of course.
You don't even have to ask.
Thanks.
Thanks for accepting my proposal.
I wanted to take you to somewhere fancy,
but I was in such a rush to share the good news with you.
This is so sweet.
I won't be able to forget...
this moment for the rest of my life.
Isn't it such good news?
Wait a minute.
Why are you so nervous? It's not like you.
You're right. But I can't help being nervous.
What's that?
It's a pill to calm myself down.
My heart was beating so fast, I bought at the chemist's earlier.
Honestly, I'm a bit nervous myself.
Then do you want to share this?
Why...
are you bowing all of a sudden?
(Certificate of Appointment)
I received this certificate from the Education Office today.
What is it you want to say?
Please let me marry Hyo Won.
With just a certificate like this,
don't you think you're acting too arrogant?
What do you mean by just a certificate?
Are you kidding me?
I know I can make Hyo Won happy.
Please. I ask for your approval.
Please, Mum.
You've spent enough time with him to get to know him.
There's no one in the world as honest...
and consistent as Tae Yang.
You're blinded by love.
You're right. I'm blinded by love.
But I promise you, Mother.
We'll live the rest of our lives like this.
I can't stand listening to this nonsense.
Don't spoil this. Be quiet, will you?
Hyo Won. You shouldn't act like that to your older brother.
All of you, be quiet.
I understand that you'll become a teacher soon,
but what will you two live off of for the time being?
We've gone bankrupt, and as far as I know,
the money you used to get this house was your entire fortune.
If you approve of our marriage,
I'll make sure to take care of the practical issues.
Mum. We'll take care of everything.
Please don't worry and give us your approval.
If you make an account, I assure you, you won't regret it.
Such a thing shouldn't happen, but just in case,
you can get compensation if there's a fire in the market or store.
- The terms do sound good. - Of course.
But unfortunately, we've put the store up for sale.
Why?
We'll be moving to Busan due to a family affair.
That far away?
Yes. I've become so fond of you.
Me, too.
That's right. Mrs Bok.
Everyone praises you for your cooking skills.
Why don't you take over our grocery store?
- Me? - Yes.
I had no choice but to put up the store,
but we have a lot of regular customers.
This store brings quite a good income.
That I know, of course.
Exactly.
I wouldn't want to give it up to a stranger.
You're late.
Yes. I had some urgent matters to care of at the office.
Where's Yun Shil?
Dong Jin. Yun Shil isn't feeling too well.
Why? Is she sick?
I don't think so. Earlier, at the opening ceremony,
you must have done something wrong.
What did I do wrong?
According to Ms Geum, she's been in a bad mood...
ever since the opening ceremony.
I wonder what's wrong.
Us men could never understand women's profound thoughts.
That indeed is true.
Most women often tend to get upset and act grouchy...
without telling us the reason.
Men can never in their own nature...
find out the reasons on their own.
Therefore, when you're just dating,
you can be let off by just apologizing.
However, once you get married, you shouldn't use that method.
It's important that you become the forestaller from the beginning.
Otherwise, she'll end up controlling you for the rest of your life.
That's nonsense.
Did you just laugh?
You should pay attention to our advice.
Did he just laugh?
- Yes. - What Tae Pyung said is true.
The first argument after getting married is most importance.
If you don't take control, you'll end up being controlled.
Do you want to end up like me? Do you? Look at me.
That's enough. I'll take care of this on my own.
It doesn't seem like he can do this on his own.
You're right. His eyes looked too soft. This doesn't look good.
He should've have taken our advice seriously.
Where could have she gone?
Why are you here when we have our room?
I'm going to sleep here tonight.
Did something upsetting happen today?
What's wrong. You'll have to tell me in order to know.
Please get up and talk to me.
This is so frustrating. What's wrong?
Do I make you frustrated?
That's not what I meant.
It's just that I can see you're upset, but since you're not talking,
I have no idea what the problem is.
All right. You don't have to tell me. Let's just go back to our room.
I don't want to. I'm going to sleep here alone.
We're already using separate rooms? We're newlyweds.
This will become a habit.
Anyhow, I refuse to speak with you.
What could be the problem? Why is she acting that way?
Why are you coming out of that room?
It's nothing.
Did you argue with Dong Jin?
We didn't argue,
but I'm just a bit upset with him.
Did Dong Jin do something wrong?
Not exactly.
I'm just so mad for some reason.
Then that means he did something wrong.
Women don't get upset for no reason.
It means Dong Jin somehow made you upset.
It's not that.
It could be because of my inferiority complex.
No. You're wrong.
When you're upset, you should just express it.
If you act nice and try to understand everything,
men will start to look down on you.
In the first argument as newlyweds, who takes control...
will change everything.
Make sure not to be defeated.
Yun Shil.
Let's talk.
I don't have anything to say to you.
Why is she acting liking this?
Don't put ideas into her head.
That's the way to do it. Be strong.
I'm her sister-in-law. Shouldn't I take Dong Jin's side?
Don't act as her sister-in-law.
As a female, you should take Yun Shil's side.
You think so? That would be better, right?
Indeed.
Let's go see.
Wait. Where do you think you're going?
I told you. I want to be alone.
Using separate rooms is out of the question.
Here you go.
What is this?
During the years that you wasted,
you regretted being unable to pursue your studies the most.
I thought about what I could do for you,
and I decided I want to support you so that you could pursue your dream.
That's a register card for a college entrance exam preparatory institute.
What are you talking about? It's too late.
What do you mean it's too late?
You can study hard and enter a college.
You've always wanted to study fashion. Once you enter college,
you can study that field professionally.
I haven't looked at books in years.
I don't think I can do it.
Why worry when you have an excellent tutor right here?
When I was in college, I tutored many students as a part-time job.
All of my students went to prestigious schools.
Even so,
I have work to do at the tailor shop and chores to do in the household.
I'll help you with that as well.
I'll be your husband, tutor as well as a housekeeper.
I'll take on three roles.
It'll be difficult, but I can do it.
You're happy that you married me, aren't you?
Do you feel better now?
You sure met an amazing husband, didn't you?
I sure did.
You were upset one minute and now you're smiling. You're too easy.
Come here.
My pretty, pretty, nice wife.
I told him to take control.
He's obviously been defeated.
That ended too easily.
I was impressed by Dong Jin though.
Me, too. Yun Shil must be so happy.
Are you jealous?
If you want, I could support you anytime.
No, I don't want that.
I hate studying.
No thanks.
Sun Nyeo, why don't you register for an institute this time...
and get a high school diploma.
Where are you going?
May I come in for a minute?
All right.
Why didn't you go to bed?
Why didn't you, Mum?
I have many thoughts,
so I couldn't sleep.
Are you thinking about Hyo Won and Tae Yang?
Why don't you...
let them get married?
Hyo Sang.
Why are you saying that? Are you all right?
I've seen a lot of people, but there's no one...
who is as good as Tae Yang.
Even I think he's a nice guy.
You had a tantrum saying never to let them get married a while ago.
I did that because I was grumpy...
to see that he was so confident all the time.
He's a good man...
and treats Hyo Won well.
Also, if he becomes a teacher,
he has income enough to live on.
Hyo Sang!
I'm really moved.
Thank you so much.
What are you doing? It's weird.
Are you that happy?
I'm very happy. I'm too happy to death.
Once you get married,
you'll realise that it was happiest when you were with me.
Hyo Sang.
All right.
- Long time no see. - How are you?
- I meet you here. - Right.
She is so beautiful.
I didn't realise that a traditional wedding would be like this.
I heard that they won a competition,
so they can have a wedding for free.
Right.
Tae Yang is good at writing. He wrote a story...
and won the competition.
I'm fortunate to have him as a son-in-law.
Do you think you don't have a good daughter-in-law?
Well, you're...
not bad.
Hyo Won, you're so beautiful.
Mum!
All right.
You're excited.
- Are you that happy to get married? - Yes.
They say a bride should not smile too much, so I'm holding it back.
But I can't help it.
Stop acting like a child.
You would understand how I feel once you get married...
and have a hard time.
You don't know anything about housekeeping.
How are you going to live after you get married?
I'm so worried.
Don't worry, Mum.
Tae Yang said that he wouldn't let me face hardship.
He said he wouldn't let me wash the dishes.
Do you believe that, Hyo Won?
I surely do.
Tae Yang would never tell a lie.
He says he'll do anything if you marry him.
But once you live with him, it's hard to keep half of those promises.
I'll live happily with Tae Yang.
And be there for each other.
We'll be all right, so don't worry, Mum.
It feels like it was only yesterday...
when you were a little baby and crying in my arms.
You're all grown up already and getting married.
Time flies.
Mum, thank you...
for giving birth to me and raising me so well.
It would be a lot different from when you were dating.
I think Tae Yang would do well,
but still,
I wish you be considerate to each other...
and live happily.
I will.
All right.
Make sure...
you live happily.
The groom...
enters.
Everyone,
get out of the way!
He's all smiling.
- Get out of the way! - He looks so happy.
You did it.
Everyone,
- get out of the way! - Get out of the way!
- It's nice. - Do you think so?
Shall we hold a wedding again in a traditional way?
Are you sure?
- I'm kidding. - You're silly.
The bride enters.
- Get out of the way! - Get out of the way!
Everyone,
- Get out of the way! - How are you?
You're so beautiful.
How are you?
Here's the bride.
- Congratulations. - Thank you.
Ji Yun, thank you.
Hyo Sang.
She looks happy.
Dong Jin.
- Get out of the way! - Get out of the way!
(The Gentlemen of Wolgyesu Tailor Shop)
I feel like I'm dreaming.
It feels surreal.
If only we didn't become bankrupt,
we wouldn't let her get married like this.
Yun Shil, are you all right? Why are you eating like that?
- Are you sick? - You kicked out my family.
You should live well by yourself. What's wrong with you?
Let's forget about him. You're sick because of Dong Jin.
I'm happy that I can study again.
I'm glad that you're happy, Yun Shil.