(The following content may not be suitable for viewers under 15.)
(Viewer discretion is advised.)
The groom and the bride,
please wash your hands in the basin.
Are they going to wash their feet after they wash their hands?
Be quiet.
That's how they wash their hands.
Bride, bow to the groom.
Groom, bow to the bride.
My goodness.
Why did she drink it all up?
The bride must be just like her mum. She drinks very well.
What did you say?
I'm sorry.
She drank the whole thing up.
She's just like her mum.
- Did you drink up? - I did.
Are your hands cold?
I feel warm now.
The groom and the bride will...
- march now. - Have a good life.
Thank you.
- Live happily. - Be happy.
Why are we throwing this?
I have no idea. Just do it.
The adzuki beans prevent bad luck...
and the rice means that it'll bring them wealth.
That's why the guests throw them to the bride and the groom.
I'm sure it means well.
Be happy!
Always be happy just as you're now.
How do you know such a thing? You're young.
She's a KBS anchor who has both beauty and intelligence.
I see.
You're a dull fellow.
Honey, why don't we...
have a wedding again after 10 years in a traditional way?
No thanks. That would be troublesome.
You lack romance.
Goodness.
It's you who have menopause, not me.
Let's all have a wedding again after 10 years.
Okay.
If you're not going to do it with me,
- I'll do it with another woman. - What?
Dong Jin, you and your wife can join us for the wedding later.
- Shall we? - All right.
All right, let's do it.
- The bride and the groom... - Will march.
I'm hungry, honey.
One.
- Two. - Three!
Is this the wedding car?
Can they go to Busan in this car?
It seems that it's not in a good condition.
My friend said...
that it doesn't have any problem even though it doesn't look nice.
Still, it's unreliable. I'll lend you my car. Take my car.
No, thank you. We're fine.
Thank you all...
for coming to the wedding.
Of course, we should come to their wedding.
Thank you for the wedding song.
It was moving.
It's not that I'm taking credit,
but my husband is so popular nowadays.
People want him to sing for their weddings, 60th and 80th birthdays.
It was his present to sing the wedding song for nothing.
She promotes her husband even today.
She's his manager non stop.
Be careful when you drive.
- All right, Hyo Sang. - Call me right away...
if something happens.
Don't worry, Mum.
I'll make sure to spend an unforgettable first night.
An unforgettable first night? You fool.
That's not something you should say in front of your mother-in-law.
It's fine. That's part of her charm.
You two should get going in order to beat traffic.
- See you all when we get back. - See you all when we get back.
Have a safe trip, Tae Yang.
Thanks.
- Go ahead and leave now. - Let's get going.
Tae Yang.
We'll be going now, Mum.
All right.
Drive safely.
They're really going. Here they go.
- How wonderful. - The honeymoon period is the best.
Sam Do. Did you give Tae Yang that thing?
What do you mean?
That thing you always give to the grooms.
That thing elders have in order to have some fun. The blue pill.
He wouldn't need that.
That's something you or Dong Jin would need.
That's nonsense.
What are you talking about?
I thought I saw you put one in the car. You didn't give it to him?
You must have taken it yourself.
Stop the nonsense.
They'll live happily, Ms Ko.
Don't worry about them.
I'm just worried we might have rushed things.
If only our family hadn't gone bankrupt,
we wouldn't have hurried things and held such a simple wedding.
Don't cry, Mum.
That's right. I almost forgot.
Our father asked me to give you this.
He sent this from Gangneung? He shouldn't have.
Why check what's in the envelope while you say that?
Thank you all for coming.
All my relatives have turned their back on us...
because they were worried we might ask them for money,
but I can see I can rely on my friends and neighbours.
By the way, where's Hyo Joo?
She left in a hurry right after the ceremony.
I'm sorry, Dong Jin.
When we were taking the group picture at the wedding earlier,
I realised that we don't even have a decent wedding photo.
All because of me, not only do we not have a decent picture,
we weren't able to hold a proper ceremony. I'm sorry.
Nonsense. That wasn't your fault.
We made a promise with Samdo and Tae Pyung earlier, didn't we?
Us three couples can hold an anniversary wedding someday.
What's wrong? Do you feel sick?
The food was so good at the wedding.
I must've have eaten too much. I think I have an upset stomach.
Really? Shall we go to the hospital?
No. It's not that serious. I'm sure time will ease the pain.
Why don't you sit down. I'll try giving you a massage.
Why are you drinking beer in the daytime?
Did the wedding ceremony go well?
Of course, it went well.
I think I know what's wrong. Our daughter is sad to see...
her first love get married, so she must be having a drink.
I just thought...
I think I deserve to drink at least two cans of beer...
on the day my love of two years gets married.
This is a pitiful sight.
I think it's a good idea.
Have one can for each year you had a crush on him and forget him.
If only he wasn't my in-law, I would've married him.
Why say that when you act like you've gotten over him?
Do you still have feelings for him?
No. It's not that.
I just feel a bit sad,
and I feel ashamed of myself.
Don't cry.
Da Jeong. How should I put this? You see, a first love...
is like a lottery ticket you haven't scratched.
You know you have a low chance of winning the first prize,
but you somehow can't seem to lose hope.
A first love gives you that kind of feeling.
I'm sure you'll soon meet a guy that will love and cherish you,
so don't feel sad anymore.
Why don't we...
bid farewell to your first love...
and have a can of beer.
Cheers to Da Jeong's first love of the past.
Cheers.
Don't cry. You'll be all right.
Move it to the left. To the left, please.
- This way? - Yes, it's slightly tilted.
- Push it from that side. - Just slightly.
Yes. That's perfect.
(Sun Nyeo's Side Dishes)
Did you finish fixing the taps?
Yes. I repaired the taps and fixed the fridge as well.
Everything's been taken care of, Mrs Bok.
You'll see. Starting from tomorrow...
I'm going to attract all the people in Hyoja-dong to our store.
Don't set such high goals.
Money's important, but you have to take care of yourself.
Don't worry about me. You should worry about your menopause thing.
What are you talking about?
You saw that I've overcome my menopause with your own eyes.
You didn't seem to be as good as your heyday. No need to boast.
- What did you say? - I'm just joking.
Wait and see. I'll buy you a building some day.
A building? That sounds great.
I guess I'll be able to live in luxury thanks to my amazing wife.
(College Preparatory Institute)
(Honest Institute)
What's the matter? Are you nervous?
It's not that I'm nervous.
I'm just worried I might be the oldest student.
I guess I'm a bit embarrassed and worried.
Age doesn't matter when it comes to studying.
There's no need to worry. Just focus on getting adjusted.
I'm sure it'll be a bit tough catching up with the class.
I refuse to take it easy. I'm going to do well from the start.
I'm going to study really hard and do well...
so that I can enter the school you graduated from.
What? My goodness.
Why are you laughing? Are you doubting me?
At first, you should set goals that suit you and then move up.
Don't set your goals too high from the beginning. You'll get exhausted.
You don't think I can do it, do you?
Of course not. I'll fully support you.
Good. I'll make sure to become an alumna of your school.
Great. I'll look forward to it, my future junior.
- I can do this. - You can do this.
I knew I'd be the oldest.
Seeing you among young students,
Ms Shiny Eyes looks like a teen.
You look the youngest and prettiest to me,
so don't be discouraged. Cheer up. You can do this, Ms Shiny Eyes.
- I can do this. - You can do this.
I'm nervous.
Concentrate and study hard.
I will.
I don't deserve to be a mother. I couldn't give any financial support.
It breaks my heart that she got married in such a hurry like this.
My poor, Hyo Won.
A fancy wedding's all useless.
Ji Yun and I cared so much about appearance...
we spent a fortune on a fancy wedding.
But seeing the two today, Hyo Won's couple looked much happier.
What I'm trying to say is that how other people see us...
doesn't matter at all.
What's gotten into you?
It's not like you to say something so mature.
Hyo Sang's changed, Mother. He's not the person he once was.
He paid a fortune to learn a lesson.
- He should change indeed. - Gosh.
It's only natural for him to change somehow.
Eat your dinner, Mum.
It's Hyo Joo.
What's up? You didn't even tell me that you're leaving at the wedding.
It...
hurts so much.
Please help.
You're sick? What's wrong?
- Where's the housekeeper? - There's no one here.
What?
I'm all alone.
Hey.
I thought she'd change the door code,
but she left it the same.
Thank goodness.
- Where is she? - I don't know.
- Hyo Joo. - Hyo Joo.
- Hyo Joo. - Hyo Joo!
Are you okay? Here.
What's wrong?
Hyo Joo! What's wrong with her?
- Hyo Joo. - Call an ambulance.
- Okay. - Hurry.
We need to see the test results to know for sure,
but it looks like it may be appendicitis...
or gastritis.
Based on her blood test,
she's malnourished and anaemic too.
Malnourished?
In this time and age?
It looks like she hasn't eaten...
at all lately.
Didn't you know?
Well...
We don't live together, so...
She will...
wake up, won't she?
She has a high fever and is dehydrated,
but she's getting some fluids now, so she'll wake up soon.
Let her rest for now.
I'll be back once the test results are out.
Goodness. You poor thing.
Hyo Joo.
- Are you awake? - Are you okay?
Do you see me?
Calm down. I'm not dying.
How could you let yourself get like this?
You should've been eating well and doing well...
after kicking us out. What is this?
How could you get malnourished?
Must you talk to your sick sister like that?
We're the ones who were kicked out.
Why is the person who kicked us out sick?
Darn it.
Hyo Sang...
is just upset,
seeing you sick.
Don't mind him,
okay?
Here, honey.
- More? - Yes.
Aren't you tired?
Should I drive?
No. I'm fine. Don't worry.
Once we get to Busan,
let's go to Jagalchi Market and eat grilled fish.
That sounds good.
- And tomorrow morning, - Yes?
let's go look at camellia flowers.
I think camellia flowers are the prettiest.
- Honey. - Yes?
Do you know what the camellia flower means?
What?
"I love you more than anyone."
It's the same as me.
What's this?
Is that smoke?
Smoke?
Yes. There's smoke coming from under the hood.
Honey, pull over.
Hold on.
Yes. There's smoke coming from the engine.
Okay, we'll wait.
What did he say?
He said he'll come right now and wait.
It wouldn't explode, would it?
It won't, so don't worry.
Will we make it to Busan today?
He'll be here soon, so don't worry.
Let's hurry and eat grilled fish.
Of course.
It's cold.
Here.
Didn't you go home?
Where would I go?
I waited until your class ended,
like a student's parent.
It's cold out and you must be tired.
You didn't have to wait.
It's dark out already.
What if someone takes my pretty wife away?
Who'd want an old woman like me?
What do you mean?
I saw your class earlier.
You're the youngest and prettiest.
Seriously. What nonsense.
I was obviously the oldest there.
It's tiring to study again, isn't it?
I was so sleepy, I must've yawned like 10 times.
You must be tired. Let's go home.
Wait. I'm hungry.
You felt sick earlier. Do you feel better?
I think so.
I want a steamed bun.
- A steamed bun? - Yes. Steamed bun.
That means we need a convenience store.
A convenience store.
Goodness.
I won't steal your food, so slow down.
Here, have some milk.
I'm hungry. Maybe it's because I haven't used my brain in a while.
Is it that good?
I don't usually like steamed buns,
but it's really good today.
Here. Have some.
I'm fine. Eat slowly.
Drink some of this too.
The CT and x-ray showed...
- that her appendix is fine. - Good.
You may take her home...
after she finishes getting the fluids and painkiller.
She doesn't need to be admitted?
Even if she gets admitted, all we can do...
is give her fluids anyway.
She must've been under a lot of stress lately.
She should rest and eat plenty of good food,
- then she'll be fine. - Okay.
Ma'am. You know you are anaemic, right?
- Yes. - Anaemic people...
must be extra careful about eating right.
Don't forget to take your vitamins and iron.
- Okay, then. - Thank you.
Sorry.
I should've been more attentive.
Don't do that.
You shouldn't change so much so quickly.
You rude brat.
Hyo Joo.
Let's...
forget it all.
You're sick...
because of Dong Jin.
You wanted to get him back somehow,
but it wasn't going your way.
That's why it was eating you up inside...
until it destroyed your body.
Looks like we'll be spending our first night together in a car.
I'm sorry.
I shouldn't have listened to my friend.
I like it. It was thrilling and very special.
Do you mean it?
It's completely different from everyone else's first night.
I'll never forget it for as long as I live.
True. Even if we fight, if we think about tonight,
it'll probably make us laugh.
You're right.
I'll make money and save up so that we can buy a house...
and a car.
I won't make you...
suffer like tonight.
I told you, I didn't suffer at all.
It was a memory.
It was a gift I will never forget.
Take a nap until we get to the body shop.
(Upload)
(Vision Tailor Order Form)
(Sending)
(Vision Tailor, Beautiful Suits, Incheon Tailor Shop)
(Download)
(Sending complete)
(Tonelli and Wolgyesu Tailor Shop)
(Wolgyesu Tailor Union)
(Tonelli and Wolgyesu)
(Wolgyesu Tailor Shop)
This is the first time I'm reporting to you since...
I took over when Meesa was in a dire situation.
I did my best to convince creditors and stabilise our stock price.
As a result, I finally but barely made the creditors agree...
to not demand we repay them immediately.
Our stock price has stabilised since the market realised...
we won't go through a liquidity crisis.
Our shareholders were dumping what they owned,
but prices have risen by 50 percent.
Although we haven't yet made a full recovery,
once we release our performance of the first quarter,
I believe our share prices will rise exponentially.
I believe this was made possible by the shareholders,
you and the hard work of all our employees.
After a storm comes a calm.
Let's learn from this crisis to serve Korea and Koreans.
I'd like you to help me make it happen to better ourselves.
I heard you took a few sick days. Are you okay?
Yes. I was bedridden for a few days.
I guess I was under a lot of stress.
Let's talk.
I heard that thanks to you, Meesa's back on track.
I'm a bad judge of men, but a good judge of character.
You're the best businessman.
Were you very sick?
It was nothing. A bout of love sickness.
It was a joke. There's no need to tense up.
Find a good guy.
You're still very beautiful and full of charm.
Thanks for saying that.
I had such a great ex-husband...
I'm not sure if anyone can satisfy me.
I'll think about it.
We got another order from the department store.
I couldn't do all this if I had 10 clones.
Don't we need another experienced worker?
Maybe. So this is what it means when they say something...
sells like hotcakes.
Get that.
Hello, this is Wolgyesu Tailor Shop.
Hey, Gianni.
Yes. It's me, Hyo Sang.
I'm doing the paperwork right now to request that headquarters...
send us tailors for our tailor training.
By the way, I heard that we're experiencing...
a huge backlog in orders.
Yes, we've been getting a more...
explosive response from our customers...
than we previously expected.
The entire union is working non stop.
Yes, Mr Lee said that.
Headquarters didn't expect such a strong response either.
They are amazed at the potential of the Asian market.
Yes, so if you want to increase the working staff,
the tailor training skills programme...
needs to take place as soon as possible.
Yes. I'll send out the report to Mr Lee.
All right. See you later.
Okay. All right, bye-bye.
I must give it to you for your amazing pronunciation.
I studied abroad, you know.
I speak the Manhattan dialect.
Did you study abroad?
Get me some water.
My goodness.
Hot or cold?
I said water.
I know. Hot or cold?
Didn't you hear me? I said water.
Do you want hot or cold water?
What?
- Lukewarm water. - Okay, lukewarm water.
Coming up.
I don't use any artificial seasoning,
and I use less salt, so it'll be better for you.
Your food tastes just like what my mum used to make for me.
That's the Sun Nyeo's Side Dishes motto.
We take care of your food with the love of a mum's.
I prepared everything without using anything that's bad for you.
Just enjoy the food.
I will.
Tell others about us.
- I will. Good luck. - Thank you.
Have a nice day. Come by again.
Madam Ko, will you stop eating?
You eat more than I manage to sell.
I slave away for you so hard that my feet bleed.
These don't cost that much, so be nice.
You work here?
Let's be honest here. Are you a good cook...
or are you nice to others?
You're just here to watch the store,
so don't act like you work here.
I really don't like your logic.
I have my own business,
and I felt sorry that you were doing everything yourself.
Also, my son is under your husband's wing.
That's why I took time out to work for you for a teeny pay.
Don't you dare talk like that.
I bought you a crocodile skin bag many years ago.
I also acted as a barricade between you and the others.
I believe...
I stayed loyal to you.
Okay, fine, I get it.
Then do the dishes.
The sink's absolutely full.
Okay. After I finish eating this.
What a nuisance.
Once a madam, always a madam.
My goodness.
(Sun Nyeo's Side Dishes opening sale)
Hang on.
Who's that?
It's the oil lady.
I swear I will get you today.
I'll fight you to the death.
Give me my money. I want my money back.
I'm sorry, Sun Nyeo.
If you are, give me my money back!
I got swindled myself and I've got nothing left!
(I'm Sorry, Sun Nyeo)
Whenever I made some money, it went into the account.
Once I'd saved up at least half of what I owe you,
I was going to come here and ask for forgiveness.
I'm sorry, Sun Nyeo.
How will you manage by saving 5 or 10 dollars at a time?
I got swindled while trying to get your money back.
I didn't set off planning...
to spend your money. I really didn't.
What's this?
It was made in Korea, not China.
Who said I wanted sesame oil?
I want my money back.
Come on, Sun Nyeo.
Stop it.
Welcome.
She's a part-timer who will start today.
What?
Did you just fire me?
No. We worked together in the market in Daejeon.
I hope you'll get along and work together.
Let's clarify the ranks here.
I'm Ko Eun Sook, the manager at Sun Nyeo's Side Dishes.
I'm your superior.
Okay.
Superior?
Stop eating the food.
You ate it all.
Seriously.
It takes five days to get...
the family relationship certificate for the marriage registration.
Are you done?
Yes.
- Here you go. - Thank you.
Have a nice day.
Okay, finally. We have our marriage certificate.
Sung Tae Pyung.
Lee Dong Sook.
Hold on. Excuse me.
The name is correct, but the birthday...
is incorrect.
You still didn't tell him?
It's correct.
But it says Lee Dong Sook...
was born on July 28, 1974.
(Lee Dong Sook, July 28, 1974)
- Were you born in 1974? - That's not...
It's not wrong.
You said you were a couple of years younger than I am.
At heart.
At heart? You're younger at heart.
Age is but a number. Who cares?
Are you legally a married couple now?
Of course.
Ms Lee Dong Sook,
you, Da Jeong and I, Sung Tae Pyung...
are officially a family.
Okay. Then...
Ta-da.
- What's with the rings? - It bothered me...
that you didn't have proper rings.
You don't have money for that.
I should've gotten them.
You can just get her an expensive diamond ring later.
Thank you.
Me too. Thank you, Da Jeong.
And Ms Dong Sook. Thank you...
for giving me such a pretty and grown-up daughter...
for free.
Go on. Put them on.
Shall we?
- Here. - Mum's.
And Dad's.
It's a perfect fit.
- What do you think? - How pretty.
Really?
Now that you have your rings,
how about a picture to commemorate the moment?
Shall we?
Okay.
Hold up the registration.
One, two, three.
(Application Receipt)
- Cheese. - Cheese.
You know the Korean teacher?
He's handsome and has a great voice.
My eyes and ears are so happy now.
You know...
he was a model before coming to our school, right?
- Really? - Yes.
- "You look extra pretty today." - "You look extra pretty today."
I know...
- The make-up. - The make-up.
Hey. The Korean teacher is mine,
so hands off, got it?
Don't make me laugh.
I got dibs.
What are they saying about my husband?
Honey!
I'm Mr Kang Tae Yang's wife.
- Is this woman really your wife? - Yes.
"This woman"?
That's no way to speak about your teacher's wife.
She's so annoying. Let's go!
- Let's go. - Let's go.
Look.
Those little brats.
Don't even try.
You got off work early.
I had a meeting. It was too late to go back,
so I decided to come here instead.
The manager shouldn't slack off.
I didn't slack off.
I've been working late every day since I got back from our honeymoon.
Okay.
Rock-paper-scissors!
Yes! I won!
You're in charge of dinner tonight.
Like this?
What's for dinner?
I'll have to think about it on our way home.
Rock-paper-scissors!
Yes! I won again!
You're doing the dishes too.
Goodness.
You only put out scissors.
Are you good at rock-paper-scissors?
Rock-paper-scissors! I won again.
Hello.
Goodness. Hi.
I was taking down your laundry in case it drizzles.
- Thank you. - Thank you.
When Hong Gi Pyo and his mum lived up here,
I didn't want to come up here,
but now that our sweet newlyweds are here,
I keep wondering if there is anything I can do to help.
- Thank you. - Is the boiler working well?
Yes, it's very warm.
I'll let you rest.
- Good night. - Good night.
Ta-da.
Here.
Did we get any mail?
Look. It's japchae.
My mum must've left it.
We won't have to worry about dinner tonight, thanks to her.
- Tonight's dinner will be... - Japchae rice!
Correct.
Okay.
That's good.
It feels like a dream.
What does?
Eating with you,
sleeping with you,
getting up and leaving for work with you and coming home with you.
It doesn't seem real.
It's the same for me too.
It feels like a dream, living together with you.
It shocks me several times a day.
But honey...
Before starting class tomorrow, tell them,
"I'm a married man!"
Start with that, okay?
The girls think you're single, and...
Just in case.
I don't like it.
You're so silly.
You mean old lady.
I'm not an old lady.
(College Preparatory Institute)
You must be tired taking classes right after...
working at the tailor shop.
It is a bit tiring, but it's fun, so I like it.
The fact that I can go back to school now...
is amazing and it makes me feel good.
I'm happy.
Since you're happy, so am I.
But still, don't push yourself too hard.
But Dong Jin,
- I want a steamed bun. - Again?
I couldn't concentrate in class...
because that was all I could think about.
- About steamed buns? - Yes.
You want it that badly?
We'll have to go eat steamed buns, then.
Steamed buns. Steamed buns.
Steamed buns?
- Steamed buns! - Steamed buns.
I'll take these to go.
Hold on.
You ate so many already.
You want to take all these home?
What if I can't sleep later because I'm craving them?
You are so funny.
Okay. How much is it?
Here. Have some water.
What's wrong with me?
Wow. That looks good.
Thank you.
Aren't you going to eat?
I'm not hungry.
Of course, not. Not after eating so many steamed buns.
This soup tastes really good.
Do you want to try some?
I'd rather have a steamed bun.
Again?
I'll eat this steamed bun,
so you eat your dinner.
Goodness.
But...
I'm too tired to lift the spoon.
With the company and playing a student's parent,
I must be exhausted.
You crybaby.
I mean it. I'm really tired.
Look. My hand is all limp.
Fine.
Open wide.
Stop it.
What was that?
Find a good guy.
You're still very beautiful and full of charm.
What are you calling for?
To ask how you're feeling.
Are you okay?
I am.
Did you eat dinner?
You're sick because you don't eat.
Even if you're upset or something's bothering you,
don't skip a single meal.
You nag more than usual these days.
I was too scared of you to nag when we lived together.
Now I don't have to stay on your good side.
Who cares if I nag or not?
So nothing stops you?
I'll call morning and evening and be an evil stepmother, so be prepared.
Bye. Let's talk tomorrow.
Did you just talk to Hyo Won?
No, Hyo Joo.
That was Hyo Joo on the phone?
Yes. Why?
You sounded so sweet.
You used to hate each other's guts.
Why the sudden change?
Did you just say I hated her guts?
How dare you say that to your mother-in-law!
You're an anchor, aren't you?
Don't you know what not to say?
Mum.
Why do you act like you hate Ji Yun's guts?
I just can't stand this.
I should save up and move out of here.
I can't stand living with my newly-wed son.
Let's go.
My goodness.
I should just...
My head aches.
That's awesome.
How much is that if you included the credit card slips?
No way!
Hang in there. I'll buy you a building.
If you really want to make big money,
you should run a business, not work for a pay.
Was dinner too salty? I feel thirsty.
No way.
Freeze.
What were you doing?
These two bills were sticking out and I was...
going to put them back.
You look so normal and you steal from your wife?
The older you get the sillier you become.
How dare you say that to your respectable husband.
Respectable husband?
Move.
Massage my stomach and I'll give you 20 dollars.
Okay.
Why do you need a massage?
Are you sick?
I've been feeling weird after meals for a while.
I feel nauseous and just generally not too good.
You got worried about the new store and got stressed...
about meeting the oil lady, that's why.
Do you want some medicine?
No, I'll be fine after a good rest.
Give me a massage.
I'll give you a great one if you pay me in advance.
You love money too much.
Here.
Thank you.
Get well, get well soon.
Get well, Sun Nyeo.
That is gross. How could you?
You have a great touch.
I feel so much better already.
Keep going.
Get well, get well soon.
Get well, Sun Nyeo.
That's lovely.
Dong Jin, are you busy?
No. Do you need help with something?
I just can't understand what this means.
Let me see. It's a quadratic inequality.
What do you not get?
The answer says...
"X" has a real positive value.
Why must I start with zero?
Can't I start with one?
A number with a real positive value...
is larger than 0, not 1.
Using the formula in the answer sheet,
start by putting zero instead of "X".
The answer is whichever results in "A" being equal to...
or larger than zero.
When "X" is larger than zero...
"A" has to have a real positive value.
Look at this.
The line on the graph goes up...
when "X" is larger than -2.
I still don't get it.
You can't look at the answer whenever you get stuck.
You have to try to solve and understand it yourself.
You'll never get there if you use the answers.
Should I struggle with a question...
I've been stuck on for hours?
When learning how to sew, you look at...
a good example and copy what you see.
I need to look at the answer sheet to know...
how to solve maths problems.
You can't compare maths to sewing.
Why not? Learning the steps to solving a maths problem...
is just like learning how to sew stitch by stitch.
You're pushing it.
- You're unbelievable. - I'm what?
Did you mean me?
Yes. Why?
What's wrong now?
I'm just trying to teach you,
and I just said you shouldn't rely on the answers.
I just can't do it by myself...
and was going to refer it for hints.
You made me feel bad.
I didn't want to make you feel bad.
Maths isn't about getting the answer right away.
You learn by solving problems.
Forget it. You show off just because you can solve a maths problem.
What was that about?
Is she upset that I tried to teach her?
I asked because I got stuck and he did nothing but nag.
Why do I feel hungry already?
- Yun Shil. - It's still good cold.
Are you upset...
Gosh.
There's no point in hiding it.
You're eating so soon after getting angry with me?
I need eat and gain the energy...
if I'm to fight you.
I don't believe this.
Are you sick, Yun Shil?
What? No.
Why are you picking at your food?
I was just a bit distracted. I'll get back to eating now.
Are you not feeling well?
I still have an upset stomach.
Have some meat. It's nicely cooked.
Are you feeling sick as well?
I'm really sorry. I suddenly felt nauseated.
Hang on. Do you think you could be pregnant?
You could be. Morning sickness is usually a sign.
Is that what it is?
I'm not sure. I don't really know.
Dong Jin, take her to see a doctor.
Let's go right after breakfast.
If you are pregnant,
Mum and Dad will be really pleased.
I doubt I'm pregnant. I'm not. I can't be.
What now?
Honey.
What are you doing? Don't copy things like that.
I didn't do it on purpose. I suddenly felt nauseated myself.
I told you to take some medicine before going to sleep last night.
It's not indigestion or anything. I feel nauseated.
It's the same thing.
I think Sun Nyeo's jealous that Yun Shil could be pregnant.
Sorry. Eat up.
- Honey, that's enough. Stop. - Stop.
That's enough. Don't copy things like that.
Now stop it.
The results of blood test and the ultrasound...
Congratulations. You're pregnant.
Really? I'm pregnant?
Yes. The blood test confirmed it.
It's still too small, so it may be hard to see,
but the placenta is already in place.
Thank you.
Give me that.
(Examination Room)
I'm fine.
The doctor said you need to be careful...
because it is still very early.
You're clumsy and fall all the time.
You have to be very careful.
You are so over the top.
What do I do?
I'm so happy, I don't know what to do.
You're incredible.
I love you so much.
People are staring.
You're embarrassing me.
Why are you embarrassed?
I want to scream from the top of my lungs that my wife is pregnant.
- Go ahead. - Shall I?
Yes!
What's wrong with you?
Seriously.
I'm just so happy.
I'm so happy right now.
I'd better call my parents.
Wait. I'm still very early in my pregnancy.
Let's not tell anyone yet.
We can let them know once I'm stable.
Okay.
I should've noticed when you kept eating steamed buns.
You don't usually eat those.
Now that you mentioned it,
I'm craving steamed buns again.
What?
Looks like we have a foetus name already.
- Let's call it "Steamed Bun". - Steamed Bun?
It loves the stuff.
Let me see.
Steamed Bun.
I'm your daddy.
I can't wait to meet you.
- Hello? - It's me, Dad.
- Hi, Dong Jin? - Yes.
- Where's Mum? - She went to the market.
I'm taking a walk...
near the house.
- Are you okay? - Of course.
I'm used to...
the layout of this town...
as much as I am of Hyoja-dong.
How is everyone?
Everyone is doing well.
I called with some good news.
It looks like...
you'll be...
a grandpa once more.
Are you saying Yun Shil is pregnant?
- Yes, Dad. - Goodness. Congratulations.
Your mum will be very happy to hear that. Congratulations.
It's all thanks to your and mum's prayers.
When your mum gets back,
I'll tell her to call.
Okay. We'll come down soon.
She needs to take care of herself during the early stage.
You have to help her out a lot.
Yes, I will.
Dong Jin.
I'm sorry,
but when I had you and your sister,
I wasn't completely thrilled as you are now.
You were my gift,
but at the same time,
the burden of having to feed you, clothe you and educate you...
as the head of the household...
kept me up at nights...
when I watched you sleep.
Dong Jin.
I hope you will not be burdened...
by the responsibilities as I was,
but be happy with the gift that you are given.
I have faith that you will...
share the difficulties...
with your smart and kind wife...
and increase the good things...
and live your life to the fullest.
I'm back.
Congratulations.
- What for? - We heard you're pregnant.
How did you know?
How else?
Mr Lee called and said you're in your early stage of pregnancy...
and asked us to make sure you're careful.
He went on and on.
Are you pregnant?
I was going to try to keep it a secret for the time being.
Thank you.
Mum. Mum. Big news.
Dong Jin is going to be a daddy.
What do you mean?
Dong Jin's wife is pregnant?
Yes.
Yes, it is good news,
but your sister will be upset once she finds out.
Yes. Okay.
Yun Shil really is pregnant?
Yes. That's what they say.
They must be blessed.
They're pregnant already.
What?
You said you've been feeling ill all day. Go see a doctor.
- You look pale. - Right?
- Would you finish up? - Sure.
Should I get you some medicine from the pharmacy?
I think I'll go to the hospital.
- Be safe. - Okay.
Be careful.
Hello.
We're having a buy 3, get 1 free grand opening promotion,
so look freely.
- I see. - Yes.
(Internal Medicine, OBGYN)
(OBGYN)
It can't hurt.
I have a strange feeling about this.
So, what's do the test results show?
Ms Bok Sun Nyeo,
The test results show...
Hi, Sam Do.
The four of us are having an emergency meeting.
Is something up?
Dong Jin's wife is pregnant.
She is?
The four of us need to do something on this happy day.
We need to throw a big party.
Of course. I'll come over right after work.
- Mr Kang! - Mr Kang!
Sam Do is hosting a party tonight to celebrate Yun Shil's pregnancy.
Do you want to go?
Yun Shil is pregnant?
Already? They haven't been married that long.
That's great.
Congratulate her for me.
I'm tired. I want to go home and go to bed early.
Okay.
Have fun.
- Mr Kang! - Mr Kang!
Mr Lee!
Hi. Are you leaving now?
- Congratulations. - What?
I heard you're going to be a daddy.
Oh. Yes.
Wow. Word spreads quickly.
I heard you're having a party tonight to celebrate.
I heard from Tae Yang.
We need to have a party.
What is it?
Don't hold it in. Just cry.
It'll fester if you hold it in, so just let it out.
Why do I always cry when I'm with you?
I'm your sister.
Cry freely.
(Congratulations on Your Pregnancy)
Ta-da.
- Congratulations. - Thank you.
- Thank you. - It's for Yun Shil.
I have one too.
- Congratulations. - Thank you.
- One for you. - Thank you.
Congratulations, Aunt and Uncle.
Thank you.
Me too. Congratulations, Yun Shil.
- Thanks. - Thank you, Tae Yang.
- Sure. - Thanks, everyone.
Until the day he or she is born,
I will look after Steamed Bun and Yun Shil well.
I'll need your help with that.
You should say something.
I'm grateful for this, but it's also a bit embarrassing.
I'll look after myself and be careful at all times...
and make sure Steamed Bun is healthy.
Why are you calling the foetus "Steamed Bun"?
Yun Shil was never a fan of steamed buns, but she couldn't...
stop eating them once she got pregnant.
That's why.
Stop!
You're back. I told you on the phone.
Yun Shil's pregnant.
So am I.
Don't do that.
You can't ruin someone's party.
I'm not kidding.
Are you drunk?
I'm sober!
It's an ultrasound of our baby.
Congratulate me too!
Is this...
really a photo of your womb?
Did you...
find someone else's photo?
Why won't you believe me?
You're going to be a dad.
Is that true, Sun Nyeo?
Maybe you're just being jealous because...
Yun Shil's pregnant.
Who says only you can have a child? I'm pregnant too!
Hoorah for Korea!
Hoorah for Sam Do!
Hoorah for Sun Nyeo!
Bravo. Bravo!
Congratulations, Sam Do, Sun Nyeo.
- We did it. - Sun Nyeo.
You said you'd given up on trying.
I'm so impressed.
Sam Do succeeded at last.
I overcame it all!
We overcame it all!
This is good news. This is great news.
This is great news.
(The Gentlemen of Wolgyesu Tailor Shop)
- In-laws? - I think...
our kids share the same fate.
This is fate.
What a fuss.
It's looks like she's running for congress.
I swear I will become the president this time.
I'm sorry I made you a liar.
What should we do now?
Mum, we're newlyweds!
Will you stop coming by and disturbing us?
When will you go back to Meesa Apparel?
You can't sew in that small store forever.
Don't get too upset, Dong Jin. Your father...