(The following content may not be suitable for viewers under 15.)
(Viewer discretion is advised.)
Please follow my instruction.
Place your hands forward.
Let your knees be parallel to your hands.
Make your body form a right angle.
Next,
stretch your hands forward.
Stretch your hip backward.
Let your chest almost touch the floor.
Put your left hand under your right hand.
Relax your head.
Raise your right hand toward the ceiling.
Sun Nyeo,
- don't you feel tired? - Not at all.
Maybe it's because I'm in my last month of the pregnancy.
Just standing up makes me out of breath.
Dong Jin has to help me stand up with his hands.
I found out...
I'm fit for pregnancy.
Neither do I get swollen nor I have morning sickness.
I would be totally fine even if I have 5 more babies.
You're amazing.
What's wrong with my age
My age is just good enough for getting pregnant
Excuse me, Steamed Bun's dad,
I've been thinking...
How about you and I...
become in-laws later?
In-laws?
If my Overcome is a daughter,
- and Pancakes, right? - No, Steamed Bun.
Right. If Steamed Bun is a son, let's get them to marry each other.
- What? - I think...
our children have the same destiny.
See? You and I are just like blood brothers.
They will be born on the similar dates.
They will be a fantastic couple.
Are you saying...
that I should marry off my son to a girl who resembles Sun Nyeo?
Right. Why?
Well, I'd love to,
but I can't ask Steamed Bun his opinion now, that's why.
What makes you hesitate?
Sun Nyeo has strong ability to maintain her livelihood,
she is healthy and strong in body and mind...
and she has a good personality.
There's nothing lacking.
Are you being haughty?
All right. I'll tell Sun Nyeo.
It's not like that.
The babies are not even born yet,
and you're talking about in-laws, so I was embarrassed.
By the way, why is the foetus name...
"Overcome"?
I...
overcame the andropause which is called a man's death...
and went against nature and had a baby.
That's why I named the foetus Overcome...
to overcome. Overcome!
I see.
It had a profound meaning.
- I'm tired. - Honey!
Be careful. How was the exercise?
I was tired and lost my breath...
because I'm in my last month of pregnancy,
but Sun Nyeo was very good at it.
You worried that you were the oldest among the mothers.
As I already told Yun Shil,
I guess I'm fit for pregnancy.
I was not tired at all. I had no problem.
- Honey. - Yes?
After I give birth to Overcome,
how about having one more baby a year apart? All right?
- Great. - Good.
Overcome.
Let's have a baby a year apart too. All right?
No thanks.
Having Steamed Bun is enough for me.
We made a promise to have at least three kids.
I didn't know having a baby would be so hard back then.
- What about a year apart? - No way.
It's good now. Have a seat.
Slowly.
There you go.
Let's see.
Here's your book.
I envy Yun Shil.
That's what I'm saying. I really envy you.
Mister, I will definitely meet a man like you and get married to him.
Hey, do you think a man like him is common?
- What kind of man am I? - You're handsome,
competent and sweet. How nice!
You're like a hero in a comic book.
You're a man of my dream.
Did you hear that? I'm that kind of a man.
All right. You can go now.
All right.
Don't work too hard.
Call me right away if you feel anything strange. Okay?
See you.
Please take care of Yun Shil.
- Sure. - We will.
- Bye. - Bye.
An airmail came for you.
Airmail?
It's an invitation.
It's Madam Ko.
You've been coming by every day...
since Ms Min got discharged from the hospital.
I came here as soon as I left the store after my shift.
Ta-da. I brought chicken soup today.
There.
Hey, it's much better than most short rib soups I've had.
The owner of the store is such a good cook.
Try it. Come on.
No, it's okay. I'll eat it later.
When are you going to eat it then?
Just eat it when I'm here.
Why are you bugging me so much?
How is it? Isn't it so good?
It's not bad.
Like I said, the owner is such a great cook.
She's literally sweeping up all the money in the neighbourhood now.
Getting paid is obviously good,
but being able to take leftover dishes home for free is awesome.
What does that mean? Is this also one of the leftovers?
What? No.
Of course not. I bought it because it's for you.
You cranky girl.
Eat it while it's still warm.
Don't get sick again from malnutrition.
Here. Try this too.
I'm sorry. You got hand dermatitis because of me.
Why is it your fault?
I got it because I love doing housework.
Still.
I should've at least helped you with washing dishes.
Then you wouldn't have gotten hand dermatitis.
You would've broken a bunch of plates though.
A bunch of plates?
Are you making fun of me for being clueless on doing housework?
Gosh, I'm not making fun of you.
I'm stronger than you, so cleaning is easier for me.
I'm also more used to cooking at home,
so I want you to feel comfortable with me taking care of housework.
Still, let me help you with washing dishes from time to time.
Let's see. I can't do that because you'll break the dishes.
What would be good?
I'll let you hang, fold and put away clean laundry.
Okay. Deal.
Hyo Won.
Tae Yang.
It's me.
Gosh, Mum is here again. Goodness.
Hi.
Hello, Mother.
Hi, I thought I should stop by on my way home.
Have you guys had dinner?
Yes. What about you?
Yes, I stopped by to see Hyo Joo and ate with her.
It's getting late. You should've just gone home.
Why did you come here?
I didn't want to go home because I get bored...
and claustrophobic at that tiny place.
I just wanted to play cards with Tae Yang before heading home.
Mum, we're newlyweds.
So what?
You can just go home and play cards with Hyo Sang and Ji Yun.
Why do you keep coming by our place and being a nuisance?
Playing cards with those two is no fun.
I need to play with someone who is compatible with my style of play.
Those guys bore me.
Still, how can you keep dropping in on newlyweds like this?
Don't be like that to Mother.
You just heard what Tae Yang said, right?
You shouldn't be so rude to me.
Aren't I right, Tae Yang?
Yes, Mother. Shall I bring out the blanket?
Sounds great. Let's do this!
Let's use the one I bought recently.
- Okay. - That one is great.
What are you doing now?
Hey. Master taught me how to sew, you know.
It was fun, so I wanted to practice at home.
You find sewing fun?
Yes. Honey, have a look at this.
This is the padding stitch technique.
Using these stitches instead of adhesives...
in order to secure the lining when you make a suit,
prevents distortion and makes it fit better as well.
Hyo Sang.
Have you lost your mind?
What will you use sewing for? Why did you bring that home?
What are you talking about?
I'm learning how to make suits.
Dong Jin must've wanted me to learn this.
I bet that's why he made me work at the shop.
What are you saying?
Well, observing everyone at the shop...
and learning sewing and tailoring there has made me...
realise that I shouldn't think of suits just as a way of making money.
Look at this. I made this curtain too. Isn't it nice?
If anything needs to be ironed or has buttons that are falling off,
bring it to me. I can take care of it.
- What is wrong with him? - Sorry? What?
Nothing. I'm just speechless.
- What? - It's nothing.
Dear all merchants at the market.
Hello. I'm Candidate Number Two, Bok Sun Nyeo.
First, let me tell you a little bit about myself.
Starting with my great-grandmother,
every generation of my family has worked at this market.
It's been the legacy of my family for four generations in a row.
I was born and raised at this market.
Please think of me as your daughter...
and place your trust in me.
If I'm elected as the chairwoman of the market committee,
I'll make sure I dedicate myself solely...
to you and your continued success...
and promise you my loyalty!
- Don't you think this is too much? - Why?
You need to be focusing on our baby's prenatal education.
How can you be practicing that?
Yelling like that...
will stress our baby out so much.
Listening to my speech in my belly...
will make our baby grow into a very eloquent speaker.
From a lawyer, prosecutor and judge to an announcer,
she'll be able to have any job she wants.
You'll have so much on your plate after she's born.
Do you really have to run in the election?
I've decided to run in the election...
for our daughter's future.
Revitalisation of traditional markets...
will ensure a brighter future for our daughter.
Whatever. I know that you're doing it because you want the title.
Do you think anyone can run in the election? Know your place.
- "Know your place"? - I wasn't talking about you.
What did you just say?
Nothing. Never mind.
All right.
Gosh, I'm not totally happy with my live performance today.
Tae Pyung, is it true that you're married?
Why have you been lying to your fans?
Is your agency really owned by a daughter of a business tycoon...
who ran away to the States 15 years ago?
Does that mean you're married to her?
No, my wife is...
my manager here, Lee Dong Sook.
I sincerely apologise to my fans for not being honest with them.
No, it's not Tae Pyung's fault.
I wanted him to become as popular as he used to be,
so I told him to lie.
No, it's all my fault.
I sincerely apologise.
I'm sorry, Tae Pyung.
I made you become a liar.
It's not your fault at all.
I've had many opportunities to fix it,
but I've been willingly keeping my mouth shut.
What should we do now?
Popularity is...
as fleeting as the wind.
I shall start again from scratch.
I have nothing to worry about as I have you and Da Jeong.
I don't want to act like I'm single just to become popular again.
I just want to spend time with you and Da Jeong comfortably.
I prefer that much more than regaining popularity.
Tae Pyung.
Overcome. Overcome.
You said you had a TV show today. Did it go well?
- Yes, of course. - I want to go in.
Did you two have a fight?
No.
Then why is she so downcast?
I guess she's tired.
By the way, why are you jumping rope in the middle of the night?
I'll become a dad soon. I need to stay fit, don't you think?
Overcome.
Overcome your midlife crisis and attain happiness
You're still awake?
Yes. Yun Shil's exam is just around the corner, you know.
What's the matter with those two mums-to-be?
Both Steamed Bun's mum and Overcome's mum.
What is their problem?
Have they forgotten how old they are? One wants to become a student,
and the other wants the chairwoman title. What's wrong with them?
That's what I'm saying.
- Sam Do. - Yes?
Because of your andropause, you've been throwing hissy fits...
and have been complaining about feeling tired and weak.
How exactly did you manage to conceive your baby?
One day, Sun Nyeo took me to a spring...
and made me jog up and down steps and do the hula hoop.
It was our project to overcome andropause,
and it worked.
Sun Nyeo is amazing.
Why don't you...
make Da Jeong an older sister?
Start your own project to overcome andropause.
Shall I?
I'm too old to consider making Da Jeong an older sister.
Forget it.
I should go to that mineral spring.
To make Steamed Bun number two?
Of course.
Steamed Bun, Grilled Bun and Pancake Bun.
Pancake Bun sounds odd.
What other buns are there? Fried buns?
Dong Jin's a true patriot.
Our population's falling.
Overcome. Overcome.
Seriously.
My goodness.
Mum. Mum.
What now?
Go home.
Why now? It's too early in the morning.
I'll go later on in the morning.
Get the hint.
Why do you keep intruding into our newlywed space?
What?
How can you say that to your mum?
That really hurt.
- Did you sleep well? - Yes.
- Did you sleep well? - I did.
Do you think...
it's a nuisance that I keep coming by?
Not at all.
Breakfast is ready. Wash up and eat.
I will.
I said go home.
Gosh.
I'll go after breakfast.
Tae Yang told me to stay for breakfast.
I really think we should...
- find my mum a boyfriend. - What?
Are there any nice teachers at your school?
My mum looks quite young.
She can date a man 10 years her junior...
and maybe five years her senior.
Why are you smiling? I'm serious.
What gave you that idea?
Mum keeps coming by all the time...
and ruins our newlywed life.
You didn't get to kiss me this morning.
It was so upsetting.
Will that do?
Honestly,
are there any nice teachers?
How about the headmaster?
No way, he's too old.
He's young.
- Is he? - Yes.
Then yes.
- It's warped. - Oh, you're right.
Good morning, everyone.
Good morning. Hello, Yun Shil.
Welcome, both of you.
Walk slowly, now sit down.
Slowly, slowly.
Don't strain yourself.
Thank you.
You're practically her servant.
I have to be. Do you like the work?
It's okay.
He's gotten better. He even does things he wasn't told to do.
- Master. - What?
Are you okay? I can't believe you complimented me.
What? How dare you.
This is why I always end up scolding you.
I'll call you back to Meesa soon.
Hang in there a while longer.
What you learn here will come in useful later on.
I hope so.
How about a coffee while you're here?
Do you all want one?
- I would. - I'll make it.
- No. - No way.
Stay still, Ma'am.
I can take it from here.
What got into him? He's obedient all of a sudden.
Hello.
(Sun Nyeo's Side Dishes)
My goodness.
- You're late. - You're going all out.
People would think you're running for congress.
Do you want to represent the merchants here...
enough to wear a sash?
Back when I was in Daejeon,
every time I tried to become the union president,
I lost to the opposition by just a few votes.
This time, I'm determined to become president.
You should focus on your business.
Why do you want to win a title?
Once someone has money,
they want power as well.
Someone might think...
you're earning a fortune by selling food.
Put on a sash.
- Me too? - Or you can quit today.
I hate my job. Fine.
Sun Nyeo.
Hello.
Why are you here?
- To help you get elected. - What a mess.
Thanks for coming. I won't forget this.
It's fine.
I'm paid in advance.
Do you accept payment in side dishes?
Or eat whatever you... Okay, okay.
You're a tough customer.
Here you go.
Put it back.
Is it too little?
Be generous.
- Here you go. - I said it's fine.
We're family.
Do you want all of it then?
- Number 2. - Number 2.
- Number Two. - Bok Sun Nyeo.
Bok Sun Nyeo, Number Two.
- Number 2. - Number 2.
- Number Two. - Bok Sun Nyeo.
- Bok Sun Nyeo. - Bok Sun Nyeo.
I'll work for your rights and our prosperity.
Vote for Number Two, Bok Sun Nyeo.
- It's Number Two. - Bok Sun Nyeo!
- Number 2, Number 2. - Bok Sun Nyeo!
Sun Nyeo goes, goes, goes
She goes at full speed
She is coming to you
Do not say a word
Please vote for me.
- Number 2. - Number 2.
Bok Sun Nyeo goes
Number Two, Bok Sun Nyeo.
- Number 2, Number 2. - I need your support!
Put that there.
- If not, use another ruler. - Okay.
- Welcome. - Hello.
I'm Nina Song and I work at the Italian Embassy.
Our ambassador wanted to visit,
so I brought him here.
He's... He's an ambassador.
An ambassador?
Hello.
To what do we owe this pleasure, Mr Ambassador?
Well, I wanted to see for myself...
how the partner of our great Italian brand...
of Tonelli looks like.
I'm curious because I was told that...
the tradition of this place goes back 100 years.
Yes.
Well,
I can still feel the historic ambiance of this place.
Thank you. It means a lot to us that you think that way.
Chief Designer Gianni...
spoke very highly about your suits.
So, I would like to have a suit for myself and while we're at it,
I would like a double jacket and a coat which goes along with it.
Hey, hey. What did he say?
He wants a suit, a double jacket...
and a coat made.
- All three? - Yes.
We're very backlogged at the moment.
I don't think we can make three items for one customer.
This is our Master Tailor Mr Sam Do Bae.
Unfortunately at the moment we're currently swamped with orders,
so unfortunately, we made a rule...
to only take one order per customer.
But the ambassador came here in person.
Do you think you could take two orders then?
Then...
he can order a suit.
Since it's getting warmer, the coat can wait.
In return, tell him that I'll make...
the best quality suit for him possible.
Ms Geum, Ms Geum.
Do you know who was just here?
Who was here?
The ambassador from Italy...
ordered a suit from me.
Bae Sam Do just made it big.
Is that true? Congratulations.
He took the measurements,
and he didn't tremble. He was very professional.
- You were so cool. - I'm shaking now.
- Me too. - Intern.
- Your English was great. Well done. - Really?
You did it! Congratulations.
I'm going to go to Belgium.
Belgium?
What for?
I'd sent my portfolio to the Royal Academy,
and they offered me...
a place as a researcher and artist.
I can study again...
and study European fashion.
I'll stay a few years.
I'll travel a lot too.
I see. When will you leave?
On Friday.
I bought the ticket on the way here.
So soon?
There's nothing for me here.
Thanks to you,
I regained the freedom to go where I want.
I'm sorry.
You were hurt.
For whatever reason that was, I'm sorry it happened.
If we talk about hurt,
I'm pretty sure I caused you a lot too.
Your wife.
I heard she's due soon.
Yes.
This must be...
the happiest time in your life.
I hope...
you get to experience this happiness.
I should.
I will.
Hey. Come in.
Come in.
What brought you here? You didn't tell me you would come.
Hyo Joo, what brought you here?
I came to ask you a favour.
What favour do you want to ask us?
Have a seat first. Sit down.
By the way, what do you want to ask us?
On Friday,
I'm leaving to Belgium.
Belgium?
Why are you going there?
I'll study fashion...
and travel around.
I'll come back after several years.
I really envy you.
By the way,
are you going alone?
I'm going alone. Who would I go with?
So I was wondering...
Will you stay in Pyeongchang-dong house while I'm away?
- You mean us? - You mean us?
Why? Don't you want to?
Are you all right?
I dozed off again.
You were not dozing off. You were sleeping.
You drooled a lot.
Stop it.
Lie down here and sleep comfortably.
I still have a lot to study.
I don't know why I get so sleepy nowadays.
It's worse than when I was in my early pregnancy.
What if you doze off during the exam?
I'm serious, and you're making fun of me.
What are you doing?
To arouse you from sleep. Are you awake now?
Aren't you? Shall I do it one more time?
No, thank you.
Steamed bun.
Dad totally fell for Mum's charm which surprised me.
You should meet a woman like Mum when you grow up, all right?
What?
All right, Dad.
- Did you hear that? He answered. - Yes, he answered.
He said, "All right, Dad."
You might be greedy for a title,
but you will deliver a baby soon.
Why do you have to join in the election for the president?
You're not young. You're an old mum.
It's very dangerous to go around for the election campaign.
Overcome inside you must be very tired.
They say a mum's pain is a child's pain.
I thought you were not nagging for a while, and there you go again.
Haven't you overcome the andropause?
I did overcome it.
If a husband meddles with...
what a wife does on every single detail,
she can't do her work outside.
Aren't you answering me?
All right.
That feels good.
Why aren't you sleeping?
I got a phone call from Mum.
Hyo Joo is leaving to Belgium.
Belgium?
She majored in design.
It's a good opportunity for her to study there.
I should be happy for her,
but I feel little strange.
I just became familiar with her.
I'm worried if she leaves now, we could be awkward when we meet again.
The mental distance is more important...
than the physical distance.
You can call her often and write her from time to time.
Mum and Hyo Sang will live in Hyo Joo's house.
She said we can live in her current house.
Will they live in Pyeongchang-dong?
Yes. Hyo Joo told them to live in her house.
Do you want to live in Pyeongchang-dong house?
No, I like it here.
It's our first home.
I want to enjoy the newlywed life more in this house.
Then we should sell the house Mother is now living.
This is great.
- Aren't you hungry? - I'm hungry.
Shall I cook something for you?
I'd like to eat instant cup noodles.
How many instant cup noodles do you want?
I want two.
- Good luck on your exam! - We will be cheering for you!
- Have a cup of coffee. - Good luck!
- Good luck on your exam! - Good luck on your exam!
Don't get nervous. Take it easy.
If you feel something strange or tired during the test,
don't endure it. Tell the test official right away.
I get it.
Ms Shiny Eyes can do it. Go for it!
Go for it!
(Korean Language, Na Yun Shil)
Next is candidate number two, Bok Sun Nyeo.
Bok Sun Nyeo. Bok Sun Nyeo.
Testing, testing. It's working well.
Dear merchants in the market,
To tell you about me, Bok Sun Nyeo,
every generation of my family has worked at this market,
starting with my great-grandmother.
If you vote for me to be the president,
I will do my best...
to be loyal to your votes.
- Bok Sun Nyeo. - Bok Sun Nyeo.
People in the back, stand up...
and collect test papers and answer sheets.
Please help me!
The person who is elected as the president of the market co-op...
is candidate number two, Bok Sun Nyeo!
- Thank you. - Thank you.
- I'm about to deliver a child! - I'm about to deliver a child!
Goodness.
I think the baby is coming.
- Oh my. - It hurts. Bae Sam Do!
Bring Sam Do here. Bae Sam Do.
(Delivery Room)
Who's the guardian for Na Yun Shil?
Yes, that's me.
Congratulations. On 21:03,
she delivered a son.
Both mum and baby are healthy.
Thank you.
- The guardian for Bok Sun Nyeo? - Yes, I'm her guardian.
Are mum and baby healthy?
Both mum and baby are healthy.
She delivered a girl on 21:04.
Congratulations.
Thank you.
We became dads!
Did Sun Nyeo deliver a girl and Yun Shil a boy?
That's great.
How are the mums?
Did you call Dad?
That's good.
Congratulations, Dong Jin. Bye.
Did Uncle have a son and Sam Do a girl?
Yes, they did.
The babies must be very cute.
Dad, do you have a plan to make me a sibling?
I'd love to.
However, your mum says she won't.
You can do it.
Don't laugh.
What are you doing standing in line?
We've been waiting for you to see you out.
Are you pretending to be a happy family or what?
Isn't it too much?
You're going far. We should see you out.
Don't get snippy with anyone in Belgium.
Take care of yourself.
Don't skip meals so that you don't get malnourished.
I get it.
I'll miss you a lot.
You can visit me if you miss me. Don't be such a drama queen.
Can I do that?
I'll pay for your airline tickets.
You can all come for vacation.
Have a safe trip.
Once you're there,
if you feel lonely and worn down,
don't fight it and come back.
Remember that this is your home.
Thank you.
Mum.
Did you...
just call me "mum"?
Did you just say "mum"...
and not "stepmum"?
You're a bit too old...
to be my new mum.
I thought I'd never get to hear you call me that.
Thanks, Hyo Joo.
Now...
I can die in peace.
Don't say that.
I'll have a good time.
Look after the home until I get back.
Take care.
Can I...
see you off at the airport?
No thanks.
Hyo Won and Tae Yang's enough.
You're still so cold-hearted.
- Call as soon as you get there. - I will.
Bye.
See you.
We'll take her safely to the airport.
Get some rest.
We'll see her off.
Don't worry.
Honey, I know it was hard work.
I saw our baby a while ago.
She's beautiful and looks just like you.
She looks like me?
She can't.
She must look like you.
What are you talking about?
Half her looks are from me and half are from you.
She's definitely ours.
- Was it painful? - I thought I was going to die.
The whole world turned yellow,
and I saw twinkling stars.
Was it bad for you, Yun Shil?
I think I saw stars as well.
Did you?
- Great job. - Did you see Steamed Bun?
Of course.
He's the healthiest and the most handsome baby here.
For you.
Thank you...
for having our baby...
and for being all right.
Thank you.
Didn't you bring anything?
I was too distracted to buy anything. Sorry.
Dong Jin would have been distracted as well.
- Hello. - Hi.
- Hi. - Hello.
Congratulations.
You're better than my husband.
Thank you.
Thanks, Tae Yang.
Congratulations.
Thank you.
We wanted to come over as soon as we heard,
but we had to drop by the airport.
You have a son.
Congratulations, Dong Jin, Yun Shil.
Thanks.
- Why were you at the airport? - My sister...
left for Belgium today.
She told me to give you this.
She said...
she's sorry for everything.
Thank her for us when you talk to her.
Tae Yang.
When will you become a dad?
He's right.
You must have a kid when you're still young.
It's better for the child, and younger mums...
recover faster.
I'd love to have a baby.
Tae Yang, shall we start trying...
in earnest tonight?
Don't say that here.
I see that...
Hyo Won's outspoken and frank and totally our type.
Good luck, Hyo Won.
Thanks.
We'll try.
- Right? - Stop it.
Why aren't you in bed?
I can't sleep.
Are you worried about your sister?
That and...
I was thinking about all sorts of things,
and I couldn't sleep.
Do you want some wine?
What should I do?
I'll carry you until you fall asleep.
No, don't.
I won't fall asleep for a while.
You should go to bed.
I think I'll have to stay up all night as well.
Then...
keep your promise.
- What promise? - My drawing.
You said you'd model for me.
Nude, you mean?
Why not?
- Don't you want to? - It's not that.
I'm not ready yet.
I'll let you off this time.
It's too cold to pose in the nude.
I'll draw your face instead.
To celebrate our wedding.
Right now?
Look at me.
What was it?
All done.
It's complete, Mr Model.
What?
It looks just like me.
The Tae Yang on paper is nothing...
compared to the Tae Yang in front of me.
I knew it.
Thank you.
It's a waste not to show anyone.
Let's take a photo.
I'll show it to my students.
Turn around.
You want me in the photo?
My students want to know what you look like.
I'm not ready for that.
I look a total mess.
No way. You're too pretty.
Don't be silly.
1, 2, 3.
I'm right between two Tae Yangs.
You shine.
I don't. You shine brightest.
Good morning.
- Business is booming. - It is.
- Hello. - Ms President.
The alley out there is too dark.
Can you get the public officials to put a lamppost there.
- I will. - Thanks.
- Take care. - Bye.
Hello!
Hello, President.
Please get rid of the standing signs and banners that violate the policy.
Things are getting pretty tense here these days, you know.
Officers from the district office will take care of it today.
Please be patient for just a little longer.
That's such great news.
- Have a great day. - Thank you.
- My gosh. - You're so adorable.
My gosh, look who's here!
Steamed Bun and Overcome.
I was getting a bit of cabin fever at home,
so I came out for a walk with these two.
My daughter, have you been a good girl today?
Gosh, my future son-in-law is always so well behaved.
Exactly. Dong Jin's son is always well behaved,
but your daughter is so stubborn just like you.
She's such a troublemaker.
It's only natural for toddlers to whine and throw fits.
It's unnatural for babies of this age to be mature and well behaved.
Aren't I right, my baby?
Be careful.
Hold on a second. Why is her diaper so wet?
I just changed it. Did she relieve herself again?
She keeps getting diaper rash.
How many times have I asked you to change her diapers often?
Are you really going to be this careless with her?
This is why babysitting is so unrewarding.
Gosh, I don't want to babysit any more. You do it yourself.
Goodness. Come on.
I was just a little upset. Why are you getting so mad?
Do you know how exhausting babysitting is?
Even my bones and muscles ache.
You get paid a lot more than me.
Why don't you work then? I'll babysit them.
All right. Swap your jobs then.
It's not like I'm a good cook.
There's nothing I can do here.
Overcome! Come to me.
I'll change your diaper so that you can feel much better.
Come here.
Gosh, you're just so adorable.
- Come here. - Let's go change your diaper.
Who's a good boy?
Look at this. Look at me.
Just a second.
I really can't go in.
Goodness. Just trust me.
- You should go in first. - Wait...
- Tae Pyung! - Tae Pyung!
- We love you, Tae Pyung! - We love you, Tae Pyung!
- You're so handsome, Tae Pyung! - You're so handsome, Tae Pyung!
(Fan Club Inauguration Ceremony)
(We're here for you, Tae Pyung.)
Congratulations, Dad.
Nice to meet you.
- You look dashing. - I love your song so much.
Thank you so much, everyone.
I know that I still have a lot to learn. I have so many flaws,
yet you're giving me so much love. I'm not sure how I can thank you.
When I returned to Korea with nothing but my guitar...
- Don't cry! - Don't cry!
All of you, thank you very much.
Until the very last day of my life, this precious moment...
will be engraved in my heart as an unforgettable memory.
I love you all!
My brother goes, goes, goes
He goes at full speed
He is coming to you
Do not say a word
Just hold me tight
To you, right now, immediately
My brother goes
(Italy in Love with Tailor Bae Sam Do)
My gosh, it even talks about how you made the ambassador's suit.
Master, you're our shop's...
No, you're the pride of all tailors in Korea.
Gosh, stop flattering me so much.
You rock.
Are you giving me some credit now?
Gosh, what are you talking about?
I succumbed a long time ago.
That's right. When he first came to our shop,
he was like an angry bull.
He used to lash out at you all the time, you know.
But he's as gentle as a lamb these days.
- When did I lash out at anyone? - Goodness.
Yun Shil.
As of tomorrow, you will...
officially be working as a garment cutter at Wolgyesu Tailor Shop.
Seriously?
I already hired two people who can take care of sewing in your place.
My gosh, that's amazing. Congratulations, Yun Shil.
Can I really work as a garment cutter, Master?
Of course. You've learned everything from me.
And you're also studying very hard these days.
Thank you. I'll do my very best.
What about me?
If Yun Shil will take care of garment cutting from now on,
does that mean I'll be put in charge of sewing?
Hasn't Dong Jin called you?
Pardon?
You'll be transferred to the head office.
- Pardon me? - Oh, my.
Are you serious?
Really?
Pack up.
Thank you.
Dong Jin!
Oh, why are the two of you here?
What do you think? The same reason as you're here.
Welcome back to Meesa Apparel,
Chief Marketing Officer Min Hyo Sang.
Chief Marketing Officer?
Dong Jin.
Yes, I know how hard you've worked to learn everything at the shop.
Thanks for being patient.
Thanks, Dong Jin.
I promise I'll be loyal to you until the day I die.
No, I don't need such a promise.
Just do a good job, okay?
No, I'm going to be your guy.
Let me know if any directors or executives get on your nerves.
I'll take care of them for you.
Gosh, Hyo Sang.
Mind your own business.
Here. I look forward to working with you.
Thanks again.
What is it?
It's a gift for your mum.
It's your cousin's wedding, so your entire family will be there.
I feel so bad that I can't make it as her only daughter-in-law.
You're busy with work, so you have no choice.
She said she understands. Don't worry about it.
I'll give her a call tomorrow.
Don't sleep here alone. You should go over to your mum's place.
I have to go to work early tomorrow. I'll just sleep here.
Will you be okay by yourself?
I'll be lonely without you,
but maybe it's because I think of this place as home now.
I'm a lot more comfortable here than at my family home.
Then make sure you lock the door before you go to bed, okay?
It's the first time we'll be apart since getting married.
I don't want to let you go.
I'll come back right after the wedding.
I'll probably run out of power since you'll be gone all night.
Charge me up before you go.
Are you all charged up now?
Really?
Are you charged up too?
Yes, I'm fully charged.
Honey, honey!
Honey!
Go in.
Gosh, Hyo Won.
See you tomorrow.
- Bye. - See you tomorrow, girls.
Excuse me. Hello. You're Na Yun Shil, right?
- Yes. - I'm in Business Administration.
My name is Choi Hyun Seok.
What can I help you with?
I'm actually in your fashion marketing class.
I've been watching you because I'm smitten with you.
If you don't mind, would you like to talk over some tea?
As a matter of fact...
Honey.
Our baby's hungry. We should hurry and go feed him.
Yun Shil. You're married?
- Yes. - Our baby...
was whining so much because he missed his mother.
I couldn't help but come all the way here to pick her up.
- I see. - I'm sorry, but I'll have go.
- Let's go quickly. - All right.
Do you want to say goodbye to him? Say goodbye.
- Let's go. - Shall we?
Steamed Bun. We're home now.
You're at home now.
By the way,
who was that guy earlier?
I have no idea.
He says we're in the same class,
but it was my first time seeing him today.
You're not acting like you're single, are you?
Of course not.
The students in my class know that I have a child.
Dong Jin. Are you jealous?
Why would I be jealous?
I don't get jealous of anything.
Then why did you act like that earlier?
What are you talking about?
You called me Steamed Bun's Mum out loud, didn't you?
There were so many people around. It was embarrassing.
Then what would I call you other than Steamed Bun's Mum?
Why is that embarrassing?
You're silly.
All right. You're right. I was jealous.
So make sure to make it clear that you're married...
- and have a child from now on. - Gosh.
Steamed Bun.
Your dad's acting too jealous, isn't he?
- Don't you think so? - Steamed Bun. When you grow up,
make sure not to meet a girl that's too beautiful and has a baby face.
I can't seem to leave her alone without having to worry.
You're so silly.
I have to change his diapers.
All right. Here you go.
- I got him. - Lay him down.
Steamed Bun. There you go.
Here you go. Here's your pacifier.
It's your pacifier.
Do you want to suck on it?
There you go.
Let's change your diapers now.
Let's take a look.
My goodness. You little rascal.
Goodness, Steamed Bun.
That sure was powerful.
You're husband has urine all over him.
How could you be laughing?
You were laughing yourself.
This is a first.
I never thought something like this would happen.
Steamed Bun. It's all right.
We'll get you in some clean diapers.
It's all right.
You're all done.
I was grateful that I could see even if it were something tiny.
But I guess now...
I won't be able to see anything.
The wedding was held in Gangneung,
so I thought I might as well pay a visit to Mr Lee.
I see. Please say hello to him for me.
I will. I'll see you later.
Hello, Mr Lee.
Who is it?
It's me, Tae Yang, Mr Lee.
Goodness. Tae Yang.
What brings you here?
I attended my cousin's wedding in Gangneung.
I thought I'd come pay a visit while I'm here.
Thank you...
for coming all this way to see me.
Can you...
not see me at all, Mr Lee?
- You're such a good boy. - Overcome.
Overcome.
I feel so left out.
I told you. You should...
go to the park to get some exercise done...
and try getting a baby as well.
You can overcome this as well.
Overcome.
Have a warm cup of quince tea, everyone.
Thank you.
Are you doing well in the evening classes, Yun Shil?
Not only is she doing well,
she received a bursary last term.
That's impressive.
I couldn't have done it without Dong Jin's help.
You guys are unbelievable love birds.
When will they ever stop?
- Overcome. - Yes, Tae Yang.
Don't be too shocked, Dong Jin.
What is it? Has something happened?
I'm in Gangneung right now.
Mr Lee...
has completely lost his eyesight.
What?
Where's Mum?
It must've been a shock to her.
She's lying down in the room. She's not feeling well.
You really...
can't see anything?
That's right.
It just happened.
Father.
There's no need to cry.
This was expected.
Dad.
Mr Lee.
Father.
For my sake,
please accept this in a calm manner.
Come back with us to Seoul.
I can't...
leave you here any longer.
All right.
I won't be stubborn.
I don't want to become an ill-tempered old man...
who lives his life making his children worry...
when you should all be busy with your own lives.
Let's go home.
As soon as Mother is feeling better,
I'll pack their important belongings and take them home.
Dong Sook said she'd take care of Steamed Bun for us.
- All right. - Drive safely.
I will.
You mustn't panic...
in order for Father to remain calm.
I won't.
I know.
Pull over for a minute, will you?
I want to take home the feeling of the sea breeze...
in my heart.
The wind's quite chilly, Mr Lee.
Will you be all right?
I'm all right. I like the cool breeze.
Isn't it frustrating now that you can't see the view of the ocean?
I don't know.
I thought I'd feel...
uncomfortable once I lose my eyesight.
Surprisingly,
it feels like I can see a whole different view now.
What is it you see, Mr Lee?
I can see my life.
When I had good eyesight, I only saw what was in front of me.
Now that I can't see and forget what's surrounding me,
the images of my past...
seem to unfold in my head like a beautiful painting.
So there's no need for me to feel frustrated.
What was your life like, Dad?
It was dazzlingly beautiful.
Luxurious beyond measure for me.
The trade I'd learned as a child...
was to see and make grand suits.
I couldn't love my job more.
Now those times stretch before me...
like a roll of beautiful fabric.
The verb we use to say we make clothes means "to form".
We use the same verb on building houses or cooking food.
The verb goes for clothes, food and shelter.
That means...
clothes aren't a mere accessory.
Making clothes...
means we make a life that goes with it.
A gentleman isn't someone...
who wears expensive or grand clothes.
It's a man who lives a life that suits his outfit.
That is a true gentleman.
A gentleman...
Isn't someone who wears expensive or grand clothes.
It's a man who lives a life that suits his outfit.
That is a true gentleman.
(Thanks for watching "The Gentlemen of Wolgyesu Tailor Shop".)
(The Gentlemen of Wolgyesu Tailor Shop)