(The following content may not be suitable for viewers under 15.)
(Viewer discretion is advised.)
You're selfish, but you pretend to be naive in front of others.
Aren't you tired of being two-faced?
You got it all wrong. That was...
You hypocrite.
What did you just call me?
- A hypocrite? - Get out of my way.
- Look, Mr Lee Dong Jin. - I don't have to look!
Get out of my sight right now.
How dare you say that to me.
Look here.
Stop right there. I'm not done talking.
He does all the talking and never lets others speak.
What did you do that for?
I didn't do it on purpose.
Sorry.
You are not sane.
What a horrible day. Everything went wrong.
My father-in-law created a slush fund for my mother-in-law?
I don't understand.
The late chairman felt sorry for Madam Ko...
being looked down upon just because she was his second wife.
He wanted to compensate her for it.
He had me wire her a certain amount every month for living expenses.
Where did that money come from?
He set aside some of the profit...
from transactions with subsidiaries and affiliates.
CEO Min Hyo Sang saw the account books...
and plans to report it to the prosecutors as corruption.
He's threatening you because you sided with me.
The prosecutors won't just target me.
The public will think that Meesa is corrupt,
and the late chairman will be painted as a corrupt businessman.
I don't know what to do about this.
I'm home.
You're late.
Were you at work all this while?
No. I made a stop on my way home.
Why do you look so downcast?
Did something bad happen?
Ms Geum, do you think...
I'm an evil, two-faced person who pretends to be naive...
when I'm around others but is actually selfish?
If someone acts out of character,
shouldn't you assume something's wrong...
and wait until they're able to explain?
Isn't it wrong to misunderstand an be judgemental?
I have no idea what you're talking about.
Be more specific so I'll understand.
What I mean is...
I'm tired. I should just go to bed.
See you tomorrow.
Mr Min is like a train with no brakes.
He will destroy the whole company and take down everyone with it.
How did you know I'd be here?
I called the bar to ask and they said you were here.
Are you still trying to decide whether to pick me or the employees?
Something came up.
- What is it now? - Your dad...
wired Mother some allowance every month.
Hyo Sang wants to...
report it to the authorities as an illegal slush fund.
What?
He wants to report the money that went to his own mother?
He's doing that so he can fire the director of finance who is my ally.
Above all,
he probably knows that I won't fight for Meesa's ownership...
at the expense of the your late father.
He has lost his mind.
Did you meet on the way home?
- Were you on a date? - A date?
In this situation?
You came in together, so I assumed you had a good time.
Too bad if you didn't.
You thick-faced witch.
You used my dad when he was alive,
and now you're defaming him.
You aren't even human!
What do you mean? What does she mean?
You should ask your precious son.
Stop it. Let's go upstairs.
What was that about?
I'm home.
- Tell me the truth. - About what?
Hyo Joo said you're defaming your dad.
What does she mean?
Oh, that? It's the ace up my sleeve.
What is this ace?
Dad wired you some money every month.
I threatened to tell the prosecutors about it.
- What? - Don't worry.
Dong Jin adored the old man. He wouldn't risk his reputation.
- Wake up, you fool. - What was that for?
I know you want to own Meesa, but you can't use your own dad!
What's wrong with you?
We decided to keep the store.
Dong Jin came by today to pay the penalty.
Sam Do will move in as soon as possible...
and reopen the store.
You don't have to spend too much time on the road.
Come home as soon as you can, okay?
What's that noise?
It would taste even better with three drops of sesame oil.
I wonder where they keep it.
- Thief! - My goodness.
Who are you?
It's you, Leather Jacket.
- What? - Hello, it's me, Jun.
What are you doing in my kitchen?
Dong Sook said I could come downstairs and eat...
whatever's in the fridge if I ever felt hungry.
Even so.
You can't sneak in and eat without my permission.
What's this?
I jumped when you shrieked and spilled the sesame oil.
The sesame oil?
Oh, no. My goodness.
Do you know how expensive this is?
I'm really sorry.
It's not the imported stuff.
I bought Korean-grown sesame seeds and watched...
and waited at the mill to make sure they got every drop.
What a waste.
I should have been more careful.
This would have lasted us more than three months.
It's all gone.
This is terrible.
I did a terrible thing.
The bottle was full to the brim.
Now there's less than half left. What should I do about this?
I will buy you a new bottle.
- Will you? - Yes.
I'll get you a new bottle of Korean-grown sesame oil.
You do that, then.
Just a moment.
Give me that bottle.
I said I'd buy you a bottle of it, so you can give me that.
Fine, then.
This is the good stuff.
My goodness. That's disgusting.
Do the dishes when you're done.
I will. Don't worry.
This is enough to last me three years.
There we go. Korean sesame oil is precious.
It tastes lovely.
He doesn't think like most people his age.
"I'll buy you a bottle of Korean sesame oil."
"You can keep whatever's left of this bottle."
Wouldn't it have been nice if he had said that instead?
I'm home.
What's wrong, Mum?
Ouch. That hurt.
Do you think before you speak?
What is it now?
Did you tell Leather Jacket to come down when he's hungry...
and eat whatever food's in the fridge?
Do we run a charity?
We should help those in need if we live under the same roof.
- I told him to eat our food. - What?
Will he eat with us three times a day?
Jun isn't that rude or presumptuous.
It's just for a while until Sam Do moves in.
What does Sam Do moving in...
have to do with us feeding Leather Jacket?
He'll share the appliances with Sam Do when he moves in.
Do you mean Leather Jacket doesn't have anything?
The stuff he brought when he moved in, was that it?
I guess so.
He looks fine, but he's practically penniless.
You never know what will happen.
When his next single becomes a hit,
he can buy 10 houses like this one.
When will that be?
That hurt.
My goodness. How much have you eaten?
How many chickens did you eat?
Can't a fried chicken seller eat her own chicken?
Don't talk like that to me.
How many bottles of soju did you drink?
I drank a few bottles because...
I feel so lonely and desolate that I pity myself and my life.
Why are you so lonely and desolate?
The other store owners...
won't talk to me any more.
They leave me out of everything.
The dried seafood lady, oil lady and fishmonger...
went to eat lunch without me.
It's your fault for using your dead mum.
It takes two to tango, you know.
You ruined everything by telling the truth.
You're insane.
Why did you tell them it's your dead mum's 80th birthday?
What else should I have done?
Once we move to Seoul,
we'll never get back the money we gave out at their parties.
I wanted to...
make them pay up before we moved.
Are you that crazy about money?
Let's go home. We can clean up tomorrow.
Let go.
Can't you even stand up straight?
Are you that drunk already?
How much did you drink?
- Carry me. - What? What did you say?
- Give me a piggyback. - This is unbelievable.
You're fine in every other way,
but you care too much about money.
That's your crucial flaw.
I bet that when you were born,
you came out screaming "money".
It's not nice to always talk about money.
Spend more than you earn, and you'll end up penniless.
That's not what I mean.
I'm more afraid of losing friends than money.
What you did today...
ruined friendships we'd built up for years.
Now we have to move to Seoul as if we're on the run.
Why do we have to have such a horrible ending...
to the great few years we had?
You're all about emotions and ties and if I leave it all to you,
we'll end up with nothing to our name.
It's not worth being abandoned by friends...
so we can live in a palace.
It's much better to get along with others...
and share what we have even if we live in a tiny space.
We don't have kids to take us in later on.
When I'm dead and you're poor,
you'll be left alone, and no one will care about you.
I want to earn a fortune for you before I die...
so that gold-diggers will hang around...
even if they may be old hags with dentures.
You worry too much for your own good.
People cursed you out so much that I bet...
you will outlive me by at least 20 years.
That's true.
The number of women I grabbed by the hair is...
at least 10.
It's way more than that.
Count all your fingers and toes...
and add five to that.
Sam Do.
What?
Why did you defend me earlier?
You used to call me ignorant and tried to shut me up.
Why not today?
I was grateful.
For what?
You hate anything about tailoring and suits.
But you feared for me...
and gave in to me.
I was grateful for that.
You've grown up at last.
I have.
How about you? When will you grow up?
What?
What did you say?
Don't hit me. I can barely carry you.
You don't mean that.
I do mean that. You're heavier than a sack of rice.
What? A sack of what?
- That's nonsense. - Don't move. I might drop you.
- That's a lie. - I'll drop you.
- I'm not rice. - Be quiet.
Stay still.
Sam Do...
You're selfish, but you pretend to be naive in front of others.
Aren't you tired of being two-faced?
You got it all wrong. That was...
You hypocrite.
A hypocrite? How could he say that?
My gosh, it's so hot.
Ouch...
Why do I feel like crying when I eat something hot?
Dong Jin.
Come and join me.
No thanks.
It's been over 30 years.
That's how long people mocked me for being the other woman.
Do you know what made me hang on?
The dream of making Hyo Sang the owner of Meesa Apparel.
That was my only goal.
I know that makes me seem shallow,
but without that goal,
I wouldn't have made it this far.
You're drunk. You should go to bed.
The same goes for Hyo Sang.
He's going to the extreme and defaming his own father.
I know you don't think much of him for that.
But that's just how desperate we are.
Do you think that justifies this?
Help us out, Dong Jin.
It's late. You should stop drinking.
I'm not asking as your mother-in-law.
I'm asking as...
Eun Sook who used to work at Wolgyesu Tailor Shop.
Please help us out.
(I'll be away for a few days to clear my head.)
What is he thinking?
The phone has been turned off. Please leave a message after...
Where is he with his phone turned off?
Is he crazy?
It's me, Mum.
I'm going on a business trip, so I might be hard to reach.
Don't worry if I don't pick up my phone.
I'll call you when I return to Seoul.
(Wife)
(Power off)
Your husband's trial starts today.
Leave the store to me.
There's still time. I'll help you finish up.
Is your mother-in-law coming?
No. Gi Pyo told her not to come all the way to Seoul.
I'll be there alone.
Are you cleaning up?
Good morning.
We've been distracted for a while, so the whole place is a mess.
It's so clean now that even a fly would slip and fall.
Yun Shil came in at the crack of dawn.
She's good at everything she does.
I know she is. She's diligent and meticulous...
and perfect in every way.
Even if Gi Pyo threatens you, don't ever sign the marriage licence.
- Promise me that. - Okay.
I'll marry you off to a better man if I find one.
Don't do anything to mess up my plans.
Don't say things like that.
I have to go to court now.
It's Gi Pyo's first hearing.
Okay. Go on, then. Don't worry about us.
Thanks.
(Sun Nyeo Chicken)
Don't sit there and sulk. Go and make amends.
Didn't you hear what I told you yesterday?
The dried seafood lady, oil lady and fishmonger ate lunch without me.
What? Without you?
I should teach those three a lesson.
Forget it. They'll just say I'm bragging that I'm married.
They were all widowed.
15 years ago for the dried seafood lady, 8 years ago for the oil lady,
and three years ago for the fishmonger.
That's why you, the woman with the great husband,
should hand out an olive branch and try to patch things up.
No. I have nothing to lose.
Don't be like that.
I fried you these.
Go and share it with them or you'll regret it forever.
If you do as I say, then your lovely Sam Do...
will give you a long kiss.
Where?
Here?
Or here?
Here.
What if people see?
I'll kiss you again if you don't go right away.
Okay.
Sam Do.
I'd rather not listen to you and get another kiss.
Don't push your luck. Take what you're given.
Get going.
You're so mean.
Fine. I'll go, okay?
It was so funny.
- They are hilarious. - I know.
- My goodness. - Seriously.
- Have some chicken. - No thanks.
I'm scared of what you'll ask from us if we do.
I'm sorry about what I did yesterday.
I gave out a lot of money to your birthdays and funerals,
and the idea of moving away made me want to collect on it.
I'm really sorry. I cared too much about the money.
When are you leaving?
The landlord wants to move right in.
And the business was good, so a lot of people want to buy us out.
We'll be gone in a few days.
That soon?
I thought you'd need at least two months.
Be honest.
Are you upset that I'll be gone so soon?
- My gosh. - Be nice to me when I'm still here.
- Eat this. - My goodness.
Don't regret it once I'm gone.
Here. You, too.
Look at you three.
- What a sight this is. - What?
I need a photo of this.
In 1, 2, 3.
Move in closer. Three. Click.
Hello.
Why aren't you at your store?
I hired a part-timer.
Are you going somewhere?
Yes, I'm going to Hongdae to go busking.
Bus... What's that?
It's called "busking".
It's when musicians perform for the public.
I basically perform in the streets.
- Can you make money? - Of course.
People who are touched or impressed...
leave money in my guitar case as they go by.
If I needed money when I lived in Manhattan,
I would busk in Central Park.
That is so romantic.
Not at all.
You're basically a snake oil merchant.
I'm not, Ms Choi.
Back in my day, markets were held every five days.
And snake oil merchants painted their faces white...
and carried a drum on their backs and sang and danced.
They sold snake oil and rat poison.
Snake oil and rat poison?
How could you compare...
a musician to a snake oil merchant from years ago?
You're such an embarrassment.
Don't let it get to you. She's old and doesn't get it.
We should go.
Bye, Ms Choi.
Wait for me.
- Where are you going? - Where else?
I'm off to watch him perform.
- Why would you go there? - Why do you think?
It's his first official performance since his return.
It's my duty as his neighbour to cheer him on.
- Do you have feelings for him? - What?
I don't. I do not, Mum.
You can't fool me.
The way you look at him...
reminds me of a catfish with an eye problem.
Don't you dare lie.
I'm Sung Jun and in 2000, I received the Best New Artist Award.
It's been 15 years,
but I'm finally back.
This is my first official performance,
and it's an honour and privilege to sing for you.
I will sing the historical hit that you all remember.
This is "Susanna's Handkerchief". I hope you enjoy it.
When I looked at your beautiful face
Children, you shouldn't listen to things like this.
Come with me.
- Da Yul, Jin Young, let's go. - Bye.
Walk hand-in-hand.
- Ducks... - Quack.
- Chicks... - Chirp.
Hand me your handkerchief
You used to always tell me
(Tae Joon)
- Hello? - You sound terrible.
Are you sick?
No. Is something wrong?
Mum went to Seoul. She should be there by now.
Have you heard from her?
Why did she come to Seoul?
She felt bad that she didn't do anything for Ji Yun's birthday.
She went to say hello.
She hurt her leg. You should've...
Okay, let's hang up for now.
Hello.
I'm here to meet Choi Ji Yun. She's an announcer here.
Who shall I say is here?
Tell her that her mum misses her and came to see her.
She's going to marry my son.
So she calls me "mum", you see.
- Ji Yun, are you getting married? - What?
Your future mother-in-law is in the lobby.
It must be a prank. I should go and check.
Over here, my baby. Over here, Ji Yun.
Ji Yun.
- Ji Yun. - Why didn't you call ahead?
I felt bad that I missed your birthday,
and it's been so long since I last saw you.
Let's talk outside.
- Can you walk a bit faster? - It's good to see you.
You can't just show up like this.
I missed you too much.
- I didn't think, my baby. - Stop calling me that.
I guess you haven't heard.
Tae Yang and I broke up.
You broke up? Why?
He graduated three years ago,
and he still doesn't have a job. I can't wait any longer.
I know how hard it is for you.
I do, but you two have been together for so long.
We were young and clueless.
So please don't talk or act like Tae Yang and I are married.
(My Ji Yun)
The receiver isn't picking up. Please...
I brought you sweet potatoes, your favourite.
And these are black beans which are good for you.
I don't want it.
Take these home and eat it. Here, take it.
Stop it.
Oh, dear...
What a waste. Oh, no.
Mum.
What have you done?
- Why are you using her? - What?
Where's your pride? Aren't you upset?
Must you be so clingy when I said I'm sick of you?
Don't turn me into a monster.
- Stop it, Ji Yun. - You stop it.
Sorry.
Sorry, Mum. You came all this way, but there's nowhere you can stay.
I should find a job and save up...
and rent a place so you can stay over.
You do that. You always do whatever you set your mind to.
I'll go. You should go home.
(To Gimcheon)
Don't cry. I'm fine.
I'm sorry you saw me like this.
To me, you're the greatest son a mother could ever have.
Don't ever let anyone tell you otherwise, okay?
Kang Tae Yang and Choi Ji Yun dated when they were in college.
They dated until recently,
but it's a private matter, so that's all I know.
I was able to find out that Kang Tae Yang...
reached the final round of interviews at Meesa Apparel.
That means I interviewed him.
Kang Tae Yang?
Most of all, it showed us an example of how warm,
safe and family-like a company can be.
I remember him. The smart guy who looked good in a suit.
(Resume)
This just got very interesting.
Well done. You can go.
Kang Tae Yang. This must be karma.
Will you knock before you come in?
What did you just put away?
Don't ask. What do you want? Why are you here?
Can you have lunch with me?
I don't want to eat alone.
Why don't you have anyone to eat with?
Are you anti-social?
Will you eat with me or not?
I have a meeting in 10 minutes.
You're so mean. Forget it.
Hyo Sang.
Well...
Is there a way to hire someone...
who failed the final interview?
Does that person have to wait until next year?
What do you mean?
Never mind. Forget it.
What's wrong with her?
How do you feel to be up here?
The scenery is amazing. It's very refreshing to be here.
I know, right?
People keep going no matter how rough the path is...
in order to reach the peak and feel this,
fully knowing that they have to descend...
after admiring the scenery for a little while.
Dong Jin, on that note,
I hope you never forget that there are times...
when you have to descend.
What are you talking about all of a sudden?
As a father, I don't want my children...
to be enveloped in greed to go up higher,
which will only make them live with anxiety.
I've lived long enough...
to know that letting go of greed...
makes you see greater happiness.
I want you to be grateful about little things in life.
I also want you to be kind and giving to people around you.
Don't forget.
After you ascend,
you must descend.
You can't keep going up.
I didn't want to find happiness in little things in life.
That's why I worked so hard,
and I thought that I deserved to be at the top.
But was I wrong, Dad?
Is it time for me to stop...
and start descending?
Ms Na.
You've watched the trial, so you must know...
that the Department of Justice values how regretful Mr Hong is.
Meesa Apparel is also requesting a merciful arrangement,
so considering all circumstances, his sentence won't be too heavy.
I see.
Let me tell you this again.
Until your husband returns to you safe and sound, don't forget...
that you should trust no one but me and Mr Min Hyo Sang.
(11 Missed Calls, 13 New Messages)
(Wife)
(Call me back now. Where are you?)
(Why aren't you answering? What are you doing?)
(You have a new voicemail.)
Have you lost your mind? Call me. Call me back immediately.
I went to Hong Gi Pyo's first trial yesterday.
It looks like he'll end up with a light sentence...
as Min Hyo Sang planned.
You don't need to worry about it any more.
Hong Gi Pyo's case is one thing, but there's still...
evidence on the cheques as well as Ko Eun Sook's finances.
I'm sorry.
What do you mean?
You're not giving up, are you?
You've been so helpful to me.
I'm really sorry.
I'll be in touch again after things get sorted out a little.
It's been a while, Dong Jin.
I heard you went to the countryside to get some fresh air.
Did you have a good time?
(Letter of Resignation)
- What's this? - Can't you see?
"Letter of Resignation". It's written right there.
Right.
Why are you giving me this?
Let's not let this drag on.
Transfer those employees back to the head office...
and protect Father's honour.
If you can promise me that you'll do those two things,
I'll leave the company.
Sure thing.
But I didn't think that you'd submit a resignation letter.
Aren't you going to regret this later?
Whether I regret it or not, it's none of your business.
Just make sure to protect the company.
Father dedicated his entire life to growing this company.
It's too precious to be given a monetary value.
So many people's sweat and hard work...
made it come this far.
Try to grow it even further and make it become the company...
Father always dreamed about.
I will, of course.
But I didn't really want you to resign like this.
I'm sorry.
All right. I better go now.
Let's go out for soju next time.
There's no way Hyo Joo agreed to him resigning.
- Hello? - Where on earth are you now?
I need to see you now.
I came to see my mum briefly. I'll be home soon.
Did you disappear for days only to submit a letter of resignation...
without telling me a word about it?
Are you out of your mind?
Let's talk in person. I'll call you in a bit.
- Do you live here, Sir? - Yes.
There is a registered mail for Mr Lee Man Sool. Are you his family?
Yes, I'm his son.
(Hangook University Hospital)
I need your signature here, Sir.
(To: Lee Man Sool)
Hangook University Hospital?
(Ophthalmic Medical Record, Amblyopia, Visual field loss)
(You have ongoing contraction in visual field and amblyopia,)
(so we suggest you continue to get regular check-ups.)
"You have ongoing contraction in visual field and amblyopia,"
"so we suggest you continue to get regular check-ups"?
What is this?
It smells so delicious!
Are we having a feast or what?
You know that Mr Bae is moving in today.
I thought all of us should gather for a meal.
Right, Sam Do is moving in today. I forgot all about it.
You must be here because Mum called you for help.
Stop making Yun Shil do all the work, Mum.
I'm happy to help.
I wouldn't need to make her work if you knew how to do these things.
You just know how to dress up.
You can't even season bean sprouts, so just be quiet.
If I hadn't moved back home after breaking up my marriage,
my mum would've been so bored.
She gets so much kick out of giving me a hard time.
Yun Shil, what kind of nonsense is she talking right now?
Oh, my!
How crispy. It's grilled perfectly.
I can't eat this alone.
What are you doing now?
I want to take some to the part-timer.
Are you sure you're not taking them to the guy in the leather jacket?
Gosh, no! Not at all, Mum.
That's really not what I'm doing.
He said it's around here.
What's that?
I see a lot of people gathered. That must be it.
Excuse me. I'm sorry.
What?
It's not Jun.
I'm sorry.
Where could he be?
Susanna
- What? This is Jun's voice. - I will stay
By your side
- I won't let go of your hands - Why is he all alone?
We will be
Forever happy together
I'll love you forever
Don't cry alone any more
Susanna
What brings you here, Dong Sook?
I brought you lunch.
I can just order jjajangmyeon.
Singing consumes a lot of energy. Jjajangmyeon isn't good enough.
You brought gochujang bulgogi...
along with all sorts of jeon made with mung beans,
zucchini, oysters and perilla leaves.
It's like a jeon party. Is today a special day?
Sam Do is moving in today.
Oh, right. I forgot.
You must be hungry. Eat up.
Here.
It melts in my mouth.
Didn't you sing all morning?
Is this all you've made so far?
I can buy a bottle of soju with this amount of money.
I just need enough to buy a bottle of soju. Why should I make more?
You're so artistic.
An artist is doomed once he starts becoming greedy for money...
because he'll have to produce commodities, not artworks.
Why are you bringing that? Just throw it out.
Why should we throw it out?
If we take it to a junk shop, we'll make a few cents.
Goodness, you're so thrifty. Let's get going.
- Honey. - Yes?
Let's stop by the market.
We don't have enough time. Why should we stop by there?
I want to say a proper farewell.
Let's go see our store for one last time.
Goodness.
All right. Let's stop by the market.
We'll go to the market first.
Please get in, Ma'am.
(Sun Nyeo Chicken)
Honey, they're taking the sign down.
They must be changing the name of the store.
- Are they changing the name? - Yes.
The owner thinks it's too dated and wants something more sophisticated.
It doesn't sound dated at all.
Sun Nyeo Chicken. It sounds so cute.
I can finally say goodbye to that deep fryer which I'm so sick of.
You worked so hard to handle the boiling oil...
in that deep fryer, Bae Sam Do.
- Good work. - Good job, Honey.
- Sun Nyeo. - Sun Nyeo.
- We were about to visit your place. - For what?
The chairman of the market committee...
and all of us prepared something for you.
- What is it? - Just a moment.
"Certificate of Contribution".
"Bok Sun Nyeo and Bae Sam Do".
- Certification of Contribution? - "With your passion..."
"and superior work ethics, you have made..."
"immense contributions to the growth of Daejeon Jungang Market."
"Hence, we give you this to thank you for all of your hard work."
"From the market committee of Daejeon Jungang Market."
Congratulations!
What's the matter? Why are you crying?
This is just so touching.
I just worked hard and battled my way through...
to earn money.
I didn't expect to receive this, so I don't even know what to say.
You can come across as blunt and harsh,
but we all know how caring you are.
That's right. You attended every sad and happy occasion we had...
and volunteered to do all the tough jobs.
Stop crying.
I was out of line the other time. I'm sorry.
What is this?
You're moving, so you probably need to buy new things.
It's not much, but I hope it helps.
- Gosh, don't do this. - Stop being silly.
Buy a new pot with this.
The one you have now looks so worn out.
Why do you guys keep touching my heart like this?
This is from the market committee.
We wish you much success in Seoul.
No, it's okay. You really don't need to do this.
It's not much. Please just accept it.
No, we can't accept it. Please take it back.
The chairman is giving it to us.
We should gladly accept it with gratitude.
Rejecting it is impolite, Honey.
- Aren't I right, Sir? - Yes, you're absolutely right.
That's right.
The Bok Sun Nyeo we know would never reject money.
- Is that right? - Yes.
You, seriously...
- Best of luck. - Good luck.
- That woman is a piece of work. - What now?
She acted all generous and giving, but she only put in 30 dollars.
I gave her 50 dollars when her daughter got married.
Enough is enough, you money greedy woman.
My goodness. This is ridiculous.
- I honestly can't believe this. - What is it now?
The market committee has so many members.
How can they only give us 200 dollars?
Don't you think it's so petty?
Gosh, I'm so sick and tired of you going on about money.
I guess his family had no idea.
Mr Lee Man Sool...
has been diagnosed with pigmentary degeneration of the retina.
What does that mean, exactly?
To put it simply,
information about objects we see with our eyes become...
converted to the kind of information the optic nerve can decipher...
through photoreceptor cells in the retina,
which gets delivered to the brain.
Those with this condition...
experience gradual deterioration of eyesight...
caused by impaired function of the photoreceptor cells.
In the final stage, patients end up losing their eyesight.
What do you mean they lose their eyesight?
Are you saying that my dad will become blind?
Please leave a message after the tone.
Press the star button to end recording.
It's me, Dad.
I met with your doctor today.
Your eyes...
I know that you're losing your eyesight.
How can you do this to me?
You may think I'm pathetic, but I'm still your only son.
You should have told me.
How can you make me...
feel so horrible and helpless as your son?
Ms Choi!
Yes!
Welcome. We've been waiting for you.
- We're here. - Good to see you.
It must've been a big decision for you. Thank you.
I'm going to thank you for this until the day I die.
Let's wait and see because you might end up regretting it.
I mean, who buys suits at tailor shops these days?
You're so good at discouraging people.
Today is our first day here. Let's not cause trouble.
All right. I'll keep my mouth shut.
Ms Na. You're here, too.
You must be tired from the long drive.
Not at all.
Hey, let's be friends from now on.
We're neighbours now, so let's try to get along.
What's the matter, Jun?
I suddenly got muscle spasm in my hand.
- Oh, no. - I'm okay, Dong Sook.
Bring your stuff in. Let's have dinner after.
- Sure. - Sure.
If each of you can take one thing,
- Okay. - it'll help us out a lot.
- Give me something to carry. - No, Ms Choi. Please go in.
- Please don't worry. - It's fine.
Then...
- you can take this. - All right.
I'll take that one. Sam Do, give me that one.
Okay, sure.
- I'll take something heavy. - You won't be able to carry it.
- I'll be fine. - Be careful, okay?
You got the heavy one!
- Hey, you. - Ouch.
- What do you want? - Everyone is helping us out.
How can you go in empty-handedly?
Goodness! This can break my arms.
- This is so heavy! - You have to carry it.
I mean, aren't you going to be using our kitchen tools?
Hurry up and take it to the kitchen.
You have to come back and help us carry our refrigerator.
Your refrigerator?
You don't have to help us if you aren't going to use it.
I'll be right back.
Nice.
With people like him, you need to show them who's in charge.
You're absolutely right.
These are about to start sprouting.
Mum worked so hard to grow these.
Sweet potatoes and black beans?
Then bring them to Mr Lee's place.
I live alone, but this house is filled with people.
Yes. Okay, call me when you're here.
Who was that?
It was Tae Yang. His mum sent him sweet potatoes and black beans,
so I told him to bring them here.
Are they almost done with moving their stuff in?
You know how frugal Sun Nyeo is. They don't have much stuff.
Is dinner almost ready?
Yes. We just need to heat up the soup.
- Try calling Dong Jin. - Why?
He hasn't called since leaving for the countryside for work.
I've been having nightmares, so I'm worried about him.
He's not answering.
Is something going on at work?
Close the store.
- Sell it. - What?
Don't cling on to something that's losing money.
Take Mum travelling. Eat nice food and have fun.
I'll give you 20 times what you make in that store.
I wasn't able to tell you this,
but to tell you the truth...
Dong Jin.
He came to my office...
to tell me about it.
I had no idea and just got all mad at him.
I'm sorry, Dad.
Ever since my husband left home,
I've been feeling so lonely as if I'm living in an empty house.
With you two moving in, the house feels a lot more lively,
and I feel so much better already.
Mum, please.
- You have Jun, too. - What?
Right, sure.
Jun does live here, too.
Yun Shil!
Hey.
You're here.
- Hello. - Yes. It's good to see you.
I haven't seen you at the convenience store.
- I quit recently. - Did you?
Come in and join us for dinner.
It's okay. I have a shift, so I have to get going.
You still have time. Eat with us before you go to work.
Yes. Come in and join us. We owe you for all the driving you did.
Dong Sook, what are you doing? Go and bring cutleries for him.
Okay, Mum.
We need a fresh bowl of soup, too.
Come in.
- I'll join you, then. - Yes, come on in.
Dong Sook, I'll do it!
Come and have a seat here.
Let me introduce myself properly.
I'm Bae Sam Do.
I'll be working as the master tailor...
at Wolgyesu Tailor Shop starting tomorrow.
I'm Kang Tae Yang. Please feel free to talk casually to me.
All right, then. Shall we shake hands?
Be careful.
His hands are as strong as those of the Terminator.
- Nice to meet you. - Likewise.
You have such a strong grip.
Yes. Men must be strong.
You're in much better shape than that guy.
What?
All right, everyone. Here comes the delicious curled mallow soup.
Here.
All right. Let's eat before the food gets cold.
Where shall I take you, Sir?
Home. Take me home.
I have something to tell my mum and my family.
Please give me your address.
The address is... What was it?
I can't remember.
If you tell me the neighbourhood...
Oh, right. Wolgyesu Tailor Shop.
Let's go to Wolgyesu Tailor Shop.
My place is nearby.
Wolgyesu Tailor Shop?
Okay.
The world's greatest master tailor,
Mr Lee Man Sool, owns that shop.
Wolgyesu Tailor Shop.
We sincerely thank you for your warm welcome.
I'll do my best to revive Wolgyesu Tailor Shop as soon as possible...
so that Mr Lee can return soon.
Mum. You should say a few words, too.
I don't really have anything to say.
I just want all of us to get along and live like a family.
Then let's make a toast, everyone.
To our success!
- To our success. - To our success.
All right!
It's time...
to lift up everyone's spirits.
Our new neighbours,
Sam Do and Sun Nyeo, will show us a performance to celebrate today!
What's he talking about?
Think of it as a hazing ritual.
The two of you should stand up and sing for us.
Everyone, give them a big hand!
Well, both Sam Do and I will seriously party it up...
if you get us in the mood like this.
- You're ready, right? - I'm baffled.
Goodness.
In 1, 2, 1, 2, 3, 4.
- Between the sky and the earth - Between the sky and the earth
- Came down the flower rain - Came down the flower rain
- After passing a forest in a valley - After passing a forest in a valley
- We met for the first time - We met for the first time
- It was meant to be - It was meant to be
- So we understood each other - So we understood each other
- With a bundle of happiness - With a bundle of happiness
- We loved each other wholeheartedly - We loved each other wholeheartedly
- Then one day - Then one day
Then one day
- The fairy left - The fairy left
- She left everything behind - She left everything behind
- And went far away - And went far away
- Please find my fairy - Please find my fairy
- This story of the woodcutter - This story of the woodcutter
- Fills my lovelorn heart - Fills my lovelorn heart
- With sadness - With sadness
- It was meant to be - It was meant to be
- So we understood each other - So we understood each other
- With a bundle of happiness - With a bundle of happiness
- We loved each other wholeheartedly - We loved each other wholeheartedly
- Then one day - Then one day
- The fairy left - The fairy left
- She left everything behind - She left everything behind
- And went far away - And went far away
- Please find my fairy - Please find my fairy
- This story of the woodcutter - This story of the woodcutter
- Mum! It's me. - Fills my lovelorn heart
- With sadness - With sadness
- Then one day - Then one day
- The fairy left - The fairy left
- Mum. - She left everything behind
- Dong Sook! It's me, Dong Jin. - And went far away
- Please find my fairy - Please find my fairy
- This story of the woodcutter - Gosh.
You should've called.
Did you just get back from your work trip?
- Yes. Well, I was... - Oh, no. Are you okay?
- What's this? Let go! - My gosh!
- Dong Jin! - My goodness.
(The Gentlemen of Wolgyesu Tailor Shop)
He literally drank until he dropped.
No matter how hard I try, I just can't like him.
Only Hyo Sang and I...
- know about Dong Jin's resignation. - Are you kidding me right now?
Stop loving freebies so much and just get married already.
Shall I set him up with someone?
- Come with me to Anseong. - Pardon me?
I'm warning you for the last time. Don't show up before me again.
How can it be so easy for you to end this?
- What's this? - I said I'll divorce you...
if you can't become the CEO. I clearly warned you.