Congratulations, Tae Joon.
See you at the prosecutors' office.
I love you.
Somebody named Song Hui Su left a message.
She's sorry about today and didn't mean it. She wants to treat you.
She masked herself and hid her identity...
Did she go by "Kim Ji Young"?
Yes.
I found out that it's about how he had an affair with another woman.
Have you heard of...
Kim Ji Young?
No,
I haven't.
Are you sure?
If you haven't heard of that name, this investigation ends here.
(Missed Call)
Where are you? I'm at your firm now.
I saw Ji Hoon, Seo Yeon and Mother.
(Zigbang)
I know it's late, but may I see the apartment?
What do you think? Isn't it exactly the same as the photos?
Take a look at the ambience for now.
Come back tomorrow or two days later to take a better look.
If you pick a place in a hurry, you'll regret later.
I'll sign the lease here.
I waited for too long.
Where are you right now? I kept looking for you.
Did you read my text?
People are asking where you are.
They want to meet you, but I don't even know.
I found a place.
What?
A place where you'll live.
When did you find one?
Are you there? Is it nice?
Come alone without telling anyone.
Do you want to be alone with me?
All right.
I'll be there as soon as I finish here.
Okay.
I can take care of the children,
but isn't she making a big deal out of this?
You should rest too.
How can she be so selfish?
Mother.
She and I have to make up so that you worry less about me.
Please, Mother.
- Okay. - Prosecutor Lee.
May I talk to you for a minute?
Sure.
Ma'am, may I borrow your son for a minute?
Please go ahead, Congresswoman.
You should go. Say goodbye to your father.
- See you at home. - Okay, go home.
- Go home first. - See you later.
Take your grandmother and go home.
Your mother has a great fashion sense.
I heard your father used to be in politics, too.
Things didn't work out well for him though.
It's okay as long as you make up for what he couldn't do.
I think the party is over.
Shall we go somewhere to finish our conversation?
I invited people from the city commission. Meeting them will help.
I'd like to, but I can't today.
My wife wants to see me.
I can come see you any time if you contact me after tomorrow.
Goodbye.
Prosecutor.
Let him go. It'll be a great approach.
Lee Tae Joon by himself is a very common man who had an affair.
However, when he's with his wife,
he's an incorruptible prosecutor and a powerful politician.
When he returns to work, tell him to focus on the investigation on...
bribery while keeping his wife close to him.
It's a once in a lifetime chance.
We must bring him back no matter what.
Hello, Ji Hoon.
Hi, Mum. I heard you'll be meeting Dad.
Yes.
We're going to Grandmother's house,
so talk everything out with him tonight.
You should go to bed soon since it's late.
You surprise me sometimes.
I'll send you the rest of your stuff tomorrow.
Have you always had it in mind?
It's close to your work, so it'll be convenient.
You told me you'll forget it.
You said we should work it out at least for the children.
Everything is over now,
but what's wrong?
What about Kim Ji Young?
I'm glad I wasn't wrong.
Who...
Who told you that?
Do other people know about this?
Who told me is more important to you.
My feelings are nothing to you.
That was a mistake I made a long time ago.
I had forgotten it completely.
Is that your excuse?
I didn't tell you because it was over.
It was because I knew...
you'd be more confused had I told you.
It was before I changed.
It's all my fault.
But you forgave me now.
Digging through the past won't help...
I sincerely wanted to work on our relationship.
I thought it was best for us and our children.
But I guess it wasn't.
There are still people...
who are out to get us.
Right now, they're watching us while staying quiet,
but once they find a crack, they'll attack us.
We can't separate at a time like this.
There will be rumours.
They'll try to accuse me for something else to take me back in.
Our kids. Our kids.
Think about our kids.
Do you want them to go through all that again?
Don't make them your excuse. This is your problem.
I'm sorry.
I just got too upset.
I understand how you might feel.
What should I do? I'll do whatever you want me to.
If you want me to quit being a prosecutor, I will.
Please, stop it.
(The Good Wife)
The civil participation on the trial of the damage claim suit...
against the antidepressant Elvatil starts today.
The family of the victims and the lawyers claim that...
the medication caused violent side effects...
including the urge to commit suicide.
Stop the sales of antidepressant Elvatil!
- Stop! - Stop!
The plaintiff Do Han Na's father Do Jae Cheol murdered his wife...
and committed suicide after taking the medication.
There are more than 20 victims...
who committed suicide after taking the antidepressant Elvatil.
I believe that they must not only compensate for the losses,
but ban the drug from being distributed.
This is the first civil trial in history...
to involve civil engagement.
It's pretty good. Your face looks sincere.
Stop joking around and be serious.
It took us two years just to get ourselves a trial.
If we lose at this point, I can't bear to look at the victims.
We have to win no matter what.
The media is interested. It's a huge medical case.
If we win, it'll definitely help promote our firm.
If we can help people while getting more famous, it's perfect.
We're on a roll after winning Lee Tae Joon's case.
If we win this case on top of it,
our law firm's name will be engraved in the public's mind.
That way, we won't have to fire people again.
- Lawyer Kim. - Yes.
You did some research on the antidepressant, right?
Yes. Lawyer Lee and I studied some dissertations...
and interviewed some doctors.
Then you must know this case well.
Well...
This is the summary of the case.
You need this information to explain to the jury.
You should read it over.
Okay.
You can't make a mistake in front of the jury. Prepare well.
The trial is at 2pm.
Does she mean...
Yes, she wants you to be the second chair.
- But... - She looks nervous, doesn't she?
That's because she is.
The pharmaceutical company's lawyer is apparently really good.
The jury can't take their eyes off that lawyer.
I don't have enough experience.
Do you think I'll be all right in a civil participation trial?
Don't worry. She's giving it to you because she trusts you.
Just do as you have done up to now.
If civil participation trials become more common,
this industry will change a lot.
Lawyers who are talented at speaking...
will be at an advantage than those with talents in writing.
You're right.
You should do your best.
This might be your strength.
I'm not so good with words.
Anyways, I'll try my best.
Okay.
(Cerebrum MRI Analysis)
Can we talk?
That's our client, Do Han Na.
She's very sensitive right now.
Please talk to her so that...
she can calm down.
Okay.
Ms Do, say hello.
She will be co-defending the case.
Nice to meet you.
I saw the news about your husband.
Congratulations.
Thank you.
You two should have a chat.
Okay.
The other families felt pressured to bring this to court.
I heard it was a hard decision for you to make.
President Seo tried to persuade me for months.
I was hesitant for a long time,
but then I thought that...
I shouldn't let my parents go just like that.
To be honest, I'm still worried...
if this is the right thing to do.
Right...
Will there be photographs...
of my parents during trial?
I think so.
When you're testifying,
there might be conversations difficult for you to listen to.
Don't worry too much. We'll be right beside you.
If we continue to discuss and fight together, it'll turn out well.
Just trust us and leave it up to us.
I'm scared,
but I will do it.
I'll do it for my late parents.
I'm sure they would want me to testify for them.
Lawyer Kim Hye Gyeong. You got involved in this case...
as soon as your husband was released.
How do you feel?
What did Lee Tae Joon say about your involvement in this case?
I'm only planning to give my best to this case.
Also, my husband...
is supporting me the most more than anyone else.
The plaintiff lowered the compensation money...
and asked for the ban of Elvatil.
Is this a strategy to make the pharmaceutical company settle?
No.
It's to show that the plaintiff is not doing this for money.
This lawsuit is for the honour of those who died or got injured...
due to Elvatil's side effects, and also to prevent future deaths.
If the pharmaceutical company admits to the side effects...
and apologise with a prevention plan for the future,
we might consider settling.
Our opponent hired the best lawyer in civil participation trials.
Yes. I heard from Lawyer Seo Joong Won.
That's why...
I want you to lead the arraignment.
Me? I've never talked in front of the jury...
I chose you myself.
Don't doubt yourself.
I know you can do it, and you'll do well.
I still think that you're better...
Of course I'll be better than you.
I prepared it for a long time and I know this case the best.
However, this is a civil participation trial where...
the lawyer's charms will influence the outcome.
That's why I'm asking you.
I trust your abilities and I want to use you.
A lawyer must use every means to get a win for his or her client.
It could be someone's image, their looks...
or their talent with words.
As the law firm's president, I believe you're perfect for this.
Okay. I'll try my best.
You'll be great.
I need to go to the restroom for a minute.
Hello, I'm Lawyer Kim Hye Gyeong.
We're here today because a family was ruined because of Elvatil.
Hello, dear jurors.
Firstly, I'd like to thank you for making the time...
to come here during your busy schedules.
Many died from the side effects of antidepressant Elvatil.
However, the pharmaceutical company MRG...
denies this fact and is continuing to sell the drug...
which will lead to more victims.
Right over here in the dock...
(Mother)
Goodness.
Are you all right?
Yes, I'm all right.
Do you need help?
No, it's okay.
Okay.
Oh, right. My bag...
I forgot.
Could you bring me my bag?
I left it by the vending machine.
I see.
I'd really appreciate it. I can't move easily.
Okay, stay here. I'll bring it right now.
Okay, thank you.
Are you President Seo Myeong Hee from Law Firm MJ?
I'm Son Dong Wook.
I'm defending the pharmaceutical company.
I see.
It's nice to meet you.
The man over there is the vice president of the company.
If you have any problems with the trial, you can talk to him.
He'll help you out as much as possible.
Whenever you can't endure it any longer,
please let me know.
Okay.
Everyone, please rise.
Members of the jury, please come in.
Plaintiff, please start.
I'm waiting for the joint lawyer.
She's nearby, so she'll be here soon.
Then let's start with the defendant.
- Is that all right? - Yes, it's all right.
Thank you for coming.
My name is...
Lawyer Son Dong Wook.
Before I talk about the trial,
I'd like to explain my condition.
Hello, Lawyer Kim Hye Gyeong.
You were a little late, so we decided that I start.
I see. Okay.
Thank you.
- As I've mentioned before, - I'm sorry.
-I'd like to talk... - Where were you?
I had to see someone outside.
I have what's called tardive dyskinesias.
I can't control all of my muscles,
so I keep moving like this.
Sometimes when I'm happy, I do this.
It's okay to laugh.
In Korea, there's a huge distance between normal and disabled people.
Many aren't sure how to act when they see someone who's disabled.
By the time this trial is over,
I hope that the gap between you and me...
will get smaller.
The great news...
is...
this medicine.
I take this medicine once every few hours every day.
This medicine doesn't get rid of my symptoms completely,
but it reduces them greatly.
My condition is rare,
so selling this medicine won't bring enough revenue.
The company that made this medicine...
despite significant financial losses...
is also the manufacturer of antidepressant Elvatil,
whom you'll judge today.
Objection, Your Honour.
Objection dismissed.
I must tell you that...
my symptoms get worse when I get flustered.
That's why I can neither tell lies...
nor hear other people lie.
Objection, Your Honour.
Both parties, come this way.
Your Honour.
While explaining his condition, the lawyer of the defendant...
is trying to make the defendant look positive to the jurors.
Your Honour, I only explained my condition beforehand in case...
I surprise the jurors.
The issue of the trial is whether the antidepressant manufactured...
by the defendant causes violence and suicidal urges.
The lawyer of the defendant shouldn't compliment the company...
while pretending to explain his condition.
What you're saying is also reasonable.
Lawyer Son.
It's okay to explain your condition,
but don't relate it to the pharmaceutical company.
All right, Your Honour.
Also,
it's a demonstrative trial where citizens participate.
The Supreme Court is also watching us.
Please...
try not to be irrational.
Let's just follow the rules,
all right?
I'll do my best...
as long as the defendant doesn't do anything funny.
All right.
You must be happy that your husband's so famous.
Your bag wasn't by the vending machine.
I'm sorry. I forgot that my colleague had it.
Do you think you can win the case by playing games like this?
Of course.
You're already upset.
Lawyer Kim, did the trial go well?
Your mother is waiting for you in the office.
Hello, Mother.
Why did you do that?
What do you mean?
You abandoned my son.
Tae Joon was alone in the apartment.
As soon as he was released,
he got kicked out of his house and went to a strange, new place.
Yes.
Did you decide to break up with him...
after he was released?
I went through all the difficulties and broke up after he got released.
Why do you think I did that?
Are you seeing another man?
Please continue.
I can't understand you.
I told Tae Joon...
that you're scary because you don't share your thoughts.
Should I tell you...
why I'm doing this?
No.
Forget it. Fine.
Let's say you break up.
Whatever the reason may be,
I can't stop you if you want it.
However,
what will you do about your children?
Ji Hoon and Seo Yeon...
are excited to live happily with their father again.
What will you tell them?
Will you tell them honestly?
Yes.
I'll tell them myself.
They'll understand since they're grown up.
I understand how you feel,
but...
things won't work out...
as well as you'd like.
I won't see you off.
Sir.
How can we let him return to the prosecutors' office?
Even if he was tried innocent for bribery,
how can we let him return when the whole nation knows of his video?
We don't hire womanisers a prosecutors.
No, I'm sorry.
I should have won the case. But Sir, this is...
We're already here.
Okay. Take your time.
What did they say?
Forget it. Just find out who that woman is.
The disciplinary committee will think otherwise when we reveal her.
The district attorney will be here soon.
He told me to go ahead without him.
Sang Il,
let's end it here.
It's not good to show the public that we're fighting internally.
What do you think, Do Sub?
I agree.
Families shouldn't fight.
Even if we reinvestigate Dream UCT's case,
I won't touch a hair on you.
I don't plan on hurting your family either.
I'll let you keep working at the prosecutors' office.
All I'm asking is for you to just sit still.
Don't do anything.
You know, your superiors feel pressured by you.
You...
Well? Did you talk it out?
Yes. He's so understanding.
Thank you,
Sang Il.
I decided to take some time away from your dad.
Why?
Well...
Because that's the best for now.
I can't understand it.
I thought everything was sorted out.
He won the case and everything.
You said you'd try again with Dad.
Yes.
I tried, but it didn't work out.
Then...
Are you two going to break up forever?
It's not like that. We're just taking some time to think.
Nothing has been decided yet.
Then before you make a decision,
are we banned from seeing him?
No.
No matter what happens between us,
you two are still our children.
I understand it's hard...
but there wasn't anything else I could do.
Also,
let's keep this between ourselves.
Because it could harm Dad?
Because it could put all of us in a difficult position.
You're saying that you might get together with Dad again, right?
Is that why we're keeping it a secret?
Ji Hoon, there are a lot of people that like to talk about others.
They want other people to be ruined.
They add false information before spreading rumours.
There's nothing good in people like that...
subtitles ripped and synced by riri13
knowing about us.
I'll do whatever you tell us to do.
I know how hard it has been for you.
I...
just want you to be happy.
I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry to you both.
- Gosh. Come in. - Mother.
- Did you drink? - Mother.
- Mother. - My goodness.
You reek.
- Mother. - How much did you drink?
Hey, watch it. You'll trip.
Hold on.
- I had a few drinks. - All right.
I met up with my colleagues.
I'm going to put them all in jail.
Okay, go ahead. I don't know who they are but go ahead.
Stay still. Let me make you some honey water.
- Sit down for a minute. - Mother.
All right. What's with you?
- My mother. - Okay, okay.
Gosh. My goodness.
Goodness.
How much did he drink?
Thank goodness I brought some food for him to eat.
Did you see Hye Gyeong on television today?
She was acting as if you guys were doing fine.
She was smiling so much.
I know she does it deliberately.
You need to wake up and watch out.
Make sure she doesn't do anything strange.
You have to set things straight.
What did Lee Tae Joon say about your involvement in this case?
I'm planning to just do my best in this case.
Also, my husband...
is supporting me the most more than anyone else.
The plaintiff lowered the compensation money...
Also, my husband...
is supporting me the most more than anyone else.
Doctor Kim Sae Young.
In a recent clinical demonstration,
you found out that the patients who took Elvatil were...
three times more...
My apologies. It was because of my condition.
Three times more...
They were three times more likely to commit suicide.
Yes, that's correct.
The serotonin transporter gene...
known as 5-HTT...
must have increased the synaptic serotonin levels.
Could you explain in words that are simpler to understand?
Imagine a train station.
The neurotransmitter serotonin...
is like the train engineer.
The rail tracks can be seen as the absorption rate.
Then the gene 5-HTT...
can be seen as coal. That would be easier to understand.
Thank you.
No further questions.
The defence counsel may now ask questions.
Yes, Your Honour.
Doctor. Let's talk about sex.
What? Talk about what?
What was that substance called? Sel...
Serotonin re-uptake inhibitors, right?
Anyway, that substance has an influence on people's...
sexual behaviours and emotions, doesn't it?
Yes. It does, but...
But it would only amplify one's feelings.
It cannot create feelings one never had, am I right?
If someone commits murder from this substance's influence,
that means that the person originally had hatred inside.
How are the jurors reacting?
They think the way you talk is too hard.
They like the male lawyer because he's nice and easy to understand.
They say that a company working to find cure for a rare disease...
would never harm their patients.
When recess is over, Ms Do has to testify right away.
Is she ready?
Yes, she'll be fine.
We have to turn the tables over now.
We might end up losing.
Okay.
Our family used to be so happy.
I'm the only one left now.
I don't care about the compensation money.
I just don't want them to sell Elvatil any more.
That's why...
Please help us so that there won't be any more victims like us.
Please.
No further questions.
The defence counsel may now ask questions.
Yes, Your Honour.
First, I'd like to pay respects to your late parents.
Did your father work in an interior design company?
Yes. He designed wallpapers and lights.
Were all of his colleagues females?
I'm not sure about that.
Then I'll tell you.
He worked with 11 women.
He used to work late a lot, right?
He was late time to time, but...
I'd like to submit this as evidence.
The police found this bag when they arrived at the site.
Is it your father's?
Yes.
This is a list of items inside the bag.
Please read out loud the third item.
I'll read it out loud instead.
"A woman's black underwear".
"Small size".
I'll ask the witness.
What is your mother's size?
Objection, Your Honour. The question is irrelevant to the case.
To prove what happened to Do Jae Cheol and his wife...
isn't related to the side effects of the medicine, it's important to ask.
Objection dismissed. The witness should answer.
I believe her size is 77.
Then it wouldn't be small size.
Even if Elvatil causes side effects, not that it does,
but if it does,
it can't create feelings that don't exist.
If her father killed his wife and committed suicide,
isn't it because they had mistrust...
between the two?
That isn't true. My dad...
My father wasn't someone who'd do that.
They had no problems.
Problems of a married couple stay between them.
If he were that happy,
why did he take antidepressants?
Why was a pair of woman's underwear found in his bag?
Objection, Your Honour.
That'll be all.
Members of the jury, do you have any questions?
Witness, you may step down.
Lawyer Son.
Wasn't that too harsh even though winning the case is a priority?
What do you mean?
How could you say that to Han Na when she lost both of her parents?
Do you really believe in what you say...
or are you doing this for the money?
You're only wasting time if you're trying to see...
if I'm conscientious.
Right, you don't seem conscientious.
Lawyer Kim, let me give you an advice.
You can't win solely based on good intentions.
You need skills.
I...
I really want to win this case.
We should. We'll win this case no matter what.
Is this...
your new office?
I'll be hired officially after the meeting with disciplinary committee.
But they told me to prepare for the investigation on Dream UCT here.
Higher management ordered them, so they gave me a spot,
but they don't want me to be noticeable.
I've been a prosecutor for a long time,
but I've never been here.
From now on, you'll only sit...
in a much better office than this.
At the appointment today,
will Lawyer Kim join?
Congresswoman Lee wants her there.
Let's meet without her today.
She's busy with a trial.
Did the trial go well?
No, we need to talk.
Did something happen?
It can't be helped because medicine is boring.
It's true though.
That truth is boring.
The defendant is making it dramatic...
while we talk about boring things, so who would listen to us?
That's why we're discussing this, to change our strategy.
My strategy is a little aggressive.
As you know,
the first civil procedure where citizens participate can get messy.
I know your strategy,
but what else can we do when the defendant's side is acting that way?
We need an aggressive strategy.
Yes, it's been unfair to many.
We must win this case for them.
Okay, let's review the case together.
What's the name of our witness in medicine?
Pardon me,
but what do you want me to say?
I reviewed the dissertation you wrote.
It said taking Elvatil reduces one's libido.
I don't think it does.
It was part of the results in your research.
Patient 18...
said so during an interview at the clinical test.
That's more likely due to another factor.
Therefore, we moved on to the next topic.
Doctor, you know about the side effects of Elvatil...
better than anyone else.
For the victims to receive...
an apology and compensation from the pharmaceutical company,
this is the only way.
I'm a scientist.
I can't lie just because you want me to.
All right, Doctor Kim.
But as you only fulfilled half of the contract's requirement,
you'll have to return half of the payment.
I'll review...
the research results.
Thank you.
Do you have any recordings of animal testing?
I need the most violent one.
What kind of influence did an overdose of trytophane...
have on the test subjects?
Their libido was reduced.
Objection, Your Honour.
It's irrelevant to the case.
The defendant's argument...
is based on the fact that Do Jae Cheol, who took...
the medicine, did what he did as he had an affair.
By showing that Elvatil reduces one's libido,
we'll prove that Do Jae Cheol couldn't have an affair.
Objection dismissed. Please proceed.
Is the reduction of libido permanent when Elvatil is taken?
Further research is necessary,
but it is possible.
This is what happens when...
a minimum amount of Elvatil is injected into white mice.
Yes.
Among cells that produce dopamine,
we wanted to find out the influence of 5-HT2C.
This happened as a result.
Yes.
All the mice died except for one.
That's all, Your Honour.
Members of the jury, do you have any questions?
Yes.
"Are there other medicines that use ingredients in Elvatil?"
"My libido has diminished recently."
Goodness.
- Sir. - Yes?
Questions irrelevant to the trial are not allowed.
Skills are more important than conscience, right?
Were we too harsh?
No, you were completely appropriate.
There are already articles on it.
"Antidepressant Elvatil reduces sexual desires."
MRG's shares will drop by tomorrow.
Now, I understand...
what you meant...
during the Lee Eun Joo case.
We have to protect our clients, not our beliefs.
Back then, I thought it would be fine as long as I was proud.
Even if I lost,
I tried my best and it just couldn't be helped.
Maybe I thought of it too simply.
No.
I only said that because I was afraid we wouldn't get paid.
Also,
it ended up the way you thought.
Eun Joo got her apology.
You did well then.
I was lucky.
I got Tae Joon's help.
Hye Gyeong.
I don't regret it.
I still have hope.
Hope that I'll be able to protect my client as well as my beliefs.
When I build more experience...
and become a veteran, wouldn't I be able to do it?
Not now, though.
That's why I want to win a lot.
For the clients...
and for myself as well.
Then again,
even during a mock court,
you would never give up even when everyone else did...
and got extenuation.
The trial wouldn't finish even at 1am when it started at 2pm.
All of the kids were dozing off.
The professor said that...
you lost legalistically,
but gave you the win in order to finish the trial.
Yes, I was like that back then too.
I can be stubborn.
Do you remember that your opposing prosecutor...
was me?
Was it you?
Yes. Whenever I said something,
you would scream in objection.
Towards the end, I would just flinch at the thought...
of you getting up.
The professor called me over...
and told me not to become a prosecutor.
That's how bad it was.
I'm sorry about back then.
Forget it.
While watching you that day,
I was really amazed.
If you ever find out...
anything in life,
please share with me.
It'll likely help with my life as a lawyer.
Sure.
I'll tell you whatever I find out.
We're all here. Please go ahead.
I think we both understand where we stand through the trial.
Why don't we come to an agreement now?
An agreement?
The trial is far from being over.
Hello?
Yes, we're listening.
It's better for your side to settle as well.
You won't get much from winning the trial.
Let's talk in person tomorrow.
I'll give you a call after discussing with the other lawyers.
We did it.
I'm happy, but it's a little strange.
They looked like they wanted to go all the way yesterday.
Lawyers are great bluffers.
I'll talk to Do Han Na.
Hye Gyeong.
Do you want to have dinner together?
Sure.
Are you Lawyer Kim Hye Gyeong?
Yes.
I'm Song Hui Su.
Hello. Are you waiting for someone?
Yes. Joong Won.
Right. He's in his office. Should I tell him you're here?
That's okay, I can wait here.
I heard you went to school with him.
Yes.
We're institute colleagues, too.
He talks about you all the time.
I'm so jealous.
That's because we're good friends.
To be honest, today is our first date.
I guess that's why I'm jealous.
Right, dinner plans.
Hye Gyeong, this is Song Hui Su.
She's a student at the school I gave a lecture once.
I forgot we were going for dinner.
Do you want to come with us?
No, that's okay. I don't want to bother you.
I have a lot of work to do anyway.
Right. Your husband was released, right?
- Congratulations. - Thank you.
Enjoy your dinner.
Let's go.
Are you free tonight?
We are supposed to have drinks after every first jury trial.
We keep on missing it.
Lawyer Kim.
Kim Ji Young.
That's enough.
We have to continue working at the same office.
I didn't think it was necessary to tell you.
- It was such a long time ago... - It's selfish to make an excuse.
If you step into politics,
you lose interest in women.
Politics is so much more fun.
It excites you and you get addicted to it.
Gosh, it's incomparable to women.
You'll be able to have a better relationship with your wife.
You two will become partners more so than a husband and a wife.
You should tell her that.
I prefer being a husband and a wife than being partners.
I prefer that as well since that's less complicated.
Anyway, good luck with your investigation.
Please send your wife my greetings.
Okay, I will.
Did you know about the problem between my wife and me as well?
Yes. I had some assumptions.
I think the congresswoman has an idea as well.
It would be best to sort it out in one way or another.
This is not a matter to sort out.
She's my wife...
and it's my life.
It's not something other people should get involved in.
Tell this to Congresswoman Lee.
If I don't have any value to her,
she should just give me up.
If I must make up or break up, it's up to me.
I won't move...
according to your plans.
I think Lawyer Kim Hye Gyeong...
is a nice person.
She's a talented lawyer.
What's the relationship between you two?
Not what the rumours say. What's the truth?
(Hello.)
(It's been a while.)
(He's never been here before so we need a few more minutes.)
(Yes, no problem.)
(Who is he?)
(Are you friends?)
(Or is he your boyfriend?)
(I'm not sure yet.)
(Right now, I'm interested in him.)
(Well, best of luck.)
(If you need anything, just let me know.)
(Thank you.)
He says you're handsome.
Yes.
It won't be decided tomorrow. We have to adjust the terms.
However, the company would want to avoid their shares from dropping.
So it won't take too long.
Yes.
I'll let you know if anything confirms.
Goodbye.
- Hello. - Long time no see.
Do you come here often? It looks expensive here.
I sometimes come here with my dad.
Your dad must be someone famous.
I'll tell you if you promise you won't be shocked.
If you say that, I feel like I have to be shocked.
He owns Calim Financial which rents buildings.
Calim Financial?
Didn't it rank fourth place in real estate industry?
It ranked third.
Not that it's important.
You're buying dinner tonight, right?
Yes.
Most people get quiet when they find out what my father does.
That's not your case.
It's because they're too scared.
How do you say, "What's the most expensive wine here,"
in Spanish?
Can we talk?
Weren't we done talking?
We need to talk more.
That's what married couples do.
All right.
What more do I have to hear?
I found a good marriage counsellor.
The counsellor has a lot of experience in marital issues.
I'll go see the counsellor starting next week.
And? Do I have to go, too?
Yes.
We must understand each other for us to reconcile soon.
I'll think about it. You should go before our children arrive.
Hye Gyeong.
I said I'm sorry. I know you're angry.
I know you don't want to talk to me right now,
but we can't continue like this.
Right now...
is the most important time for us.
Many have high hopes for us.
If we only get through this,
I can be in a position where...
I can change the nation.
I never wanted that.
What I wanted...
was for you to be a good person.
Okay.
I've changed a lot because of you.
That's why I got rid of Cho Guk Hyun.
No.
You haven't changed since that accident.
I believed you then.
I believed you were standing up for justice.
Even after giving up...
my experience and my future,
I thought I could be together with you.
I know why you're angry with me.
I understand.
I accept it.
However,
it's not the right time to get angry.
For now, please do what I ask you.
You must think...
I'll forgive you again.
We're married.
Ji Hoon.
Seo Yeon.
We can't separate.
That's not it.
You think I'll come back to you as long as...
you beg for forgiveness no matter what you do.
The Kim Hye Gyeong...
in your head is someone who took the blame for your mistake.
She thought that was love for 15 years.
You think I'll keep being that way as I've been that way until now.
I understand now...
what kind of person you thought I was.
But I'm sorry.
To me, I'm more valuable than you are.
- Hye Gyeong. - Please leave.
Are you the good one and the only one who's hurt?
Is it all my fault?
You've lived with me for 15 years.
Don't pretend that you're the victim and the only good person.
Both you and I are the same.
That's why we stayed together.
Then tell me.
Tell you what?
You said I pretended to be the victim,
but what about you?
You said you loved me so tell me what you've done for me.
Have you ever...
asked what I really wanted?
Have you ever been curious?
You always said what you wanted to say.
"I need you," "I'm sorry". Did you say those things for me?
Have you ever put me before you?
What do you want me to say?
Say what will make me believe you...
so our relationship can be recovered.
Tell me.
What about Seo Joong Won?
Is he any different?
Should I compliment on how he's still a great colleague...
as he was before? Is that what you want?
You changed your mind because you met someone else.
All you want is that I leave you. Fine, I'll leave.
Do you want to take it all the way?
I only made a mistake once, but you...
fell in love with him.
Between you and me,
whose the worse one?
Is that what you've been thinking...
while apologising to me?
Were you wondering why I was taking so long to forgive you?
My apologies were sincere.
You were the one who didn't believe me.
Right, you're always sincere.
I'm the bad one if I don't forgive you.
I have to believe you whenever you want me to...
and ignore when you do wrong.
I can be a good wife only if I always stay by your side.
Isn't that what you want from me?
We're too riled up.
Let's talk later, Hye Gyeong.
I'm not riled up.
I can see most clearly now ever since I've met you.
Get lost.
(The Good Wife)
I want to follow my heart from now on.
You must push it forward...
or postpone it as much as possible. It's one of the two.
Tae Joon will raise the children. You don't have any right.
Is there something?
It's somewhat illegal.
Let's just do our work and talk only about work.
There won't be any turning back.
I'm good at punishing people who have done wrong.
What kind of rule is that?
I found your name during Dream UCT investigation.
Did you look for my name on purpose?