You're already awake, I was worried that I might be calling too early,
What is the matter?
Well, it's about Ms Kim Hye Gyeong,
I looked into it to report to the higher-ups,
Gosh, how should I word this?
I don't care whether you two stay married or become business partners,
but you shouldn't do anything that will cause trouble later,
I halted the investigation for now,,,
and told them that you'll take care of it,
Thank you,
I'll take care of our business, so please turn a blind eye to it,
I'll be sure not to worry you,
This footage itself is quite shocking,
but his will doesn't say that it's because of pressure from work,
It could be difficult to prove it,
Bae Dong Joon has been mistreated ever since,,,
he refused to be laid off,
He worked alone by the bathroom for seven months,
He even saw a psychiatrist because of depression,
We haven't heard anything from the company, right?
No, no words from them yet,
They said they'd be in touch some time this morning,
but they haven't, Does it mean they want to take it to court?
They must be busy calculating, This isn't just about Mr Bae,
Eight employees didn't give in to the company's pressure,,,
to make them voluntarily resign, and seven of them sued the company,
And one of them committed suicide just before the trial,
This is a big headache for the company, too, They'll try to settle,
If every single one of them go up on the stand,,,
and reveal what the company did to lay them off,
the company's brand image will be ruined completely,
How about we choose Mr Bae's wife as our first witness?
She can testify immediately after we play the footage,
That can boost the number of articles about the case,,,
and make the company become more inclined to settle,
Has she seen this footage, though?
No, she just know that the footage exists,
Then it's a little,,,
I'll try to persuade her,
They have three children, and she's a stay-at-home mum,
She must need money,
Also, she probably doesn't want her husband's death to be buried away,
We must be forceful from the get-go in order to make the company,,,
apologise and give proper compensation,
I think that's the best thing we can do,,,
for the late Mr Bae as well as his children,
- Mum, answer my call - I'm sorry,
- Mum - It must be your kids, Answer it,
Hye Gyeong has gotten quite aggressive,
Isn't that what you wanted?
I didn't mean it in a bad way,
We must think carefully when we choose clients,
But once we decide, we should do whatever it takes to win,
In that sense, she is doing very well,
That is true,
but you can't stop once you cross the line,
We'll be like, "Just a little more," Then we'll ruin our reputation,
Are you talking about yourself?
We still have a long way to go, It's too early to worry,
The former director, Yun Jeong Ki, who fled to the States got,,,
in touch through his lawyer to say that he wants to return to Korea,
He wants favourable arrangements in return for files,,,
about the Dream UCT slush funds,
What should we do?
But isn't it illegal to bargain for a lighter sentence?
What in the world are you talking about?
Shall we stop the investigation, then?
He'll be sentenced to five years in prison upon landing in Korea,
Will you come back if you were him?
Joon Ho,
We're dealing with scums here,
There's only one mistake we can make,
It's being clumsy and letting criminals walk away,
Okay,
Also, Congressman Kim basically notified us,,,
that he'd respond to the subpoena after his term,
Tell the media about the investigation on him,
especially things about money and his women problems,
Keep doing it until he volunteers to show up in court,
Sure,
All right, Let's begin,
Oh, there's one more thing,
I looked into Law Firm MJ and there is something fishy,
Seo Joong Won does run a lawyers' baseball team,
and it's also true that the firm won almost every case,,,
which the team's judges were in charge of,
How should we approach this?
We don't have any firm evidence, though,
We can't really start investigating just based on our suspicions,
We could get on the wrong side of the judges, too,
You have a point, too,
However, we can't just bury our suspicions,
Pick out a few suspicious cases that Joong Won has worked on,
Then get in touch with him and see what he says about them,
Yes, Sir,
We heard from the company,
They said they needed more time to finalise their settlement offers,
They'll send their legal representative at 6pm,
That's great, That means they want to settle,
Well, Dan looked into who their lawyer is and,,,
Lawyer Son Dong Wook?
I'm sure he charges a lot,
Exactly, If they wanted to settle, they wouldn't have hired him,
We'll need to talk to him to find out,
All right, I'll be back soon,
Mum, answer my call
Where are you now?
I'm just having some food,
When can you be back?
If I leave now, it'll take about 30 minutes,
Okay, Hurry up,
Yes, Seo Yeon,
Mum, It's my friend's birthday today,
Can I skip the academy today to go to the party?
All right, Go ahead,
Wait, Which friend is this?
Soo Jin, Han Soo Jin,
The one you met at the English camp?
Yes,
I'll think about it, Let's talk when I get home, Okay?
All right,
Yes, President Seo,
Where are you now?
Oh, I was having lunch with Lawyer Seo,
Okay, Come back to the office as quickly as you can,
Okay, I will,
(The Good Wife) Synced & ripped by kurirmalam\NSubtitles by VIU
Oh, you're here, I'm sorry,
I was just reviewing the case,
You can't prove anything with this,
There's no evidence that Mr Bae's suicide was because of the company,
It's nice to meet you again, Lawyer Kim,
It's good to see you again, Have a seat,
Lawyer Son, it's been a while,
Hello,
Shall we talk about the settlement terms right away?
Sure,
The company laid off 150 employees in the last year,
Mr Bae Dong Joon was one of the people who held out against it,
They are not layoffs, It's voluntary redundancy,
Only those who agreed on the terms left the company,
It's 100 percent legal,
"Do you want a severance pay equal to three months' salary,,,"
"or do you want to be terminated with nothing at all?"
Do you call threatening employees like this legal?
The company never kicked anyone out,
Everyone who refused the company's offer got to stay,
They were bullied and harassed until they chose to leave,
They were forced to move by the bathroom,
They weren't given any tasks, so they had to just sit all day,
They couldn't even use the bathroom freely,
Penalty points were given when they used the bathroom over three times,
When the penalty points reached a certain level, they had to go,,,
to the training centre and practise greeting,
That's impossible, I'm sure they got trained on other things, too,
You're defending a company that has a lot of money but no conscience,
The high-ups who are responsible for the company's loss weren't fired,
They're trying to create profit through the layoffs,
Lawyers should refrain from judging such values,
Here are our conditions,
Mr Bae's family will get 200,000 dollars,
The others in the class action suit,,,
can continue to work as contract employees,
Contract?
It'll be renewed annually,
They'll be paid 1,5 times more,
We can't accept those terms,
Then I'll see you in court,
All rise,
It is so unfortunate,,,
to see you both again,
Can we please not let it get too messy this time?
That's a warning, not a request,
You don't have to worry,
I only took this case when I heard,,,
you'd be presiding,
Really?
I know you're fair and just,
I agree,
Hearing you both say that,,,
scares me even more,
My husband,,,
was under a lot of stress at work,
He said no one gave him any work to do,
He said they did all they could to make him resign,
But,,,
we had loans,,,
and tuition to pay,
What little severance pay he'd get wouldn't be enough,
I told him,,,
to try,,,
to keep the job,
I had no idea he was,,,
that distressed,
I feel so guilty,
That's all,
Will you cross-examine the witness?
Yes,
First of all, I offer my condolences,
I can only guess,,,
what you went through before deciding to testify,
However, we are in court,
So forgive me for the questions I must ask,
- Okay, - Your husband,
Was he seeing a psychiatrist?
Yes,
At first, he was slightly forgetful,
Then he'd gaze into the distance,,,
and get angry over trivial matters,
I found out later on that,,,
it was around the time his desk was moved near the bathroom,
They did that so everyone could see him,
My husband,,,
had worked loyally for over 10 years,
Was he diagnosed with depression?
Yes,
I am physically disabled,,,
and I also almost had depression,
I found out then that,,,
depression has no exact cause,
Biochemistry, your genes and the environment,,,
all come together to trigger depression,
You can't contribute it to one,,,
Objection,
The defence is distracting the court,
This case is about a company's unfair treatment,,,
that led to a man's suicide,
The plaintiff has a point,
I don't like where you're going,
Your Honour, I'm not trying to distract anyone,
I'm trying to prove Mr Bae could've died over something else,
Please let me continue,
Okay then, Continue,
Thank you,
Was your husband treated for depression?
Yes, He did his best to,,,
What was he prescribed?
Did he take his medication?
Yes, I don't remember what the medicine was called,
but he never forgot to take the medicine the doctor gave him,
However, the stress he got at work was just too much,
He couldn't sleep at night,
Thank you,
It was Elvatil,
That's what he was prescribed,
Was Mr Bae,,,
aware of the medication's side effects?
Objection,
Lawyer Kim's in court,
I'm not here to see her,
We should've met for a meal after the lawsuit,
I'm always here,
You have a lovely office,
My mother always told me to be a lawyer,
That way, I could make millions,,,
in comfort,
So why are you a prosecutor?
I couldn't stand watching criminals,,,
get away with it,
Do you understand how I feel?
No, I'm a lawyer,
I'm investigating judges for giving and taking bribes,
And your brother's name keeps popping up,
I'm giving you a heads-up before I begin,,,
because of the relationship I have with this firm,
That's such a comfort to hear,
So what?
I want to help,,,
your brother,
But,,,
once I find something on him, I can't cover it up,
Joong Won manages a baseball team for legal professionals,
Many judges are on his team,
We believe,,,
he introduces judges to wealthy entrepreneurs,,,
where they exchange money,,,
for shorter sentences,
Prosecutors assume that no one is innocent,
That's why I'm a lawyer,
I believe you are blameless,
Why?
I don't, actually,
I can't be sure of anything until the investigation's over,
One who looks innocent,,,
could be guilty,
The one who looked guilty,,,
could be innocent,
Tell Joong Won that,,,
if he's guilty,
he must tell me,
If he confesses now,,,
and names the judges he bribed,
I'll cut him a deal,
And if he's innocent?
Then,,,
I will apologise,
Lawyer Son defended Elvatil's manufacturer,,,
in a lawsuit where he insisted there were no side effects,
I'm aware of that, I was the presiding judge,
But now, he's saying the death of my client,,,
can be linked to the drug's side effect,
He has no moral scruples whatsoever,
That is not true,
I did defend them in court,
but MRG, Elvatil's manufacturer, admitted there were side effects,,,
and settled out of court,
They even took the drug off the market,
What I did,,,
was justified and is neither ethically nor legally wrong,
Then Mr Bae's family should sue MRG as well,
They're a victim of Elvatil's side effects,
They can do that,
I don't defend MRG any more,
Your Honour, I would like to submit new evidence,
What is it?
It's a footage of an experiment that proves Elvatil causes,,,
violent and suicidal behaviours,
- Ob,,, - Objection,
We took this footage for the Elvatil case,
I know that, I saw it, too,
Are you saying the video you took is not applicable,,,
just because it's a different case?
Lawyer Son has a point,
I accept the evidence,
We need something else,
Something that proves the company drove Mr Bae to suicide,
Won't we find something on their security footage?
It's all gone,
They had a problem with the server or whatever,
We only have footage of the suicide because,,,
we got it right away thinking it was murder,
What about the prosecution?
Won't they have other tapes?
They could,
but would they hand them over?
Lawyer Kim,
I was very disappointed,
How dare you make the widow watch her husband kill himself?
Are you saying you can do anything but I cannot?
You have a reputation to keep,
Lawyer Kim followed my orders,
Then I guess,,,
that means she's still,,,
the sweet, kind and gentle lawyer,
What a relief,
I'll see you soon in court,
Why did you say that?
We did what we should to win the law,,,
It's obvious,,,
what he'd do if I said it was your idea,
He'd have alerted the media and said you were corrupt,
To a lawyer, his or her reputation,,,
is very important,
Remember that,
Why say you gave the order if it's that important?
That's what I'm like,
President Seo,
Can we have a word?
I'm speaking with a bank representative,
He came over when I said I was too busy,
- If you have anything,,, - Right now,
Should I sign here?
- Yes, right there, - Okay,
What is it?
Tae Joon came by when you were out,
I thought he was going to thank us for getting him out,
but then,
he said he'd investigate you,
He'll offer a deal if you confess,
The bribery charges?
Don't worry, I did nothing wrong,
I'll be fine,
Don't say that to me,
Stop seeing her,
Who?
Hye Gyeong,
Don't you see why he's doing this?
It's because you're dating his wife,,,
and he's looking for a reason to come after you,
So stop it,
I,,,
No,
We're serious,
Hye Gyeong will leave him soon,
I understand,
You two are serious,
I'm sure there's a reason to be,
But it's just not wise,
You're Hye Gyeong's superior,,,
and Tae Joon is everyone's favourite prosecutor,
This will ruin not just you but our law firm,
We fought hard to protect it,
Must you ruin it yourself?
I'll help you,
With Tae Joon,
Why do you want to help?
I don't like him, either,
I'll meet Joon Ho and see if he has evidence,,,
or if it's an empty threat,
Thanks, Just a moment,
Can you do something else while you're at it?
I need the security footage the prosecution has,
You always put your cases first,
Okay,
Why did you call?
To ask you something,
Do you know we took a class action suit?
- Yes, - We need footage from the day,,,
Mr Bae died,
Great,
I had a question for you, too,
- What is it? - It's not too hard,
Don't make that face,
We're investigating Joong Won,
Really? For what?
For bribing judges,
We're going over all his cases,
Is it bad?
Yes, pretty bad,
That's why,,,
I need the internal files on the cases,,,
he has worked on,
Let's swap that with what you want,
Then give me the names,,,
of the judges you suspect first,
President Seo worked on so many cases,
I can't get them all,
Here are the court dates and the names of the judges,
You came prepared,,,
and you wanted to balk?
Just in case,
I think you settled in pretty well,
I'm fighting to survive,
Call me when you're ready,
Still at work?
Yes,
I should head home,
What about dinner?
I'm eating with the kids,
I've been going home late,
Shall I join you?
They came by a few times and I never got to say hi,
Getting to know them over dinner,,,
could be good for us,
Well,,,
I'm sure I'll make a good impression,
I know that,
But right now,,, The timing's,,,
Thanks for offering,
Okay, Next time, then,
She lives in Seowon?
Do you have to go that far?
Is it about Soo Jin's brother?
He was jailed for a misdemeanour,
He's a model prisoner and will be out soon,
That's not an issue,
Even your father did time,
I'm just,,,
worried that you only get along,,,
with people who live far away,
You never have school friends over,,,
or go out to see them,
You can't just avoid them,
You have to try to get along,
How can I do that?
Here,,,
everyone knows who Dad is,
Do I have to give up on a friend I've finally made?
Okay then,
Don't be too late,
If you think you'll be late, call and I'll pick you up,
I have it,
The list of cases they think you bribed the judges over,
It's quite long,
Only 1 or 2 will be the real targets,
They gave you a long list,,,
in case you betray them,
Did you really bribe a judge?
No,
But I can see why these cases,,,
are the targets,
Tell me everything, I said I'd help,
Thank you,
Give me the internal records of those case files,
I said I'd swap those for the security footage,
They'll take it by whatever means possible,
It's best to hand them over and win your case,
Dan,
You will help, right?
There better be no tricks,
Did you take anything out or add anything?
Look who's talking,
You duped me once before,
No, that wasn't me,
That's everything we have,
I didn't delete a single file,
Call if you need anything else,
I'm up for a deal if the conditions are right,
You're Ji Hoon, right?
Yes,
Hello,
My name is Seo Joong Won, I'm your mum's boss,
Yes, I know,
I heard that you're here to fix her computer,
You must know a lot about computers,
No, just a little,
It was infected with something called "ransomware",
It disables files inside the computer,,,
and asks for money in return for a removal software,
Gosh, I don't understand anything you just said,
Your mum was going on about how smart you are, You must be good,
No, It wasn't anything too complicated,
Well, I should go now,
- You're leaving already? - Yes,
Shall I treat you to something delicious?
No, it's okay,
- Goodbye, Sir, - Bye,
I'm going through the security camera footage,
There are many parts that show how the company harassed the employees,
However, none of them are impactful enough for us to use in court,
Nothing can serve as pertinent evidence for the suicide, either,
Collect everything, though, They might lead to something,
I actually have one question,
Other employees sued the company together,
but this woman chose not to participate,
I can't really see her name from here, but,,,
Her name is Noh Eun Ah,
She quit just before they sued the company,
She visited our firm a few times with her colleagues,
but she gave up just before they filed the suit,
Why?
I don't know,
It'd help us to have more employees in this case,
so we tried to get in touch with her through her colleagues,
However, she hung up as soon as she heard the word "law firm",
She refuses to meet with us, either,
I'll go meet her,
She won't see you,
Don't worry, I can make it work,
The car with the licence number 1780 is yours, right?
I'm so sorry, I think I scratched your car a little,
It looks like a brand new car, I'm very sorry,
I'm right in front of your place now,
Where's the scratch?
I'm from Law Firm MJ,
You're Noh Eun Ah, right?
You worked at the same company,
As you know, Mr Bae passed away,
So please help us just this once,
We just need you to answer a few questions,
Sure, go ahead,
You were friends with Mr Bae, right?
We were colleagues,
Did you know that he was on antidepressants?
The company is insisting that the medication's side effects,,,
are what made him commit suicide,
You mean Elvatil?
Yes, You even know the name,
Of course, Many people died because of that drug,
I heard it makes people become violent and have suicidal thoughts,
There was a lawsuit regarding it recently,
Dong Joon wasn't on that drug,
How do you know?
I saw it on the news and told him,,,
about how a lawsuit would commence soon because people died,
He thanked me and said that he was thinking about taking it,
Would you be able to say this in court?
Gosh, no way,
You said you're just here to ask a few questions,
I cannot go to the trial,
If you make me go, I'll say that I don't know anything about it,
Where do you work now?
What do you mean?
You quit, so I'm just wondering if you've found a new job,
Of course, I did,
My new job is all right,
Why are you at home during a weekday afternoon, then?
It's none of your business,
I'm just asking because I'm curious to know how you were able,,,
to afford a new car after giving up the lawsuit and quitting your job,
Someone died, He was your friend,
No, your former colleague,
You must've read all the articles about the incident,
The prosecution is immensely interested in the case,
If you don't answer now,
I might ask the prosecution to start investigating,,,
the relationship between you and the company,
It's accounting fraud,
The company's financial situation must've been worse than we thought,
They've been hiding a loss of over 300 million dollars through it,
How did you find out about this?
Noh Eun Ah told me, She found out while reviewing accounting files,
So high-ups in the company bought her off and made her leave,
Bringing up their accounting fraud,,,
will increase our chances of winning in court,
but it'll make the company collapse,
Then our clients won't be able to get a single penny from them,
We need to turn a blind eye to the fraud,,,
if we want our clients to be compensated,
What should we do now?
Should we choose social justice or our clients' profit?
What do you think, Hye Gyeong?
We'd like Noh Eun Ah to be our witness,
Your Honour, Ms Noh isn't in their witness list,
We have the right to ask anyone who was on the company's,,,
layoff list to be our witness,
Noh Eun Ah was on that list,,,
and she resigned one week after Mr Bae's death,
Is Ms Noh here?
Yes, she is,
I accept your request,
Ms Noh, please proceed to the stand,
Your Honour, we'd like to request a short recess,
We weren't expecting this, so we are not prepared to examine her,
Wouldn't it be better to listen to her testimony,,,
and take a recess after?
That way, it'll be better for you to plan your examination,
I'd like to consult with the opposing counsel during the recess,
Prosecutor Lee Tae Joon,
Do you think this will change anything?
What are you talking about?
I'm just investigating suspicious matters I've stumbled upon,
Lawyer Seo, Admit it if you're guilty,
If not, just continue doing what you're doing now,
I didn't do anything wrong,
You're the one who is guilty,
You were always the problem,
Hye Gyeong would've been much happier if it weren't for you,
You mean if she was with you?
Do you think her life would've been better with you?
Do you really think so?
Just punch me,
Be a man, all right?
That's much better than being in this mess,
If you bribed a judge,
you must get locked up in prison,
Only one of us,,,
has experienced what it's like to be locked up in jail,
I'll see you at the trial, then,
Let's say that the company was engaged in accounting fraud,
It is true, We also have a witness,
But you won't be able to reveal it because your clients,,,
won't get any compensations if you do,
Does that mean the company has decided to compensate them?
If the amount is right, yes,
However, the company can't pay too much because it can't,,,
be held responsible for what happened,
The main shareholders won't be okay with it,
500,000 dollars per each employee who sued,
One million dollars for the late Mr Bae's family as an apology,
Aren't the amounts appropriate?
Did you not hear what I just said?
The chairman can use his own money,
He should volunteer to do so to apologise to his employees,
And why should the chairman do that?
If he doesn't do so, he'll be locked up in prison,
We'll tell the media about the fraud if we can't settle today,
If we lose, we won't get a single penny anyway,
We should at least fight for justice in that case,
The amounts you've suggested seem appropriate,
I'll speak to the chairman about it,
Don't be too disappointed,
Are you going to laugh again?
Are you going to stay at this firm?
What do you mean by that?
Come to my firm,
I'll pay you double of what you get now,
You don't even know how much I get paid now,
That doesn't matter,
You're worth every penny,
It's not because of your husband,
It's because I think you have the potential to become a great lawyer,
However, that won't happen at this firm,
We won the case against you, Do you still think it's impossible?
Do you think I lost?
I guess we paid up more than we expected,
Lawyer Kim,
You're maturing fast, It's so entertaining,
(Missed Calls)
(Seo Yeon)
The number you're calling is currently not available,
(Voice mail)
First message,
Hello?
Ji Hoon, are you with Seo Yeon?
No, I'm home, Why?
I missed a call from her when I was working,
I think she went to the academy,
She probably called you by accident, She does that sometimes,
All right, Tell her to call me when she gets home,
Okay,
Bye,
I heard you guys settled, Good job,
Thank you,
Should we grab some food to celebrate?
Sure,
Let's try this first,
I haven't practised in so long,
We're getting together next week,
They might end up changing my number,
Aren't you guys doing it as a hobby? You must be about the same,
No, we're all different, It depends on how much we practise,
The player number is really important,
It reflects our ability in an objective way,
They say it's random,
but the number really gets to you,
You must be the last number on the team or maybe the bench,
Are you provoking me?
You know you look down on me these days, right?
What are you talking about, Sir?
No way,
My goodness, Me?
Fine, How about a bet, then?
If I hit seven times or more in one game, I win,
Otherwise, you win,
Deal,
How about granting a wish?
No, that won't do,
What if that wish is to get 100 wishes?
Since we're lawyers,
let's just bet on a meal to be sure,
Fine, Today's lunch, The price doesn't matter,
Deal,
Foul,
You're killing it,
Joong Won,
You said that you wanted to be a better person when with me, right?
Yes,
When I'm with you, I think I become my true self,
I'm sorry I missed your call,
Why aren't you picking up, Seo Yeon?
I'm worried so give me a call back,
What do you want to eat?
Order for me,
He's bluffing,
He's making things up after losing the case,
I can't tell,
He looked quite sincere,
Maybe I'm bad at reading people,
Are you waiting for a call?
Well,,,
I just can't get in touch with Seo Yeon,
Really?
Ji Hoon, did Seo Yeon call?
No,
Is she still not picking up?
Maybe her phone broke,
Anyway, tell her to call me when she gets in,
Okay,
She's still out of reach?
Yes, I'm sure it's nothing,
but it's bothering me,
Right, Can we stop by at her academy? It's around here,
Which way is it?
Seo Yeon?
I saw her leave with some guy on a motorcycle,
A man? What kind of guy?
He looked a little older than us,
He was average height and had short hair,
- Right? - Yes,
Did they look like they knew each other?
We thought so,
Isn't it her brother?
Do you have anyone in mind?
No,
Let me call Tae Joon, Thank you,
- Bye, - Bye,
Yes, hello?
Did you get any calls from Seo Yeon?
No, why?
She's out of reach,
Apparently, she was last seen leaving with a guy on a motorcycle,
A motorcycle? With a guy?
Yes,
I'm not sure,
but they say he looked a few years older than her,
Can you think of anyone?
Did Seo Yeon say anything?
Did she talk about her friends?
I heard that her new friend from camp has an older brother,
She told me she was going to see her on the weekend,
It's probably nothing much,
They must be friends,
Don't worry too much, I'll look into it,
Call me if you find her,
Okay,
- Prosecutor Park, - Yes,
Come here,
I received a call from my wife,,,
and she says Seo Yeon is out of reach,
Pardon?
I'm sure it's nothing, but you never know,
Well,,,
I need you to track her phone,,,
and get a list of the call records to find out where she is,
But it'll take 3 to 4 hours if we go through the procedure,
Okay, I'd appreciate it, Please do it as soon as possible,
Yes, Sir,
Thank you,
She'll be fine, don't worry, Let's look for her together,
It's okay, I'll go wait for her at home,
I'll drive you home,
It's okay, I can go by myself,
Don't worry, I'm sure she's fine, Bye,
Let me ask you for a favour, It's for Hye Gyeong,
Give me Seo Yeon's number,
It's me, Can you help me track a number?
Are you crazy? How can you ask me that after all this time?
Please, I'll do you a favour in return,
- Mum, you're early, - Yes,
What about Seo Yeon?
She's not home yet,
I just sent it to you, That's the last location it was tracked,
Thank you,
Did you find her?
Prosecutor Lee,
The thing is,
Seo Jin has a friend named Han Soo Jin and her brother,,,
is a kid you arrested before,,,
for assault,
He was given an overnight release from the juvenile hall today,
He's currently missing,
However, he was considered a model prisoner,
He got himself a hair stylist certification,,,
and he doesn't talk to any of his past friends,
I don't care about that,
Report it as an emergency,,,
and find out where Seo Yeon is right now,
Yes, Sir,
(Beauty Supplies)
The number you're calling is currently not available,
Is that you, Seo Yeon?
Is she not back yet?
No,
Don't worry, I'm sure she's fine,
I have people looking for her,
Do you think Mum's really mad?
I'm not sure,
It was just for a few hours,
My friend's brother was released today and he promised,,,
to perm our hair for the birthday party tomorrow,
I didn't call her,
I think I pressed it by accident when it was in my pocket,
You don't have to explain to me,
Don't worry, I'm sure she isn't mad at you,
She'll be happy to see you,
Aren't you coming in?
No, I'll just go,
She'll want to thank you,
And I'm scared to go up alone,
Can't you come up with me to explain?
You should tell her yourself, You have to,
Also, don't tell her I found you,
Just say that you came home on your own,
Why?
Just because,
Thank you,
Seo Yeon,
Mum,
Gosh,
I'm sorry, Mum, I didn't know you called,
Let me see,
It's okay as long as nothing happened,
- Seo Yeon! - Dad,
Where have you been,,,
Are you all right?
- Where have you been? - Sorry, Dad,
I was so worried,
- You scared me, - Sorry,,,
Dan,
What are your thoughts on marriage?
Something other people do, but you and I don't,
Why do you ask?
I was jealous of Hye Gyeong's family,
I thought, "It'd be nice for me to have people like them,"
People who,,,
care for me more than I do myself,
No,
"I want to be,,,"
"with the people that I love,,,"
"more than myself,"
Do you think I can't?
No, You can get married if you want to,
What exactly do you want?
Is it just a marriage or a marriage with a specific someone?
I'm not sure,
I'd want Hye Gyeong,
then I'd ask myself if what I'm doing is wrong,
I have my sister and the law firm,
I'm not sure if I should fight against Lee Tae Joon,
I don't know what to do,
I don't know if I'm a coward,,,
or too practical,
I don't know,,,
if I can give up on everything,
Do you even know,,,
what Lawyer Kim wants?
I don't know that either,
You should ask her that first,
I'm sure Lawyer Kim,,,
would want you to tell her,,,
what you really want, too,
Thank you for today,
Hye Gyeong,
Can't you reconsider,,,
for the kids?
Not today,
Don't talk about your greed today,
It's been a long day,
Goodnight,
Going down,
Yes, Ma'am,
I'm sorry to call you so late,
Can we meet?
Well,,,
I'm sorry, but I can't leave home tonight,
I'm in your neighbourhood,
Hello,
I thought about this a lot,
I wasn't sure if I should talk to you about this,
However,
I think that you should know,
The prosecution is investigating Joong Won,
They will charge him after gathering evidence,
Even if he gets lucky and doesn't go under trial,
it'll be a huge hit to the firm,
What is he charged for?
For bribing judges,
Could it be,,,
Tae Joon?
I don't want to force you,
I want to respect your private life,
However, you need,,,
to make clear choices,
Okay, I understand,
Are you here to visit me?
Did something happen?
No, I just have something to give to you,
It's on your desk,
Yes,
I heard Seo Yeon is fine,
Yes, thankfully,
I'm sorry,
About what?
About Seo Yeon,
I don't think I was of any help,
No,
Nothing happened,
But even if something did,
it wouldn't be anyone's fault,
I thought about it all night,
All of the reasons why I should break up with you,
My family, my husband and my career,
However, I wasn't a part of it,
I don't want to lie to myself and give up on my feelings any more,
I want to be with you if it's all right with you,
(Divorce by Mutual Consent)
(Lee Tae Joon, Kim Hye Gyeong)
(The Good Wife)
Will Lee Tae Joon prosecute Joong Won?
Have you made your decision?
An investigation on President Seo Joong Won?
President Seo,
They say Law Firm MJ fabricated the evidence for the divorce,
It's the case when you first started work here,
Don't you remember?
Are you suspecting me?
I won't let it pass if you or Hye Gyeong damages our image,
I believe this is the best decision I've ever made in my life,