I looked up your records.
I was wondering why you registered late as a lawyer,
and I found out that you had a car accident before.
I'll take care of you until the end.
All you have to do is trust me. Got it?
I know you started work late because of me.
Good work.
That's when...
My leg also became like this.
Can you define one's feelings?
I love Lee Tae Joon,
but I also hate him. My feelings change every day.
Are my feelings that important to you?
Are you that curious?
What is it? Do you have something to say?
What is it?
Dad, take a look at this. It's weird.
I'm not sure. I captured it from the front of our house.
Ji Hoon, what are you doing in Dad's room?
Coming.
Take a look and we can talk about it later.
You're not having breakfast?
No. See you later.
Good morning.
Can you bring me the files I asked for?
Sure.
This is Lee Tae Joon's trial record,
and this is the investigation record.
These files were not open for review so I had trouble getting them.
The prosecutors' office says that it could affect other cases.
Luckily, I found some photographs that weren't released during trial.
It's on the last page.
- Thank you. - Why did you want these anyway?
Is it because of Lawyer Kim?
I have to review something regarding Dokwang Development.
I see. Okay.
Dan.
- Did you work with Prosecutor Lee? - Yes.
What is he like?
He's smart, hearty and loyal.
He has a lot of friends.
He's like the big brother type.
That's more positive than I thought you'd say.
He always had to have what he wanted.
Whether that's an investigation, a person or information. All of it.
That's why he had a lot of enemies.
I like it.
- Like what? - The apartment.
It reminds me of the time when we were newly-weds. It's cozy.
It's half the size. At least the kids were smaller then.
What is it? Do you miss our old place?
No.
Yes, sometimes.
It feels more strange than I expected...
to see you off to work while I stay home.
Shouldn't you help with housework?
What should I do? Dishes?
Shall I do the dishes?
By the way,
did Eun Sook say anything else?
I must have acted impatiently.
Sang Il wiretapped your phone.
- What? - That's all she knows.
You figure out the rest.
Whatever you do, don't harm us any more.
Where shall I put these?
Please put them here.
You look very tired.
I have quite a lot of work these days.
How's your husband?
He's the same.
But he tries to be more careful than before.
Lawyer Kim, you should still show no mercy.
Once you start being forgiving since he's your children's father...
after all,
tragedy will start again.
There are many men out there who are handsome and strong.
If you'd like, I can introduce you to some.
I'm too busy with meetings with Cho Guk Hyun.
What do you think of President Seo Joong Won?
He's nice and sexy.
We're just friends.
He's the only one I have left.
- Lawyer Kim. - Yes?
You have a guest waiting outside.
He seemed like your son.
Really?
He seemed to be in shock.
Ma'am.
Hello, Jae Yeol.
Hello.
Hi. You've grown a lot.
What brings you here?
I have a problem.
I was hoping you'd help me.
What I mean is,
as a lawyer.
(The Good Wife)
I need the passcode to look.
Let's talk later after you take a look.
Tae Joon, do you remember me at the hospital?
I'm Seo Joong Won.
Yes, it's good to see you again.
I can help you only if you tell me what's going on.
I saw it in a drama that between a lawyer and a client...
What was it called?
Attorney-client privilege?
Right. Yes.
Whatever you tell me,
I'll have to keep it confidential.
Otherwise, my license as a lawyer will be removed.
You can tell me honestly.
Actually, Dong Hyun suggested we should steal the test papers.
He said he knew where the key to the test papers' cabinet was.
You and Dong Hyun?
Is this the Dong Hyun that I know?
We were just joking around. I was planning to just go home,
but the teacher's lounge was unlocked.
I was on the lookout, but the security came.
That was unlucky.
Did someone get hurt?
No, I ran away as soon as I saw the security,
but there were police cars at the school the next morning.
Dong Hyun didn't answer his phone.
Tell everything to your mum and ask for forgiveness at school.
Don't make it worse. Just do as I say.
Dan, may I ask you for a favour?
Your son doesn't take after you at all.
He isn't my son.
Someone reported to the police at Sosang High School last night.
Could you find out what's going on?
Who is he?
I know his mother. Thank you.
Yes?
Do you have time?
Come in.
My friend's son came to see me.
He said he got into trouble.
Does he need a lawyer?
No, it's not that.
May I give him a ride back home?
Ms Kim Hye Gyeong.
I know what you're going to say. I'll do my best from now on.
I'll do my tasks the best I can and look for clients.
I feel bad just sending him home when he came to see me here.
Fine.
I just hope you'll think about why...
you started working as a lawyer.
Okay.
- Thank you. - How's Hye Gyeong?
Is she all right at work?
She's doing very well.
She may have been too old to be selected as a new hire.
Thank you for taking care of her.
How does it feel being out?
I'm quite busy.
I'll have to get ready for trial.
Anyway, what brings you here?
Do you know President Cho Guk Hyun of Dokwang Development?
Yes, I do.
He's hired us for legal advice.
Based on the records of your case,
President Cho's name was mentioned quite a bit.
Strangely, he avoided being charged by the prosecution.
I've only met President Cho a few times...
to collect some information.
Close to him,
there was a person related to Lawyer Kim's accident in the past.
Do you remember Driver Kang Seok Beom?
Yes.
I heard President Cho helped out a lot with the settlement.
I was excited as I was finishing at Judicial Training Institute.
I regret not having to stop him.
Yes, I find it very unfortunate.
Had I been there that day,
it wouldn't have happened.
What can we do about the past?
We can't...
turn back time.
You're right.
Still, we shouldn't let the past bring us down.
You're going through a lot already.
Sir.
Please talk to President Cho.
He seemed to have a lot to say to you.
Exclude Lawyer Kim Hye Gyeong.
Have a private talk.
I'll do that.
Thank you for coming all the way here...
to give me advice.
I care a lot about Lawyer Kim.
There's no other reason.
If you're worried about the talk...
on television...
It all happened because of me.
I'm the one at fault for being absent from home.
You don't have to say any more.
So did you not go to school?
I haven't gone for a few days.
I don't like studying anyway.
You were good at school though.
It's because I studied all day and took private lessons.
I'd be a fool if I weren't.
But I've hit my limit.
I'm going to give up soon.
Aren't you giving up too soon?
It's all my mum's fault.
She knew students in that neighbourhood were studious.
My grades would have been much better in my old neighbourhood.
Don't say that. She moved all because of you.
You're too cool.
- Me? - Honestly,
Mum wouldn't have gotten along there if it weren't for you.
But she stopped contacting you after what happened.
Isn't it too cold-hearted?
Jae Yeol.
Your mum just wasn't strong enough.
Are you ready?
Yes, but...
could you talk to her first?
You're a lawyer.
You used to be cute.
- Wait, is that a diamond? - Yes.
- Wow. - Did you get another one?
- It's beautiful. - My husband...
earned 10 million dollars again from his investment.
- Again? - Really?
- Thank you for the food. - No problem.
Let me help.
No, it's okay. You should go and chat.
I'll finish this up fast and join you.
No. You've been working all by yourself.
- No, I'm okay. - Can you guys bring empty plates?
Hye Gyeong, why are you making a big deal?
We were just careful with her china, that's all.
We didn't intend on slacking off.
Here you go.
Thank you.
- Here they are. - Thank you.
No problem.
It must still be unfamiliar since you just moved.
You'll get used to it soon.
Thank you.
I'll do the dishes.
I'm really okay.
How did you get this?
You know... I know someone and they helped me get a deal.
- I want it, too. - You're lucky.
- I was surprised. - We can go together next time.
It's all about connections.
Gosh...
I want one, too.
Long time no see.
Hye Gyeong.
I was so worried about you.
I didn't call since I figured you would be busy.
I'm sorry. Are you well?
I've been busy.
- We moved and I started working. - I see.
Do you have some time right now?
- Really? - Her husband...
Hye Gyeong, can I call you later?
I'm talking with my neighbours.
I think it'll be uncomfortable for both sides. I'll call later.
It's about Jae Yeol.
It's me.
Can I see you at our place?
He's driving me crazy.
He's been making so much trouble lately...
and he doesn't study at all.
I don't know what it is, but he's going astray.
Jae Yeol is waiting outside.
He regrets what he did.
You should talk to him when you've calmed down.
I'm sorry.
I caused you so much trouble.
It's okay. I couldn't just send him away when he came to me.
By the way,
how are your kids?
It must be tough for them after what happened.
Are they being bullied or anything?
Did their marks drop?
Everyone's doing well.
Is that so?
Where's Dong Hyun's mum? She seems to be away.
She says she has something going on at home.
She texted me this morning.
Ever since you left,
she acts like she's our boss.
- About Jae Yeol... - Yes?
Actually Dong Hyun...
Hurry, come outside.
Come on, hurry up. There's trouble.
- Come on. - Hurry.
- Hurry up. - Jae Yeol!
What are you doing to my son?
What are you doing?
On what charges are you taking him?
Are you his family?
No. I'm his lawyer.
Do you have a warrant for his arrest?
It's an exigent arrest. We gave him the Miranda warning already.
- What's his charge? - Homicide.
- My goodness. - Homicide?
Mum! Mum!
Jae Yeol...
What should we do? Should we call the police?
Or do you want me to prepare a press conference first?
If we arouse the public...
by the wiretapping and breaking in,
the court will also be pressured.
Do you think we can prove...
that the prosecutors' office did this?
No, it won't be easy.
It'll become a huge scandal.
I think it would be better to leak information about a politician...
or a prosecutor you were investigating on.
That will be enough to turn the tables around.
Prosecutor Choi Sang Il...
will spread the recording from the illegal wiretapping to the media.
It'll be a dirty fight.
We'll both be disclosing each other's secrets.
We'll still have the upper hand.
They will be more pressured than us.
What if it's not the prosecutors' office?
Who else would do that?
I'm home.
You're here.
I got this a few days before you were released.
Do you think it's Cho Guk Hyun's doing?
Who else would record such a thing?
Right. One more.
This came first.
Is that really you?
Ji Hoon.
That's not me.
I swear. I never did that.
Someone's trying to break our family apart.
They fabricated the photos.
Ji Hoon.
I would have been fooled if it wasn't for you.
It's thanks to you that I got this chance.
Thank you.
Okay?
Also, this is just between the two of us.
Mum might misunderstand if she finds out.
When the ambulance arrived, he was already dead.
Jae Yeol told me he ran away as soon as he saw the guard.
How can you believe what he says? He even dropped out of school.
He didn't drop out. He just missed a few days.
Also, we all go through puberty.
You must know him well.
His mother and I were the closest when I lived there.
Then again, she was the first to stop calling after what happened.
Life is full of betrayals.
You betray others and others betray you, too.
You should get used to it.
In the police report, it says that the security guard...
found Jae Yeol when he sneaked into the teachers' room.
Jae Yeol.
Hey.
- Who's there? - Run, run!
Jae Yeol pushed the security guard down while fleeing.
The security guard had a cerebral haemorrhage as he hit his head.
And the kid fled.
Hello?
It's me. Can you come home early tonight?
There's something you should know about.
Why? What is it?
It's really important. I can't tell you over the line.
I'm doing something urgent as well.
A client was arrested for committing homicide.
We'll talk later.
You're doing well.
Ms Kim.
Ms Kim, over here.
Can I leave right now?
I can't stay here any longer.
Not now.
Did you lie to me about anything?
I really didn't know that happened to the guard.
It wasn't me.
I ran away as soon as I saw him.
Did you push him?
You shouldn't lie.
They'll check if your DNA is on the security guard's clothes.
We bumped into each other, but that's in front of the door.
You bumped into him, but that's not why he died?
Why didn't you tell her earlier?
I'm sure of it. Dong Hyun must have seen it. He was in the room.
I told you, I was going to drop out.
Why would I need the test papers?
I was only helping Dong Hyun.
Go and ask him.
Is that Kim Dong Hyun you're talking about?
- Your class president? - Yes.
Why do you ask?
He's the one who said you pushed him over.
Does Kim Dong Hyun admit that he went in to steal test papers?
He claims that he went along because he's scared of Jae Yeol.
He never wanted to steal the test papers...
and never knew where the keys were.
He says Jae Yeol went up to the teachers' room alone...
and that he stayed on the first floor.
They're blaming each other.
It doesn't seem like we'll have a good chance.
Who will people trust more? The class president or Jae Yeol?
They're well off, so they won't have any trouble paying us.
We should do our best in defending them.
Good job, Hye Gyeong.
It might get more complicated if you're personally related.
They will blame you if you lose and say they had their trust in you.
You should focus on this case for a while.
I'll take care of Dokwang Development on my own.
Actually,
I'm not on good terms with Jae Yeol's parents.
We drifted apart after what happened to my husband.
They may not hire you as their lawyer then.
That's why...
I wanted to suggest making someone else their official lawyer.
We can't help ruining the relationship during trial,
but it isn't right if our prior relationship affects the trial.
I don't understand.
If you weren't close, why did you visit Jae Yeol's house?
We aren't close any more,
but we've known each other for a while.
And I didn't know things would get this bad then.
Even if the lawyer is someone else, since I know the school and...
the neighbourhood, I'll take care of the paperwork and finding witnesses.
You want someone else to take the case while you only assist?
Yes, I think that's best for everyone.
I'll have more time to work on Dokwang Development case.
Focus on Jae Yeol's case for now.
That kid shouldn't be sent to prison.
Here you go.
About Dokwang Development...
Did I do something wrong?
No, you didn't.
Then...
is it because of Tae Joon?
Do you want me to be out because of President Cho?
It's not about that.
Dokwang Development case is yours.
I'll keep your name on the documents.
However, you should focus on the murder case.
I'll take care of the other one.
Pardon me for interrupting,
but Jae Yeol's parents are here.
Okay.
I'm sorry. I must have been sensitive.
Still, you don't need to protect me.
See you later.
- Hello. - Why are you representing my son?
Jae Yeol asked me for help.
I'll pay for what we owe you today, so let's end it soon.
Another lawyer I know will take his case, so you should leave it.
I'm probably not as experienced as the other lawyer,
but I'm confident that I care about Jae Yeol more.
I know about the school and the neighbourhood better than anyone.
I can be his best lawyer.
Still, aren't you too inexperienced?
Honey,
please listen to her.
If you can't trust me,
I'll work with another lawyer from my firm.
Would you trust us more then?
I changed the passcode.
I changed it temporarily. Let me know if you want to change it.
Why did you change the passcode? Is that why you called me today?
Dad, it's your turn.
- Hello. - Hello, Mum.
Wait a minute.
- She's doing well. - Really?
- Here I go. - One, two, one, two.
You're doing so well.
Dad, you're hitting me too much.
Come on, Seo Yeon.
You're so good.
I heard Jae Yeol is arrested for murder.
How did you know?
Our children told me...
that it was posted on their old friends' SNS.
I heard their exams have been postponed.
Can you believe that a child that we know have been...
arrested for theft and murder?
They're uneducated and greedy.
You took good care of them when they moved here.
After what happened to you,
they stopped contacting you, right?
They're no better than that.
Just consider it only as your work. They're not good for us.
Who's good for us then?
After what happened to you, everyone else turned their backs.
Our children have a father who cheated on his wife.
Who would welcome us?
That's why I'm working hard to fight...
to prove my innocence...
so that you and the children can live the way you used to.
Hye Gyeong.
Even the politicians have their eyes on us.
Once things straighten out, I can climb higher up the ladder.
We can't care for people we used to know.
You must help me.
We must trust each other and work together.
What do you want me to do?
Trust me...
like you used to.
Can we go in when they have exams?
Exams are postponed until they find out if the exams have been leaked.
It'll be easy for us to work since the students are studying.
How do you know that?
I used to live here.
I was part of the management committee of this school.
What's wrong?
I'd forgotten that you used to be a local here.
I'm not any more.
Don't we know that person?
Lawyer Kim, Dan.
Keep playing.
- Hello. - What are you doing?
I'm playing a football game. Didn't you see me score?
I played football when I was young.
That's not what I'm asking.
Why are you here?
I heard you needed a lawyer to take charge of the trial.
- Then... - Don't worry.
I worked on many student cases while at the legal aid corporation.
Not to brag, but I get along with children very well.
That's good to hear.
Let's do well.
Okay.
Other students told me that Jae Yeol was unique but not bad.
If he wasn't sleeping in class, he listened to music.
He sometimes skipped class.
He was peaceful like a plant,
but the class president was quite troublesome.
Do you know how rich and studious kids become bullies these days?
His grades were getting worse these days,
which was his motive for stealing the test papers.
Did the students tell you all that?
Did you see me play football?
They tell me everything when I ask them while playing sports.
I think you got the answers you wanted to hear.
No, they're helpful to us.
Joon Ho,
will you argue that Dong Hyun persuaded Jae Yeol to steal?
Yes, why would Jae Yeol have a reason to steal the test papers?
He said he'd quit school anyway.
It was all planned by Dong Hyun.
We should argue that Dong Hyun tripped the security...
which led to his death.
Isn't that too extreme?
We should defend Jae Yeol instead of...
All the blame will fall on him.
He might even go to prison.
Are you all right with ruining his life?
Don't worry. I'll take care of it.
You called me because you can't do things like this.
Aren't you Dong Hyun?
I'm Ji Hoon's mum.
Have you been well?
Can we talk for a moment?
He...
told everything to the police.
If you have questions,
ask the police.
It's been a long time.
Right.
It's our first time after your husband went to prison.
You must be struggling these days, taking on a case like this.
I couldn't ignore the situation Jae Yeol was in.
Come on, it's not like we don't know each other...
You used to be good at meddling in...
other people's business, but unfortunately,
this isn't some issue at a PTA meeting you can solve.
I'm trying to give them a chance...
to solve things instead of making them worse.
Why would you give them a chance?
Do you still think that problems will be solved and others will be...
happy as long as you try hard?
You should take care of your husband instead.
We'll take care of ourselves.
(Kim Dong Hyun)
Court file number 2016137.
The accused Jung Jae Yeol, please come in.
- Jae Yeol. - Jae Yeol.
Jae Yeol.
Detective, please tell us what you found when you reached the school.
When I arrived after getting the report,
the ambulance was packing up.
Kim Dong Hyun and the corpse were at the scene.
What did Dong Hyun say?
He told me he went inside to steal test papers with his friend.
I arrested him on the scene and took him to the station.
That means he admitted to his attempt of theft.
That's correct.
In your experience, are such confessions most often true?
Yes. If they're in their teens,
they tend to say the truth...
when there isn't enough time to make up a story.
That's all.
Counsel, do you have any questions?
Detective.
Well...
One moment, please. Let me check something first.
He never mentioned Jae Yeol during the time of his arrest.
I know.
Detective. When Kim Dong Hyun confessed about the crime,
did he mention who pushed the victim?
He told me that information the morning after.
That must mean that he had enough time to come up...
with a new story.
He told me he was hesitant to betray his friend.
That's all.
It's still pretty good for your first trial.
Lawyer Kim.
Don't act as if you're my superior.
I'd like to call Kim Dong Hyun to testify as witness.
Dong Hyun. Can you tell us what happened that night?
Jae Yeol told me he wanted to drop out of school...
and wanted to show me something.
He asked me to come to school at night,
but I never imagined he would be stealing test papers.
I thought he might beat me if I didn't go.
I had no choice.
Hey, it was your idea! You asked me to help!
Hey. Tell them the truth.
- You told me to do it. - No, you did.
This scum made me do it!
He's the one who made me!
- You better not lie. - Silence.
- Silence! - Tell the truth.
- You made me do it. - No, you did!
Defendant, silence!
How was the trial?
It was a mess.
There was some trouble during witness interrogation.
I'll be taking over now.
Did Joon Ho do something wrong?
I'm not blaming him.
He tried his best. He worked hard to prepare for it.
I tried to help him as well,
but it just didn't go well.
Why would you help him? I sent him so you could crush him.
It's your chance to show everyone that you're better than him.
He only had settlement cases until now. This is his first trial.
You can really shine in a case like this.
That's why I sent Joon Ho.
Show him what you got...
while helping your client.
What about Jae Yeol?
That boy will be sentenced for murder at such a young age.
Do we want our political fight to add onto their mums' dispute?
I know you always try to solve things in a positive light,
but do you think it'll be possible again this time?
I should try at least.
Nothing will change even if you put in so much effort.
Joon Ho would never be thankful to you.
No. Actually, he would hate it.
You won't change your mind?
Just ignore it. I'll see what I can do.
I want to try.
You should think for yourself...
instead of others.
You have to.
Thank you.
I'll get going.
Hye Gyeong.
I'm sure you'll do well. Don't worry.
Aren't you...
Kang Seok Beom?
Hello, Lawyer Kim.
Hello. It's been a while.
How are you feeling?
I'm good.
Do you have business here?
No.
I brought my boss here. He's waiting inside.
I see.
I heard that you know my driver.
The prosecutor says on March 9 and 16 of last year, Lee Tae Joon...
contacted President Cho Guk Hyun of Dokwang Development...
and promised to give him the authority to build Dream UCT.
Then he asked for money.
My driver apparently has a close relationship with the prosecutor.
When you see Prosecutor Lee,
tell him my driver and I are worried about him.
You didn't come to our meeting today.
No. I had some personal business to attend.
I belive President Seo Joong Won attended in my place.
Was there a problem?
No. No problem at all.
I just wanted to ask you for a favour.
I miss Prosecutor Lee.
He keeps avoiding me so I can't set up a time.
Can you pass this to him for me?
Tell him it's herbal medicine from the driver.
Why don't you go see him at home? He should be there.
You know very well that I can't.
There are too many eyes around.
Tell him this.
I can't guarantee what will happen if he keeps avoiding me.
Yes, Dan.
They haven't found the test papers on the scene.
Both kids claim that they never touched the papers.
Of course the police cares more...
about the homicide, so they're not so concerned about the papers.
Why did you ask me to look into this?
There was something that bothered me.
Thank you.
Are you going somewhere?
Yes. I need to find out something.
Do you want me to come?
You can't go.
You're only allowed at home, office and the hospital.
It'll be quick.
It's not like someone is watching me.
They might be.
Also, I'm going out to work. It's not for fun.
By the way,
I have a present for you in my room.
It's from Cho Guk Hyun.
Cho Guk Hyun?
Did he say anything?
He wants you to call him. He wants to see you badly.
Right. Kang Seok Beom picked out the present.
We haven't talked properly for a long time.
We pretended to be happy instead of talking about important things.
I think it's about time that we talked...
honestly without hiding anything.
All right.
Long time no see.
I have something to talk to you about.
I have nothing to say to you.
The police will start investigating on the theft of the test papers.
Do you want one?
When it happened to you, did you know...
how happy the others were?
Everyone disliked you and your husband...
because both of you acted arrogantly.
You especially...
bossed people around and meddled in their businesses.
Did you think that would last forever?
Things were going well for you for a while,
but everything went down the gutter.
It's all in the past.
What's important now...
is Dong Hyun.
I know that what Dong Hyun did was terrible.
No, why would he do that?
He's different from Jae Yeol.
He's a good student.
He's always been a good son, too.
His grades...
are great as well.
Didn't Dong Hyun ask you where the key to the cabinet was kept?
You know because you're part of the management committee.
"Did Dong Hyun steal the test papers?"
"Did he kill someone by mistake?"
I'm sure you keep wondering.
It was the same for me when the news broke out.
Don't talk nonsense.
Don't compare my son to your husband.
Leave.
Ask him to what extent is true. He can be helped only if he tells...
I said, leave.
Second chances are given only when we know the truth.
There's nothing if you don't accept the truth.
It's worse for both of us if we hide something from each other.
- Hey... - Don't go!
It took me too long to find out,
but I hope you'll realise it sooner for your child.
Hello, Dan. Can you unlock locked doors?
I was so lucky today.
Why did you call me suddenly?
Thank you so much.
It's fine as long as you're thankful.
You should take better care of me and listen to my advice.
May I ask you a question?
Go ahead.
Why did my husband fire you?
I was secretly investigating his case that he had closed.
Was that the only reason?
I exposed some information as well.
I quit when he asked me if I wanted to quit or be punished.
You should break up with him soon.
Why are we here?
Jae Yeol said he ran away after seeing the security.
Dong Hyun was caught while he was stealing the test papers.
What if the murder took place because of that?
The test papers.
There must be Dong Hyun's fingerprints on the papers.
Dong Hyun must have taken it.
Knowing that the police would arrest him?
He was probably too scared to do that.
Then he must have thrown it away.
Where? In a trash can?
What if someone finds it?
He said it took seven minutes for friends and the ambulance to arrive.
He had to either throw it away or hide it during that time.
What would you have done?
I'd have eaten it.
It's not hard to eat a few pieces of paper.
It's hard for average people.
I think...
I know what you're thinking.
I met Dong Hyun here.
I was curious why he was at school.
He came to retrieve the papers.
Shall we open it?
Dong Hyun's mum.
I thought you'd come here to find it.
You...
He killed someone even if it was by mistake.
You can't solve it by trying to hide it.
No way.
My child wouldn't do that.
You should worry about your husband instead.
Worry about your husband instead!
- Stop it. - Hey.
What are you doing? Let me go!
Worry about your husband!
Hey. No! Don't do it!
Don't do it! Dong Hyun didn't do it.
He didn't do it. Please stop.
Please stop.
Stop it.
Jae Yeol will be tried again at the juvenile court.
It's not likely that he'll be sent to a juvenile hall.
He'll serve community service or be under protective supervision.
Lawyer Lee will help you with the rest.
Thank you, Hye Gyeong.
Come this way.
Thank you so much.
Once things go well with Jae Yeol,
let's get along like before.
Well...
How about lunch? I'll call you.
I know you won't call me or have lunch,
but it's really okay.
I understand you.
Jae Yeol's mum.
Please save my child.
My Dong Hyun...
Say that he made a mistake.
Please, I beg you.
Please.
Please say it in court.
Jae Yeol's mum.
Please, I beg you to say...
You did well.
I thought I interacted with people honestly.
It's not because I'm a good person. It just feels natural to me.
But I didn't expect them to take it that way.
I really didn't.
Was I wrong...
or did I not understand them?
I don't think they disliked you from the start.
I'm sure they liked you and were thankful at times.
Then, when things started to get bad on your end,
they decided they disliked you from the start.
What would they gain from that?
Aren't the good times we spent more important?
It was so that they wouldn't have to help you.
They were making an excuse for themselves.
It was their way...
to forgive their cowardice.
You're quite dull when it comes to things like this.
Did you know I used to like you at Judicial Training Institute?
Did you?
Really?
You absolutely had no idea?
I thought it was quite obvious.
You were very dull.
Why didn't you tell me? We hung out all the time.
I wasn't sure either.
It was too late when I had realised it.
I realised it when we were almost done with our training.
Prosecutor Lee.
I've waited for so long.
We'll talk on our own now.
Keep my wife out of it.
Of course.
Lawyer Kim is a nice lady.
What's the point of bringing up bad memories?
That poor man Seok Beom still gambles.
I helped him because you're close with him, but people misunderstand.
It's so tiring.
Especially Head Prosecutor Choi.
He's grinding his teeth at us these days.
Prosecutor Lee.
We must stick together.
That's the only way to win.
If we don't, he'll keep on poking at us.
You know what he's like.
To be honest, wasn't our business...
pretty clean compared to what other people do?
It was clean enough to me.
So why does he keep on trying to get dirt out of it?
Just look at what he does.
Isn't he more at wrong here?
Prosecutor Lee. Let's partner up to beat him.
Don't lie to me.
I clearly remember your going on...
blind dates with girls during our school days.
Did you think I'd just move on if you lied about the past?
Can't you just accept things without picking at it?
No.
I don't think I can handle secrets or lies any more.
I just want to know the truth.
Even if the truth is ugly,
I prefer to know about it than not.
I feel the same.
Especially if it's about you.
Wow, look at the time.
I better go. What about you?
I'll have another drink.
- See you tomorrow. - Okay.
I swear. They told me so.
I'm not lying.
- What? - What is it? Do you know him?
Yes. He's a gangster I'm trying to catch.
Hey, Kim Hyun Soo!
Hey! You punk.
Gosh.
That little...
- Hey... - Don't go!
Don't.
Tae Joon,
I'll call 911.
- I'll call them right now. - Hye Gyeong, no!
Hye Gyeong, hold on. Come here.
Let's talk.
I can't be ruined like this. Hye Gyeong...
Hye Gyeong. All of my cases will now...
be buried. Buy me some time.
Only you and I have to know for now.
I'll tell them the truth later.
I'll take responsibility for it later.
Please buy me some time.
Do you think this is the right thing to do?
If you do as I say, everything will be fine.
I'll take care of you until the end.
Don't worry. Don't worry.
(Joong Won)
You could not connect to this number. You will be...
Tae Joon.
I'll do my best to help you in any way I can.
Everything will be fine as long as we're together.
So please...
(The Good Wife)
I want you to tell me when you can about the truth...
that has happened so far.
I'll delete any records related to you.
In return, bring me evidence...
so that I can arrest Tae Joon.
Sang Il bugged my phone.
Can you check what he recorded?
I'm waiting for a miracle.
I know I'll regret it and blame it on myself if I just let it go.
Objection, Your Honour.
You can tell she's a newbie.
You were just being yourself.
We're only doing...
what we're assigned to do.
You were just fooled by my acting.
We need Kim Hye Gyeong.
If we want to win the trial and go up higher,
you need her.