Subtitles by DramaFever
[Episode 16]
Why are you bringing so much stuff?
These are all things
that we'll be needing.
And I'll read a book or two...
You're going to stay cooped up in the
hotel room, at this rate.
You really do hate moving around.
I'll call us a cab!
Are you expecting someone?
Nope, nobody.
Hyun Soo!
What?
Look!
- Oh my gosh!
- Wow.
Oh my gosh!
Please come in, Chef Ohn!
Hello.
We're leaving for a trip
today, though.
I know. I came to carry
your things for you.
Aren't you opening your
restaurant today?
It's closed until tomorrow.
Is this the stuff you need carried?
Um...
Yes!
Oh, um, this too.
There will be tons of traffic if you
wait much longer, so hurry up.
All right.
Oh my gosh, I can't believe
that this is happening!
What's with you?
I know, right?
Why am I being like this?
It's not like this happened to me!
Oh my goodness!
Oh my gosh!
All right, they took the 7:15
bullet train from Yongsan Station
so they'll probably be eating
lunch in Yeosu by noon.
Wow, you seem so excited.
I'm actually excited for the
first time in a while!
Why is this tugging at my heartstrings
when it's someone else's love story?
It's been such a long time since I last
fell into that crazy thing called love!
Can't we play some music, Chef Ohn?
We sure can.
Can't we turn the music off, Chef Ohn?
What are you doing?
What do you mean? I'm pretending
that he's my boyfriend!
I just really wanted to try it
because I'm so envious!
Come on, Kyung!
Ms. Hyun Soo won't like it
if you say things like that.
Oh, she's not like that.
Hey, what's with you two?
I'm your mutual contact!
So I don't think it's nice for you to
team up and tease me.
Who else would we tease, then?
We can't tease someone
we don't know well.
Thumbs up, Chef Ohn!
So you think I'll just sit here
and take this? Yeah, I will.
Come on!
Can't we play some music, Chef Ohn?
Hey, stop it already!
Let's go get it on!
Writer Park!
Oh goodness, Hong Ah!
Oh, you!
Here you go, Writer Park.
Goodness, what's this?
I bought it because I figured
that it'd suit you well.
Congratulations on getting
your script chosen!
It's only because you taught
me so many things.
You're doing well, I presume?
How could I possibly be doing well?
I'm sure you heard the news, too.
Oh... I see.
I mean, that girl Hyun Soo keeps
going around insulting me so much
that I can't even look
my seniors in the face!
Really?
She's going around portraying me
as this completely villainous person!
And all the other writers who
don't really know Hyun Soo
all believe that nonsense!
Do I seem like the type of writer
who'd go behind another writer's back
and strike a deal with their director
to backstab them?
You're not that kind of
person, Writer Park.
I'm sure that people will realize this
for themselves, in time.
Right?
So go around saying that to
people you know, okay?
My story will sound more credible
if someone who spent a lot of time
with Hyun Soo, like you, says this.
Wow, how disgraceful!
I don't think you'll suffer any
huge losses just because
Hyun Soo is insulting
you behind your back.
As long as you're successful,
insults are...
Don't worry about it too much.
It's because I'm not successful
that I'm worried!
It's so hard to get a new project!
They like younger writers for
genre-specific work.
You're so honest, Writer Park.
That's why I like you.
What can I say? I'm the same,
inside and out.
At any rate, thanks
for having my back.
You're a great writer
and you're so refined
so all you need now is to make it big.
Thank you, Writer Park.
Have you introduced yourself
to Chief Producer Yoo Hong Jin?
No.
Go to him!
He'll help you use your
background to your advantage.
Thank you for your advice.
This is why you need a mentor.
Tell Hyun Soo to stop going around
insulting me!
Why does she know so many people?
Because she graduated from a good school?
Goodness, what's this?
This is our room.
Head in.
My room is over there.
See you in the lobby
in 30 minutes, Chef!
All right.
Hyun Soo!
Chef Ohn is super great!
He's super, super great!
So what?
If you let him slip away,
you're stupid!
Does he seem that good
of a guy to you?
Did you see the look
in his eyes?
There are stars in his eyes!
I've never seen a man
with stars in his eyes!
I'm only letting you have him
because you're you!
Stars?
As if!
No, he really has
stars in his eyes!
Twinkle, twinkle!
- [Director Kim Joon Ha]
- Ugh.
He can't stand to see me
even a little bit happy!
Do I have to imagine that I'm talking to
Chef Ohn instead of Director Kim?
Do it.
You got jealous just now,
Hyun Soo!
No, I didn't!
Yes, Director?
Where are you?
I just arrived.
I'll come out by myself.
Hyun Soo is busy.
What?
Where are you?
All right.
Hyun Soo checked in!
I confirmed it with Writer Hwangbo.
I can only get together
with them around dinnertime.
There's some business I need to
take care of since I'm here.
I knew it was weird that you didn't
put up much of a fight.
You only came because you had
business here, didn't you?
What are you going to do?
Um... I'll stay with Writer Hwangbo.
You go do everything
you want to do.
I'll set the mood for you two
before then.
Let's go.
Sure.
You're downstairs already?
Oh, yes!
Hyun Soo will be down soon.
I'm going to go off on my own.
Why?
A director I know is here, and
I have to keep him company.
He has a weird personality, so he'll
ruin things if he gets involved here.
It's okay.
But if you can't handle him
on your own, give me a call.
All right!
Have a great time with Hyun Soo!
He said he's in the lobby,
so where is he?
Where should we go first?
You've been here before?
Of course! Yeosu is famous
for its fermented soy crabs.
So you still only remember places
based on their food, I see.
How about I give you a feast
for your eyes before lunch?
Oh, this is nice.
I'm hungry.
That's a bit out of the ordinary.
What do you mean?
I didn't expect that.
I thought you's say something like,
"This view is so nice!"
How did you think to
come here with us?
Because I was bored?
Your appeal is that you're honest,
and your appeal just dropped.
From the number one spot?
Geez.
Let's just go eat some
fermented soy crabs.
The best way to eat fermented soy crab
is to scrape it out of the shell
and eat it with rice!
You know the right way to eat it.
What other dishes is
Yeosu known for?
Wow, this tastes amazing.
Put your glasses on.
People are supposed to look prettier
without their glasses, right?
But you look better with
yours on, Writer Hwangbo.
Did I make you feel bad?
You really hate hearing things
like that, don't you, Writer Hwangbo?
First of all, you didn't
make me feel bad.
And as for my glasses, I'll
wear them if I want to
and take them off
if I want to take them off.
But I want to keep them off right now
because of you, Director Kim.
It's okay to just speak
your dialect.
You're trying so hard to
speak in the Seoul dialect.
It's pitiful to watch.
Geez, seriously!
You're not wrong.
You're right.
The reason I don't use my dialect
is because people can tell
exactly where I grew up just by how
I speak, so I'm trying to work on it.
Because I want to seem a bit
mysterious and such.
You wouldn't seem mysterious or anything
even if you used the Seoul dialect.
You're paying, right?
Yes.
That's why I'm holding back!
I want to focus on
just eating.
Here.
Don't you dare do
things like that.
I don't want to be
close to you.
This is one of the
many rock crevices.
They say your wish will come true
if you pass through all seven of them.
Don't say it out loud.
Just think it.
Did you come up with a wish?
I did, too.
I'm off!
Be careful.
Don't get lost.
There's no way I'd get lost here!
I even drive now!
I have a sense of direction now!
[DF Ver] E16 Temperature of Love
"I'll be the Bridge to Bring You Two Together"
-= Ruo Xi =-
I found out because
Writer Park called and told me.
Why didn't you tell me that your father
is the CEO of Yoosung Chemicals?
My cousin works there.
My father's company and me being
acknowledged for my work
have nothing to do with each other.
What a great way to think.
Oh.
[High Society]
Please read this.
Are you discussing a contract
with any other company?
I'm considering an offer that
On Entertainment's CEO Park made me.
On Entertainment is great.
And CEO Park is smart.
Hey, Director Min!
Oh, hey.
You go ahead and get things ready.
I'm going crazy because of the script.
I told you that getting new writers
would just drain you.
I don't know why you're
putting yourself through this.
It may be a bit too late, but
call Writer Lee Hyun Soo!
I can't do that!
Not even if I bite my tongue and die!
Oh!
Hello, Director.
Um, hello.
Her work was chosen as a finalist
for HNC's open call.
Oh, really?
Congratulations.
Oh yeah, since you're Writer Lee's
assistant writer
you know a lot about
"Foul Detective," don't you?
Did you help her come up
with the story?
Well, no. But I do know
the work well.
Oh, then can you become
one of our writers?
Are you asking me to join
your writing team?
Wow, you understand exactly
what I meant, huh?
Why would I get onto
a sinking ship?
Wow!
You can tell that she's super sensible
just from the way she's talking!
Right, Hong Jin?
But if you get onto our ship,
our ship may not sink.
I don't want to.
If this project doesn't tank, let's
work together next time too.
You still don't want to?
Wow.
This is so nice.
I'm going to go to the bathroom.
Have a safe trip!
And don't get lost.
Why, you!
I told you, I've been here before!
[Lee Hyun Soo]
[Ohn Jung Seon]
To be honest, there was only one
thought running through my mind then.
"I have to find Jung Seon."
The man I thought of
in my most desperate moment.
I've never caused anyone
emotional turmoil before.
So why should I be the only
one making you feel secure?
Ms. Lee Hyun Soo, who pushed aside
the man who loved her because of reality!
Why should I start over with you?
Give up on me, then.
If you like me so little that you can
give up on me, give me up now.
There is a man I love.
I realized that fact
when it was too late.
That this is what it
feels like to be in love.
I only realized this
after that man disappeared.
Where am I supposed to go
to meet that man now?
I thought you said that you
weren't going to get lost anymore.
I'm sorry.
It's all my fault.
I ruined everything.
I was too busy acting
high and mighty and cool
that I ignored all of the signs
that you were giving me.
When I say "you," I don't mean "you."
I mean the other kind of "you."
You're concerned about that
at a time like this?
There are some things that need
clarifying, despite the circumstances!
Oh, forget about thinking!
I thought and I thought, which
is what led me to lose you!
I thought about this a whole lot
while we were apart for five years.
I love you.
I'm in love with you.
I know.
There's no reason why a woman who
pushed you away once can't do it again.
Saying things like, "reality is always
difficult", is too harsh!
Wow, you've quoted me verbatim.
So how could you tell me
that you love me?
How could you tell me that
you thought only of me?
I told you, I have more
trouble with other things.
You did.
Stop talking.
I'll be seeing you
next time, then.
[Chief Producer Yoo Hong Jin]
Yes, Chief Producer?
Hey, CEO Park.
We have a great new condition
for our agreement.
What is it?
You know Ms. Ji Hong Ah, right?
Writer Lee Hyun Soo's assistant writer.
Yes.
I think it'd be good to kick out the
two writers we have now
and have Writer Ji take over.
She was on Writer Lee Hyun Soo's writing
team, so she knows the story well.
At this rate, "Foul Detective"
will be canceled early.
Then we'll incur huge losses.
We won't be able to sell the
rights overseas, either.
Yeah, Jung Woo.
Where are you?
Are you done taking care of
your business?
Yeah, you can hang up.
I'll text you.
Why isn't Hyun Soo coming?
I'm sure she'll come
when the time is right.
Where is she?
Tell her to come back.
Is she with someone else?
That's none of your business.
But I'll ask her where she is.
Aren't you going to read it?
I don't want to,
because I'm with you.
You can do anything
precisely because you're with me.
Where are you, Hyun Soo?
It's Kyung.
Should I tell her to come here?
Do you want to do that?
We came on this trip together
but I feel like I'm the only one
having a good time.
Do as you please.
Nah, I'll just meet up with her
when I get to the hotel.
Hyun Soo said that she went to
the Soho Floating Bridge.
It'll be just like a movie
if you meet her there!
But why did Hyun Soo go to
that bridge by herself?
When did I say
that she went by herself?
She's not by herself?
No!
She's not there with a man, is she?
It is a man!
Geez, why are you
only telling me that now?
Because you just asked now!
[Jung Woo]
What's his problem?
[Incoming call: Kim Joon Ha]
Yeah, Joon Ha?
Oh, sorry. I made a mistake.
Hyun Soo isn't there.
Just come straight to the hotel.
Really?
All right.
You'll come here, right?
No, I should see the
Soho Floating Bridge while I'm here.
This is so nice.
You're not cold?
No, I'm fine.
I don't think you'll be okay.
It's okay even if
I'm not okay.
I wish that...
time could stop,
and we could stay like this forever.
There's a man I love.
I only realized that this is what love
is, once that man disappeared.
I want to propose to someone.
When?
Who's the lady?
I tend to make decisions about
really important things on my own.
The woman who is a really important
decision to you must be so happy.
Do you really think so?
Yeah.
You're a man among men!
Subtitles by DramaFever
[Monday night at 10 p.m…]