(Episode 18)
(Producer Kim "Star's Favorite Dish")
Yes, Producer Kim.
Mr. Park,
Apparently Chef On told us he won't be on the show anymore.
Aren't you changing your attitude too quickly?
It hasn't been long since you asked me desperately to let him on.
I'll look into it.
Make sure he's on this episode.
You have a 6pm dinner appointment with CP Yoo at Good Soup.
Call Writer Ji Hong Ah to come if she's available.
And Director Min too.
Have we met before?
I think I've seen you before.
Yes, we met five years ago in Yeonnam-dong.
You had Kenya Double A then.
You have a good memory.
Can I talk to you comfortably?
You seem much older than my son.
How much older are you?
I'm not that older.
I'm six years older.
Only six years?
Six years is nothing.
After I ended things with Jung Sun's dad, I only met younger men.
You can't go back to older guys after seeing younger men.
Whether they are older or younger, men are children.
It's better to humor younger men.
I see.
What do you do?
I'm a drama writer.
I'm preparing for a new project right now.
When it's not on air, I'm basically unemployed.
I like that you don't show off.
Were you in touch with Chef On when he was in France?
No, we reconnected when he came back.
Right? There's no way I wouldn't have known if you were in touch.
What do your parents do?
They're both elementary school teachers.
That's nice.
I feel like they'll be young at heart like elementary school kids.
Yes, they are innocent.
Let's share phone numbers and be friends.
I have to get going.
I'll get going too then.
There's someone you should meet before you leave.
It's my fiancé.
Hello, Soo Jung.
- Can I get another glass? - Sure.
Professor Min.
This is Chef On's girlfriend.
Hello.
Oh, are you?
When did he get a girlfriend? He didn't have one before.
They've had a platonic love relationship for a while now.
She's a drama writer.
Oh, you're a writer?
I'm a writer too.
I'm basically unemployed now.
She's so humble.
It's not good to be so humble.
She's older than Chef On.
It's less than our age gap though.
I like that she's older than my son.
Chef On and I are indeed similar.
Right, have a seat. Let's eat together.
No, it's okay. I have some work to do.
I'll get going then, Mother.
Mother?
Oh my, it feels so strange to hear that.
Should I not call you that?
No, it's not that I don't like it.
Then see you later.
Okay.
Mr. Park.
Hello. Where are you headed?
Home.
Let's walk together.
Is she even real?
I've never seen you with a woman.
Just get ready to greet her.
I'll look forward to it.
Go in.
Okay.
Mr. Park.
I have something to tell you.
Number 1, it's personal. Number 2, it's work-related.
Number one.
Don't say it.
I'm taking off.
For the past 10 years, I planned to name...
my future company as "On".
But as soon as I heard your name, On Jung Sun,
I felt like I had lost.
What are you thinking about?
You.
Goodness. Stop it.
I heard you said you won't be on the show today.
The producer called me.
Are you in trouble?
A little bit.
I asked for you to be on the show.
So someone had an allergic reaction at Good Soup?
Wow, you know everything.
I've figured everything out.
Go on the show.
I had some thoughts...
while taking that customer to the emergency room.
"This isn't it."
"This isn't the way to go."
- You still have to go on once more. - No, I won't do it.
It's too early to let your guards down.
Your customers aren't coming to the restaurant for your cooking.
That's why I won't do it.
It's right to go slowly.
As long as I don't lose the customers I have now, that's fine.
In the end, you'll do what you want...
regardless of what I say.
Then why do you need me?
You may be the owner chef of Good Soup,
but don't forget I'm the person who can take you down from that place.
I haven't forgotten.
That's why I'm making changes and compromises.
I feel like they aren't enough though.
Can't you just trust me until the end?
The same feeling you had in the beginning.
Feeling.
What are you doing?
(I have to talk to you. What are you doing?)
Hyun Soo.
Are you really going to start working now?
- You're up early. - Yes.
Do you want some tea?
No, I want food.
How can you eat as soon as you wake up?
What are you doing?
She woke up early.
Why are you eating that?
You hate boiled eggs.
You're right.
I got changed.
Where? Why were you changing?
He told me earlier that he's drinking water.
Why did he drink water? What is he trying to do?
He should become a writer.
He makes me so curious.
Hyun Soo.
- Yes? - Do you like him that much?
- Is it obvious? - It's very obvious.
I want to date too.
- You should. - With who?
Where can I find a man like Chef On?
You should find a man that suits you.
Why are you looking at my man?
What's wrong with me?
Did I really just say that?
I'm sorry.
Do you like him that much?
I do.
I might buy a bicycle.
Why all of a sudden?
If we want to do research,
Good Soup...
is too close to drive and too far to walk.
I can get there fast on a bicycle.
Is it Chef On? Like last time?
- Oh, my. - No way.
Hyun Soo.
Does he not have a home?
No one's home anyway.
What brings you here?
Make me some breakfast.
You didn't have to make soup.
I like making soup.
I had to make a lot of soup because someone likes it.
Is it not good?
No, it's delicious.
Come.
Okay.
Clams are good for people that have to use their brains.
Have you ever felt this?
Once you find out the result of the things you didn't know,
all the pieces come together like a puzzle, becoming a single picture.
Yes.
Because of one incident,
everything lines up, and you come to a realization.
That's pretty good.
If the woman you like likes another man,
will you give up?
I might give up, but not before I give it my all.
Same with me.
Then what if that man was me?
Would you still go all the way?
Of course.
Wouldn't you do the same?
I would.
I'm going to propose next week.
I'll make sure to prepare it well.
Even if she likes someone else, you'll become the star that night.
Eat this too.
[VIU Ver] E18 Temperature of Love "The Same Feeling"
-= Ruo Xi =-
(Lee Hyun Soo)
What are you doing?
Can I come over for an interview?
Let's go, Hyun Soo.
He didn't reply yet.
How frustrating. Why are you texting him?
Just call him.
He's busy.
I might disturb him at work.
What if he finds me annoying?
He loves you. Why would he think you're annoying?
Here it is.
What are you doing?
I'm going to an interview.
(I'm going to an interview.)
She's working.
At least she's not seeing her boyfriend.
It's for real this time.
Come.
Kyung, we should go now. Let's go.
It's so strange to see you like this.
I'm sorry, Kyung.
Don't be sorry.
I'm just saying I'm jealous.
Why are you here at this hour?
I don't want to be a part of "Unruly Detectives".
You didn't say anything yesterday. What happened?
I saw what Director Min's team wrote,
and it's not going anywhere.
I'm sure it will fail. It'll just be hard work.
I need you to take care of it.
All right. Let's do that.
I like that it's simple.
I'm glad I decided to work with you.
Please let me think the same about you too.
Of course.
You and I are both achievement-oriented people.
But...
there is one thing I'm worried about.
You and I are really different when it comes to love.
It was unexpected and disappointing.
I know you like Hyun Soo.
I'm very sharp when it comes to things like this.
I knew it when I met you.
And?
Why haven't you made a move?
You have all the qualifications of becoming the perfect man.
I thought you would date Hyun Soo and marry her.
What have you been doing for the last five years?
Why are you behind?
Do you even know who you're against?
That's enough.
Ms. Ji.
You have a tendency to push people to the edge.
You aroused me enough.
Please write your work like this.
It's so nice to eat while working.
Isn't it good?
How did he think of making a sandwich with sea urchin?
Hyun Soo, do you think there is a reason why...
the course meal is set this way? Maybe it's a theme.
I'm sure.
Do you want more wine?
Yes, please.
Is it okay?
It's delicious.
Enjoy.
Okay. I'll see you later.
Okay.
"I'll see you later."
Gosh. I need to lie down.
Kyung, please be understanding.
It's because I've been holding it in for so long.
Sure. I understand.
Why haven't you made a move?
What have you been doing for the last five years?
What are you doing?
(Come!)
What do you think? I came to see you after work.
Does it bother you that I'm always texting?
Are you always waiting for me since I reply slow?
Yes.
How did you know?
Because everyone is like that.
Same with me.
Do you know what "What are you doing" means?
What?
I miss you.
Why don't you ever ask me what I'm doing?
I'm always curious what you're doing,
so whenever I open my eyes in the morning...
Why didn't you tell me earlier?
Then I would have asked you.
Can I touch it?
Go ahead.
(Salt)
- Did it hurt? - Yes. It hurt a lot.
How did you get hurt?
- Were you beat? - No.
It happens to all chefs.
I got it while training. I'm still training now.
That's a relief.
Why did you get this? "Salt"?
Is it because you can't season without salt?
Did you know that your brain is the one recognizing taste?
- I do. - When the brain finds salty taste,
it helps you taste the other tastes as well.
I guess salt is a good guy.
It helps other tastes to come alive along with it.
Yes, it's a good guy.
After my parents got divorced,
I moved to France with Mom, and it was really tough.
I was 16 years old then.
I was really lonely.
But I couldn't be broken.
That's why...
Why are you crying?
I'm not crying.
I want to kiss you.
You can dodge me if you don't want to.
Come on!
Did you think I wouldn't dodge you? You can't laugh after crying.
You're so mean.
Back then,
I...
was really nervous that you might dodge me.
I was so happy you didn't.
Then why did you do this to me?
To make you laugh.
We can start kissing now.
Then I won't let you just do it.
Fine.
You can choose.
The teenage version, the 20s version, or the 30s version?
I'll take all, and add a refrigerator kiss on top.
(Temperature of Love)
Is Mr. Park getting married?
I think he had someone in his mind for a long time.
There won't be any space for you to get in between them.
Did Mom call you?
When are you getting married? You should do it soon.
Was it strange when I proposed to you before?
There's no answer to such a thing.
We need to change our relationship.
Mr. Park's proposal will succeed thanks to this cake.
I have a girlfriend now. I want to introduce her to you.
You can ask her to come on the day I propose.
Let's meet together.