A long time ago, a boy loved a mermaid
and heard her voice.
Am I... that boy?
He was the boy who loved the mermaid and heard her voice.
But he didn't know one important thing.
That mermaids have a special ability.
That she can erase herself from a human's memories with a kiss.
Even if you erase my memories over and over...
Even if he's born in a different world,
he is a boy whose fate is to love the mermaid again.
Please save me.
Argh!
I'm also different.
- Heo Joon Jae... - If he knows I'm different,
Heo Joon Jae will probably hate me, right? He'll probably leave me, right?
Don't come, Heo Joon Jae!
My secret is that I'm different from you.
That I'm a mermaid.
So in the end, he is the boy who will eventually hear the mermaid's voice again.
I love you.
He was...
me.
- Excuse me, have you seen someone who looks like this?  - No.
- Excuse me, have you seen someone who looks like this?- No.
Today is the day where the Black Moon will appear.
The Black Moon is the second new moon in a single calendar month.
It's said that the moon disappears into the darkness,
and that's how it got stuck with the name Black Moon.
In the past, it was thought to be an ominous sign.
Yang Seung Gil sent a message to the Hanyang official Jo Bong Hak, whom he's been sending bribes,
claiming that the town head of Heupgok village is bewitched by the wicked mermaid and disturbing the public,
and that you had framed him of murder.
Thereafter, Jo Bong Hak has submitted a written petition to the King. What shall we do?
In addition, Yang's underlings are casting all kinds of fishing nets every day,
frantically trying to capture the mermaid.
Open the door.
My Lord, why are you like this?
Die.
And don't ever be born again.
Why are my dreams like this?
It's a real mermaid.
Just watch and see. I will make that mermaid mine again, no matter what it takes.
That naive town head...
I will get rid of him with my own hand.
Die and don't ever be born again.
Heo Joon Jae...
and the mermaid.
Legend of the Blue Sea
Episode 11
Refund all of this with money.
All of this?
Did Cheong not come yet?
Tae Oh was looking at the CCTVs of the house and the neighborhood,
and you know those bags from the Gangnam department store? I think she was carrying those out.
- To do what with those?- I don't know. Maybe she's selling them and getting a rental room.
Why would she get a rental room, leaving her own house? Move!
Is this Cheong's house? It's your house. You'd always say it's your house.
Where did she go? Did you see the department store?
- Do you think it's easy to get inside the department store?- Do it quickly! Quickly!
Are you really a hacker?
Do you know how many people are in a department store? Do you think it's easy to find her? When will we?
Find her location with your phone.
It's turned off.
Hey, I somehow have this bad feeling about this. Did she leave for good, by chance?
Thank you for renewing the contract with favorable conditions.
Of course I should. You've kept good relations with my father.
I hardly ever see CEO Heo anymore.
Oh, my father's condition is not that great.
Well, since his son is so dependable like this, he is entrusting it to you.
Oh...
Wait... She shouldn't be riding that.
Oh!
It's time to close the shop, and there are no customers here,
- so let's just leave her for a bit.- Ah, yes.
My secret is that I'm different from you.
That I'm a mermaid.
If you find out who I am, you're going to be surprised, hurt, and scared of me.
You're going to leave me.
So I'm trying my best to not get found out.
Did I come into some kind of children's book?
Or...
Did you come out to the world?
You guys match each other so well,
so when are you guys planning to marry?
We will soon. Thinking about Dubai or Europe early next year.
Oh my! I see!
That's right. I'm a person who lies.
I cheat others and get money off of cheating them. That's right.
I'm that kind of person. That is my secret.
What's yours?
Oh? Heo Joon Jae's family?
Ah, just call me Heo Chi Hyeon.
Mr. Heo Chi Hyeon.
Yes. Thank you.
But did you come by yourself? What about Joon Jae?
There are a lot of pretty and good things here.
There wasn't anything like this where I lived.
Where is it? Wherever it is, there's bound to be a Christmas.
There's a place where there's not.
Where's your house?
I live with Heo Joon Jae.
You live together?
I'm the upper room; he's the lower room.
Heo Joon Jae's the house owner.
Ah, I see.
You didn't bring a car, right?
Should I give you a ride?
Then instead of driving me home, will you drive me to that place?
Ah, you're really going to sleep here?
Yes. Looking at the TV, there were a lot of people who sleep here when they come out of the house.
Well, okay, but be safe.
Bye.
Cheong Hae Spa SaunaMen / Women
- Oh, wait! - Hey, you!
- What are you doing? - Hey!
This is the women's side. No!
I'm sorry.
Here is the ladies' side.
She went inside well, right?
Will it take much longer?
To protect the VVIP room, there's no CCTV.
Ah, just do it quickly.
I did think it was very nerve-wracking yesterday.
You guys weren't talking and were just trying to out-stare each other.
Wow, when Cheong was like that, I feel some type of unapproachable charisma.
- Hyung.- Yeah?
Do you know the story of the Little Mermaid?
Oh my. So suddenly. Really sudden.
Well, isn't it like the mermaid princess goes up to the land and falls in love with the prince?
Yeah, and the witch gave her legs,
but after midnight, it turned back to a tail,
and she couldn't wear her glass shoes, and the prince was searching for the owner of the shoes...
Isn't that something else?
Cinderella.
You find this instead.
Aren't children's stories the same thing?
Like that, the prince and the mermaid falls in love and get married. The end.
- Was it? - That's Disney's version. She dies in the original version.
- Dies? - I think so.
Who? The prince? The mermaid?
That's right! I think the mermaid died.
Why does the mermaid die?
What kind of lame children's story is that?
Yeah, I know. Kids read that so why would they do that?
But why are we talking about that at dawn? These days, they say that even kids don't read the classic children's stories, either.
Ah, I don't know.
Hurry up and find her.
- Oh, it's refreshing.- Isn't it good?
Miss!
This is my spot!
What was that about?
Hello.
We meet again.
Ah, yes. Did Cheong perhaps come here?
What's the story that's read with great emotion?
What?
I think it's Romeo and Juliet.
I cried. Shakespeare isn't a maestro for nothing.
Did you see her? Cheong?
Sit here for a bit.
In this world,
there are many love stories. But from all those love stories,
if you take out the rhetoric and unessential words,
there will be only one sentence left. What do you think it is?
- What is it?- "Be good to her when she's with you."
Aish!
What I'm saying is that if you treated her well when she was with you, she wouldn't have left. You wouldn't be searching for her like this, either.
It's the eternal truth.
If you see Cheong, tell her to make sure to contact me.
Make sure! For sure!
See? He should listen to me. Otherwise, he will be regretting later.
He's going to come back again. He's going to come again.
I am here at this time on Mondays, Wednesdays, and Fridays.
Come on Monday, Wednesday, or Friday.
It is not possible to track the location.
Wow, daebak!
Daebak!
What does she do?
Hey, I can see something else. Let's look for more things. Turn the cell phone on.
- Hey, hurry up!- Watch out for people.
Hey! I found that girl first!
- I'm the one who found the money.- Hey, let's just divide equally.
Stop right there!
Hey, hey, hey! Stop! Stop! You guys are playing hard.
For now, give me the phone.
Where did you find this?
It's mine.
Oh, is that so?
It's my girlfriend's.
Where's my girlfriend?
- I don't know. - You guys can keep all the money. Just tell me where she is.
- The Cheonghae Sauna in front of here.- Hey!- What?
Thanks! Friend, let's do a hand shake.
- Who are you?- Argh! Seriously!
Me? I'm a scammer.
If you guys are like this, you'll turn out like me.
If the guy you like asks you what you do,
then you'll have to lie about everything. Lies.
Do you like that even then?
- Ah, what is this? He took everything! - Ah, seriously!
My heart fluttered a bit just now. Bad-boy style.
He was a bit cool.
Did you sleep well?
No, I didn't sleep well,
and so I think that's why I don't feel like eating.
I was worried about you.
Since it was my day-off, I came here.
It looks like your hunger came back. Please eat it with this rice shake.
You're a good person.
I don't have a name, but I was told I'm not a strange person.
-Who?-A good person.
Do you know me? You don't have anything to say to me, right? Then don't follow me.
Then are you not leaving? Take that and leave.
♬ When I enter, my eyes are dazzled ♬
Heo Joon Jae.
♬  A wide world welcomes me ♬
♬ I approach you. I want to be embraced. ♬
♬ I want to stay in that world which is you ♬
♬ I owe you I miss you  ♬
You seriously. Who told you to leave the house and stay at a place like this?
Do you know how much I tried to find you?
♬ Eternally in your arms ♬
How did you come here knowing this place?
Heo Chi Hyeon drove me here.
What?
-Why are you here?-Don't misunderstand.
We coincidentally met each other outside yesterday, and Cheong said that she didn't want to go home.
Not come?
-You said that?-Yeah.
You go ahead.
And you. Let's talk somewhere private.
Heo Joon Jae. I switched all of those items I bought last time into money.
I don't need those clothes, so I'll return it to you.
Yeah, I got it well.
What happened?
Take care of your phone too.
How do you have that?
I'm also a bad guy, but there's a lot more people who are worse than me here.
So please be careful.
What about food? Did you eat?
I ate an egg and drank rice shake.
Do you not want to eat anything more?
No.
Spicy rice cakes, blood sausages, laver rolls, strawberry-flavored shaved ice, melon-flavored shaved ice, fried dumplings, steamed dumplings, round-shaped dough seaweed soup.
I see you don't have an appetite.
I thought you would come, so I made grilled ribs at home.
Ah, beef ribs is the best when seasoned.
It's seasoned beef ribs.
It sounds delicious.
It's really tasty.
I thought it was melting in my mouth.
I'm fine.
I want to eat it, seasoned beef ribs.
So, you're really not going to come?
I'm not.
- Really?- Yeah.
- Why?- Because you're a con artist.
You're a bad bastard who tricks people. You tricked me too.
But, why am I not disappointed? When you're a bad guy?
Why can't I leave you, who fooled me?
If you don't want to come home, stay here.
Instead, don't go anywhere else. Stay here.
You can't leave without saying goodbye.
Okay.
You promised.
Then... I'm leaving.
I said I'm leaving.
Go.
What the heck? "Don't go, Heo Joon Jae."
I thought she would say something like that. Why is she so cold-hearted?
Joon Jae. Father is ill these days.
And?
Why? Where and how is he ill?
The doctor said it was cataracts. His eyesight has impaired quite a lot.
I told you to take care of him well.
Escort him to the hospital well.
I was grateful that he became my dad.
So I always want to be in his favor and protect him.
Sure.
Be grateful. Continue to be in his favor, and protect him.
After my father became your's,
there were many things that I failed to protect and lost.
- Yes, thank you.- Of course.
Kang Ji Yeon?
Did Ma Dae Yeong marry?
Kang Ji Yeon. Who is that?
Kang Ji Yeon, Kang Ji Yeon...
She married twice.
Both of her husbands died.
Of course.
But, the husband suddenly died.
- A year after their marriage.- Why?
A little bit after their marriage, her husband's eyesight started to worsen.
Honey. How do I look?
I'll have to visit Doctor Kim again. The medicine...
I called Doctor Kim.
First, you should diligently take your medicine. He said resting at home after that would be the best.
Just rest.
Okay.
You can't contact them?
I can't.
Goo Baek's dad has been ignoring my calls.
And for CEO Kim's office, no matter how much I call, they won't connect me to him.
That day, what did we do wrong?
No, up to the meal was good. It was, right?
It was. Did you see CEO Kim eat two plates of egg rolls?
Exactly. After that,
what was the problem?
What did you say, Ahjumma?
When I was walking by, it seemed to be that
From the other's perspective, it could've beem burdensome.
Ugh, I can't live because of you, Honey!
I could see it.
What kind of people are they? Would they not know?
That's right. They were burdened.
Aigoo, because of you, it's all ruined! What are you going to do?
I can't live because of you!
Ugh, what about Cheong? Did you find her?
Why? She wouldn't come with you?
The boiler in my room isn't working, so it's cold in there.
I'm sleeping here tonight.
No, if there is a problem,
you should face each other in the same place
and solve it through communication!
Why, did Cheong say she didn't want to come home?
Where did she learn about running away and other bad habits?
I don't think that's something for you to say, when you ran away from home in high school.
What? She doesn't want to come home?
Who did Cheong say that to?
There's some psycho like that.
He's a psycho, that bastard.
Did he treat you well?
He gave me an umbrella when it was raining, and held my hand when I was alone.
He made ramen for me too.
Ra... Ramen?!
Wow... ramen.
He asked you to eat ramen with him? Wow, what a perverted bastard.
What's wrong?
That bastard...
- was me?- Huh?
Don't hang out with people like that. You have to be careful of guys like that.
I'm saying those guys are totally perverted!
Agh!
- Hey!- That was me?
You psycho!
Wait.
So,
that bastard...
was me.
Not some other guy.
What did you say?
No, that guy.
It's me. Hyung.
It was me.
That guy was me.
Hey, I'll sleep in my room even if it's frozen.
- Hyung.- You should rest. Or take medicine.
♬ It means it's you I'm waiting for ♬
♬ That's what's happening, idiot. My heart will keep beating ♬
♬ Why don't you know my heart  ♬
♬ That warm blowing breeze is ♬
♬ whispering to me it is today, ♬
♬ I'm going to give you my ♬
♬ pent-up confession of love. ♬
That bastard...
Aigoo!
Sorry. I can't see that well.
♬  More than any word your eyes  ♬
♬ mean more, I can sense it ♬
♬ In last night's dream while you smiled ♬
♬ You were blowing like the wind ♬
♬ On the path I walked alone In the dream I chased alone ♬
♬ You are at my side now ♬
It's Heo Joon Jae.
♬ Why will I remember it forever? ♬
Don't open your eyes, Heo Joon Jae.
Don't wake up, Heo Joon Jae.
Just stay like this. So I can see you.
So I can make up for the time I couldn't see you.
I don't have to ask you anything.
And you don't need to hide anything from me either.
Don't open your eyes, Heo Joon Jae.
♬ From the moment you come to me ♬
♬ Come a step closer ♬
Ah, it's cold.
♬ My heart is leaning toward you ♬
Heo Joon Jae will be cold too.
Ah, why is it so hot?
BioskopKeren