Subtitles brought to you by The Blue Sea @ Viki
Die.
And don't be born again
Stop!
Criminal Kim Dam Ryeong, accept the royal command.
What did you say?
You have been entranced by a witch and have not been able to fully complete your duty as the local government official.
Kim Dam Ryeong who has disturbed the public sentiment
and will be under house arrest exile in Gyeongsang Province, in Geoje. Come out and receive the command.
Man, I was right, you slippery fellow.
I feel like I came to catch a tiger and caught a rabbit, but having caught one is having caught one anyway.
Byeong Hwan, request some backup support to the square.
- I'll go.  - What?
I'll follow along quietly so don't call more people.
Heo Joon Jae, come quickly.
Heo Joon Jae, where are you?
Legend of the Blue Sea
Let's go punk.
Episode 12
I'll just answer my phone.
Your phone.
You don't have to release these. Just hold my phone to my ear for me.
You bastard, you. You said the same thing three years ago saying your parents would be worried about you.
Then you called your friends and rabbitted, you punk!
This time it's really not like that.
My girlfriend is waiting alone.
She'll probably wait and leave if you don't come.
I'm neither a criminal who has been caught in the act nor someone for whom you have an arrest warrant.
I've agreed to voluntarily comply with the investigation and I'm going with you voluntarily.
You can't put these handcuffs on me to begin with and I can use my cellphone too.
If you violate this you are violating the law on the performance of duties by police officers and under Article 12
- the punishment is up to one year of incarceration and labor.  - Yeah, yea
Okay. I'll live in prison. Let's live there together.
You'll live there a little longer though.
Aish, Seriously!
Your party can't answer the phone so you're being connected to voicemail. And after being connected...
Where did Heo Joon Jae go?
What are you doing here? After sending out so many men to catch Ma Dae Young?
This is the that punk. The Heo Joon Jae that goes around pretending to be me.
Oh, that con artist!
What did you just say? Did you just say 'Ma Dae Young'?
Don't try your tricks
Ma Dae Young... That bastard is here?
We don't know either. We came after getting a tip from someone who supposedly saw him.
Let me go.
Let's go. Let's confine him somewhere for now and come back. It's really noisy.
- Hey, you punk!  - Hey, hey, hey! What are you doing?!
Listen well. It is me whom Ma Dae Young is after.
What is he saying? It's correct that he's a con artist.
Why would that punk be after you?
I don't know either.
If Ma Dae Young is really close to here he followed me.
But that woman is alone right now! Hurry up and give me the phone!
The person I know best
If you long press #1 my voice will come out.
Answer.
Please answer.
Heo Joon Jae changed it.
Heo Joon Jae.
Where are you right now?
I'm where I was earlier, where I was waiting.
I had something urgent come up.
I have to go somewhere so hurry up and go home right now.
All right.
Can you go? Do you have money?
I have money.
Okay. I'll get into a taxi right now. There's a taxi.
Yeah. Okay.
Don't hang up and get in.
Do you know the house address?
Yeah, I know it.
Ahjussi.
Personal  Best TAXI Driver
What happened? Why are you quiet? Cheong.
Sim Cheong.
Hello?
You wore a hat today also?
He wore a police hat and a black hat too.
The man that wore the hat is Ma Dae Young, right?
It's Ma Dae Young, right?
Cheong! Cheong!
Tell me what you see around you! Where are you right now?
Heo Joon Jae. Where we agreed to meet when it first snowed.
That's looking bigger and bigger.
The phone got disconnected. Call again.
The cell phone is powered off right now...
She's not answering.
As for our "next time" we meet over there.
- Namsan?  - Yeah. Let's meet there.
Namsan. They're going in the direction of Namsan.
Ma Dae Young is disguised as a taxi driver and he's driving.
Go towards Namsan also, hurry!
What, should I really go?
Well, go for now.
If this is really a scam, I'm really going to kill you dead and go to prison.
If something happens to that woman I'm going to kill you dead too.
Hurry up and take these off.
You bastard.
I'm feeling uneasy about what you punk are doing.
What are you doing?
Hurry up and call the local patrols near Namsan and request their cooperation.
Notification  GPS locator confirmation not possible
Why is the GPS locator not working?
The taxi thought to have Ma Dae Young driving it is fleeing Namsan bound.
Yongsan, Seodaemun district, and Central, I'm requesting check points be set up in the vicinity.
Namsangongwon-gil
Tell them to check among the recently stolen private taxis passing through that direction.
He's presumed to be driving a stolen taxi so confirm reported stolen taxi lists
I expect meticulous confirmation.
You have to tell them that there's a woman that's been kidnapped.
There's a woman inside.
Early 30's.
- Long hair.  - Long hair.
She's really pretty too.
They say she's quite a beauty.
Let's go quickly.
Does he think he's in some taxi?
Checkpoint
Do they say nothing has been caught in the inspections yet?
- Not yet.  - In order not to get caught and escape
there's only one road...
Take the side road toward the tunnel from Hanoelro.
Take it?
That's the only way out of Seoul that avoids checkpoint inspections.
Hey, take it. This punk's specialty is scams and his co-major is in escape.
You can't know the Seoul city streets better than me.
That's something to proud of.
Call me.
Call for me.
I will hear.
I will hear and come.
Love Hospital
What are you doing?
Don't try to get up. You won't be able to move anyway.
I have no intention to do anything to you. My personality is such that I can't stand being curious so I'm trying to confirm something.
What are you confirming?
I keep dreaming these strange dream frequently.
At first I thought they were just dreams but those dreams
I keep getting the feeling that they could be true.
Why are you confirming your dreams with me?
Because they have to do with you.
Dreams to do with me?
It's not precise but inside the dream
It's really a mermaid.
it seemed like you were a mermaid.
When you were inside the water a mermaid, and when you were on land you appeared to be human.
And the tears that mermaid shed became pearls.
I thought that being a nobleman in a past life at first didn't make sense either.
I kept getting a strange thought.
Well, if I threw you
into that water.
It would confirm it.
They say that there isn't a car that's been caught in the inspections yet.
Until when do we have to keep going?
Detective Jang. Isn't this the way to that hospital in Ma Dae Young's treatment records?
Yes, that's right.
But that hospital was closed down the year before last.
That's true. That's why we struggled so much in finding those hospital treatment records.
- Go to the hospital.  - We're going there right now.
Don't keep ordering us around.
Hurry up and go.
Hey, Heo Joon Jae!
Operating Room Restricted Area
Cheong. Cheong.
I don't know what kind of dream it was
but if I was a mermaid in it, did I give you a warning of some sort?
A mermaid doesn't leave alone a human who has touched her body.
A mermaid can erase whatever memories she wishes.
Be careful Sir. If you mistakenly touch a mermaid
they say the mermaid will take your soul and erase your memories.
I heard this is the way that the mermaids have to protect themselves from humans.
Whatever you want to decide is the price.
Would it even compare to a hundred roots of wild mountain ginseng?
I heard that the quality of oil that's collected from a mermaid
is unbelievable.
I will definitely make that mermaid mine again.
I'm going to kill that immature official fellow by own hand.
Until she dies I'm going beat the tears out of her drop by drop.
I'm thinking to spread the pearls on the path you
walk upon. - A foolish love
makes me so happy.  - Die.
And don't be born again.
Among the fishermen, there was one who put his hands on a mermaid
and I heard he went insane.
The moment you put your hands on me
you will lose all of your memories.
That is the way in which a mermaid can protect herself from humans.
Confirm it.
Heo Joon Hae. I'm scared.
I'm sorry
that I came so late.
I'm sorry.
Aish! Ma Dae Yound, you bastard. Where did you go?
Requesting back up support.
Joon Jae, did you see the news?
There's a huge commotion going on right now in Seoul with searches and inspection checkpoints to catch Ma Dae Young.
Hey, and you know who the detective in charge of Ma Dae Young is?
Don't be shocked, okay? That Mi Mi Hong Dong Pyo.
I think I'm that Mi Mi Hong Dong Pyo.
What's the Mi Mi stand for?
Michin Misery (crazy miserable).
I'll be right back.
Sit down since you're here.
Wow.
I... From before, if I ever met you
I always wanted to tell you.
When I die I'm thinking to donate everything I have to society.
Are you going to take us in?
Heo Joon Jae. That person earlier...
Let's talk about it later. You had a hard time today.
Don't think about that and don't worry.
Today sleep here deeply. I'll sleep up in the attic room.
They say you suffer when you leave home. It's so nice to come home.
That's right.
So don't go out so recklessly and just keep staying here.
- Forever?  - You can't forever.
Why?
This is a long term deposit lease ending in two years.
There's a lot left though, about a year and a half?
- Long term deposit lease?
In truth, I'm saying this house isn't mine.
What's mine is only this furniture and baggage.
Later we have to move all of it.
- Move all of it?  - Yeah.
- Who?  - You have to move all of it.
Since you're going to go with me.
Together?
Go on and sleep. I have some more things to discuss with the person outside.
To be frank, I should ask the woman inside over there a few things.
You can't because she's really in shock.
And with regards to Ma Dae Young I know more than her so ask me instead.
If Ma Dae Young attempted to take that woman there should be a reason.
I told you. It's me.
Tae Oh, show them Mae Dae Young's security cam footage.
Look, isn't it from that day that that loan shark died?
It is. I was right.
He came to that house wearing that. Not long ago he
Joon Jae. Shortly after 7 p.m. at 29-21 Banji in Yeonjoong-dong, I'll see you. I'll be waiting.
What's this?
It's an ajusshi that I'm close with, but after his DUI incident he's been in a coma.
Then I received such a text message.
Joon Jae went out because of that text and almost died.
It was disguised as an accident and it probably means Ma Dae Young is somehow involved.
Have you ever scammed Ma Dae Young himself or his acquaintances?
No
Let's not be so confident. You never know.
Anyway, Ma Dae Young is one thing and you all are--
But then, it won't be easy to put us in for fraud.
None of the victims have ever reported anything.
They probably can't because it's all money that wasn't clean anyway.
Is it not a crime if they can't report it?
And you, you always go somewhere pretending to be me.
It isn't like I pretended to be a police detective and embezzled.
I never injured anyone.
As for impersonating a public servant, don't I only need to pay a fine?
This thing really. If at least he couldn't be so eloquent.
Let's first catch that crazy bastard Ma Dae Young. I'll help.
Does he get caught because you said something?
I was planning on catching him from the beginning.
Let's talk about the problem we have between us after catching Ma Dae Young.
After that I'll do as you ask Detective.
- On what? Do I take you on your word?  - I even let you know where I live!
Now that I have a lot to lose I can't go running away anywhere I please anymore.
Even if you don't believe me, just do so. Just for today could you please just go?
You can move it all later.
Someone will move all of these? Who will?
You need to move all of them since you'll be going with me.
What does it mean to move a "yearly deposit home" together?
Does that mean let's get married? No that's not it.
It didn't seem like he was saying let's get married.
He told me that I have to move all the stuff.
Did he perhaps need me so I could move all the furniture?
Do you think that's what that meant?
Idiot.
Does he mean he'll marry someone else and expects me to move the furniture?
No, I don't mean that. That's not it.
- But then...  - But then?
"But then" what? What then?
why did he touch my hair?
He definitely lovingly fluffed it.
So cute.
Heo Joon Jae maybe it's not that he only plans to like me but does he already like (me)--
Has he fallen deeply for?
Is this the start of romantic love?
Oh no! Oh my god! What do I do!
No...for him to like me, he bickers too much.
Is that how it is? Why did he touch my hair? He touched it because he liked it.
His pj's are green too. Oh my is he even turning his whole body green for me?
A green light for me to come! Is that how it is?
Hey! Let's go to sleep! Please!
What, Heo Joon Jae?
- You're not asleep yet?  - Yeah I'll go to sleep.
Why don't you hurry off to sleep since you're tired.
Don't do things like thinking too much. You have to sleep deeply.
That way you can wake up early and watch the morning soaps you love so much.
Ok. Good night.
Ok, good night.
subtitles ripped and synced by riri13
Don't think, okay? Go to sleep.
His tone was slightly angry. Why is he mad?
Please don't. Stop.  - No that's not it. He said, "good night" and smiled at me. - Please!
What's the significance of his smile?
He worried about me. Does he perhaps like me?
No...that's not it. He told me to move all the stuff.
Does...does that mean let's get married?
It was a slightly annoyed voice. That's so strange.
Goo Baek's Dad is not picking up. All this time he's not answering.
I think things will still take some time on this side.
Because they're on a different level.
- Did we try for naught?  - Honey!
In this world, without black (illegal) money, it is difficult too and all for nought!
If we put in effort, it's bound to yield rewards back to us.
- Does it?  - Let's think.
We should once again try on Chairman Heo's front. Right?
Hello Madam, you've been doing well right?
Oh Madam, we need to have a
Shall we then?
Yeah around 7. I'll see you there. Okay.
Did the two of you not sleep well? Your faces look so haggard.
Yeah, because I had a lot to think about.
Yeah, because she had stuff to think about.
What?
Because she was moving around, I couldn't sleep well.
- I moved around? - Yeah. A lot.
Did he get angry at me just now? Why is that?
Did he start to dislike me in the span of one night?
What did I do? He told me let's move a "yearly-loan house" together and was even green. Why's he mad?
No! It's not!
It's that now that I think about it. It didn't seem like you were being particularly noisy when you moved around.
Let's eat.
Hyung, shall we go out today and buy a tree?
- A Christmas tree?  - I want to go! I want to go too.
No, you stay home.
I will go with Hyung Nam Doo and Tae Oh. The three of us will go,
so you stay home. By yourself.
You want me to be by myself?
Stay home alone.
I'm telling you to go inside the water you like.
Why is he saying I should stay home alone?
Is it that he's telling me to in torment by myself?
Why? Just why?
No. That's not it.
As you live with three guys,
there might be things you can't do.
That's true.
Yeah. So do those.
For us, 7 o'clock. We won't be back at the house before 7,
so until then, you stay in this house alone.
So do the things you want. Do that.
Think you're the house owner.
Is he telling me to clean? That I should think I'm the house owner and clean?
No, cleaning, chores, not those kinds of things!
The thing you can do to relax most comfortably.
Do those kinds of things!
-What are you doing?-Hey, that looks like it hurts. Why are you pinching her cheeks like that?
Weirdly, I want to.
Why is my face so hot? Is it hot because he pinched it?
No? It's hot even without pinching.
What's with me?
Then let's buy a tree,
a wine, and some things to eat, and have a simple Christmas party.
-Invite Si Ah too.-Sure.
Okay. Then I'll come out after I get ready. Let's head out after 10 minutes.
This hurts a lot. For some weird reason, I like it.
What is this feeling? Am I going crazy?
I can't be the only one feeling something good like this. I want Heo Joon Jae to feel this too.
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey!
When you're alone,
do what you want. For sure.
What's this now?
I couldn't think of anything for a short while.
What does this mean? What's the meaning of this?
What does he think about me? What is it? Does he like me or what?
What happened? What's the meaning of this? What happened?
Two of the friends said they would be the witnesses.
That neither has a conflict of interest in the matter of being entrusted with the task
has been confirmed through the paperwork you have sent in advance.
But, Sir,
what is the reason for rushing the making of your formal will.
About my son Joon Jae.
I want to give him all of my fortune.
Whether it's stocks, real estates, international assets, whatever it is.
You're saying everything?
Everything that I can within the limits.
But, Sir, the current wife
and Heo Chi Hoon need to receive at least the legally reserved amount of inheritance.
That way, there won't be inheritance lawsuit problem later.
If I exclude those,
how much inheritance will Joon Jae possibly receive?
He can receive at most 9/14.
You must be busy during the year end holiday season.
Thank you for giving up this time.
Nah, I'll pay today.
We only ever ate good things from you guys.
No, no. I'll pay.
Would you like some Chinese wine (白干兒)?
Sounds good.
Please take some.
For me, too.
Madam, let's do a cheers.
For your family and my family's friendship,
as well as for our business alliance.
Cheers!
I'll one-shot it.
Have some.
You know, my husband is not brave enough
to bring this up, even though he's been wanting to...
About our co-investment or stock sharing-
Oh, wait.
Hello, attorney Lee. Yes, of course.
Yes, yes. Then please work hard.
Unnie.
Unnie?
You're a lot older than I am.
You're old! So you're an unnie.
Here, Unnie. Let's drink a glass.
Jin Joo. You're very drunk.
I'm very drunk, but, to be honest,
I'm very sad at you.
Soy sauce seasoned crab, monkfish stew,
Kimchi, and fermented salty side dishes; With all the things I've sent you,
if you put all those together, you could open up a nice full course Korean restaurant!
You received all those and now you ignore me?
Do you just "eat and run"?!
If you take it everyday, you should know how to give some times, seriously!
Why are you playing hard to get? Huh?
Am I dating now? Huh?!
Secretary Kim, get the car ready.
Let's leave.
Shut up!
Listen carefully.
Listen to me, okay?
Are you going to include us or not?
Somber up and come out carefully.
Since she is so mean like this, she seduced her high school classmate's husband. Geesh!
What? What did you just say?
I read everything in Gangnam Tabloid!
You stole your high school friend's husband.
That friend went missing, and their son got thrown out.
It says you've completely ruined that family.
Wow, seriously!
You really are something else, eh?!
Amazing.
Wait, what's going on? Why isn't our Cheong coming out?
Are these clothes better? No. Heo Joon Jae doesn't like short things.
This is long. No, no. This is too hot.
You shouldn't be hot.
Is this moderate?
I need to look prettier than Cha Si Ah.
Wow, today you're Party Cheong, Party Cheong.
Wow, pretty!
Come over here.
I told you not to take a picture, didn't I?
This rascal. I told you! Come over here.
Come over here!
Stop drinking, Dog Nam Doo.
Merry Christmas.
I want to try too.
You do?
Wow, there's nothing Cheong can't do.
I want to do it again.
You're good.
I can't really do it, Joon Jae. You hold this and...?
You just put this here and you hit right here.
Why am I uselessly doing this well?
Because I'm already doing this well, Heo Joon Jae can't teach me.
Why am I so good at this?
Even if I try to stop, I can't. The snack is too good.
Hey, don't laugh and teach me correctly.
Is it good?
You came again?
Yeah, Cha Si Ah.
This is my house, so I go outside and come back.
Of course I'll have to move with him when Heo Joon Jae moves his lease after a year and a half.
What? Are you marrying Heo Joon Jae?
Although we didn't say it was a definite thing,
we did say there was a plan like that between us.
Plan? What plan?
The plan for Heo Joon Jae to like me.
-Joon Jae said that?-Yeah.
Looks like Joon Jae did it again. He says that a lot.
-What?-You're always saying this inside, right?
"Oh? Does he like me? His gaze is a gaze that he likes me."
"Is it not? Is he only treating me well?"
But what does he mean by him having a plan to like her?
"Does he like me?"
"But why hasn't he said to date him? Does he not like me?"
Can you hear something from inside?
Not that I can hear anything,
this is called "managing the aquarium." (Managing several potential suitors)
Managing the aquarium?
They throw out the bait and then keep them inside the net,
and then having them keep high expectation.
You can't handle Joon Jae.
I am capable of not being swept by it and can stay by Joon Jae.
That's exactly what you are. A fish captured inside an aquarium.
I'm not a fish.
No. You're a fish.
It's enough that you were here for this long. Now go back to where you lived before
whether it's a river or an ocean.
Pick up.
The phone cannot be reached.
Mother.
Chi Hyeon.
Why? Do you have something to say?
Who's my father?
Gosh,
your father is sleeping in the master bedroom now.
My biological father.
Why? Did you suddenly become curious?
I was always curious, just couldn't ask you, is all.
Hey Chi Hyeon,
Your real father is loving you
in his own method. He knows well that not appearing in front of you,
and you not knowing him are
the things that would make you happy, hence isn't making an appearance.
So you don't have to know that. Okay?
The fact that you have to know is the fact that the onlypeople trustworthy in this world
are you and me, only the two of us.
Yes, Mother.
It seems to be true.
It really seems to be true.
Is that you? Come and have a seat.
Why, Noona (elder sister)?
Come have a drink.
What's this for?
Silly kid. If you wanted to have a picture of me, all you had to do was ask.
Why would you take a picture secretly in such a crowded place?
Noona, that earlier isn't what you're thinking, but...
Don't bother explaining. Makes you appear unseemly.
I told you. Though I can't accept your feelings,
but don't look down on your love.
Don't do things in hiding, but instead fess up to me of your pain.
I'm not in pain. I'm saying this because I'm really not hurting.
Listen well, Tae Ho. It's been 7 years for me.
From the first day of my college entrance when I saw Joon Jae, and from then for the 7 following years,
I've been watching from a far and maintained this type of relationship
continuously. Why do you suppose that is?
You're curious, right?
It's because I didn't let on.
Without burdening the object of your interest to remain neat & clean.
While maintaining the appropriate distance.
Don't you think the mature person's love
would be something like that?
Joon Jae, do-o-o-n't hang up.
Are you guys the only people with a plan?
For me, I won't do the engagement party with you Joon Jae,
but go straight to getting married.
You know that's trendy these days.
I'm gonna do exactly that.
Either on the Jeju island Ol Leh trail or buckwheat field in Gang Won Province
hang up an iron cauldron...
That's what I'll be doing there.
When we deliver a baby, I won't do the 100th day ceremony,but give a charitable donation to UNICEF.
That's right now... That's now very much...
trendy.
Joon Jae! Joon Jae, don't hang up.
By the way,
what is it that I've done so far, huh?
Have I been making porridge to serve the dog? (wasted time and energy)
Is that I've been doing?
Joon Jae! Joon Jae!!
If you get so loud in the middle of the street, the police will be called.
Quickly go home.
Who are you with? Tae Ho?
Joon Jae!
Ask Tae Ho to take you home. I'm really going to hang up now.
The end of the year did come I guess, seeing how Cha Si Ahis placing a drunk call.
She seems to hold it in well until the end of the year when she does that once.
Why...are you here in that posture?
Get on up to your room now.
What's the matter?
Heo Joon Jae, are you seeing me as a fish?
Are you regulating your fish-farm? (managing many potential suitors)
Aren't you going to go up?
What is this attitude? Is he inferring that since he can't standthe sight of me that I should go up?
Does he mean for me to get lost?
Nah-nah-nah no. Never mind.
I'll go up. You sleep here today too.
And,
don't think anything at all tonight and sleep well.
I beg you.
My heart gave a thump again.
Would it ever be possible to escape this fish-farm?
So much for sleeping...
I just want to go to sleep, seriously. How many days has this been?
Are you okay?
After meeting up with the wife of Chairman Heo, what...?Did you go to the 4th rounds or something?
You were totally wasted.
What... did you speak of something deep?
Are you going to eat and run?
Shut up!...broken the home into pieces...
You are a bad bitch, seriously!
This probably is a dream, right?
Please tell me it's a dream, huh?
Come on seriously. Tell me it's a dream! A dream!
What's gotten into you?
Oh, Missus. I think I need to run to the hospital to pick upa blood pressure medicine.
Go on. Go on ahead.
What brings you here, Ms. Jin Joo?
Secretary Kim told me that [you] were here, and so...
Missus. Please just kill me.
- You're asking me to kill you?- Yes, please.
My drinking habit is usually pretty neat, you know?
But why do you suppose I did that yesterday?
Come on. Why not tell the Gangnam gossip in detail?
Go-go-ssip? Oh my gosh, Missus. I don't watch things like gossip!
Missus. Whatever I may have said yesterday
that isn't me. That isn't An Jin Joo.
Just please consider some beast living within me wailed...
Can't you just consider it that?
Oh god, Missus.
Is your pallor originally red?
You seem to be red every time I see you.
Can you teach me that?
What?
Computer. There's a limit to [learning] it through TV.
They say that you can find out all sorts of things using computers?
Then can you know that, too?
What?
- If someone's on the hook.  - Hey! What are you guys doing up there?
How to now be on the hook or how to find out if someone's just flirting with you. That kind of stuff.
Get off each other!
Don't whisper in ears, just think instead.
Hey, Tae Oh. Why are your ears getting red?
Don't get them red. What are you guys doing?
Tae Oh's going to teach me computer.
- I will teach you.  - No!
I have to find out if you like me or are just flirting with me.
Hey, do I have to say it out loud so you know?
What?
What did you just say?
I-I mean do you have to say it out loud to teach you computer.
Can't you just learn by looking from the side like this a few times?
Fine. If you want to learn it from Tae Oh, learn it from him.
I will show you how to search online, first.
Okay.
That's weird. You've been taking your medication diligently,
why did it get worse?
I'm dizzier and it's still blurry, I can't even see your face well.
We can't just leave it like this. In worst case, you can lose your sight.
Doctor, what do we do, then? We have to do everything we can now before it gets too late.
At least it's the outside hardwear that's hurt, so we can do a surgery.
If if was the inside retina that was damaged and progressed to a macular degeneration,
we probably didn't have any other way.
Right.
I guess we have schedule a date for surgery, then.
Yeah, we should. Surgery is one thing, but you need to be careful after, too.
Did you really not get poked or hurt your eye?
No.
Sit here. I'll go check out.
Okay.
Subtitles brought to you by The Blue Sea @ Viki
Honey, I'm done. Let's go.
Yeah.
Honey, shall we go have lunch with Chi Hyeon?
- Sure.  - What do you want?
- Whatever.  - Whatever?
I'm sorry. We weren't that closed when we were at school yet I barged in.
It's okay, Ji Hyeon.
I changed my name. I had reasons.
- My name is Kang Seo Hee.  - Oh, really?
Anyway, welcome. My husband's work is going well,
so we have plenty money.
It's not easy raising a kid by myself after my husband suddenly died like that.
I was going to get an insurance anyway.
I will get one and I'll tell my husband to get one, too.
I'll let him know, so go visit him at work sometime.
- Thank you so much.  - No problem.
[Breaking News; Fugitive Ma Dae Young attempts abduction of a woman in 30s. Increased uneasiness of citizen.
Heo Chi Hyeon
What?
Wow, it's the real son.
It's me. The fake son.
Do you think you got close to me?
No way. How can a fake
get close with the real one?
- Are you drunk?  - Joon Jae.
I don't think
I'll be able to protect your father.
Protect your own father.
I will protect my mother.
What are you doing?
It's my last warning
and the present
- from the fake to the real.  - What?
Are you just going to take this room now?
I waited to ask you something.
What?
You know...
Why did you tell me that you are planning to like me? Why did you come to save me?
Why did you hug me? Why did you touch my hair? Do you like me? Or just like Cha Si Ah said, are you just flirting with me?
There are all kinds of things in the internet but even though I searched all day, it doesn't have somthing about your heart.
I don't know. Do you like me? Or not?
Nothing.
Why don't you ask what you were going to ask?
No. It's not sorted out, yet.
You're not the kind who sorts out. You're the kind who just spurts out.
No. I want to sort it out before I say it. I'll think it over tonight.
You will think it over tonight?
Yeah. I'll think about it all night.
And I'll talk to you after I sort everything out, tomorrow.
Wait.
How much of thinking are you planning to do?
Just all night.
All night? I don't know what kind of thoughts you have in your head.
I don't know, but whatever that is, can you not do it?
What is this, now? Is he saying to not think of him?
What is that look? Is he mad at me? Why?
Now it's nice and quiet.
From now on, don't think about anything,
and don't do anything.
♬ I want to approach you. ♬
♬ And be embraced. I want to stay ♬
♬ in the world called you ♬ ♬ I owe you I miss you I need you I love you  ♬
♬ Eternally in your arms ♬
♬ There will be much that I don't know ♬
♬ Please show me your world and your heart ♬
♬ Will you come to me and take my hand ♬