Subtitles brought to you by The Blue Sea @ Viki
Thinking... how much are you planning to do?
The whole night.
Whole night?
You... I don't know what kind of thoughts you have in your head.
I don't know but whatever that is
can you not do it?
What does this mean? Does he mean not to think of him?
What does that look mean? Is he mad at me? Why?
Now, it's nice and quiet.
Starting now don't think of anything.
And... don't do anything either.
♬ This is love story  ♬
♬ I cannot hide ♬
♬ My two eyes which only see you ♬
♬ I cannot close them ♬
♬ This is amazing ♬
♬ Even if everything in the world ♬
♬ Were given to me ♬
♬ I cannot exchange it with you, my love. ♬
Heo Joon Jae.
There's definitely a reason that the village head released the sky lantern into the sea.
When it is released into the sea the mermaid will definitely
come above the water.
No. Se Hwa!
Are you alright?
It's okay. You're no longer in a dream.
- Did you have a scary dream?- Yeah.
It was scary.
How come?
I know.
I originally didn't have anything to be afraid of since I had nothing to lose.
But now
it's scary. Now that I might lose things...
Who?
- Huh?- Se Hwa? - Come again?
I heard it all you know going, "No. Se Hwa."
Who is it? Who is Se Hwa?
Is she also a fish that you are flirting with?
- No. It's not that.- Then who is it?
Is it a WOMAN?
Well, yes she's a woman.
Oh it's a woman I see.
Is she pretty?
Should I tell you honestly?
You need to tell me honestly. We promised not to lie.
She's pretty. Very.
Really pretty?
Then what about me?
You are pretty too.
What the... you should decide. What are you trying to do by saying both of us are pretty?
Are you two-timing us like an octopus? Is that how it is?
What? You also know how to say those?
Hurry and answer me. I'm speaking with Gungsuh font on.
What's "Gungsuh" font?
It's Gungsuh font. It means I'm serious. Don't you know this word, Heo Joon Jae? It's all over the internet.
Anyway, hurry and answer because I'm speaking in Gungsuh font.
Well, of course...
it's you.
Is this really true? He's not just telling me to keep me under his thumb?
How does he feel about Se Hwa? Is he for real?
Isn't he scamming me? Am I really prettier than Se Hwa?
Where does she live? What does she do?
I'm saying it's you.
Gosh darn dog-good.
In this case this word, dog-good. Doesn't mean that I like dogs. It means that I like this a lot and very much.
Everyone on the internet uses it. If you don't know, then you should memorize it, Heo Joon Jae.
Where are you going?
I have to go up.
Don't go.
Heo Joon Jae, are you drunk?
That's something you say when you are drunk.
Let's just say that I'm drunk. Anyway, don't go.
I won't go.
Heo Joon Jae.
Huh?
You know...
Earlier, that...
What about that?
No, earlier that...
This?
This... can I not forget this one?
Of course you can't. Would it do if you forgot?
Deal. I won't forget this one this time.
Let's go to sleep
I need to sleep with you like this so that I won't have scary dreams.
Heo Joon Jae, I wish you will have a scary dream everyday.
Scary dream... I really like it.
♬ I love you, idiot! ♬
♬ It means I'm waiting for you ♬
♬ That's what's happening, idiot. My heart keeps palpitating ♬
♬ My heart goes bounce. Bounce. Why don't you know my heart  ♬
Heo Joon Jae likes me.
Heo Joon Jae likes me!
Heo Joon Jae likes me too. Heo Joon Jae likes me. Heo Joon Jae likes me.
Heo Joon Jae likes me.
At this rate what if this bursts!
It's so pipping hot, seriously. Why do I feel so hot? (She's embarrassed)
My strength... I can't control it!
The Legend of the Blue Sea
Episode 13
Yes.
Ahjumma, can you get me some honey water...
What are you doing?
Seriously, I feel like throwing up when I see alcohol.
Soju and even with kimchi at that, seriously.
Ahjumma, why were you drinking? Did something happen?
What?
Because I'm thankful.
Having someone ask me what is wrong has been such a long time ago.
What's wrong? What happened?
Honestly, I met my ex-husband today.
Oh my! Coincidentally?
Even though
our eyes definitely met but he pretended not to see me.
Really?
He may be taken aback, is that why?
I can understand if he was taken aback or flustered,
but he just really...
had the gaze of looking at a complete stranger.
There must be things that time cannot heal.
Time has gone by like this.
But it still hurts.
What are you doing? You said you feel like throwing up even at the sight of alcohol.
How can I not drink after listening to this?
Ahjumma, don't drink soju. Let's drink wine.
Here. How could you have lived with that kind of jerk?
Let's have a drink.
I was also really upset today.
Why?
That woman whom I always serve side dishes to...
No... after drinking...
I acted up in front of that woman.
Because I did so, you can't imagine how coldly she shrugged me off.
I even knelt and she just pretended not to see.
You even knelt?
Yeah. I did.
But honestly, I didn't say anything wrong.
That woman, stole the husband of her schoolmate
to secure that position.
She's really foul-hearted right?
The 1st wife didn't receive a single farthing of alimony
And she just left as if she was chased out.
They don't know any news of her.
She's missing.
Which household's story is that?
You probably don't know this person very well. There's a person named Heo Il Joong.
He's a real estate chaebol. Out of say 3 or 4 useful buildings in Gangnam, at least one are theirs.
They're really no joke.
But do you know what's funny about that family, they are developing a new city.
But then, they won't let us get involved you know?
We offered up so many side dishes.
But she won't let us get involved.
That household was that one?
I told you it is.
My side dishes.
That household is the one you kept on bringing my side dishes to.
But then if they continue to ignore me like this then I won't just stand still.
I will spread that rumor through the whole Gangnam!
My mouth... does what it says it will do.
The world is so small.
It is. So small. The rumors would spread in no time.
Just they wait and see.
You fixed the contents of the will according to what I told you, right?
So that everything will be inherited by Chi Hyeon and me.
Yes, however...
we need to make sure the minimal amount of inheritance needs to be in Heo Joon Jae's name
And about Representative Lee and Executive Director Jeong? They'll be witnesses right? Everything's been agreed upon right?
Yes, well it was done.
But will it really be okay?
Everyone won't do it for free, right?
The same goes for you, too.
If this case goes well, you will can probably set up a law firm.
I arranged it as you told me to.
Notaried Last Will and Testament  Drafted on December 28, 2016,
the last will and testament of Heo Il Joong.
Have you confirmed it?
Yes. We have.
CEO, please affix your stamp.
I can't see properly so where is it?
Here.
Seems like a lot has changed.
Yeah. Since I couldn't fall asleep and stuff so I fixed it up a bit.
Alone? This would have been so heavy.
It wasn't.
It was really light.
She's strength-Cheong. Strength-Cheong today.(Strength rhymes with Sim)
Heo Joon Jae likes me.
♬ Heo Joon Jae likes me.
Such a relief that only I could hear it.
♬  Heo Joon Jae likes me
Enough now. ♬ Heo Joon Jae likes
Good morning.
Heo Joon Jae!
Heo Joon Jae, when the lease expires where will we move to?
I'm not sure. There's still so much time left so I should think about it still. Why?
My health status is so good so I was thinking of moving the furniture one by one prior.
What?
Joon Jae about this kid, our Strength-Cheong.
Whose the one who decided to change her battery? Take it out. It's so disorienting.
- Why take it out? It's good. What do you want for breakfast?- Rice.
Pasta.
Why eat noodles early in the morning? Let's eat rice.
We don't have pasta noodles though.
I will go and buy. I will.
I said rice.
Will you? Go and buy.
Tomato pasta?
Call! (means deal like you would in poker)
Subtitles brought to you by The Blue Sea @ Viki
Grandma, I will help you.
- Oh no, it's heavy.- I'll pull it.
It's heavy though.
Thank you.
Look for a number.
There's none.
Still this car needs to be moved.
There was a car here before.
Did she go and make pasta noodles? Why is she taking so long?
Try calling her, Tae Oh.
Heo Joon Jae likes me.
She's almost here.
Almost here? How do you know?
I'm here.
Do you guys communicate through telepathy now?
Cute.
You know let's close up the Ahn Jin Joo case because the losses are too big.
I have new work I'm looking into.
No, this time it's not a bad thing. He's the worse person.
He's someone who amassed a fortune from voice phishing.
I told you I'm not doing it.
- You're not? - Yeah
As expected, Heo Joon Jae really likes me.
Eat.
Eat a lot.
What?
Sit down.
What now?
Are you sick of having to talk with me like this?
Did anyone say so?
Tae Oh found Ma Dae Young's taxi so we will be meeting with Detective Hong.
Nice going. A conman revealing to the detective his place of address.
Did you make a promise to meet up? Are you best friends?
Later on, you would probably will confess as a symbol of friendship.
What do you want to say?
Right. You... I know you are especially fond of Cheong.
But then how long have you met her? It hasn't been long. It's only been 3 months.
You and I are 10 years.
Are this and that the same?
Three months with Cheong is important but the 10 years with me is rubbish I guess.
I... made a promise with her. I want to keep that promise.
Didn't you make a promise with me? You said we'll work together until you find your mom.
Just with that promise, I took in a runaway teenager whose blood on his head hasn't even dried  (really young)
Fed him, clothed him, housed him and sent him to school!
You are the one mooching off and living in my house right now.
I was wondering why you didn't mention that.
Anyway, even if you tell me not to leave when the weather lets up, I was still going to leave.
When was it when I told you that the heater burst in my room. You didn't even fix it.
Now, I am exhausted from your indifference towards me.
Sit down.
Hey. There's an old saying: 빈천지교불가망(貧賤之交不可忘). 조강지처불하당(糟糠之妻不下堂)
You can't forget friends that you made when you were low and poor. You can't throw away your first wife (who went through hard times with you)
Are you my first wife hyung?
No! I'm the friend you made when you were poor and low.
Hey, let me ask one thing.
If Cheong and I fell into the water, who would you save first?
Hyung.
- Really? - Yeah
If I leave it be, I think Cheong would save you. I don't like that.
Nevermind me, what about Tae Oh?
You lured him, who was living well in Japan.
You lured him that nowhere else has faster internet than Korea!
I didn't say anything wrong, though.
What are you going to do about our simple minded Tae Oh who followed us here because of those words
you irresponsible punk!
Yes, Detective Hong.
Where are you now? I will go out.
Crime Scene Investigator
It's skill.
These... for people who hack.
Do it.
For now, only you said it. Whether Ma Dae Young drove this, we still don't know that.
Even if we watch the black box video, it was dark and he was wearing a cap so we can't tell who it is.
Something must come out, be it DNA or fingerprints.
He is soooo despicable.
I oughto! Can I hit him once?
I won't stop you.
We can't find a fingerprint.
You don't need to mind him. Didn't anything come out?
Ah, yes.
The only thing that's in the car is this doll.
Octopus. This is yours, right? The one you dropped?
Please take a look at the trash can nearby.
Yes.
I warned you. Who are you to command...
Hospital.- What hospital?
Since he abandoned the taxi so I let go of that question.
Since he fled from the hospital in a haste so he wouldn't have time.
There was a big container filled with water inside the operating room.
If Ma Dae Young moved that water container, there would still be fingerprints left.
But then, if that is the case, why did Ma Dae Young get water?
Out of nowhere.
You are quitting?
Oh my, why ahjumma? Did I do something that upset you?
No. Just, I want to rest.
No. It's not easy to find someone who works as hard as you do.
And at first, I thought you had a weird personality.
But I adjusted to it now.
I'm sorry. Because of personal reasons.
Ahhh.
Aren't you protesting to have your pay raised?
No. It's not like that.
Aunt. You should step out of this.
No. It seems like she has set her heart to it, so why hold her back, Unni?
Ahjumma, even if you go at least until we get someone to take over
work until then. That is manners.
Yes. I will work until you get someone else. I'm so sorry.
Then, for the mean time you are still working, right?
Let's go somewhere after I get off work.
Where?
I will send you the address, you just have to go there. Would that be alright, Unni?
Agh! That!
Over here.
Oh my world. How?
Thank you.- It's okay.
I'm so grateful so I should do something.
No, it's okay.
Then, bye!
Bye.
I met such a whacko.
Ahjummoni, I waited for 10 minutes. Why are you so late?
I'm sorry. I met a pickpocket on the way.
Whose house is this?
My boyfriend... to be's house.
Since your cooking matches their tastes, I leave it to your care.
Why aren't they opening?
Oh, Miss. Is this your house?
Ahh! Are you Cha Si Ah's mother?
She's not my mother. She's the ahjummoni working in our house.
But then, how do you know each other?
I told you I met a pickpocket earlier. She's the one who got my bag back.
Do you also hit pickpockets?
Yeah.
Leave it, I will do it.
That, seriously!
As expected, Heo Joon Jae. His room is also clean.
So that is the room that girl lives in?
Joon Jae, these are the files you asked for regarding Kin Dam Ryeong.
As I looked again when organizing the files, I think you and Kim Dam Ryeong really look alike.
Is she his mother? She's beautiful.
No. No, she's probably someone who looks like her.
Faces are just
like this and that.
What treatment did Ma Dae Young get from there?
Well, psychologic
He used to go once or twice for treatment and get prescriptions.
Then he would probably need medication to be able to drive even now.
If not, how would he be able to live?
Well, that could be.
As if. What crazy doctor would give treatment to a fugitive?
Right. We'll also check it.
Please stop right up front.
No, not here. A bit there. It's cold outside.
More, more, more.
Then, work hard.
I thought I was escorting a team leader. Why are we so obedient?
It's fake. Heo Joon Jae is just a bait to catch Ma Dae Young.
We are just using him.
Why do I always feel that that is not the case?
Now tell me about Joon Jae's mother.
I also don't know well. They got separated when he was 10 and he's looking for her until now. That's about it.
I don't know where she has been hiding well. She's going around and not leaving traces so I can't find her.
I want to find her. Where is she?
I really have confidence I could do well.
Is that so?
You don't know. It's something people in the internet use a lot.
Anyway, it's a relief since you're saying it's delicious.
Oh my. When is your boyfriend coming? I'm almost done.
Whose boyfriend? Perhaps Heo!
Should we go now?
Oh my, what's wrong with you Cha Si Ah?
Right now?
Yes. Right now.
I'm going.
Bye.
Let's go. Go straight.
A little bit more.
Go on. - Oh my, I could open it myself.
There's an urgent matter.
Elizabeth.
Who do you take after...
that you still can't do that multiplication table.
I'm back.- Yes.
What should I do with you?
Unni. - You're here.
Solve it, what are you doing?
Where did you go with ahjumma?- You said ahjummoni has a son, right?
Yes, why?
Have you heard anything about her son?
Well...
Her son is so good looking and...
He went to KAIST.
No... they don't keep in touch.
After she got divorced they lived apart and just heard news from each other from time to time.
Ahjummoni, are you teaching me now?
Unni, why is she like that?Are you my mother-in-law?
Oh my! It seems like I'm in talks for marriage.
No, I think she's set her heart to it so why hold on to her, Unni?
No, no.
What's wrong with her?
Why is 6x6 = 40? Aren't you going to get your head straight!
Aunt.
What are you doing in my room?
That... perhaps...
That picture...
is he your son?
That's right.
Your son doesn't look like his mom.
What do you mean? People always said he looked like me.
What's wrong?
I have thought about this... until now, ahjummoni-
Madam... can I call you mother?
Why am I your mother?
You seem like my mother or could be my mother.
Are you sick?- No.
It seems like I was sick before. Until now, I was not in my right mind.
Now rather, I have got back to my senses.
My throat is so dry. Can you get my a glass of water, mother?
No, no. Would you like a glass of water? Should I get you one?
No. I'm fine.
I will get you water.- No.
That is... The truth is...
What's wrong? Do you have something to say to me?
Just a little... just a little more...
I will tell you just a little later.
I'm so sorry.
Mother.
What's with her?
What's with you, Heo Joon Jae? You always told me "Hey, upper room come down."
Aren't you cold? When I looked earlier this side was a bit windy.
If it's cold you can sleep downstairs.- With you?
I will sleep up here.
No. It's not cold.
I have something I am curious about.
You... the day you were taken by Ma Dae Young.
Perhaps...
did that bastard get water?
Why?
Ma Dae Young knows.
That I am a mermaid.
He said he saw in a dream and wanted to personally confirm it.
But, Heo Joon Jae...
I can't tell you this.
Don't.
If it's something that's hard to say
you don't have to force yourself to say it.
I'm scared since that person has found out my secret.
You don't have to be scared.
Nothing will happen.
Nothing will repeat itself.
Whatever happened before
will not happen this time.
I will make it so.
Honey.
Seo Hee.
Honey!
Father!
Father.
Secretary Kim, please come here.
Father...
collapsed.
He had a lot of internal bleeding when he came to the ER.
But the surgery went well.
Thank you.
Is regular daily activities still possible?
We would need to observe after he wakes up from anesthesia and regains consciousness so it is difficult to say so.
I think your father is looking for you.
For a moment.
Father.
Yes, Father.
Joon Jae.
The belongings of Kim Dam Ryeong that was discovered seemed like it came from a sunken boat.
It seems like on the way to exile he died after the ship sunk.
So, did you protect her well there?
Why aren't you sleeping?
Heo Joon Jae, I think I know.- What?
Honestly, today I found out a lot.
Men, even though they're easy but they fall for hard to get women.
What is that exactly? Easy but hard.
They accept date offers but refuse skinship.
Why? Such a good thing. Why refuse it?
So annoying.
You should refuse the second time
Refuse the second time but say okay on the third? Why?
First love to a man is?
Stigma
I heard that first love to a man is like a stigma.
Once it has been stamped on your heart it does not go away.
First love?
To you, Se Hwa is your first love.
Ahhh... that is not necessarily like that.
No, it's okay.
Since Se Hwa has left such a big stamp on your heart that is why you had such a sad dream.
That's not it...- I also found out.
That a man's first love does not come true.
So the stigma of first love, I will just leave time to have it tamped in.
It would have been a big trouble if I were your first love.
We almost couldn't have been came into.
Why?- Why?
I told you to get Heo Joon Jae, but you almost got caught while you were taking some other girl?
And you're not answering your phone.
Ji Yeon.- Get your head straight. Who's Ji Yeon?
I am Kang Seo Hee.
I had a dream.
What?
In my dream,
I saw my past life.
You might not believe it but it's true.
In my dream, Heo Joon Jae was in there and you too.
And that woman too.
That woman
is that the one you kidnapped?
Yeah. It's true.
In that dream, that woman...
was a mermaid.
You're not taking medication these days, right? That's because you're not taking medication.
Right, right. You might not believe but I'm going crazy.
I seem like a lunatic.
But then that dream is so vivid that I'm going crazy.
Now, we're almost there. CEO Heo is almost settled.
You just need to settle Joon Jae
and you, me and Chi Hyeon
we, three could live happily.
We have been long waited for this day.
Please get your head straight and take our medications.
Stop talking about that strange dream.
Yeah.
After that, I sometimes dreamed
but it doesn't go well.
And then one day, suddenly a strange scene comes to mind.
Ma Dae Young, starting from 2009
the person he went o the most to get treatment is this person.
Professor Shin Geon Won
So, do you want to see the end of that dream?
If that person desperately
has a story he wants to tell me
then the last... I would have to see through it.
Seeing that could somehow make a serious trauma to you,
would that still be okay?
Yes.
Neurology
My request, don't forget.
Look here.
If you leave such a request, how will I live?
When will we be able to see each other again?
What date is today?
The full moon of the third month.
At the young age of 27,
he died.
I just delayed the date that I knew of.
I see that I can't change it with my own strength.
Since the day for us to meet again is set,
we will meet again.
As good friends.
You need to set off now.
It's a relief that it's you.
I don't think of it as bad fate
I am just doing what I have to.
It's now.
Please turn the boat around.
What did you say?
Turn it around. There is something I must do.
It's impossible.
The life of the person whom I trust the most lies on it.
I am sorry, but it is impossible.
I also... can't help it.
I promise, once the thing I must do is done
I will continue to my own path. I ask of you.
If I can't protect that person, then then there would be no reason for me to live.
Stand back. This person
has saved my father who was falsely accused.
Didn't I say to stand back! I will take responsibility so turn the boat around.
Did we catch her? Look properly if we have caught her.
Shoot arrows or throw things. Even if you kill her, you have to catch her!
The one who catches her will be rewarded!
Yes!
Catch her!
This, this. Give it to me!
Aigoo! Who do we have here! Isn't it the Village...
Stop!
It seems like you still haven't grasped the situation. Who are you to command to stop or not
for a criminal!
A hunter hunts in the mountains and so a fisherman fishes in the sea is the law
isn't it?
It's blood! Blood!
What are you doing! Shoot arrows or what and catch her!
Yes!
Subtitles brought to you by The Blue Sea @ Viki
Se Hwa!
♬ I'm still dreaming. ♬
♬ The indistinct thought of someone who was ♬
♬ as radiant as the moonlight in the pale evening sky ♬
i♬ s evoked. ♬
♬ On the petals floating in the wind ♬
♬ I sense your warm fragrance and ♬
♬ our connection which was brief ♬
♬ and passed by now is my everything. ♬
♬ I am afraid being under the same sky together with you  ♬
♬ will be erased. ♬
♬ If we can walk as far as the blue sea's horizon ♬
♬ I won't let go of your hand. ♬
You can't do it. I live in the water
and later on the heaven that we will go to after we die, will it be the same or different?
The heaven that we will go to after we die... will be the same place.
Heaven doesn't have a distinction between water.
You know, Dam Ryeong.
If perhaps, we get to meet in another place
I wish you would be you and I would be me.
That way, I can recognize you.
That will be the case. If we do meet again
you are you and I will be me.
Will we be able to remember what we are talking about now?
I promise, even if we are to be born again,
I will find you, meet you and protect you.
Our conversation right now... I will remember it.
♬ I am afraidl being under the same sky together with you  ♬
♬ will be erased. ♬
♬ If we can walk as far as the blue sea's horizon ♬
♬ I won't let go of your hand. ♬
♬ I am afraidl being under the same sky together with you  ♬
♬ will be erased. ♬
♬ If we can walk as far as the blue sea's horizon ♬