Joon Jae.
I couldn't protect her.
In the end...
because of me...
Because I
could not protect her...
Will you be able to remember this story?
I promise.
Even after I am reborn, I will look for you, search for you, meet you,
love you, and protect you.
I will remember for sure.
After saying that,
after promising like that,
I forgot all about it.
Even though she was reborn and searched for me,
met me, and loved me,
I couldn't remember anything.
I only made her cry.
I could not
protect any of it.
Department of Neuropsychiatry
That guy was 27 years old.
He was the same age as me now. The girl was trapped in the net.
The guy dies while trying to save her.
And the girl stabs herself with the harpoon that stabbed the guy,
and died together with him. That is ..
That's their last story.
It is a sad fate.
Why were we reborn,
and why did we meet again?
For someone to be reborn, wouldn't that mean that there's a dream that hasn't been fulfilled yet?
That dream could be an unfulfilled love,
or it could be an unappeased greed.
Why would an ill-fate repeat?
Out of those two, which is the real ill-fate?
Is it the fate of you and the one who is trying to harm you,
or is it the fate of you and the one you love?
If you didn't love her,
and if she didn't love you,
then there wouldn't have been such a tragic ending.
Your love for each other ended up killing each other.
Is there a worse fate than that?
Do you think all this will repeat?
If you stop right here and send her back to where she had originally come from,
wouldn't you be able to avoid the tragic ending?
No.
The fact that everything has repeated is not a curse, but an opportunity.
An opportunity to change the ending.
Do you believe you can change fate?
There must be a reason to have remembered everything.
This time... I will protect her.
I will protect her for sure.
The Legend of the Blue Sea
Episode 14
Where is Cheong?
Ah! You startled me!
I said, where is she?!
I don't know. She went out a while ago. I'm sure she is nearby.
Wow, when a guy gets blinded by a girl, he becomes like that.
He was totally normal before.
Heo Joon Jae, did you have a scary dream?
The scary dream...
now I'm done with that. I won't dream it anymore.
- Is there anything you'd like to do?  - Hmm?
Something you want to do. Let's do them all.
- All of them?- Yes, all of them.
Heo Joon Jae, then should we enjoy some empty formalities and vanity?
What?
Actually, there are three levels of love: Romantic Love, Hot Love, and Dirty Love.
What we are trying to do is romantic love.
What's romantic love?
Well, it's like vain formalities.
Drink tea, watch movies, have meals together, plan a special event, confess love, things like that.
But all these are moving towards dirty love.
- Dirty?- Yes, dirty love.
I am also very curious about it, but I was told that is reserved only for the experts.
She said that if we carelessly approach it, it could end in a nasty way. So, we have to be careful.
So, we should enjoy vain formalities first.
Okay, let's do that.
What others do, let's do them all.
♬ Unusually bright sunshine ♬
♬ Warm wind embraces us ♬
♬ Walking with you in this beautiful day ♬
Say, "Ah."♬ My heart's beating like crazy ♬
♬ You keep saying weird things ♬
♬ Asking silly questions ♬
♬ The whole world knows how I feel ♬
There you go! ♬ The whole world knows how I feel ♬
♬ How come you don't know? ♬
♬I love you, silly ♬
That's right! We got this! ♬I love you, silly ♬
♬I'm waiting for you♬
♬You know, silly, my heart keeps on beating♬
♬My heart thump, keeps on thump♬
♬The warm wind blowing♬
♬Whispered to me it's today♬
♬I will confess my love that I was holding back♬
♬to you♬
Let's go.
♬  Near, far, wherever you are  ♬
It's okay.
♬  I believe that the heart does go on  ♬
♬  Once more...
You know,
I'm just saying this,
- so don't think too much about it, and answer me quickly.- Yeah.
The man saves the woman then dies in the movie we saw earlier, you know?
- Yeah, he did. - I mean, there's no way that would happen,
but if I died like that, what would you do?
I'd follow you.
Hey! What do you mean you'd follow me?! Are you crazy?!
And you need to give it some thought before you respond.
You told me to answer right away without thinking.
But still, who answers
as if they were being asked to go to the grocery store?
If you live, I have to live with you and if you die, I have to die with you.
Are you stupid?
Then what becomes of the man's death? The man died to save the woman.
The man says that at the end, "Please listen to my request."
"Promise that you'll live on and that you won't give up."
"Live until the end, find a good person and grow old happily."
Would you do that?
If I'm not in this world, would you meet another good person and grow old happily?
Yeah.
Of course, I would do that.
You would certainly do that?
So you do the same.
If, really if,
something happens to me,
you live on well.
Don't give up.
Good things, pretty things,
having them all.
What's going on, Heo Joon Jae? You said you were just saying this, but what's with this serious tone?
Is something really going to happen to you?
I told you it was just "if."
Promise me.
If anything happens, you won't think any weird thoughts.
Until the end,
you'll live well.
- I can't. -Why?
It feels like if I make the promise, something bad like that will happen.
So I said "if."
What if or what not, I don't like it!
So?
- You're not going to promise me?- No.
- You really won't?- I'm not going to!
You're not going to hold my hand now?
You're not going to talk to me?
- Promise me. -Are you talking about that again?
I told you I wouldn't. Why do I need to make that kind of promise?
Don't talk to me. I won't talk to you either.
Tae Oh, see me for a second.
What's wrong with the atmosphere between you two? Did you fight?
- He keeps saying weird stuff!- What weird stuff?
Like saying that if something happens to him, to live on well on my own.
- Huh?-It's weird, isn't it?
- Why?-It's come.
- What has come?- He grew tired of it.
The valid period of love is 3 months. It's been 3 months for you guys.
You need to overcome this well or it's a KTX (express train) headed towards your breakup.
Heo Joon Jae is not that kind of person.
Heo Joon Jae is especially that kind of person. I've known him for 10 years, and he hasn't had a girlfriend for more than 3 months.
They all break up before then.
That's right.
Hey!
Adjust the home security to the maximum setting.
Connect a line so I can monitor any space within 100m at any time.
When it detects any break-ins from outside, make it alert me right away.
Is it because of Ma Dae Young?
Hello, doctor.
Ma Dae Young?
It's been a while.
It's been 9 months, Doctor.
Heo Joon Jae came here, didn't he?
Don't think about lying because I saw it all.
Let me do what Heo Joon Jae did.
It seems like he saw his end, and I want to see mine too.
My end.
I think I need to know that.
So I can know why my life is the way it is.
From the moment I was born,
I always thought that I was being punished.
Why my life is like this,
I've wanted to ask.
I don't know why,
but I think the answer lies in that life.
It wasn't me.
Then who was it?
Who killed them?
You probably heard it already. Going forward, I will be the final approving authority.
I will personally lead the investors' meetings as well.
Is Chairman Heo very ill?
There are outsiders asking.
No, he has gone on a trip to relax and recuperate.
Even after he returns, he wants to step back from the workforce.
If you have anything to tell him, you can tell me.
But there are still things that need to be reported directly to him.
Why?
Are you afraid that I'll take out or add in the middle? Can you not trust me?
That's not it.
If you are on my father's side and cannot work under me,
you can leave now.
I'll take that as no one.
Can we start the meeting?
Father.
I met with the doctor, and he said the results are good.
Stay here for a few more days and then return home and receive regular outpatient treatment.
My eyes are worsening as time passes.
It's a big problem.
Oh, but because you just had surgery for a hemorrhage,
it's difficult to perform surgery for your eyes.
- For now, take your medication and just be careful not to worsen the condition.- Okay.
Chi Hyeon,
Yes, father.
You can contact Joon Jae, right?
Of course.
Ah, as soon as you fell, I contacted him.
- You did?- Yes.
It looks like he's busy.
I'm sure he'll come by soon.
I'll contact him again.
Okay.
Petty guy!
Narrow minded one! He is pouting over that thing and wouldn't talk to me?
I must've been blinded by love. I was naive then.
I lived in water all my life, and came to the land for the first time. So, what do I know?
The only guy that I happened to meet was that Heo Joon Jae. So I thought he was the best.
If Seoul was far, he should have told me that.
He flew in the plane. But, it took me 3 months and 10 days, just because of him,
and I swam all the way here that I thought my coccyx was about to fall off!
Why is he asking me to make that kind of nonsensical promise?
Stop it already!
Huh? What?
I told you to stop it. You are cussing me out inside right now.
Heol! How did he know?
He sure has a keen sense of what's going on.
I thought Heo Joon Jae was the only good looking guy in the world, but there are plethora of them on TV.
Does he think he is the only one who is handsome? He has the Prince-Syndrome and thinks everyone is attracted to him!
- Hey! - What?! - Ah, jeez!
Stop it already. If it's not meant to be, just break up.
Don't go out anywhere and just stay home.
I don't want to. I have an appointment.
Whom are you meeting?
See? You can't even tell me.
That's right. It has to be fair.
Then, you go with her, Hyung.
Why should I follow her?
I don't want to. It's my appointment. I don't need anyone.
Fine! Do whatever you want.
Good job, Cheong! He was hanging out with a "Me-mi" and he is about to become one.
What's "Mi-mi"?
Crazy Misery! Those who are into things like obsessiveness, and confinement.
But I don't mind things like obsessiveness and confinement.
Well, I sort of like it.
Because you are like this, he is getting tired of it.
Harden your heart and go strong!
Ahjussi, I'm sorry for not coming to visit you often.
I have a lot going on these days.
Can I tell you a story that no one could believe?
A very long time ago, you were a good friend of mine, and was always on my side.
This time, you were born a bit earlier and stood by me even when I was young.
Now, whoever made you like this...
I will find them.
If it's this person, blink twice.
Do you think there is someone who is related to Ma Dae Young around you?
Joon Jae.
I was really drunk last time. You must have been startled after receiving the call.
Saying that you will protect your mother, so protect my father, was also something you said because you were drunk?
Oh, did I say that? I must have been really drunk.
What about father's health being bad?
Oh, he is better now.
Hey, our father gave all the work to me and went on a trip with his friends.
Also, you will know this sooner or later...
Father got his will notarized.
He left almost all his assets to me and mother.
I told him to reconsider several times.
After meeting you the last time, he must have been heartbroken.
Were you always such a friendly guy?
I will hate my father on my own.
You don't need to encourage me to hate him.
If you keep doing this, it looks like you have some ulterior motive.
What about Cheong?
Is she well?
Why would you ask that?
That's right. I think of her time to time. I wonder if she is doing well.
Send my greetings to her.
Why should I?
Forget it, if you don't want to.
Oh, no. I don't know what to do!
Joon Jae, it turns out that the ajumoni at our house is your moth-
What bring you in here?
I heard you are sick. You couldn't even go to work. Try eating some porridge.
Oh, I got sick uselessly to make you do extra work.
What shall I do?
- Oh, it's okay. Call me after you are done so I can take it away.- Omo!
It's not like I don't have hands or feet. Who would I dare to call?
After I'm done, I will clean it up myself. Please do not mind me at all.
Alright, then.
Why are you doing this, Ji Young's aunt?!
I wanted to do this just once.
I am sorry, but I feel a bit uncomfortable.
I am sorry.
Subtitles brought to you by The Blue Sea @ Viki
Madam, Ji Young's aunt seems very sick.
Really?
You know, she is not her normal self. She's a bit strange.
She was never normal anyway.
-The number you have called-
Ah, Kang Seo Hee, this woman! She is ignoring my call again! Ha!
Seriously!
Excuse me.
Yes?
Their son...
Son? Chairman Heo's real son?
Yes, do you know something about that son?
Why are you curious about that, Ajumma?
Just because...
The son who's taking care of all of CEO Heo's business is
the son who was brought in by Kang Seo Hee.
His biological son ran out of the house 10 years ago, and no one knows where he is.
He ran out of the house?
He didn't go study overseas?
Study overseas? I don't think so. I heard it clearly that he ran away when he was in high school.
At that rate, if Kang Seo Hee's son receives all the inheritance, only the strangers are benefiting from his household.
Chairman Heo is not that bright.
What kind of father is he?
Why would he abandon his own son, and dedicate himself to someone else's son?
Ah, seriously. No matter how much he is head over heels over a woman, how could he?
Ajumma. What's the matter?
Excuse me. I need to go somewhere.
But it's time for children to come back from school. You need to prepare their snack.
Please go, mother-jumoni.
I will take care of the children, Unni.
subtitles ripped and synced by riri13
I will prepare kids' snacks and take them to after school academies.
That ajumma! Is she just doing whatever she wants because she is quitting or what?!
Unni, please!
She must have something to take care of.
Also, how can you call her "ajumma," seriously?!
I should call an ajumma, ajumma. What else should I call her then?
Who calls household helpers ajumma these days?
The going trend is, "Mother/Mother-in-Law."
Auntie, the age different between that ajumma and I are not that great for me to call her "Mother."
What's with "Mother."
"Mother" is nothing more than
sharing the same meal, and sleeping under the same roof.
She prepares my meals, and even do my laundry.
I've even let Mother wash my underwear!
Oh, I'm going nuts!
Chi Hyeon, go in first. Greet your father well.
Yes.
Are you leaving now? I came late on purpose, to come after you left.
Are you happy?
I'm sorry. Even though you may not believe me, I didn't do it on purpose.
Oh, really? I believe you. I need to believe it.
You have to raise my Joon Jae now. I am hoping that you are a good person more than anyone else.
That's right. I'm sure my husband told you already, but please don't show up until our Joon Jae becomes an adult.
That way he can grow accustomed to the new family.
Don't worry. I will love and raise him more than my own son.
- Who? - She says she is Mo Yoo Ran.
How dare she comes here?
Open it.
Oh my! How long has it been?
Have a seat.
What would you like to drink?
Ajumma, please excuse us for a while.
Are you going to stand up and talk? Have a seat.
Where is my Joon Jae?
Where is he?
Why are you asking me about your son? He is your son.
What?
It looks like you came knowing that your son isn't in our house. Why are you asking me about him?
I've never kicked him out. He went out on his own.
Also, my husband didn't really tried to look for him. So, what's why it came to this.
Oh, that's all it was?
I thought you two were keeping in touch, but I guess not.
You said you'd raise him well.
I was planning on. But what can I do when he went out?
Is this why you didn't allow us to me?
To make my son yours, my husband yours, and my position yours. Is that why?
You are really funny.
Hey! Don't pretend to be nice.
You just gave up.
If it were me, I would not gave up. I would not run away, leaving my son.
Just because I told you not to meet, you really don't meet him? Are you stupid?
What?
If you aren't going to have some tea, can you leave now? I'm really tired.
Kang Ji Yeon!
My name is Kang Seo Hee.
No, your name is Kang Ji Yeon.
My son... I will definitely find him and bring him back where he belongs.
You, too. I will take you back to your original position.
Yes, it's me.
Miss Cheong.
Alright!
You should watch out for cars.
Pay attention to incoming cars. He said not to be absent minded.
Who said that?
Someone that I like. We said we will go grocery shopping together.
Oh, that's right. Did you wait for long?
That's okay. This is the only schedule I have today.
Subtitles brought to you by The Blue Sea @ Viki
I can't tell her to stay home all day long.
Trail her well, without being caught.
You! Don't let your ears turn red!
When the stem is dried out like this, it's not fresh.
For fish, the gills need to be light pink color for it to be fresh.
These are not that fresh.
But it's not bad for buying it at the market.
I've never had fresh ones since I got here.
Where you are from must have a lot of good fish. Did you live near the ocean?
Something like that.
You must miss it.
But there are a lot of good food here, so it's okay.
Should we have some ice cream before heading back?
Yes, I was feeling really depressed, but I feel better now that I met you.
Thanks!
What is this?
She said she has someone to meet. Who's this ajumma?
She gets around and makes friends easily!
Here's the Ma Dae Young's psychological medical treatment report.
Have you by any chance heard of a woman named Kang Ji Yeon?
Kang Ji Yeon?
No. Why?
She is the only woman that's involved with Ma Dae Young, but I can't find her.
Her resident registration got cancelled due to unknown residency.
We are suspecting that they had a child between them.
Then, they could still be helping him to run away, whether it's the woman or the child.
That's possible.
Hand me that information, too.
Nam Do Hyang find people better than a typical cop.
Ah, geez!
How did I get entangled with this conman?
I will take responsibility, so turn the boat.
Our Police Office Hong is a much nicer person that you'd expect.
This guy! Are you crazy?! Do I look like your friend?
Jin Kyung Won
Jin Kyung Won?
Do you know him?
Since 2009, he treated Ma Dae Young most frequently once a few months.
Jin Kyung Won
Yes, he was my patient.
You know Ma Dae Young, Doctor?
Yes. He came occasionally and got treated.
He was suffering from anger control disorder and manic depression.
Has he come recently?
No.
He hasn't come lately.
It's here.
- Oh, you work here?- Yes.
This is Cha Si Ah's house?
You should have double checked everything before!
What's this?! We almost got in big trouble!
We almost got caught!
They were like that because it was Cha Si Ah's house.
Hmm? What is?
It's nothing. Here you go.
Bye then.
Bye.
Noona, that's not it.
What's not it?
Whatever you think, that's not it.
Where are you going?
You really have a serious symptom! What will you do with the picture of my house door?
You want to feel my presence even to that extent?
Hmph!
I'm going nuts, too!
My head is about to explode, just with my own problem!
The crucial fact is that there is no space for you in my heart.
It's okay not to have the space, really.
Was I too harsh?
Love is such a hassle.
Heo Joon Jae?
This is Heo Chi Hyeon. I'm near Joon Jae's house.
Cheong. Let me hold this for you.
Okay.
Neurology  Professor Jin Kyung Won
Please go ahead and go down first. I need to ask the professor about something else.
Hurry up. I'm not your personal taxi.
Since it's cold, blast the heater on.
Alright.
It's my car. I'll take care of it on my own.
Neurology  Professor Jin Kyung Won
He came yesterday. Ma Dae Young.
Why did he come?
If he doesn't take his medication, he can't control his violent nature.
He is someone who killed Dam Ryeong and Se Hwa.
He is after us even here, too.
He alsosaw the end of himself yesterday.
And said this.
- It wasn't me. It was not me.- What?
He didn't kill? Then who?
He didn't tell me so I don't know, either.
I told you that. You can't change fate that easily.
Even now, send the person back to where she belongs.
Would Ma Dae Young come back here?
I told him that I'd prepare the medicine.
He will come soon.
When he comes, can you contact me?
Sure.
I'm sorry. I couldn't tail Cheong.
- Hurry up! - I'm on the way.
I just ignored the traffic light twice!
What will happen if she goes around alone and meets Ma Dae Young? You need to take full responsibility, Officer Hong.
Why would I take that respons-
Ah, why is she not answering the phone?
Thank you.
Help yourself.
Is it "pour-eat" or "dip-eat"?
I'm talking about the sauce. Do I pour it or dip it?
Ah. "Pour-eat, dip-eat." As for me, "dip-eat."
I'm glad. I also prefer dip-eat, but since Heo Joon Jae is a "pour-eat," we always fight when we eat.
How long have you lived with Joon Jae?
Three months.
Oh, three months. Just the two of you?
No, with Heo Joon Jae's friends.
That's a relief.
What's a relief?
Oh, nothing. Just this and that.
- Would you like some fried dumplings as well? - Yes, sure!
Ah, sure! Please give us some friend mandoo, too.
Sure.
Oh, Joon Jae!
- Is that yours? - No, it's Miss Cheong's.
Thanks for carrying it for her, but you don't need to do that any more.
- Bye.- Bye.
Heo Joon Jae, are you mad at me now?
You guys fought again? Why do you fight everyday?
I met Heo Joon Jae's older brother today, and that's why he's like that. Isn't that weird?
If a guy gets mad at a girl who met his family, that means he has no intention of continuing the relationship with her.
What? You met his older brother? How?
He came to have a meal with me.
I thought he wasn't keeping in touch with any of his family members. I've never been introduced to them, either.
You've been introduced?
Yes. The last, last, last time.
What's wrong?
Is it because it's been so long since I've been in the water?
What should I do?
So no one will ever be able to get through this, right?
Unless if they get someone who is a better hacker than me, they won't be able to get into our house.
Okay. That fine. Also, go out and stay out today.
Why? I don't have any plans.
Hyung, you get out, too. Don't come back until the evening.
What should I do that?
This is my house. When the house owner tells you to do so, you do it.
Wow, he is making us pitiful again. Where could we go in this harsh winter weather?
Since you said you are not going to work, it's so hard to even set up a meeting.
Okay. Well, then, today,
no one will come back home until the evening, right?
Get out. Hurry! Out!
- I need to get changed!- Just come out.- I'm going to get changed first.
Hurry and come out. I'll wait out there.
Until the evening, no one will come?
Aish, it's so cold and where is he telling me to go?
I was wondering what you were doing.
Are you not cold? Why are you swimming during the winter?
What...what are you wearing? What's on your body?
Ah, you're going to do a part-time job agian...wearing that in an aquarium...Aigoo!
Our Cheong is so funny!
For a moment, I thought you were a merm... Hah! What am I saying?
I"m sorry. I'm sorry. I've been watching too much American drama.
It really looks like the real thing. I'm thinking about something impossible...
Miss, where's your house?
My house is far.
There's a lot of things like this at my house.
That female patient. Her BT was 29 degrees. Is it true that she regained her conciousness with just one round of defibrillator?
In just one week,
-this turned into this?-Does that make any sense?
Where'd you get this?
I worked hard to make this.
No way...
Can you give me the gown over there?
What is this? This... what?
This... what is this? Huh?
How... How did it change?
Wow, there really are things like this in the world!
Wow! What the! Do I need to report you to some international topic news, I mean FBI or something?
Are you going to tell Heo Joon Jae?
Tell him? Uh, I'm not sure.
After I see how you reply to my questions.
Don't come close.
So, when you go inside water, you turn into what you were before,
and if you come out of the water, you grow legs?
Yeah.
Wow! I'm going crazy!
So, the pearl? The pearl from last time... like how in the fairy tales...it changed from your tears?
That's right.
Cry.
Cry. Let me see if it really turns into pearls. It's because I'm fascinated right now.
Okay, well, you don't have to cry right now. Let's slowly cry a lot from now on.
Wow! This is a jackpot!
Since I replied well, you're not going to tell Heo Joon Jae, right?
Cheong! Mermaid Cheong! Why should we keep this a secret?
This is an amazing thing! We are sitting on a pile of money!
I don't like a pile of money!
I like it! What's the point of staying home?
Hey! Let's go to a place like Las Vegas together,
launch a mermaid show, and go a world tour!
Are you saying you're going to sell me off, Jo Nam Doo?
No! I'm recommending you a job. It's hard for a normal person to get a job these days.
Since it's me, I am not reporting you to the government agency,
and am going to look into going overseas for work.
-Okay!-Okay?
Yeah.
Okay.
-You want to handshake?Yeah, let's handshake.
It's not something contagious, right?
Okay, fine.
Jo Nam Doo, are you okay?
Were you swimming here?
Is it not cold in this winter?
If Heo Joon Jae also sees my real self, would he act like Jo Nam Doo?
Since I was already caught, should I have asked him first before erasing his memories?
Jo Nam Doo!
Are you not cold? Why are you swimming during the winter?
What are you wearing?
Wanting to get a part-time? I... you... a mermaid!
Can I touch it?
Wow, I'm going crazy!
This is amazing!
Try crying. We are now sitting on a pile of money!
You know all of the truth, so you probably can't see me the same way as before, right?
Of course not! To be honest, it's hard to see you in the same way as before.
Would Heo Joon Jae also be like this?
He will be worse than me! If he sees something like this, he will run away 100%!
Then I probably should never be caught.
But it's too late, because I found out.
To be honest, I was questioning whether or not it would work since I've only done it once in the water.
But it works well outside of the water too.
What?
I'm sorry.
I'm going crazy.
You know that feeling. When you're about to think of something, but it doesn't come out.
What should I do? Does he remember?
Something like seeing the lottery number in your dreams and then not remembering it.
That frustration that makes you go crazy!
I erased it, but did it not erase well?
Wait! I think I remember something.
That... in this house's swimming pool...
Cheong...!
Ow, why did you hit me?
Eat instead of being loud.
Hey, look! Look at my toes.
I feel like my toenail is going to fall off! But I don't remember!
How my foot became like this! How my foot has bumped into something!
I just can't remember anything!
It's early dementia due to alcohol.
Is that so?
So watch your drinking!
Ah, put it down.
I didn't want to live, spearing poop on the wall.
How can i be like this already?
There supposed to be three bad luck this year. Has it started already?
Subtitles brought to you by The Blue Sea @ Viki
Until when are you going to be like this?
What?
You're not talking to me or meeting my eyes or smiling.
Okay, then. Let me ask one more time. If something happens to me...
It's the same even if you ask a hundred times.
If something happens to you, I can't live.
Yeah, so why?
That...
My heart can only beat if you love me.
My heart in the land has a limited time.
If you leave me or leave this world, my heart beat stops.
Jung Hoon died because of that, too.
When a loved one leaves, the heart cools,
hardens, and stops.
Without you, I'll be like that.
Unless if I return to the ocean, I'll probably die.
You're going to die?
What?
What did you just say?
What...?
Say it again. What will stop, harden... What will happen?
You hear my voice?
You said your heart will stop.
When did you start hearing it?
You said you're going to die.
Why are you going to die?!
♬ Seeing with you; Listening with you;♬
♬Breathing with you.♬
♬There's nothing to throw away. I'm so happy.♬
♬ I want to stop by your side. ♬
♬ Everything about you ♬
♬I cannot remember ♬
♬I am ♬
There is something I need to ask you.
Is that important to you now?
Did you look for Kang Ji Yeon?
I've never done a background check that gave me such a chill.
You said you are going to quit your job. How about my house?
You've gotten much better.
I'm going to do a birthday party at home. Can you come?
I'll be there.
I have a good idea.
What are you talking about?
Let's do like this. Trust me and leave it up to me.
Tomorrow at 10pm