Subtitles brought to you by The Blue Sea @ Viki
If you leave me or leave this world, my heart beat stops.
Jung Hoon died because of that, too.
When a loved one leaves because the heart cools, hardens and stops.
Without you, I'll be like that.
Unless I return to the ocean, I'll probably die.
You're going to die?
What did you say?
- What did you just say?  - What?
Say it again. What will stop, harden... What will happen?
You hear my voice?
You said your heart will stop.
Since when did you start hearing it?
- You said you're going to die.  - When did you start hearing it?
Why are you going to die?!
You! Since when have you known so much?
From the start to the end, everything.
Who I am... and where I am from, you know all of it?
I know. I remember everything.
The crazy bastard who shared an umbrella with you when it rained,
the player who took your hand when you were alone, the whacko who cooked ramen for you.
were all me.
That you were the one who saved me from drowning and also the mermaid who erased my memory.
You remember all of that?
That's right. I remembered it all.
How?
Now answer me. What are you saying about dying?
What is that you are saying about your heart stopping?
Didn't you say you heard it all?
Those things
Are all those true?
That if I am gone, your heart would stop?
That you... will die?
You heard it all. You said you were listening to my voice.
That's right. It's just as you heard. This is not my world.
Once I gave up being on water and came here,
pettily, I got to have a heart that beats for only you.
So you're saying... if I die, you die too?
That's right.
So, if anything happens to you that you would be gone
Me by myself and watching pretty things and living happily
don't say those things. I can't make such promise.
Anyway, once you are gone, I will be gone too.
If you didn't love that woman
and if that woman did not love you, you would not have reached such a tragic end.
The love you have for each other would be enough to kill each other, what other worse ill-fate is there?
So Ma Dae Young was not the problem.
I... could be the one to kill you then.
Heo Joon Jae, that's not it.
The Legend of the Blue Sea
Episode 15
Are you thinking that this will all repeat once again?
If you stop here and let that woman return to where she was,
shouldn't you be able to avoid that miserable end?
Did you guys fight big time?
No.
Why is Cheong crying?
Is she crying a lot?
She was wailing her heart out.
Hey, you... if you aren't going to take responsibility until the end then about now it's best to start settling--
Why is everyone telling me to settle things?
I haven't even done anything for her. Did I do anything aside from making her cry?
Did I make her cry? You're the one who did but why get mad at me?
Hyung.
What?
When Cheong came to find me... it was from her greed.
But not sending Cheong away... I think it's from my greed.
What are you saying?
But then... I know it's from my greed but I keep wanting not to hear the reasons why I should send her back.
I keep wanting to make excuses of how I don't have to send her off.
If things continue like this, something bad could really happen to her.
But then, since earlier
Cheong... I keep getting a feeling that I need to get a debt back from her.
This... I think I remember but not...
What do you keep on saying about something you thing you remember but don't?
Why hit me?
What is your secret?
My secret is... that I am different from you.
That I... am a mermaid.
That's right, it was from then on.
I could have been in big trouble.
If I fell in the water I would have been totally exposed.
Hey, if you slip and fall, at the very least you'd get a concussion.
He knew back then.
He knew it all.
He kne...What does he mean?
Does he mean not to think of him?
What does that gaze mean?
Is he mad at me? Why?
Now, it's nice and quiet.
Starting now, don't think of anything.
And don't do anything.
He knew everything but... why did he do that?
I have something to ask.
What?
Honestly, I thought no one was home and while swimming I was caught by Jo Nam Doo.
But then Jo Nam Doo became a totally different person. He threatened to sell me for money.
So I erased his memory.
But how was it for you?
Even if you knew who I am, did you not hate me or get scared?
Is that important to you now?
Yeah. This is important to me.
That's right. I didn't hate you or was scared.
Just... since you were an unusual person from the start
I thought that's how you were. Just like that.
That's a relief.
That's enough for me. As long as you didn't hate me.
Honestly, since I know that I got caught I am happy. I always thought every night before I slept
if I would get caught today or tomorrow. If I would get caught, what would your expression be.
Your facial expression of you hating me
was my scariest dream.
To me, the scariest dream is
that everything would repeat itself.
A dream that everything would repeat itself?
Why did we come here?
You asked what's repeating.
I'll teach you.
Gallery of Yangyang's Shipwreck Artifacts
Huh?
I know what you're thinking but I'm better looking.
Who is it?
A man... who loved a mermaid.
This man drowns in water when he was little.
The mermaid saved his life.
And the two spends a long time together and falls in love.
But the man marries another woman.
On the first night of wedding day, the man runs away from the bridal room.
Se Hwa! Se Hwa!
He risks his life and jumps in the ocean.
To meet the mermaid again.
So the boy doesn't look for her again,
she erased all his memory by kissing him.
Time passes,
and the two meet again as adults.
And the relation that seemed to be broken off for good
starts back.
So? So what happens?
Hmm? What happens?
You said you'll tell me what repeats.
Those two...
Your favorite, soft persimmon.
♬I'm still dreaming♬
Is it snowing outside?
You didn't know?
♬The indistinct thought of someone who was♬
♬as radiant as the moonlight in the pale evening sky♬
♬ is evoked ♬
♬On the petals floating in the wind♬
♬I sense your warm frangrance and♬
♬our connection which was brief ♬
Those two... live happily.
Doesn't get sick or hurt.
Having lots of kids and raising them well.
Happily ever after
they grow old together.
I see.
Yes, they did.
That's their story that I saw.
♬I won't let go of your hand.♬
But why
am I tearing up?
Come here.
They must have seen us in their dreams, too.
Then why is it a scary dream?
Huh?
It's a beautiful dream.
Right.
You're scared that a beautiful dream is repeating?
Hey. You can't be so loud here.
It bothers other people.
What other people?
Why? What are you scared of?
It's just that we're in a different situation than back then.
What's different?
You said so. If you stay here,
you might die.
If you stay by me and love me, my heart will keep beating on.
Probably the same for them too, since they lived happily ever after.
I'm not that man.
What do you mean?
I'm saying I can't be sure of my heart.
The easiest thing that can change in the world is a person's heart.
That's why those lovey dovey couples break up,
and the marriage that seemed to last forever ends, too.
Knowing that your life depends on my heart which I don't even know—
- So you're scared?  - Yeah.
I'm scared of that.
- What?  - It's not fair.
How come you can hear my heart, but I can't hear yours?
Why do you need to hear my heart?
From a person who only tells the truth.
Don't swear. I can hear it all.
[Chief Nam's wife; 011-837-9238]
The number you have dialed is not available.
I have a good idea. Let's do this, Heo Joon Jae.
Hmm?
I'd hate to have you feel burdensome or scared because of me.
So?
Let's just erase yesterday. Just yesterday.
- What?  - If we just erase yesterday fro your brain,
we can go back to how we used to be. You won't feel burdensome and stuff.
What are you saying?
I can do it. If I just control my strength well...
I think I can get it to work.
Get what to work?
It's not that easy in the water, and I'm a little short on stamina since I've been on land for so long.
But I'll try my best, hmm? Now a lot but just a little.
I'd say maybe a day or half a day.
What are you talking about?
Just close your eyes and bear with me.
Why close my eyes?!
- It won't hurt. Just a sec.  - Hey, don't push! What are you doing?
Hey, don't come near me! What are you doing?
It won't hurt. Just trust me,
Hey.
Jeez! What's with you!
Hey!
Hey, wait. Wait up. Wait!
Hey.
Stop, really.
Hey, what are those guys doing? Are they playing catch me if you can now?
Yesterday she was crying like no tomorrow, the ground collapsed and she was heaving and crying up a storm.
Hey!
I hope the day clears up soon so I don't have to see all these ridiculous things and take off.
Hold on!
I think I just have to erase half a day.
Can't I?
Close the door.
It would be great if I could just erase half the day.
Would erasing the day make it so that nothing happened?
I told you. What if I change my heart and don't like you anymore?
Heo Joon Jae I'm a mermaid with a great amount of insight on people. Do you think that I would've come this far to follow some man that switches his mind so quickly?
I knew it the moment I saw you. "This is the man"
Someone who's worth hanging my once in a lifetime love on.
You said that there was something wrong with your eyes.
What?  - There was something wrong with my eyes. I was so naive back then.
I lived my entire life in the water and it's the first time I've come upon land what do I know? Being that Heo Joon Jae was the first man I encountered
You said you came here thinking I was the best.
You thought I was the only handsome guy in the world,
When I look at the TV there's so many. Such a patient suffering from Prince Syndrome.
You said it I was too into myself!
So you heard it all? You can think anything when you're mad.
It's that you're a bit narrow hearted to pretend you didn't hear anything when you heard everything.
Ok, then. How about we erase all that as well?
You heard me talking behind your back, how cheap of you.
I think we'd be good if we erase about one week.
Now that we're on the subject do you want to go to the East Sea?
Or should I get you a plane ticket to go somewhere? Like Boracay?
That ocean must be nice and warm. I'll visit you time to time. I can see you when I'm surfing and stuff.
Fine. I won't do anything to you. Let's just sleep holding hands.
I'm serious. I won't do anything. I'll just sleep holding your hand. Don't you trust me?
Totally not.
He's not falling for it.
I can hear all that. You're doing so well for yourself.
You're a mermaid that's supposed to be innocent and ignorant, but you're so vulgar and base, even lying!
I'm telling you to go read some fairytales in your spare time. Among your ancestors there wasn't anyone who's as much of a playgirl as you!
Geez.
You sure you won't do anything to me?
Nope. I promise.
Don't do anything. I'll just check if your heart is doing okay.
It's beating well.
It beats well by you.
What? She was their household helper?
Yes.
I was wondering where she was hiding...
No wonder I couldn't fine her since she was a resident helper.
What's wrong? You don't like it?
No, it's good. You should try, too.
Go to that house right now.
Oh, Madam, you really surprised me.
What brings you here so suddenly?
You know you've been contacting me but I couldn't get back to you.
- Please have a seat.  - Okay.
Then... that incident that day...
are you going to magnanimously pass on it?
Of course. Anybody could be like that when they're drunk.
Thank you.
Can I stay for some tea?
Of course. Is coffee okay with you?
Yes.
Ahjumma! Bring us 2 delicious cups of coffee please!
She's the one that's making us the side dishes, right?
Yes. You said the Chairman really liked them.
What can be done? She said that she's going to quit.
Quitting?
Yes. She's such a good worker,
she must have got an offer from somewhere else or something.
She suddenly told me that she's quitting.
Ahjumma, what are you doing?
Ajumma your cooking skills are so superb.
We've really been enjoying your food.
I heard you're quitting.
Have you decided where to go? If not, how about my house?
Yeah?
Can I go to your place?
Oh my! Ahjumma, are you drunk? W-what are you doing?
Can I cook at your house?
You won't give up the master bedroom but the kitchen's okay?
I don't know why you're here or what you want to verify.
You're wrong.
The reason that I was living as if I were dead
is because harm might come to our Joon Jae.
Now I have nothing to stop me.
Jin Joo.
Please excuse us for a second.
- Of course.  - You told me once
there is a bitch who stole a friend's husband and took her place.
You didn't know where the original wife who got kicked out is.
Did I... speak so... crudely?
Did I?
It's me.
That original wife who got kicked out.
And this person is
that mean-hearted bitch.
Oh my god.
Yein's mom
What a great happening so early in the year!
subtitles ripped,synced and added the missing lines by riri13
You know you know. Our house is the site of history!
I think it's going to be the site of history.
Get ready to be swept off your feet and listen carefully.
Hyung did you look into finding that Kang Ji Young I told you about before?
Yeah I did try looking
I never had ever doe any investigation as goose-bump worthy as this one.
The people and things surrounding this woman are all suspicious.
She married twice and both of her husbands both died.
But there's alibi, diagnosis, so after their death Kang Ji Hyeon won the entirety of the insurance
But that's not all
this woman is an orphan so she was adopted, but the family that she was adopted into all of the family members
are all nowhere to be found.
Are you real?
We just got goosebumps.
So what about now? Where is she?
We cannot know her current whereabouts at all.
But if it's a woman of her class, I'm thinking she's probably living under a different identity. What do you think?
But the thing is, there's another astonishing fact
Stop leaking the info piece by piece but reveal it all in one go.
I have to do it like this for there to be a thrill.
This Kang Ji Hyun is from Jecheon.
I kept wondering where the hell I kept seeing her high school name,
but it was from during the time that I looked for your mother. She was from the same high school.
Graduation Certificate - Daneon Girls' High School Hong Yeong Jik
Honey, this is your secretary who came in place of Mr. Nam.
Chairman, I'll do my best [to assist you].
Goodness, it's me who has to rely on your effort.
Then, I'll start the car.
Okay.
My gosh, never you mind. I'll do it.
Please take a seat.
Missus, I was really sorry today.
I realize that you still haven't found the new person,but I'd like to quit after setting up dinner tonight.
Unni (Big sis).
Wh-a-a...?
You would be a big sis whether you look at it from the ageor whatever else...
It's not like I have an older biological sister, and...
from now on, I'll think on you as my biological sister.
Missus.
You don't have to work. That's right. However, if you were to leave here,
it's not like you have a suitable place to go to,
so just pretend like this is your biological younger sister's home,
and stay on comfortably.
How can I?
Unni! I really thought I was watching...a great historical drama!
You were the Queen Consort Yin Hyeon, and Gang Seolthat wench is Hi Bin Jang (famous royal concubine).
However the important thing is that the Queen ConsortYin Hyeon eventually return to her own place.
Me, Ahn Jin Joo is going to help that.
Your brilliant return to the Queen Consort position.
I have no intent to do so.
No, no. Even if you don't have any intention, you should do it,least of all for me.
Whatever it may, I will help you Unni, and will never let youleave as is.
Please just know that.
Agassi (sister-in-law of the husband),
you knew all along, didn't you?
Isn't that why you were groveling to Ajumma recently?
What could you mean?
You knew our ajumma was the Chairman Heo Il Joong'sJo Gang Ji Cheo (wife through sickness in health)!
What?
You mean you had not an inkling?
Wh-a-t in the world are you talking...?
I can't even count the number of times I told this story.
But no matter how many iterations I run through,my heart still beats this wildly.
You know our ajumma was the original wife of Heo Il Joong Chairman!
But without having any idea, I've been supplying the foodAjumma has cooked to that house!
Isn't it so dramatic?
Then Joon Jae is...
Joon Jae? You know that household's son?
Not so. How would I know that? It's just my friend's name.
But seriously, that son who ran away from home,
that son's name must be Heo Joon Jae.
A little while ago, Ajumma was uttering something aboutJoon Jae or something.
Yes, Noona (older sister a male calls a female).
Were you awaiting my call?
Otherwise, how does one pick up a phone even before it rings?
It's not that, but I was gaming...
Never mind. Listen without getting all fluttered.
Will you come to pick me up?
Now?
Are you that happy? That's right. Now.
But you can't have and ulterior motive, alright?
Where are you going?
Si Ah Noona asked me to come to the club.
Really? Is that a place with good water (atmosphere of the club)?
Is that a place with fresh water (literally good quality water to swim in)? I want to go, too.
- You'd go too?- Yeah.
What? How dare you...
What? What? I'm not usually the one gets flagged.
It's not that but your attire is somewhat...
Ah... Cheong.
Okay?
Wow, today is Swag-Cheong! Let's go!
Cha Si Ah!
I told you to come alone, so why drag the unwanted?
Cha Si Ah, were you coming to such a nice place alone?
Cha Si Ah, don't drink. Last time when I saw Heo Joon Jaedrink, he became a little cuter.
It depends on a person. In case of Cha Si Ah, she alwayscall and cries,
and prohibits you from hanging up on her all night, and...
I got it. I'm hitting the dance floor.
I'm a safe guy.
As there are so many unsavory incidents, that my handsare always up above.
Don't worry about a thing, and just dance. Just dance.
Your eyes are so pretty.
Yes, what?
Where is everyone?
Ah, Detective Heo. Have you returned from your investigation?We're at a club.
- What about Cheong?- Of course she came together.
Why would you bring her there?
She'll say she's dizzy and won't like it.
What are you talking about? She's moving through space fluidly.She's completely at home here.
What?
Please move over.
Hey Joon Jae, what brings you here?
Um. Just because...
Let's play. It's really fun here.
I'd like to but I still have things to do.
Have fun with Nam Doo hyung (older brother) & Tae Ho.
Make sure you ask to be taken home when you're done.
You come here. Stop.
Heo Joon Jae!
Why? I'm going to dance some more.
Are you sweating?
Yep. The dancing is making me a little warm.But I like it!
I bet you like it, alright. Come one out.
Why? I'm going to dance some more.
Right. Come here.
My gosh.
It's raining a lot.
This turns out to be one of the things I cannot do together with you.
Walking when it's raining.
You know I can't.
There's nothing you can't do. Wait a minute here.
one step closer
Where did you find this?
Don't say I won't or I can't from now on.
I will let you do every single thing people who live here dowithout leaving anything out.
So you should know as such.
Like this shining so blindly when I look at you
You are my only one, if we get to love
My one. If my one love can begin with you.
The heart that I've guarding preciously and a love that we don't know its meaning
For you I will use it for you. Each and every moment of mine
for you.
It's so interesting. How did that Ajussi hear your thought?
I don't know. How did you come to hear me?
I don't know. I just heard it as well.
Anyway, I feel less burdened now that Heo Joon Jae can hear me.
It's not like I have anything to lie about. It's like I can now live properly here.
Normally, like everyone else.
But you know, having lived my life, even though it appears easy,the thing that's most difficult
is living normally like everyone else.
I will make sure I do this; getting old together like everyone else with Heo Joon Jae.
All those women over there appear to be holding luxury bags, right?
But look at them. They're carrying the bag overhead likean umbrella because it's raining; that's a knockoff.
And look at that woman behind.
You see she's carrying her bag like it's some ancestral tablet.That's the original.
Can knockoff be rained on? The knockoff is not that different than the original real designer product, no?
Though the outer appearance could be the same. But there is one thing that you can't deceive.
- What is that?- The bag owner's feeling.
You know you can't hide the owner. They know that theirbags are fake.
Which is why they hold them like umbrellas and run when it rains.
But even among the bag owners, whether the bag is the realone or a fake one, treat it nicely and like it
because simply it belongs to them.
I'm just saying that it could be. I feel like I'm a fake in this worldfor some reason.
Still, I feel that [despite being a fake] perhaps I still deserveto be loved by someone.
Be that as it may, why are you so earnest? I was trying to be funny.
You were trying to say that one shouldn't divide the real vs. fake by the outer appearance, right?
- Yes.- You're precise. Capable of summarizing.
Thank you, two. I'm going to try all things that other people do normally.
Speaking of which, tomorrow is my birthday party.
- Is tomorrow your birthday?- Do you celebrate your solar or lunar calendar birthday?
I don't know. Truthfully, I don't know when my birthday is, so I just decided to make it tomorrow. What's the date tomorrow, anyway?
January 5th. It's succinct date. Nice.
- Where is the party?- At my house.
I tend to refrain from visiting other people's houses,but I'll come tomorrow.
- Do you have any special Saeng Seon (fish) in mind you'd like to have?- Mackerel.
Not that kind of Saeng Seon (fish) but Saeng Il (birth) Seon Mool (present).
Can't you just give me Mackerel for the birthday present?
Ah, yes, Han Gyeol.
I'm going to drop by the house right now. You come home right after your academy, too.
I'll prepare a late night snack for you. I have to come back to the hospital right after.
Subtitles brought to you by The Blue Sea @ Viki
General Manager
You look a lot better.
It's been really chilly out lately. Oh yeah.
I saw you talking with Joon Jae the other day.
Can you answer my questions, too?
If Ma Dae Young made you like this, why did he?
Is the person you think is associated with Ma Dae Young my mother?
Of course. I knew it.
Mother seems to feel relieved about the fact that
you're lying down like this, not saying a word.
But this isn't an issue about speaking.
Right? The problem is...
here.
You mind.
Something that can betray us anytime,
your mind.
- Hello?- Han Gyeol's mom?
It's me. Joon Jae's mom.
Oh my, madam. How long has it been?
It is you.
I'm in a rush, so I'll get straight to it. Has Joon Jae not been studying abroad?
I heard he left the house. Is it true?
I'm so sorry. I actually lied at that time.
I thought you be too upset.
So, do you know how Joon Jae's been doing?
Yes, I do. A while ago, my husband got into a big accident and has been lying in the hospital,
and Joon Jae sometimes visits.
His phone number... Could you give it to me?
Of course.
Madam, I can't really seem small letters... I'll quickly go upstairs and get my glasses, so I can read it to you.
Don't hang up, and wait.
Honey!
He's lost consciousness, has no heartbeat, and isn't breathing. I will start CPR.
- Honey! What happened! Honey!- You are not allowed to enter here.
- No, honey! - Please wait outside.
Don't forget my request.
Look here. If you ask of me such a request, how am I supposed to live?
I will meet you again, as a good friend.
Ahjusshi's your friend.
Bring mom back. Bring mom back.
Honey! Honey!
Ma'am! Are you okay?
Who are you?
If you cut off his air supply like that, the alarm goes off.
Luckily, it was when they were switching shifts. You could have been in a lot of trouble.
Aren't you a fugitive? Why are you driving my father's car?
From now on don't take the initiative in doing anything.
Just think about why your mother quietly hides and watches, just think about that.
Don't talk nonsense! I'm asking you why a dangerous person like you is circling the vicinity of my mother and I?!
What, you jerk?! Listen to me well. You only need to be quiet and benefit from what others do for you.
Don't overturn an already prepared table. Do you understand?
Hello? Han Kyeol's mother?
Cheong.
Yes. Tomorrow is my birthday,
we're going to have a birthday party at the house. Can you come?
What to do? I'm so sorry. I'm not in a situation where I can go.
I would have prepared a present if you had told me ahead of time.
It's okay. I didn't really know when my birthday was so I decided it today
as tomorrow.
Then you've never had a birthday party since you were born?
No. It's the first time.
You're parents aren't alive?
No.
I'll come. Where do I have to go tomorrow?
Subtitles brought to you by The Blue Sea @ Viki
I don't know. Out of the blue she said she wants to have her birthday party.
Yeah. She says she doesn't even know when her birthday really is. She says she just decided it as today.
Aiyoo, thank you. Aiyoo, you're so pretty. Hey, we're going to have to get rid of the TV or something.
She keeps seeing bad things on dramas and wanting to follow them.
All right. I'll be right there.
Who are you?
Oh, she's my friend. Welcome.
Your friend?
what is this? Is it food waste?
Come on now, what are you talking about food waste? It's mackerel because the lady of the house said she likes it.
But don't you have house slippers here?
The lady of the house?
Oh, oh, oh! Do-o-o-on't j-j-j-just sit down and s-s-s-sit with this under you!
Don't you give steamed towels here to wash your hands? They usually give things like that.
I don't usually eat raw foods because I'm used to eating only cooked foods.
Yes, there's codfish soup here so at least have some codfish soup with rice later.
But the cod doesn't seem to be wild cod. Codfish soup has to have fish intestines in it but it doesn't have that either.
- So are you not going to eat?  - Of course, I have to eat it.
It's still a party. I can't wreck the mood. Do you have jalapeños?
Yes, Cheong. I've just gotten off the bus and I'm walking there.
Hello.
Why did you come out?
What's all this?
Things like sea urchin seaweed soup, japchae (stir fried glass noodles), and bulgogi (grilled marinated beef).
They were the things that I used to make long ago for him for his birthday. I don't know if they'll suit your tastes.
After deciding on today for my birthday I feel somewhat like I've been reborn.
The feeling of having been giving permission to live a new life here?
I'm trying to organize my life and leave the house I've been living in. I was hiding all this time.
Now, I will find the person I want to find, say what I want to... I want to live like that.
Oh. It's my dummy.
What is she so happy about? She smiles easily.
Who?
My boyfriend. Heo Joon Jae!
That dummy. I told her so many times not to call my name out loud when there's a lot of people.
Heo Joon Jae! Heo Joon Jae!
Hello!
Your boyfriend's name is Heo Joon Jae?
Yes. He's really good looking.
Heo Joon Jae's mom said that when he was young
If I was taken outside, it was hard to even take 10 steps.
Because people always wanted to touch and hug me.
What's wrong?
My son's name is the same.
Heo Joon Jae.
I haven't seen him for a long time.
Heracles Lighthouse?
They say Heracles' mom came here everyday and longed for her son who she was parted from.
After seeing that, the people who felt bad for her built that lighthouse
so that Heracles would follow the light from the lighthouse.
They say they prayed for him to cross the sea and find his mother.
So? Did Heracles find his mom?
I'm not sure. But they have a legend here.
People with whom you get separated from here, you will meet them again for sure.
Heo Joon Jae, what the legend of the lighthouse stated true.
That those who get separated there will surely meet again.
That they meet again and love.
Congratulations. You got to meet your mom now.