Subtitles brought to you by The Blue Sea @ Viki
Heo Joon Jae, the legend of the lighthouse was true.
That those who part at the lighthouse always meet again.
That they meet and love again.
Congratulations, you're going to meet your mom.
Joon Jae...
Joon Jae... I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, Joon Jae.
I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry... I'm sorry.
Sorry...
Mom is sorry... I'm so sorry...
Among the many words I've come to learn after coming here,
the best words are "happy ending."
I'm sure that this very moment is a happy ending.
But the hope and despair that life gives you is that
time keeps flowing and the moment passes.
Behind that moment of brilliant happiness,
what kind of moments await, no one knows.
The Legend of the Blue Sea
Episode 16
How is your... health?
You're not hurting anywhere?
How about you?
I'm okay.
I'm sorry.
Stop saying... that you're sorry.
I shouldn't have...
left you behind there like that.
I thought your wealthy father would raise you well.
I thought you were living well while studying abroad.
I didn't go to study abroad, but I did live well enough.
I met nice people, too.
I heard you ran away from home when you were in high school.
Why did you do that? Why didn't you just endure and live there?
Because I missed you.
I missed you so much.
I thought I could find you right away.
But
you were no where to be found. I've thought of all kinds of things.
Could she have passed away...
So, please stop saying you are sorry.
For living healthy like this,
I am thankful.
But my mom became so small.
When I was little, you always embraced me.
I should embrace you every day.
How difficult must it have been for you...
for a 10 year old cry baby to grow this much.
For such a long time, you were alone without mom.
My son, how difficult must it have been for you.
How lonely would you have been?
Mommy had no idea...
That's why
you can't go anywhere anymore.
When we are apart, you don't know anything.
So, don't go anywhere.
Really? The ahjumma that works at Si Ah's was Joon Jae's mom?
Yeah, so the two of them are talking right now.
It's not just Joon Jae who's been searching for his mom. I've also searched for her everywhere.
But I can't believe she was right here all along!
It's something to congratulate them for,
but what about your birthday party? It's a little ambiguous now.
That's true. Why did you make it today of all days?
It's because I picked the right date that Heo Joon Jae met his mom.
That's true, too. Not only are you better at speaking, you've become perfectly logical, too.
The plate's empty over here.
What is it?
Oh, it's nothing.
This place doesn't refill very well.
Other parties never let the dishes go empty.
This is driving me crazy. What is this?
I'm sure there's something. Something huge.
I couldn't have dreamt that this was the house you lived in.
I didn't know either. I ate the food that you made
and just thought they tasted similar. I couldn't have dreamed that you made it.
Whose house is this?
The house of my boyfriend...or will be.
By chance, is Ji Yong's aunt, Cha Si Ah, your girlfriend?
What? No she's not. She's just my college classmate.
Right? It's Cheong, right?
Omo, look at how you smile. You like her that much?
But... you're already living together?
She doesn't have a suitable place to go because of her circumstances.
Fate is such a strange thing. I've received helped from Cheong many times.
She helped me when I got pick-pocketed, and she also saved me from getting hit by a car when I was walking while distracted.
How did you almost get hit by a car? You and Cheong both, don't you think about getting out of the way of a car?
Be careful. Please.
Okay, I got it.
But... how can you afford to live in such a nice house?
I earned a lot of money. Although, this is a rental.
I can at least get a place for us to live together in.
So... stop working so hard and live with me.
What kind of work do you do, Joon Jae?
Just... this and that.
Let's go in.
♬ Happy Birthday to you, Happy Birthday to you,
♬ To our beloved Shim Cheong, Happy Birthday!
- Did you make a wish? - Oh, a wish.
I want to live here happily for a long time with Heo Joon Jae.
A wish should be made in your heart for it to come true. If you say it aloud, it won't come true.
Really? Oh, what do I do?
It's okay. It'll come true even if you say it aloud. Blow the candles out.
Wait.
- Let's blow out the candles once more.  - Why?
There's another thing to congratulate. You and your mom found each other.
Wait. That is... is there anyone else who needs to be congratulated?
Me. I did get a hundred on my English vocabulary test.
Oh, we should congratulate her. Let's blow it out one more time, huh?
You're doing this because you think it's fun, right?
Yeah.
Let's do it. It's not hard to do.
Okay, let's. Where is it?
Congratulations.
- Wait.  - Again?
Stop it, stop!
- What?  - You come over, too.
- No, right before that. - Didn't you hear me?
I said Joon Jae found his mom.
Not only that, she's the ahjumma who works in your house.
Things like this really do happen in the world!
Isn't this a good thing for you?
You must be really close since you lived in the same house.
Just come over. It's a big party going on.
A grade schooler and a bum are even here.
Anyway, just come.
What do I do?
Let's go. I'll take you home. Your hand.
Get home safe. Thank you for coming to my birthday party.
Unnie, happy birthday.
You too, Oppa, congratulations on finding your mom.
Yeah. Thanks, kid.
Thank you.
Bye.
By the way... aren't you giving me a goodie bag?
- A what bag?  - A goodie bag. Party favors.
When I go to parties, they always give those out.
Do you want me to pack you up some food?
I don't eat food that's two hours past when it was cooked.
Oh, I see. Go back safely.
Hey, what's wrong with all your friends?
Aren't there any normal ones?
Why? I like them. I like all the friends I made here.
Heo Joon Jae's mom is my friend, too.
Hey, how is my mom your friend?
It's true. We are friends.
See that? We're friends.
Hey, if you're friends with my mom, where does that leave me?
Ah, this house is becoming more and more strange.
Mother, you don't know how hard I searched for you.
I've got all of your old addresses memorized, and I know all of your friends and relatives, too.
I see. I was overseas for several years after the divorce
and after going through all my savings and coming back, I've just been taking care of other people's households.
- So it would have been hard to find me.  - Aigoo...
You must have been through a lot.
Shall we toast in light of that?
Cheers.
But Mother, since the emotional reunion has
died down a little, could I ask you something?
Yes. What is it?
Do you by any chance know someone named Kang Ji Hyun?
You went to the same high school.
- Kang... Ji Hyun?  - Yes.
Is she someone you know?
Why are you asking?
Well... there was some issue,
so we've been looking into Kang Ji Hyun.
Her resident ID has been cancelled and there's no record of her at all.
She is someone I know. Who I know all too well.
- Really?  - Yeah.
You know her, too.
I... know her?
Joon Jae, it's your stepmother.
Huh? What?
But... that's not her name.
She told me she changed her name to Kang Seo Hee.
She changed her name? Then there would have been some kind of record left but there wasn't anything.
I don't know about all that, but her name in school was Kang Ji Hyun. I'm sure of at least that much.
Kang Ji Hyun was that woman?
What is it? What's wrong?
- The thing is--  - No, it's nothing.
Mother, do you know an escapee named Ma Dae Young?
I think I've heard the name.
You see, we've been trying to track Ma Dae Young.
But Kang Ji Hyun seems to be a bit related to Ma Dae Young.
Related how?
- That is---  - That's enough.
It's nothing much. The detective we know was asking about it.
What are you doing?
Joon Jae's mother is i-inside, right?
Probably.
By any chance... did she say anything about... me?
- What kind of things?  - Never mind.
Aren't you going in?
Tae Ho, do you want to have a drink with me?
I...don't want to drink with you, Noona.
Come on, let's have a drink.
I don't know how much you like me,
but do you want me to make you dislike me altogether?
I... knew that that ahjumma was Joon Jae's mother.
So why didn't you say anything?
I... have been really awful to her.
So we didn't get along at all.
But then I found out. That she's his mother.
So I tried to restore my relationship with her somehow and then tell him,
but everything is all over now. Once he finds out,
he won't even want to be friends with me, right? He'll tell me to get lost, right?
I know that I'm a horrible bitch.
How do you feel? After hearing this,
any feelings you had for me disappeared completely, right?
Be thankful.
My wish is for my feelings for Joon Jae to disappear completely.
But because I can't help it, it's made it so difficult for me.
I'm telling you so that you won't suffer like me.
Your ardent feelings for me, that love, I'm telling you to throw it away.
Yes. Kang Ji Hyun, whom my mother knows, is my stepmother.
If she is still related to Ma Dae Young...
So you're saying that the reason Ma Dae Young has been after you could be because your stepmother instigated it?
But why? Why would he try to kill you?
I'm sure Heo Joon Jae bastard did something bad to annoy her.
Father's will and testament was notarized,
but he left almost all of his assets to me and mom.
The first thing I can say is that it would be over inheritance.
Inheritance? How much wealth could there be that she'd go that far to harm you?
What?
Rascal. You're defrauding me again! Stop!
You're going to get it. Is your father a Chaebol?
What?
Really?
Is that important right now? Can't you subpoena him right away?
We can't without any crucial proof.
And that could alert her that we're suspecting her,
so we have to careful until we find some proof.
I'm telling you, I have a sense about this. The puzzle is coming together.
And we don't have time to wait either.
What are you going to do now?
I'm going to do it my way. I'm going to find proof and reveal everything as soon as possible.
Fortunately, he was in the state of being able to breath on his own a little.
It happened when he was using the breathing machine only as a support.
So there was no fatal cardiac arrest.
He nearly died once. How could something like this happen again?
I don't know if he'll be able to live a normal life even if he wakes up...
In this patient's case, he has diffuse axonal injury.
In cases like his, sometimes the patient can suddenly wake up from a coma.
Since we don't know the exact process how injured brain gets recovered,
we just call it a miracle.
I hope for a miracle, Doctor.
What's the matter, Chi Hyeon?
Is he my father?
Ma Dae Young?
- Is he?  - Must I confirm it for you?
Yes.
I don't understand, Chi Hyeon.
Without knowing anything, without doing anything,
if you just sit and wait, I'll do everything for you, so why are you curious?
The fact that I'm the son of someone like him...!
I hate it so much...
Because then... it makes me feel like a clump of dirty moss
that can never go out into the sunlight...
Chi Hyeon...
I used to have...
a twin sister.
We were born in the same hour, same day, and we were put in the same basket
and thrown away at an orphanage. My sister
got adopted to a really nice home but not me.
A father who got violent whenever he drank
and a pathetic mother... being dirt poor with no future in sight...
even in that circumstance, there was still one thing that worked for me.
I don't know.
Just... I thought my father was sleeping after drinking
but when I woke up in the morning...
Don't cry.
Honey...
if you go like this, how am I supposed to live on my own?
Take me with you!
People seemed to trust whatever a powerless person says...
Coming this far while using that as my sole weapon,
it was a long and difficult road.
Chi Hyeon...
I didn't want you to take a longer way around.
Whether it's Ma Dae Young or Heo Il Joong, they're only just shortcuts.
Just take that shortcut and go out into that sunlight.
And go live as not a clump of moss but as a flower.
That's all you have to do.
Thanks for walking me home.
- Noona.  - Yeah.
I thought about it, and I will stop liking you now.
What? Oh, has it been sorted out?
- Yes, it has. - Already?
Oh, really? That's good. I'm glad.
So Noona, you should confess to Joon Jae Hyung properly, too.
In this situation? How can I?
What if I can never see him again?
Is there any meaning in continuing to see him like this?
I'll be going.
What? How can he sort out his feelings so quickly?
Well...that's good then.
Yes, it happened that way. I'll come home after sleeping here overnight.
Omo, so you met your son?
What a dramatic reunion!
Omo, so how did you find him?
Oh, I see.
- Tell me about that thing earlier.  - What?
About what kind of relationship Heo Joon Jae's stepmother has with Ma Dae Young.
Why are you curious about it?
Ma Dae Young tried to hurt me and Heo Joon Jae both.
Ma Dae Young had just one woman in his life and that is Kang Ji Hyun.
And surrounding her are all mysterious deaths.
And her adoptive family members all had suspicious myocardial infarction. Suicide, accident...
After both of her husbands losing their vision, they died of illness and accident.
You don't understand what I'm saying right now, do you?
No, I understand everything. You know I watch the news diligently these days.
Anyway, Kang Ji Hyun could have had a child,
but we couldn't find anyone since there was no record.
But if Kang Ji Hyun is Joon Jae's stepmother, then who is that, that kid, Heo Chi Hyeon,
Joon Jae's step brother, could be the child.
What's with your expression?
Just that... I feel like Heo Joon Jae was very lonely...
Well, he could have been.
But it could have been a blessing that he met me after running away from home.
That household is really chilling somehow...
If you find out anything else, make sure to tell me.
What help would she be if she heard anything else from me?
Ah... That day at this pool,
I'm sure there was something.
Cry.
Cry? Why did I ask her to cry?
Ah... tears...
Tears...?
This is my room.
Omo, it's cozy and pretty.
Can I sleep here with you tonight?
Of course.
Huh?
To my beloved Fool, you went through so much to come and be beside me, and I'm thankful that you came.
From now on, I'll make it so that you only wear pretty shoes and walk on nice paths.
Omo! Omo!
Omo! You finally came to our house!
Joon Jae gave them to you?
Because you're here like this next to Joon Jae,
I'm thankful and I feel relieved.
Me, too. I'm so thankful and relieved that you came to be with Heo Joon Jae, too.
But... if something happens and I'm not next to Heo Joon Jae anymore,
please don't go anywhere and be with him, okay?
Huh? Something like what?
I'm just saying in case...
Heo Joon Jae, thank you for the presents.
Why are you still up?
It's my birthday today, but I didn't really get to see your face properly.
Open the door.
♬ Friends say I've changed a bit♬
♬ The style of clothes I wear and even the type of coffee I like♬
♬ It's not something which is fabricated.♬
♬ What's coming out sounds like you. ♬
Since you saw my face, go to sleep. Stop making noise.
When I watched TV, a kiss was a must on a birthday.
♬ Every day one by one♬
- Hey! - Why?
Come here.
♬ I must still be filling up cautiously with you♬
♬ Look here even now I'm holding you♬
♬ Like in a dream, I'm embracing you.♬
Are you going to give me a birthday kiss?
- What?  - I'm ready.
Aigoo.
What is this?
Hey, Delinquent Mermaid, you were going on about romantic love and whatnot before,
but you keep going towards the dirty kind.
What do you mean dirty love? Over this? Are you kidding?
I wanted to warn you before, too,
but please don't think so much before falling asleep at night.
It's so noisy for me!
So shameful. Eavesdropping on my thoughts.
Who did that? I don't want to hear it either.
You keep blabbering on and that's why I can hear you.
I told you many times before, but I live in a house because I don't like floor to floor noise.
Your blabbering from the floor above me is giving me insomnia!
I get it Downstairs Mister. So did you ask me to see you to complain about noise?
Of course not.
Then why?
To do this.
I have to check and see if your heart's beating well.
But... it doesn't seem to be beating that great.
Really? I think it's beating just fine.
Now it is.
Oh, it shocked me so much that I couldn't even sleep.
So did your son grow up well?
Yes. I think so.
Oh, that's a relief. Now you can hold his hand and just go live with him now.
Why would I?
But Joon Jae should go back to his rightful place.
Omo, where are you going in the middle of our talk?
To make dinner...
Oh, what do you mean? Never mind!
Just order something today. Don't be like that and tell me more, Unnie.
Instead,
why don't we have some tea and have a conversation?
Do you want some coffee maybe?
Green plum tea.
Oh, that sounds good. Okay, green plum tea. Green plum...
Unnie, where do we keep the plum extract?
In the refrigerator on the second shelf.
Ah, that's right. In the second shelf.
Second shelf...
No, not there. Inside.
Oh!
- Shall I do it?  - No, no. I found it.
Do you think I can't make it for you? Seriously.
Oh, honey, you're home. I told you, right?
She found her son.
Oh, right. Congratulations.
Yes, thank you so much.
But...why did you...
It's cold, and it's too hard on you to go to the market without a car.
So since it's his free day, I asked him to go get grocery instead.
Oh, seriously. That's too much for you to do.
Why? Is it no good?
Vegetables are a bit wilted...and there's too much fat on the meat...
Seriously, I knew you would do this. Can't you shop well?!
I'm sorry. I just took whatever they gave me.
Oh, it's okay. It's understandable since you're a man.
I'll go and try to exchange them.
Seriously. You're making more work for Unnie!
I'm sorry.
Seriously, I can't live.
Yes?
Ji Yong's aunt?
Yes, c-come in.
You knew all along, right? That Joon Jae's my son.
That is, I was going to tell him...
Are you going to tell Joon Jae?
No, I'm not. I heard that you've been a good friend to him.
Thank you. From now on, too, please do the same.
Yes. I'll be sure to. Mother, thank you.
What do you mean, Mother? Don't be like this and be how you were before.
Then get some rest.
She smiled when she talked to me, so why do I feel so uneasy?
Did she just draw the line? Between Joon Jae and I?
Where is father?
Go on ahead.
Is that the President's real son?
Not sure. I think so.
What are you doing here?
Is he here at the company?
I told you before. He went on a vacation with his friends.
Really? To where?
To get some rest, he went to Hawaii.
Hawaii... He's been away for a while now. Because of food,
he doesn't stay longer than a week abroad even for a very important business trip.
Joon Jae, what is it that you want to say?
That I can't trust you.
That I'm cancelling how I told you to be a dutiful son to father.
We want to verify his flight records.
His name is Heo Il Joon. His resident number is 58-110-
Yeah, it's not here. His travel records.
Hawaii or wherever, he hasn't been out of the country for the past six months.
I'm certain he's in the country.
Hyung,
there's a place we need to steal from.
Where? Where is it? Where are we stealing from?
Wait a sec.
Where do you want to steal from?
- My father's house.  - What?
Hey, are you joking? How does it make sense?Stealing from your father's house?
Yeah, well, it would be good if we could get in there and gather some evidence.
But still, that Kang Seo Hee woman is frightening.
What if we get caught and croak, too? Hello?
I'll help, too.
- Help with what?  - Stealing from Heo Joon Jae's father's house.
- I'll help, too. - You heard everything?
No, it's fine.
But then again, you know Heo Chi Hyeon, his stepbrother,
and Joon Jae's mother is linked to Kang Seo Hee.
But still, you can't. If Joon Jae find out, it'll be hell! How about if we do it without him knowing?
What is it? What do you want help with?
What do you want me to do with Madam Kang?
Can you call her outside for about two hours?
About two hours?
That woman is so particular that she doesn't really like to go to gatherings.
It is kind of hard to call her out,
but I think there's way where she can't help but come out.
What? Ahn Jin Joo gathered up everyone except me?
Yes. I heard that she's going to reveal some crucial information!
Something about how lies can't win against truth or whatever.
This woman, is she crazy? Where? Tell me where and when!
She made me promise not to tell you.
You can't tell her that you heard from me, Madam-- - I got it!
Hurry up and tell me where!
Are you sleeping, Father?
Yeah...I guess the medicine is too strong. I'm a little fuzzy...
- Did you drink?  - Yes.
Father, couldn't your son be
only me?
If so, then I'd protect you well until the end.
Does there have to be Joon Jae, too?
Really?
It's because I'm upset to. I told Joon Jae
many times that you're unwell, but he says we won't come.
To me,
he said since he's your father, take care of him yourself.
Father... do you know what he's up to these days?
He's going around defrauding people. I was worried so when I looked into it, that's what he had been doing.
But still,
does it have to be Joon Jae?
You're drunk.
Go to bed.
Yes, Father.
[ 100% Customer Satisfaction! ]
[ One Shot, One Kill, Goodbye, Bug ]
Yeah.
- Where are you going like that?  - What about you?
Me?
I have work to do.
Oh, we have work to do, so we'll be going, Cheong. Yeah, see you later. Talk later.
Aren't you cold in winter like that? It's short! Change before you go out.
Why is this short?
I don't think it's that short.
Still, it's too...
pretty! Change!
You're doing all kinds of things. All kinds.
Okay? Change.
Is it? Is it too pretty?
Yeah, it's not right to be too pretty today.
Hey, we were on a stakeout here for a week,
but we've never seen your father once. Maybe not abroad but he could have gone out of town.
- Heo Chi Hyeon is going to be late tonight, too, right? - Yeah, that I confirmed.
Let's get it done quick.
Is this okay to do, really? I don't know anything, okay?
Don't do anything illegal and be careful!
Are you sending off your son?
One Shot, One Kill, Goodbye Bug, we'll do a once over.
Why are you here so early this month?
Ah, well...
The house ant traps are only good for 15 days, so we'll set up the new ones quickly after taking away the old. Don't mind us.
How many traps are in the kitchen?
I was glad you called me. Thank you.
Heo Chi Hyeon, to be honest, there's something I'm curious about.
What is it?
Do you know someone named Ma Dae Young?
Ma Dae Young and your mother and you, how are you related?
Why are you asking something like that?
Ma Dae Young keeps lingering around us. I don't know why that is.
If that has something to do with your family, I thought you might be able to stop it.
I'm sorry, but I can't.
I have nothing to do with that person.
Ahjummeoni, the ant traps that are
in the corners...
Ahjummeoni,
over here, please. Let me explain.
The ant traps,
we have to install about 10 and 10 for the cockroaches.
Then we'll start fumigating.
Ah, what is this? There's a sign of earwigs!
You see that black thing? Do you see it?
It's not dust but an earwig's excrement.
Ah, no matter how much effort you make, you can't prevent them from coming into a house.
Is it you?
Are you Chi Hyeon?
Who are you?
I said who are you?
Are you looking for this...?
Father?
Are you Joon Jae?
What were you doing in here?
Are you really Joon Jae?
What in the world did you see in here?!
What's with you?
You couldn't even recognize your own son. To suffer into this state, you separated from my mom.
and you treated me so badly?
Oh, Ahjumma, Ahjumma! Would you look over here?
Underneath this carpet, usually...
Let me just go to the room for a second.
Oh, Ahjumma! You need to hear more.
Let's leave for now.
To where?
Anywhere but this house.
Yeah, but why?
If you stay here any longer, we won't know what will happen to you.
This is my house. What would happen to me in my own house?
Like what happened to Manager Nam, you, and everybody else...! It's the Stepmother's fault.
I don't know how you entered into this house, but...
After coming back home after 10 years, all you can do is choose to slander your mother?
Who's my mother?
You probably wanted to tell me how my choice was wrong.
Yes, you chose wrong.
From the beginning to the end. Everything!
Who are you to judge that?
It's my choice! And it's my life! It's not wrong.
I was happy.
Just because my eyesight is getting a bit dull,
You want to tell me my choice and my life is a fail?
This eye will get completely better after surgery.
It's because my body's condition isn't good that I can't do surgery. If I just did surgery...!
It seems you can't only see me who's standing in front of you.
You can't see anything.
You don't even seem to think about seeing
where your life is going downhill.
Do you want to criticize your stepmother that much?
You rascal. She's a kind woman who cleans your room and waits for you to come home.
Living together for 17 years, she knows me the most.
What would you know?!
Kang Seo Hee's real name is Kang Ji Hyun. She was married twice,
You being like this...
It would be really great if it was a coincidence, but all these situations are saying it's not.
Where did you get such lies...?
If you don't want to believe it, then don't believe it.
But... I can't leave you alone like this.
Even if by force, I have to take you with me.
Let's go.
Let me go! He said you've been defrauding people!
That's why you're doing this horrible thing to me now, you bastard!
(I called) because it's weird with the loud noises from upstairs.
They said they word for a exterminator company but
I do hear "Father" and things like that.
Okay. I'll head home right now.
Don't let Father leave and if something happens, immediately report to the police.
Is this why you asked to meet with me?
It looks like Joon Jae is at home.
I'm sorry. It seems I won't be driving you home. Goodbye.
Your memory will all disappear and I'm sure you'll be arrested.
Even though you can't remember anything,
I will hope that you get a taste of hell for a very long time.
She's a real mermaid.
You have to kill her. Catch her!
Catch her!
Subtitles brought to you by The Blue Sea @ Viki
The two live well.
They aren't hurting nor are they hurt. They bore many pretty babies and while raising them well,
they happily grew old together
for a very long time.
Lies.
♬My nameless love ♬
It was all lies again.
♬ Before I knew you ♬
♬ was the sky ♬
♬ always this brilliant? ♬
♬ If out of ten thousand chances, our love came into being  ♬
Are you hurting somewhere? Why are you so cold?
Please leave me.
I like you a lot. Not as a friend but as a man.
What kind of person was Ma Dae Young?
Hey, you bastard! Why are you saying this now?
Unnie! Come inside!
I told you not to let just anyone come in!
Why did you lie?
So? Do you regret us being together?