Episode 18
If I were to be born again, I'd like to be
my wife's husband and my son's father.
That's what I wish for. It's probably my greed.
I am sorry, Joon Jae. I love you, my son.
Father.
Is this 119? We have an emergency patient here.
Any recent medications?
I'm not sure. He recently got an emergency surgery due to cerebral hemorrhage.
He was also scheduled to receive a cataract surgery, so he was probably taking medications related to that.
There are no other injuries, and looking at the spot coloring, there was no reaction to toxic chemicals.
Seeing that his lips are blue, it seems to be myocardial infarction, but we'll have more details after further examination.
Where is your mother?
She is out. She told me over the phone that she had an appointment about 2 hours ago.
- So she doesn't know that your father passed away yet?- That's right.
I haven't had a chance to tell her yet.
I thought she would be in too much shock when she finds out.
Oh, I see.
Then, let's move him to the hospital that has his medical records. Would you agree to it?
Yes.
Ah, Father!
Father! What do we do now!
No!
No, wait! Wait! Father!
It's not time yet, Father!
Dad!
Dad, I'm sorry! I'm sorry!
After the postmortem examination, a vidimus will be issued for a funeral. You will need to prepare for the funeral.
Alright.
I will do that.
Heo Chi Hyeon.
Come here. Come here, you bastard!
What are you doing? Who are you?
Because of you, my father... Because of you and that woman!
I won't leave you alone! I'll kill you. I'll kill both of you!!
Is this guy crazy?! Why are you doing this?
Get off!
You murderers! You guys killed my father!
Who are you? I asked who are you?
I am... I am Heo Il Joong's son!
I'm his son...
He is right. He is my younger brother.
Younger brother? I am your younger brother? Who are you?! Who are you, bastard!
- Who do you think you are?- Let go! Do you want to get arrested?
- Do something about it here! Hey! - Who do you think you are? Let go of me!
- Hold him, hold him, hold him. - Let go!
Not touch him, jerks!
Get off. Don't touch him.
Heo Joon Jae. Get a hold of yourself now.
That's right. Come to your senses.
Father...
Father has passed away.
I should have stopped it,
but I couldn't.
That's why you need to come to your senses, punk. You need to find everything out.
Why your father became like that... You need to find out.
Go to your father for now. I'll take care of things here. Okay?
Hey! Officer Cha!
What are you doing?
What happened to Heo Joon Jae? I'm so worried that I can't even sleep.
Since Officer Hong went there, I'm sure he will let us know.
But my Cheong, there's something I'm curious about. Can I ask you about something?
You said it earlier.
Ma Dae Young. It's Ma Dae Young, since he can't remember anything right now.
What can he not remember?
Who he is, what he has done so far...
Did Ma Dae Young really lose all his memory?
How would you know that?
Could it be that our Cheong made Ma Dae Young like that?
Why are you asking something like that?
I never thought I knew you so well,
but these days, I really am not sure who you are and what kind of ability you possess.
Who are you?
I am...
your friend.
Ah, friend.
But my job is to make someone believe I'm his friend and then back stab him.
Although I don't like that you are that kind of person, for me, once I become a friend, that's all. Whether you back stab or not is your choice.
Once I get back stabbed, I will think about what to do with you.
Until then, you are my friend.
- Why aren't you guys answering the call?- You scared me. What's going on?
Can you erase me?
The memory of my father.
Heo Joon Jae.
You can do it, can't you?
Can you make me like that?
All the good memories
hurt because they were good.
Bad memories
hurt because they are bad.
All my memories of my father
hurt so much.
I still can't erase them.
No matter how much it hurts, you loved your father.
It is said that you have hold on to the memory of love even if it hurts.
If I had gotten there just a little sooner,
I could have saved father.
No.
If I hated him just a little less,
I could have saved my father.
No.
Just a little...
It's not so.
It's not your fault.
It's not because of you.
I should have received
his last phone call.
I should have answered it.
That it's okay... that I forgave everything...
That I love him, too...
I should have said it.
I couldn't say those words.
I was too busy hating him,
Just one day... No...
just one hour... If I could have just one minute.
I want to talk to my father.
Now I can't do that.
I can't do it anymore.
Some words are said without talking.
I am sure he knew it all.
The Legend of the Blue Sea
Mortuary
Honey.
Why are you here, honey?
Why are you?
This is not possible. He told me to come back home after my appointment.
You told me to get some fresh air.
You said, "See you later."
I shouldn't have gone out.
Honey!
I can't... If you leave like this, how am I supposed to live?
No! This is unthinkable!
It can't be possible.
How could you, all by yourself...
- How can you leave me alone like this?!- Please calm your mother down.
- It will be hard to go in the mortuary like this.- No, Honey! No! You can't!
Honey!
-Mother!- It looks like she fainted from shock. Let's move her to the ER.
Wow! It's a shame to watch it by myself.
She really has great talent. She should've been an actress.
How did your father become like that all of a sudden?
They are still examining the body.
We will know the result tomorrow morning.
That's why I told him to stop drinking too much. And smoking, too.
He just didn't listen.
As one gets older,
I hear you forget recent memories and only remember old memories. That's how I am right now.
Old days seem like they were yesterday.
Your father didn't seem to be that way though.
Did you meet Father?
Yes. About a month ago, I saw him in this hospital accidentally.
He pretended not to know me.
Even though we locked eyes, he just passed me.
His gaze seemed to be of someone who really forgot it all.
Your father is such a harsh person.
If I were to be born again,
I would like to be
my wife's husband and my son's father.
That's what I wish for.
It's probably my greed.
Father had severe corneal damage that he could hardly see.
What?
He didn't pretend not to see you.
He couldn't see you.
Yes, Attorney Lee.
Please submit his death notification tomorrow.
I will send you the certificate and other necessary documentation.
Also, work on transferring inheritance.
How long will it take?
It will take about a week.
That's too long. Finish it as soon as possible.
Mom is fine now.
I won't take medication, so you don't need to get the prescription.
It was you, wasn't it?
What is?
Mother, you have to tell me.
I need to know so I can help.
That's right.
You are correct.
But...
just in case, you don't know anything.
Emergency Medical Center
Mr. Jo Nam Doo?
Attention!
A new warrior?
I am called Park Moo.
I heard your skills are excellent.
Please assist my son well.
If one posses a lot, a lot of people will be after him.
Yes, but how do you know my name?
Can we talk a little?
I heard that Joon Jae is doing some strange work.
I was worried and looked into it a bit.
Oh, I see.
While I was doing it, I found out about you. You are a bit different from Joon Jae.
Joon Jae scamed against hidden dirty money
or illegal money that the victims wouldn't be able to report the scam.
But you didn't care about the source, Mr. Jo Nam Doo.
In other words,
- you commit all kinds of crime?- Yes.
I don't discriminate.
I eat all kinds of things and I do all kinds of work. That's how it is.
So what?
As early as tomorrow, (using informal tone)
no, even today, I can put you in jail. That's what I'm saying.
What will you do? (informal speech form)
Will you listen to me or rot in jail for a few years?
Why are you speaking informally? (using formal speech)
Please treat me kindly.
I am always on the side of the one with a lot of money.
It looks like you will inherit all your father's assets, Hyungnim.
If that's the case, there is no need to threaten me so harshly like this.
I have more than enough reason to side with you.
What is it that you want?
- I'm going to get rid of Joon Jae.- To where?
Anywhere fine. So he won't be anywhere.
Ah, actually,
there is something special that I really want.
If Joon Jae disappears, I think it will be easier for me, too.
Ah, that's fine.
I was hesitating a bit because I felt a bit close to him, but sure, let's do it.
This relation was bound to end sooner or later.
The cause of death is
sudden death caused by acute heart failure.
Sudden death? Not by poisoning?
If his death were caused by toxic poison, his lips would have turned dark brown.
But his lips were bluish.
It's a typical symptom of cardiac arrest.
In addition, if it was due to toxic chemicals, his death spots should have been black, but it wasn't like that.
Based on his medical records, I believe it was a natural death caused by acute heart failure.
If it was a strong poison like cyanide, it could've been like that.
But it's my understanding that the symptoms are different if the poison was extracted from natural substance, like helmet flowers.
On the surface, the symptom is said to be very similar to that of heart failure.
I want to do the autopsy.
That way, we can reveal the real cause of death,
and find the cause of corneal damage.
You want to kill your father twice?
Why?
Is there something that you don't want to be found out?
That's not what I'm saying. Joon Jae, for sending your father
alone like that makes me crazy.
I don't want him to be hacked to pieces with a knife again.
What in the world do you want to find out that you want an autopsy?
- The evidence that you killed my father.- Hey!
Don't do it, Chi Hyeon.
It's been 10 years already, Joon Jae.
Over 10 years, your father missed you so much,
but you never visited home.
I am curious as to why you are being like this all of a sudden.
Is it because of money?
If it's for money, I'll give it all to you. So,
let's just send him peacefully. He is your father, after all.
Let's not be so cruel like that.
With such perfect acting that would even fool yourself,
you may have bewitched many people and blinded my father's eyes,
that won't work anymore.
I am Heo Il Joong's only biological son. The helmet flowers that were found in that house,
and micro-needles and a large amount of anticholinergic that belong to Kang Seo Hee's,
all those are evidence that could have been used for murder, so I am requesting an autopsy.
I am the oldest son of this household.
I am also the only son that father acknowledged.
Younger brother ran away from home 10 years ago and cut off the relationship with our father.
Because of the inheritance issue, there was a big conflict with father recently.
I and my mother do not want an autopsy.
Father will agree with that.
- This is a search and seizure warrant.- Search the place!
Ah, isn't it a bit too early for funeral clothes?
Funeral will start soon.
If we do autopsy, you won't be able to do funeral.
- I guess you are confident.- Think whatever you want to think.
No matter what I say, you won't believe me anyway.
Do you know Kang Ji Hyeon by any chance?
And, from now on,
if there are anything else you'd like to ask, please go through my lawyer.
Ah, lawyer...
I suppose you do have something to say through your lawyer.
If course you would. It's your twin sister's name.
It was really hard to obtain this picture of your childhood.
You two really look alike.
So it's fraternal, right?
I don't know what you are trying to say.
Where is your sister now?
Or is that you?
I'm going crazy.
Hey, didn't anything come up?
As you can see.
Sunbae, do you think you were wrong this time?
No. It couldn't have escaped from this house.
There must be something in this house.
Honey, today is not red. It's black.
Why?
Chairman Heo... passed away.
What? How?
I don't know, either. I just heard about it now.
Oh, how is it turning now?
If he passes away so suddenly, what will happen to our fate?
I heard CEO Heo left all his assets to the adopted son and Kang Seo Hee.
That's what I heard.
But still, even though he had notarized his will,
I thought he would give it to his biological son.
That's right. You could just change your will anyway.
But if he passes away so suddenly like this,
then they can't do anything about it.
Then did we line up on the wrong side?
It's beyond just lining up on the wrong side.
Ugh! To think what I did to that woman, Kang Seo Hee...
Oh my god! I will be put to death by dismemberment!
Can't you change the line even at this point?
How can a person be like that? As a person, it's acceptable to change the side once.
But if you change it twice, that is just wrong as a person.
- I can't do that!- What what do we do?
I don't know it, either!
Hey, how can you come here?
What do you think? I'm getting people's attention, and it will be awkward for you.
Joon Jae's father,
there were many reasons why I couldn't forgive you.
But seeing the end of you is so sad.
Can you see me now?
Watch me well. I need to say farewell.
Like mother, like son.
Your son never came to visit his father for over 10 years.
Now that he is dead, there is no better son than him.
It must all be because of money.
The petty reason you came here
is trying to find some crumbs to collect, isn't it?
If you just stayed still, I would have given you something.
If you come out so loudly like this,
would I have heart to give you even a penny? Ouch!
Hey!
- Have you gone crazy?! - The ones who crawled in to collect some crumbs are you and your son.
If you did that, you should have been satisfied by leeching off of others.
Now a thief wants to act like an owner?
You are too greedy.
What? A thief?
- What is this? - Are you trying to hit her? I don't think you are in the position to hit her.
What are you? Who are you to intervene?
You watch what you say.
Oh, is she someone you know? No wonder!
Let go! Won't you let go?
What are you doing now?
What I'm trying to do is... There's something I'm curious about.
What is this?
Don't forget to take your medicine.
What's wrong, Cheong?
What did you just do?
I could have done everything, but I didn't do anything.
Because you shouldn't forget all the wrong that you did.
I think you should remember them till the end.
You should remember all the things that you coveted,
so you will be more tormented for not obtaining them.
Let's go now.
- Get me some more side dishes.- I'm not a worker here.
Yes.
Omo, Madam.
- Madam, you must be so sad.- Omo, you've lost weight.
- Despite all that Madam, you're so beautiful.- Oh, I'm worried, will you be alright?
Wow, how could anyone have so few principles.
They're lucky.
Ugh, why do I have to be so honest when it comes to my own principles?! I'm insane.
Where's Yu Ran Unnie? We're the odd ones out at this point.
Should I do something too?
- Did they find evidences?- Not yet.
- You're not gonna go to the funeral hall?- Yeah.
You should just go.
How could I? I still haven't figured out how he passed away.
Do you have to do that?
What?
- The autopsy.- What?!
It's all in the past. Whatever truth we find now
won't make your deceased father come back to life.
We're just poking at them at this point. And besides that,
you should be sweet talking them, working it out--making sure that you'll inherit something at least.
Even if he is a stranger to you, you don't say things like that!
I don't think I said anything I shouldn't have.
Think about it.
Heo Joon Jae.
I think I saw something.
You came to stand next to me--only to get caught up in a mess like this, having to see bad things you don't need to see.
The fact that all those things become your memories, it upsets me.
Even though I'm happy that I can protect you with what I have?
You protect me?
Why, Heo Joon Jae? You think I can't?
It's true, I came up to the land without knowing anything, which made other people treat me like an idiot.
- But unlike what you see, I was totally popular in the sea.- Is that so?
Of course! Unlike what you see, I'm a mermaid of an endangered species.
Sigh, these days you human beings with your submarines and skin scuba-whatever, you call it that and barge into the underwater
do you realize how hard it is for mermaids and mermen to stay hidden and survive?
Then sharks come whenever they want, saying "We'll bite and kill you"--Our lives are hard too.
What do you do when a shark comes?
I can fight a shark and still win.
Wow, really? My girlfriend's the best!
You're smiling. From now on, I'll keep making you smile.
"I'll protect you", "I'll make you smile". These are all things that the guy's supposed to say!
I'll protect you. I'll make you smile.
Dummy, saying all the things I'm supposed to say.
What should we do? We've made no progress.
It's here.
- Where are you going?- The basement?
I looked over there already.
She made a place like this. This never existed.
Forensics and I looked over this place.
It's there.
- These are wolfsbane flowers.- Don't touch those! Don't touch anything.
Whether it's a fingerprint or anything else, it'll all come out.
What is that? Isn't that a mermaid?
Ma Dae Young. Ma Dae Young was here.
And Kang Seo Hee was Kang Ji Hyun.
Joon Jae, thank goodness you came. You should be here with your older brother as chief mourner.
I should. After I see you put in jail.
What?
From this moment, the unnatural death case of the deceased, Heo Il Joong, has been turned into a murder case.
The deceased will be immediately transferred to the National Forensic Service for an autopsy.
subtitles ripped and synced by riri13
What did you say? With whose permission?
Kang Seo Hee, no, Kang Ji Hyeon, I'm arresting you without a warrant as a murder suspect.
You have the right to remain silent and you have the right to the attorney you like so much so do as you wish.
Do you have evidence? Do you have a warrant?!
Because there was so much evidence your mother left at home, we were able to easily collect it.
And that's why we're arresting her without warrant.
Are you trying to say that I killed my husband right now?
You should frame the right person.
If my husband heard he'd be so upset.
Shut up! Don't speak my father's name so easily with that mouth.
His words have weight.
What are you doing? Why are you putting these kinds of things on me?!
Take them off! Can't you take them off? Take them off!
You guys are making a mistake with me.
If you do this to an innocent person do you think you'll be safe?!
Take them off!
Chi Hyeon! Contact the lawyer!
- Chi Hyeon! Call the lawyer, hurry! - Rascal
Chi Hyeon.
Noona.
But did something happen? Why is the atmosphere like this here?
How can such a thing like this happen? Joon Jae must be so heartbroken.
How long has it been since he's met his mother that this kind of thing should happen?
Where's your car?
I took the bus.
Should I drop you off?
It's okay. Well, do you want to? It is late.
But you can't have other thoughts, okay? It'll be burdensome to me then.
Hey, isn't this person insanely hot?
Hey, look. He's totally good-looking.
They're so loud.
♬ Why am I looking at her?♬
♬(Could it be love?)♬
♬ Why do I smile when I see her?♬
♬ (Could it be love?)♬
♬It must be a dream ♬
What's he doing?
♬ It must be a dream ♬
He's won the lotto. He'd be so excited to know that he's fallen asleep on my shoulder.
♬Why am I like this? Just why am I? ♬
How can he be prettier than a girl?
Hey, did you see this?
This is daebak (awesome)!
Oh no, I have to get off here.
♬Wake me up, oh me.♬
♬What kind of magic are you using on me?♬
♬How are you doing this to me?♬
Subtitles brought to you by The Blue Sea @ Viki
Sleep here.
But Ma Dae Young may have lost his memory but he remembers the mermaid.
I know, right.
Ma Dae Young seems to be better than Dam Ryeong sometimes when it comes to his thinking of the mermaid.
Se Hwa seems to speak so prettily. Her smile is pretty and her actions are so demure.
I wonder if just because the face is alike if the person could be the same?
Why are you like that, really?
But would everything really only be repeating from the past life in the same way?
Why?
Truthfully, when I was erasing Ma Dae Young's memory I saw another person's face.
Who?
The spear we were hit with when we died wasn't one that Ma Dae Young threw.
What does that mean?
It was one that someone else threw. I saw that person's face.
Who is it?
A person we know.
Looking at it, they only have circumstantial evidence. They don't have direct evidence.
The poison tonic,
the evidence that you gave it to the Chairman,
They're going to interrogate you with leading questions. Only listen. Keep your answers short.
If they ask you unfavorable questions, "I don't remember,"
"My head hurts, I have a chronic disease,"
You can use your right to remain silent.
Because they arrest you emergently without a warrant
they can only hold you for 48 hours.
Hurry up and tell us. If you don't speak it will just go over as evidence.
I don't know.
Look here. You had this cup, and these 10 plates...
Why did you receive a prescription for an anticholinergic?
My head hurts. No.
Using water infused with wolfsbane-!
I don't know.
I have a panic disorder...
I'm telling you that I don't remember and I don't know anything!
She's totally decided to hold out on the "I have no recollection." If this much evidence, I thought she'd confess.
If she acknowledges it she becomes disqualified as a successor and all that money disappears. She probably would desperately endure it.
If she doesn't confess it crosses over into an investigation without detention, right?
It seems like he's leaving after meeting with the Detective.
Your mother will be released about 6pm today, right?
Then, how would tonight be?
I don't think they'd stay like this forever. We strike first.
I feel a bit urgent too.
Police: We Serve You with Devotion
Oh!
What?
It's Joon Jae Hyung.
What about Heo Joon Jae?
Is Jo Nam Doo crazy? Why is he like that?
Can't I go by myself? What if it's dangerous?
Tae Ho, there's something you don't know.
If we had an actual fight, you wouldn't even be able to save your bones.
Just know that I'm way stronger than you and hurry up and step on the gas.
Tie him tighter.
Hey you bastard! How could you do this to me? How could you do this to me?!
You were the one who fell for a woman
and stopped working with me. You're the one who betrayed me!
I have to make a living too. I'm sorry about this.
Untie me. Untie me, you bastard!
Oh, and this.
What's that?
Your suicide note. It will be discovered in your room tomorrow.
You're going to commit suicide from the guilt of having killed your father today.
What?
Don't do it.
It's the component that killed your father, Acrotine.
If it's fast 10 minutes, if it's late 30 minutes. You'll become comfortable (dead).
You crazy bastard.
Since you weren't able to receive any inheritance from father, that's enough for the murder motive.
And... since you know the layout of our house well, you concealed the evidence in the basement
Joon Jae.
It wouldn't be hard to come up with a story.
- Chi Hyeon.  - Yes, Mother.
Will you wait outside with that person?
Do you think I'll leave you alone according to your wishes?
If you don't what are you going to do?
Dead men tell no tales.
Look at you father. He can't say anything.
How could you be like that to Father?
When Father was so good to you!
And wasn't I good?! It was 17 years.
I spent 17 years, acting like the tongue in Heo Il Joong's mouth and I was very good.
But when it came time to bequeath his fortune he only looked for his blood.
Is that why you killed him?
Yes. I killed him.
As it was your father was dying.
Truthfully, that poison, he hadn't been ingesting it only for one or two days.
He was becoming addicted to it in very small amounts so he didn't know.
It would have been hard for him to pass a year
but with him saying he wanted to draw up a will
I just sent him a bit early.
You killed your previous husbands like that too, didn't you Kang Ji Yeon.
That's right. But no one knew even after 20 years passed.
Perhaps, even after 20 years passes no one will probably know
that I killed you and your father.
Would that really be?
Who did it? I told you not to do that during working hours.
Come out!
What is this?
What is this?! Who are you?! Can't you let this go? Let go!
You! How dare you-
Look to see how many people put on such a show to make you confess to your crimes.
Hey, this person has a panic disorder. Hurry up and arrest her and lock her up
so she can be alone.
Let me go! Let me go! Let me go!
Hey! You, Heo Joon Jae! You're going to be in trouble!
Hey, a job came in from Heo Chi Hyeon.
Do I look like a betrayer-type? Why does everyone (do this) to me?
Heo Chi Hyeon does see a person correctly.
So what did you say?
What do you mean, what did I say? Of course, I said I'd do it.
You human being I can't trust.
Hey, it's like this. That side's a successor and you're a beggar.
Hey, you know my principle, right? First, money. Second, even more money.
Then you should just take the money and do what they ask. What're you coming here to tell us this for?
Sadly, the third principle doesn't fit.
The third? What's that?
Manners.
What?
I keep manners. This jerk kept speaking casually to me, when he's even younger than I am.
I speak casually to you too.
You're the home owner. I have a respect for the home owner. Respect, admiration.
So, did you tell him you wouldn't do it?
No, I told him I'd do it.
Why?
We have to go hit him.
What? - The back of his head.
[ We're being wire tapped nearby. I'll only speak to you through text messages. ]
Did any fingerprints come out yet?
Not yet.
You're not going to the funeral hall?
I'm not going.  [ Act angry. ]
But you should still go.
How can I go when I still don't know how my father died yet.
[ No. Be a little angrier! ]
Do you have to do it?
- What?  - The autopsy.
No matter that it's someone else's business, is that something you should say?!
That's right. You're doing well.
Let's get ready.
Okay.
I'll hit you in front of the car door.
Fall down, fall down.
Make it look realistic. Does it make sense that if you hit hit from the back that you'd drip blood from there?
It really hurt earlier.
What, it's not even a real steel pipe. Why are you making such a fuss about getting hit with it?
Hey, is it a right or a left at this port?
Straight.
Hey, I lost it because of you! Damn it.
You! You! Heo Joon Jae! Can't you let go?!
Mother.
Chi Hyeon.
Chi Hyeon!
You can't!
- Work hard.  - You worked hard.
Hey! Hey!
Chi Heyon!
Hurry up and get in.
Heo Joon Jae!
I saw that person's face.
Heo Chi Hyeon.
Subtitles brought to you by The Blue Sea @ Viki
♬ Did I wake up from a long dream?♬
♬ As soon as I recognized you♬
♬ Before I knew you was the sky♬
♬ always as brilliant?♬
♬ If out of ten thousand chances♬
♬ our love came into being♬
♬ you and I could begin♬