Let go! You... you, Heo Joon Jae! Are you not going to let me go?!
Mother.
Chi Hyeon.
Hey. Hey!
Chi Hyeon!
Heo Joon Jae!
I saw the person's face.
Heo Chi Hyeon.
Ah, really!
Heo Joon Jae, I was scared you were going to protect me again, but I'm so happy.
The ending has changed. This time, I saved you.
No.
It can't be. No. Please.
- You'll probably know this by now. -Please!
That even though I'm not by your side,
-I'll keep loving you. So...-Cheong, Cheong.
be happy in all of the moments I'm not in. Laugh a lot and receive a lot of love.
Like how normal people live, I wish you live comfortably for a long, long time.
I don't wish to be your scars or your nightmare.
Don't go.
Don't go anywhere.
I love you.
Please come here quickly! Quickly!
Please.
I love you.
The Legend of the Blue Sea
Episode 19
Ms. Kang, who was to inherit the fortune of Budongsan's chairman Heo
has been captured by the police as the murderer of her husband.
Son of Ms. Kang and adopted son of Mr. Heo, Mr. "A" also was arrested on the charge as an accessory to murder as well as attempted murder.
Ms. Kang raised Monkshood in her home and extracted (poison) from the roots
and murdered her husband with the deadly Acinotine.
She also kidnapped Mr. Heo's biological son and tried to murder him. Police already at the site
has been caught and arrested in the act.
In that process Mr. "A" evaded the police and fired a gun at Mr. "B"
and Mr. "B's" girlfriend was hit and it's known that she's fallen into critical condition.
After Mr. Heo passed away, Ms. Kang was preparing the transfer of inheritance. The notarized will was as expected...
Omo! What should we do?
see it as Ms. Kang having committed the crime aiming for the fortune.
They have announced that they will work towards tracing an accomplice, saying that there will have been an assistant in all these crimes.
They're injection ampules made with the poison Aconitine extracted from the Monkshood flower.
You might fail, so take two just in case.
Hey, are you doubting my skills?
One shot, one kill. Don't worry.
Okay then.
May I go to the restroom for a bit?
Please... don't worry. It's fine. Please... please...
You're an attempted murderer. Do you know that?
And you even stole a gun from a police officer so special obstruction of official judicial execution.
Why I'm living like an animal driven into a corner,
Why I'm living like I'm receiving a punishment. I'm not sure.
But I wish your life isn't like this.
I'm not sure who you are, but the thought just occurred in this situation.
What...?
You guys did an Entrapment Investigation. That wiretapping is illegal!
Can that be evidence?
That's not illegal. Heo Joon Jae was recording his own voice but you, Kang Seo Hee-- no,
Kang Ji Hyun interrupted herself. That can become evidence.
What a joke. You set it all up!
- When my lawyer comes--- What to do? All those lawyers have left.
Find more or request a public defender.
What?
Hey.
What do I do? I think he took the medicine.
What?
Why? Did my lawyer come? So are you guys surprised?
Ah, no, it's not that. Your son Heo Chi Hyeon...
Our Chi Hyeon? What about our Chi Hyeon?
Chi Hyeon!
Chi Hyeon! Chi Hyeon!!
Call a doctor!
We called 119 so they'll be here in a minute.
It's of no use.
Chi Hyeon!
I...endured as much as I could...
I dragged the time.
Why did you do that? Why did you go that, Chi Hyeon!?
Mother...
Okay, Chi Hyeon, okay!
Mother... that you're my mother...
It was a curse for me.
Chi Hyeon! Chi Hyeon!
Chi Hyeon! Chi Hyeon?!
Chi Hyeon!
Chi Hyeon!!
No, Chi Hyeon!
No!
Chi Hyeon!
Operating Room
Joon Jae. I just got a call from Detective Hong.
Heo Chi Hyeon died.
He originally gave me two doses of wolfsbane root.
But, I said I didn't need both of them and switched out the one that I took.
But it seems Heo Chi Hyeon had the remaining one
and drank it.
It's so potent if taken orally, it just takes more time
but it's still fatal.
He's so irresponsible till the end.
Who's the guardian?
It's me.
Did the surgery go well, Doctor?
Well... we should look at it like it went well.
This isn't the level of "well" but a miracle.
The bullet went through the right ventricle and the left ventricle.
I have never seen someone live from this.
I've never seen a case like this at school either.
Have you ever seen this?
No.
There was a lot of blood loss, and her blood pressure dropped very low as well.
In these cases, they usually go in shock so I put on the heart-lung machine.
But after I stitched up the pierced part,
It's not normally like this.
But the heart returned very easily.
What about her vital signs?
That also isn't normally like this.
They are rapidly stabilizing.
Well of course, the location of the bullet is quite critical,
so we need to keep an eye on her to see when she regains consciousness.
Thank you.
Right now is very important.
Because there was already a lot of blood loss, if the circulation to the brain decreases,
since we can't exclude the possibility of loss of brain function...
Let's talk again after she regains her consciousness.
I understand.
But this patient normally doesn't eat anything especially weird, right?
Rather than eating something weird, she especially eats a lot.
Thank you, Doctor. Thank you.
Subtitles brought to you by The Blue Sea @ Viki
This jerk.
How could you leave like that?
Which girl are you going to?
What the? From sometime in the early morning I've been dreaming that I was deserted by my husband...
And why is there a traditional bridal crown? So annoying!
Tell me. Can you... get shot by a gun for me?
I can only go as far as getting hit by a rock.
I knew it.
What about you?
I have to raise the kids. If I get shot, who will raise the kids?
Why are you guys suddenly talking about guns?
You haven't heard about it yet?
-I thought they were close to each other, but I guess not.-It seems so.
-About what?-Your friend!
Yoo Ran's son Heo Joon Jae.
-What about Joon Jae?-The adoptive son of that household
shot at the biological son Heo Joon Jae,
and the girlfriend took that gunshot instead of him.
Isn't it like a movie? Right? They're at the hospital right now.
They left early in the morning to see the surgery results.
You should watch the news! The news!
You said the surgery went well, but why isn't she regaining her consciousness?
Because it's a big surgery, it must be taking some time.
Did she talk about it to do this?
What talk?
In just a few days, your face got so gaunt.
Eat this.
-Mom, you know about the Little Mermaid story, right?-I do.
In the end, the mermaid gets a knife, right?
If she kills the prince with the knife, she would live,
but if she fails to kill him, she becomes a bubble and disappears.
What would you do?
Why are you asking that?
I think it's right for the mermaid to disappear,
because it's a story that the mermaid started
with her greed to come up the shores.
That's not how I think.
Why?
Long ago, a young man went out to sea, but the ship got overturned.
He met the mermaid and she saved his life.
He married the mermaid and had babies.
They lived happily.
The children who were born through the human and the mermaid,
some returned to the water, and some remained on land.
One became the village people's benefactor.
While communicating with the mermaids of the sea, when there was a storm
he was told in advance not to go to sea.
There's this mermaid story too.
It's not greed that the mermaid went up onto the shores but of love.
Although it would be nice to have all stories a happy ending,
but there are stories that aren't.
She talked about that?
Yeah. So with this event having happened,
my heart hurts a lot.
I need her to quickly wake up so that I can say thank you.
How did she think of running in front of a gun?
You could just easily get shot.
No. You can't. You'll die like a dolphin.
That's what I'm saying. The person who was so scared of a gun
had no fear.
But, Mother, is there really a legend like that?
Did he really marry the mermaid and have babies
and happily live for a long, long time?
Do you not remember?
When you were little and said you couldn't sleep, I would always tell you that story.
You liked it so much.
I see.
It would be nice if that was true.
By the way. Because I'm here, would you take that to Department Head Nam's wife?
Okay.
Where are you going? Wanna go together?
Let's go.
-Ahjummonim.-Oh, Joon Jae!
I heard the news. How could this have happened?
The surgery ended well.
-He's a close Hyung.-Ah, yes.
Hello. I've heard a lot about you from Joon Jae.
You have a good impression.
I feel like I've seen him a lot somewhere.
When you go straight on this road and pass the hill, there will be a place which is the Bangcheon Inn.
Pardon?
Tell them to give you the horse that Park Moo asked them to hold. Ride that horse to the capital
and do the work that the official requested of you.
Why are you doing this?
To pay back honor and enemy.
I don't have the time to explain so hurry up and move.
Hurry.
Thank you.
- My mother asked me to give this to you.  - You didn't have to. I'm so thankful.
- Don't skip meals. - Okay. Thank you.
Oh!
Park Moo.
Honey! Did your eyes open? Did you just talk? Doctor!
Doctor!
subtitles ripped and synced by riri13
Ahjussi...
Park Moo.
Park... what? I'm not Park Moo, I'm Jo Nam Doo.
Dam Ryeong.
Joon Jae.
I dreamed a very long dream.
It's good that you woke up.
Back then and even now,
thank you for being my friend.
Why is she not waking up?
That's what I'm saying. They definitely said the surgery went well.
Is there something definitely different than us, neurologically or so?
What are you saying?
To be honest, I heard the conversation between you guys.
That you to Cheong... about mermaid and things like that.
Hah! It was a joke. Do you believe that? Are you joking?
I know, right? Our house isn't even some cartoon park or something. I don't know why I believe this,
but I believe it. Cheong isn't like us.
She's a mermaid.
Hey, don't be nervous! You think I'll do something to your girlfriend?
Yeah, you could do more than that.
Hey, it's true that I may be a guy whose eyes become blinded by money, but I keep true to two principles.
What?
I, without fail, pay back my enemies. I pay back my debts if possible.
Although, Cheong didn't save me
But she protected my Joon Jae. My Joon Jae.
Hey, so would I do anything to Cheong?
What do you mean "my Joon Jae?" Are you crazy?
Hah! You're saying outrageous things! So cringe-worthy.
Hey, and this was sincere but after saying it I feel all cringey too.
Heo Joon Jae is my Joon Jae. Don't mess with him.
You woke up, Cheong?
As expected, the representative to watch Cheong!
Are you okay?
If you didn't wake up,
I really would have followed you.
Why?
You said you'd meet a prettier woman and live and eat well.
There's none that is prettier than you no matter how much I search.
You looked?
I thought about it and (realized) life is short.
I feel that my love will be longer than my life.
So that's why in this life, my love won't end.
Thank you...
for returning.
Who's saying who's cringe-worthy?
Policeman Who Devote Their All
Murderer!
You're not a human!
- How dare you!  - Murderer! You murderer!
You feel like you won everything, right? No! This isn't the end!
It won't end like this. It can't end. Okay?
My son can't be the only one to suffer like this.
Don't end it like this! Don't end it!
Hey, you murderer!
[ Professor Jin Kyung Won ]
Professor Jin Kyung
Yes, this is Jin Kyung.
Ma Dae Young?
Joon Jae, Ma Dae Young is coming this way.
Yes, I'll go over there right now.
Yeah, Hyung. It's me. Contact Detective Hong.
Ma Dae Young is going to Professor Jin Kyung.
Do you not remember anything?
I only remember from the time I met that girl.
But... why do you suddenly want to search for your memories?
Have you ever wandered without your memories?
The feeling of being trapped in the woods with your two eyes covered but hearing the sound of animals from all around.
The fear of being eaten by that animal is not what's hard, but the fear of not knowing when and where what will come jumping out at you.
That's what makes me crazier.
At times, couldn't the fear be better than the reality?
No, but I still have to know. I can't live like this anymore.
Because of a sin that I can't even remember
I can't live paying the punishment.
Husband Cheon.
Husband Cheon, I heard you can tell fortunes better than most shamans out there.
It's not that I have any special powers of divination,
it's only that I have a lot of interest in others' fates.
Anyhow, read our fortune for the new year.
The beautiful flowers that pierced the harsh snow and bloomed everywhere
are all yours.
They're all mine, the beautiful flowers?
Why? They're not gold and treasures?
The captivating scent of those flowers
permeate your body's crevices, until you die
Even if they die and are reborn, they will not leave each other and will be together.
It's something good, right?
Sin cannot determine fate's good and evil.
Then, what about me?
A tree hit by lightning still has spirit left so grows again
Are you receiving the punishment so you can live? Or are you living so you can receive the punishment?
You will live a confusing life.
What are you saying?
So, you might as well get hit by lightning and burn into black ashes.
It would have been better to not have been born again
but this is also a fate you have no choice in.
It's a shame.
This rascal...
Leave!
Get whoever.
Do you know Park No Joon?
I've never heard of, or met, or seen that person.
His ship was forcibly held at the port, so he had to stay here for 20 days,
and was found as a cold corpse just because he traveled through that part of the sea.
You wretched thief!
Even if you block the path and commit highway robbery, how could you do this?
Did you think you were making that long trip back and forth to China to fatten your belly?
I'm going to expose your crimes to everyone!
A man has died!
There's a person who has died!
I am his son, Park Moo. This is for my father,
and for Kim Dam Ryeong.
I will definitely be born again.
I will be reborn and whatever I didn't own in this world,
I will definitely own all of them.
Please do so. No matter how many times you reincarnate,
I will avenge just as many times.
This woman put poison in my father's drink?
I have prepared a poison worthy for you.
Do you know what wolfsbane flower is? It is a beautiful flower which produces a deadly poison.
Receive it.
I saw it.
In my past life, me, Dam Ryeong, mermaid.
And you. You always knew.
Just like how I received punishment in this life,
the fate I must fulfill.
You circled around me and just watched?
Whose side are you on?
You were like that then, and you are like that now.
I'm just someone who observes fate.
I am on no one's side.
Ah. You knew it all. Right?
Professor!
Remember. I have won against you two again.
Fate...
will be on my side this time as well. In this life,
in the end, everything will repeat.
A hopeless love between human and wicked.
Misery would be waiting at the end of that.
It does not matter whose side fate is on.
In the end of that ill-fate, we were together, so we were happy. It is the same now.
Joon Jae!
Put that down!
I have finally caught you.
Put your hands up!
Joon Jae, are you alright?
Why is he glaring at me? It's our first meeting.
Oh my, that scared me!
So unexpected from you. Are you here to visit me? With flowers?
Well...
I heard you were unconscious, so I was just going to leave the flowers.
Are you worried about me right now?
Well, I wouldn't say that but...
Honestly, it's my first time seeing someone who got shot.
Did you really get shot? Oh my, what to do? It must've really hurt.
So, where did you get hit?
It sort of sounds like you're enjoying this.
Hey, are you insane?
I don't really like you, but it's not like I hate you to the point that I would be glad you got shot.
Then, do you like me?
I told you. It's not that I totally like you.
I like you though.
Oh, you're quite straight forward.
But why?
I always wanted to be like you.
Ah, it shouldn't be easy becoming like me. But why?
You can grow old with the person you like.
Are you saying I'm old?
I look young for my age. I'm not the type who'll grow old with someone.
Not that, but I'm jealous.
You can spend lots of time with the person you like.
What can I do when I have lots of time? The person I want to spend time with only looks at you.
Ah, you only dream such small dreams. I'm envious of you.
Your fated person will appear.
Did you get possessed by a spirit after getting shot? What's with you?
I have waited a long time, and they appeared.
So, yours will appear as well.
You're telling me to stay away from Joon Jae, right? I was going to do that without you telling me anyway.
You'll even get shot for Heo Joon Jae. How can I beat that?
Get well soon.
Myeongseong University Hospital
It's snowing.
♬Why am I looking at her?♬
- Tae Ho.♬(Could it be love?)♬
Yes, Noona. You didn't go home?
♬Why do I smile when I see her?♬
♬(Could it be love?)♬
You're not dropping me off?
- Should I accompany you?  - No.
I thought you wanted to drop me off.
It's fine then.
♬Why am I like this? Why?♬
I said it's fine.
Do whatever you want.
♬Why does my heart keep trembling?♬
The snow is so pretty.
It is.
I'm being generous.
You gotta have some proper pictures. You always get sneak shots.
What the heck?
Isn't all of these pictures of Cheong?
Come here you!
So the one you liked was not me but Unni Cheong? Was that it?
Then why did you confess that you like me?
The thing is, the boss...
What? What did you do to me? Did you put on a show? Why didn't you tell me?
Was it fun seeing me like that? I didn't even know you were playing with me,
and I took care of your heart so that you wouldn't be damaged
when I rejected you!
I told you don't follow me!
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, Noona.
♬ It becomes clear now. That everything will be for the two of us♬
♬ once more was not accidental.♬
♬ Forever we had to meet .♬
The area of the injury stopped bleeding so I checked the wound, but
there was nothing to bandage.
That's nonsense. Are you sure you didn't see wrong? How could a bullet wound disappear that quickly?
The doctors in the operating room are in a ruckus as well.
At first. the bleeding was so excessive. Everyone was nervous, just in case the aorta (major part of the heart) was ruptured.
But, the wound was completely clean.
Really? What is this? It's scary.
Perhaps, is it something like that? Alien?
That's going a bit far.
- Zombie?- Vampire.
Anyway, the Chief said he'll report the case at the Heart Association and the AHA
and donate to the circulation of the magazine. He's really excited.
I think he contacted the reporter as well.
Oh, are we being broadcasted?
Just get to work.
Let's go.
Are you alright?
Hello. Did you get the pass to get out?
Please be careful.
Staff Only
Myeongsung College Hospital Records
Search
Delete patient records.
No records for this patient.
Cheong. Cheong.
Let's go home.
- Go home ?  - Yeah.
Hey, Second Floor Room.
- What is it?  - Well, as I see it, if Mom moves in,
I think she needs to use this room. Then I don't have a room. Even though I'm the home owner.
So, you and I should stay together in one room.
But, when I thought about it,
I wondered if there was a need to wait until Mom moved here.
Right? Should I go up?
No.
So that's it. I'll go up.
How long ago was it when you barged down here and stayed with me when I told you not to come?
She's changed.
♬  Although I can't tell you everything ♬
♬  about your loneliness
♬ Without saying anything just bear it. ♬♬
♬  If I could give you a hug
♬ Without any reason ♬
Ah, Unni. What am I going to do because of my sadness?
I'll see you often. It's not that far away either.
This is your son's place? Your son lives in a nice home.
Thanks for dropping me off here. Be careful on your way back.
She doesn't even invite me in, when that's the reason I came here.
You're home? Aren't these Ahjumeoni's shoes?
Take these and give it to her later.
What are you saying?
Ah, this is why I can't leave business to you.
Let's go. To the heir's house. (reference to Lee Min Ho's drama, Heirs)
Unni! You left this at our place. These are shoes that you cherish.
Oh my, this is what I was going to throw away.
But, I really need to use the bathroom.
My throat is a bit dry.
Oh, yes. Please come in.
Oh, this place is so nice!
Wow, it looks amazing.
But, is your son home?
Yes. He went up to his closet for a little bit.
Oh, is that so? Then that's good. We're already here,
so let's leave after we greet them.
Last time, I was going to say hello to your son at the funeral service.
I lost track of things and didn't even say hello.
Then, will you do so? Stay and have a cup of tea.
Oh, Unni. Why are you being like this? I'll do it.
Ah, the guest shouldn't do this. Sit.
I asked you to fix it last time!
- You're the one who didn't fix it for me!  - So I'm telling you to fix it yourself!
Goo Baek's Dad!
J Team?
Can I speak to you two?
Why?
I have something to say to you two.
What do we do? I was uneasy.
I didn't know they would follow us to our home. But why did Cheong take those people into that room?
It will be fine.
Did the guests go somewhere?
Momentarily...
Oh my. They are coming out of the room?
No, we were just looking at the room. This place is so nice.
Oh my, is this your son?
Yes, my son Heo Joon Jae is here.
This man is his friend.
And have you been introduced to Ms. Cheong?
Yes, we have. This young lady is so kind.
Your son is so handsome.
And,
But... I...
feel like I've seen you before.
Your faces feel very familiar.
We met before, right? Dubai?
We've never been to Dubai.
Oh my! Right!
But why did the three lettered (in hangul) word Dubai appear in my head?
I wonder why.
I'm sorry, that was quite out of the blue.
Anyway, it's so nice to meet you,
and let's meet each other often now.
Think carefully.
Cheong isn't made for mermaid shows! She erased her memory!
You erased my memories last time too! And that was why Joon Jae was acting like that after returning from Spain.
Just try saying this out loud somewhere.
Cheong, let's work together. If you can use this memory erasing skill well,
we're just applying Bill Gates. We just become worldwide millionaires.
It's fine. I won't do those things that make you uselessly busy.
If I'm busy, I won't have time to see Heo Joon Jae.
That's right.
Cheong, I'm saying this sincerely. If you break up with Joon Jae, you have to come to me.
I pulled number 2, okay?
What is this rascal saying?
Ah, really. Cheong. I really, really like you. Why do you have so many things?
Hey!
Hey, don't do that.
- Just one time.- Don't do it.
- Just one hug. - Why are you hugging her?
Cheong. Wait.
Hey, what are you doing?
This guy...
He must be insane.
What's the matter? Why? Cheong?
What's wrong? Are you hurting somewhere?
Hey, maybe you got discharged from the hospital too soon.
Does your heart hurt?
♬ The door to a new world is open. ♬
♬ It is within you. ♬
♬ When I enter my eyes are dazzled ♬
♬ A wide world ♬
♬ welcomes me. ♬
♬ I approach you. ♬
♬ I want to be embraced. ♬
♬ I want to stay in that world which is you ♬
Where did everyone go?
I sent them away.
Why?
Because I wanted to eat with you alone.
♬ I need you I love you ♬
♬ Eternally in your arms ♬
Since your condition isn't well, don't go anywhere. Let's have a party here by ourselves.
Go and change your clothes.
♬ Will you come to me and take my hand ♬
♬ I will love you ♬
♬ even if the world changes. ♬
♬ I owe you I miss you ♬♬ I need you I love you ♬
♬ Eternally in your arms ♬
Shall we have a drink?
No.
If I drink, I think I'll ask you to stay.
If there's another way, tell me.
Please. Tell me there is one.
After your surgery, you barely eat.
You can't sleep and you hold in your pain.
What am I supposed to do? Do I have to...
just watch you... die?
If you return to the sea, will you be okay?
Will you be healthy?
Promise me one thing.
That as you are leaving, you won't erase my memories.
Why?
You were like that too.
You said you would rather love and be in pain than not remember and not be able to love.
Because there are memories to be cherished, I can send you away.
Then you become to pitiable. I could forever not come return.
Then you won't even know if I'm alive or dead,
you can only wait.
If you cannot come back forever, I'll be born again.
You do so as well.
I told you. My love,
is longer than my time.
I wish you would become comfortable.
If we remember each other, we won't forget which road to return to.
So, we will meet again.
Fine.
Then you choose. If you're going to erase, or leave.
I said you can choose.
I made my choice.
♬ Did I wake up from a long dream?♬♬ As soon as I recognized you♬
♬ My nameless love♬
♬ may have started♬
♬ Before I knew you was the sky♬
♬ always as brilliant?♬
♬ If out of ten thousand chances our love came to be♬
♬ If out of ten thousand chances you and I could begin♬
♬ I will use the feeling and♬
♬ the love which may not end ♬
♬ for you ♬
♬ All of my moments are for you♬
Subtitles brought to you by The Blue Sea @ Viki
♬ With you I see and hear more, breathing with you will be everything ♬