Episode 3
Subtitles brought to you by The Blue Sea @ Viki
What is your name?
My name is Sae Wa.
I had a sister who passed away when I was young,
and that child's name was Sae Wa. It means-
It means
a "bright, shining child."
There was someone who gave me that name.
Shall I tell you that story?
Wow!
Summer, 20 years ago.
There was a child who came from Hanyang to visit his mother's family's house to play at the beach.
Can you swim all the way there?
Of course I can.
Liar.
Go then.
Okay.
My name is Dam Ryeong.
What's your name?
If you don't have a name, I'll make one for you.
Let's make your name Sae Wa. It means "bright, shining child."
After that summer,
the child returned to his home in Hanyang.
But whenever he had the chance, he tried his best to return to the beach.
Father, let me go! Please...
So after coming back from your grandparent's house in Heupgok, will you work hard in your studies?
Yes. I will do my best in studying.
That child allowed the mermaid to eat food she had never tasted before from the land
and allowed her to see beautiful things for the first time.
♬  Yesterday, and today  ♬
Those two children spent time together like that and grew up together.
♬ Without any sound ♬
In half a month, a future bridal letter (in which the four pillars of the bride & groom-to-be are written) will come to my house.
I'm going to get married.
What's getting married?
I have to live with another girl.
I can only protect and like her.
Then, you can't come to the beach anymore?
♬ The story of star lights ♬
I don't know.
You can't live on land?
It becomes possible when I turn into an adult.
I heard that if mermaids go onto land, they produce legs.
But not now.
I don't want to leave you. I don't want to protect and like another girl.
I don't want to live with her forever, if she's not you.
But what can we do? I can't go onto land,
and you can't live in water.
♬ Your breath that's going further away ♬
♬ Even that became faded as if it's stained ♬
♬ Hidden in the ocean
A sad story ♬
On the first night of their marriage,
the child left his newly-wed room.
He rode for several days, heading for the ocean.
Sae Wa!
The child knew.
That the mermaid would definitely appear to save him, who can't swim, from drowning.
But he didn't know an important detail.
Mermaids have a special ability.
It is..
That by kissing a human, they can erase memories of themselves from the person.
Just like that,
the mermaid disappeared like sea foam from the child's memories.
Why am I here?
My wife
died from a lung disease after marriage.
Right up to her death,
she resented me for running away on our first night.
I just couldn't remember, no matter what,
why I ran away that night.
Am I
that boy?
♬ Always in the same dream ♬
♬ An unfamiliar face and ♬
Legend of the Blue Sea
♬ You and I met by chance ♬
♬ I guess I was a little scared ♬
♬ I was afraid it would be a dream forever ♬
♬ Now, even when I open my eyes, ♬
♬ It's you. ♬
♬ This is love story  ♬
♬ I cannot hide ♬
♬ My two eyes which only see you ♬
♬ I cannot close them ♬
♬ This is amazing ♬
♬ Even if everything in the world ♬
♬ Were given to me ♬
♬ I cannot exchange it with you, my love. ♬
♬ Someday just once ♬
♬ Will come to me ♬
♬ That person, that love ♬
♬ I will find for sure ♬
Hey, ding-dong! I told you to follow me. Where did you run off to?
♬ Even if I ask myself again ♬
♬ This is really love, you know ♬
♬ This is love story  ♬
♬ This must be happiness ♬
♬ I'm afraid it might be a dream ♬
♬ I can't open my eyes ♬
♬ This is my love story  ♬
♬ I love you, only you ♬
I love you.
Ah, why did I jump off from there? Ugh! I must be crazy! Really!
Ah, headache..
What's this..
Would you like to have some wine?
Breaking news. An imprisoned murder suspect in Seoul detention center
is on loose who has been under the medical care for seizure.
The official released a picture of the murder suspect, Ma Dae Young, who is in his 40s.
Whoa...
Valet parking
- How long will you be away?
- About a week or so.
Have a great trip.
Taxi!
You're here! Alive!
Come here.
Get here!
Hey! Hey! I knew you'll be back safely!
That's why I didn't answer your phone.
Hey! You don't even know how I think of you. You fool...
Sure! Is that why you're entering this house as if yours?
If I couldn't return forever, weren't you going to use it as yours?
My neck, neck, neck!
Ah... that person can't be trusted!
Tae Ho!
Leave your bags there! Be comfortable!
I'm comfortable! Why? Because it's my house!
Hey! Did you crack my house passcode?
Hey, isn't there any house in Korea that Tae Ho can't open up?
- Did you have something to eat?
- Is that right? Good for you!
Got it now. Then, get out right away!
Oh, no! What does he mean by getting out? Where shall we go?
His and my houses are all broken into!
This is the only house not yet known because you've moved and quickly cleared the address.
Hey, that Madame Jang Jin Ok of Myeong Dong Capital is really
someone who firmly believes in "I can do it!" She can do everything!
Hey, Joon Jae. Between us, isn't there something important... hmm?
that we should talk about?
- What?
- Come here.
- Why?
- Come, come!
- Ah, what?!
Just for moment!
What's going on?
- Come over here.
- What's wrong, Hyung?
Let me see the object.
- What? - Don't you pretend... in front of me.
In fact, I was anxious that you might not come back because of that. I was really worried.
That... What?
What you mean what? Your and my 6 billion won! (6M USD)
- What is he talking about? I'm tired.
- Hey, the bracelet!
Jadite bracelet, the one with the texture, hardness, transparency, and color that all seemed so real.
How...did you know that, Hyung?
- How do you think I know? It's probably because you said so.
- I did?
- Yeah, you.
- You said you swindled it off of some girl that you met in Spain.
A girl? What girl?
Yeah, right. Others would believe you. They would all probably get deceived. But am I one to be hoodwinked?
Let's not be like this, Joon Jae.
What are you talking about? What girl did I meet in Spain?
You said you met some dumb, and not too bright, and weird girl!
Take a look! The text you sent me! Picture of the bracelet! You sent them to me!
Ah, I'm going crazy!
Ah! Hey, I'm going even crazier!
Hey, did you come back from Hollywood, instead of Spain? Your acting skill advanced so quickly!
- No, that's really not it.
- What is not it?
I've never sent such texts. And I've never even met weird girl.
So, you don't have a bracelet, either?
I do! I have that.
See?! You do have the bracelet!
Hey, it's not like you couldn't recognize that it's an extraordinary object!
Where did you get it? You can't remember it, either?
Ah! I don't know.
Hey, Joon Jae. I am like this.
I not only know what you are talking about, but I don't even want to know.
Let's just see the object first. We need to get it appraised anyway.
- We'll see.
- See? See what? Why do you want to see?
The situation doesn't really line up. I just feel uneasy the way it is. Let me look into it first.
Okay, okay! I will gladly take that uneasiness from you.
You just hand over that bracelet to me, and you take that burden off of you! Huh?! Joon Jae!
Will you be going to Seoul soon?
Right. That's my home.
You should go, too.
It's not like I'm seducing you to go to Seoul.
So don't misunderstand me and listen.
In Seoul, there are so many things that you'd like. For example, really yummy specialty restaurants.
You love eating so much! You are hungry at random times.
Also, there is a place called Han River. In the fall, they have fireworks there.
I watch it from a good spot in Building 63.
Wow, that's incredibly beautiful.
I'll let you watch it with me.
Together?
Yes, together with me.
You promised! A promise is meant to be kept.
Is there there a promise?
It's there to be kept.
That's right.
I love you.
Who was that?
What is this?
I'm going crazy.
3 months later
The concept of a real estate developer
is something that's novel in Korea. Could you please give us a brief explanation?
Simply put a real estate developer
uses imagination to
create something from nothing.
Typically a surveyor would look at apartment complexes or...
- Ah, you worked hard.
- You worked hard.
I think the weather was on my side today.
Next time when it's better I'll...
I'm sorry, I was looking from over there.
You look like a magazine spread, don't you agree?
What are you talking about?
They talk about being daughter crazy these days.
Maybe I'm more traditional, but I feel more secure with a son.
Daughters are lovely, but a son is like a replica.
He resembles me the more he grows.
Genes are such an amazing thing!
I received a call from mother-in-law earlier, and I think it's important.
She said it was very urgent
- I'm sorry. I'll excuse myself for a moment.
- Yes.
Excuse me.
Why?
-Watch what you say, please!
There are rumors that say that the son CEO Huh is taking care of is not his.
Really?
-That lady over there, Kang Seo Hee is his second wife.
She kicked his first wife out and brought a son with her and refused to leave.
CEO Huh's first son ran away from home a while ago, and they have no news of him.
- You didn't know at all?
- Not at all.
I told you to stop reading newspapers and read some magazines!
Things like that are a must in this field!
You don't think I messed up, do you?
I sucked up to him so much earlier; did you see how I lost to him?
I saw, of course I saw.
Let's see the big picture. Big picture, okay?
What's wrong with his biological son?
The scale of his rebellion is too big.
He's crazy!
Aish! Who drank all my beer?
There's no more?
What about my ice cream?
Are you guys not going to leave my house? It's been 3 months already!
Hey, how can we leave?
Those from Myeongdong Capital are lit trying to look for us.
They think you're dead, so they're not following you around!
They're going to follow up to the end of the world.
So what? Huh? You're going to live here? Live here?
Let's finish up a bit. We need to break ground on new work soon.
I'm uncomfortable too.
I'm not someone to sleep and eat with men in one house!
Please, collaborate.
Cheers.
Aigoo, you scared me! W-Who are you?!
- How do I get to Seoul?
- What?
Where is Seoul?
Is Seoul just straight then left turn there?
No, you need to go straight along the west coast... then right.
Really?
Thank you.
-Are you going to swim there?
But this is Jeju Island. Would you like to get in for now?
It's okay.
Wait!
What the heck?
Is she saying she's going to swim to Seoul right now?!
- Is she a haenyeo? (Korean traditional female divers in Jeju)
- No! She's a water monster!
- Hey! Should...shouldn't we file a report!
- Look, look look here!
Everyone from Marine Girls! We need to slowly wrap up!
Soon we will have our own edition of the miracle of Moses (
splitting of the Reed Sea)
start!
Miracle of Moses! Miracle of Moses!
What is that?
Oh my, what is that?
Isn't it a person?
Self-implode you land-grubber!
Look some girl with crazy hair
(she thinks she's insane)
How is she from coming there? Unless she appeared out of the water.
She's probably coming from that island.
That's an inhabited island over there! Then she was in the uninhabited island all night and then came from there?!
Is this Seoul?
No, it isn't.
I have to go farther?
This is exhausting! I swam so much I feel like vomitting!
Miss, are you going to Seoul? We're going to Seoul as well.
Welcome to Seoul
There are more people than anchovies.
How do I find Heo Joon Jae?
Today Madam Jang Jin Ok will
have a golf practice at 1 o' clock and at 3:30 she will get a massage at a spa in Gangnam. At Gangnam Empire.
Once we arrive, you go to the rooftop and immediately start working on the elevator.
Hyung keep checking to make sure her plans haven't changed.
Okay.
As expected, you have to take a break from work sometime.
I excited now that we're back at it!
Excited, my butt.
Just think about packing up your bags and leaving after this!
By any chance, do you know Heo Joon Jae?
Excuse me, do you know Heo Joon Jae? Heo Joon Jae?
The person we scammed,
who knew we would run into them at the golf course?
But I learned for the first time...that I'm faster than Usain Bolt!
You think Seoul is big, right? It's the size of your palm.
As you live, you're meant to run into them at least once.
We just don't know that.
- Aish.
- What the heck?
Excuse me!
A bottle of soju for $1
Please come by.
-That car didn't come yet?
-Nope.
Not until 3.
What would you like?
That'll be 1,000 won.
Why are you giving me this? You have to give me money. Money!
If you don't have money, go away. Quickly go away!
Smile, smile. Look ahead. You have to look ahead and walk across.
We have to look close. Okay?
I need to buy a reference book, but I don't have enough money.
-Academy fee for me.
-Quickly.
Thanks.
Thanks. See ya.
It's okay, it's okay. Smile, smile.
Look ahead. Walk while looking ahead.
Unni, why are you doing this?
Do you have money? I'm really hungry.
You don't have money?
Even so, you mug a little kid's money?
What's mugging?
This is mugging.
I'll treat you using mom's credit card, since you said you were hungry, unnie.
(kiddo used an abbreviation for mom's credit card)
What's a "mom-ca"?
Unnie, how come you don't know anything?
Mom's credit card. Mom-ca.
Is "mom's credit card" better than money?
It's a similar concept. Anyway, don't do that again.
Ok. I won't.
Money is something that's earned with great difficulty. My mom has such a hard time earning money.
Without even having time to see me,
from morning to dusk she only earns money.
But why does your mom work so hard to earn money?
Unni seriously you're helpless. Why do you think we earn money.
She earns money so that mom and I can be happy.
But if all you do is earn money from morning to dusk, then when do we live happily?
Later. Later, please.
Oh I need to go to math academy now.
Be sure to find that person, Heo Joon Jae, that you're looking for, Unnie.
Keep this well, don't give it to others, and use it well.
From now on, at least work a part-time job to earn money.
Since living for awhile, I came to know that living without money
isn't a big deal at all.
I understand.
Then I'll be going. Goodbye.
Aigoo.
Ajusshi watch yourself.
Hey kiddo. It's you who needs to be careful.
Hey, such a little thing. Hey! How can I be an ajusshi?
. You! You! come over here!
- Hey, hey, hey you're an ajusshi to her. How could you be an oppa. Let's go. It's almost time.
Come here, Tae Oh. Hurry on over Tae Oh.
Look friend, do you have money?
Your unnie here, needs to buy a supplementary textbook, but I don't have enough money.
Look here. Don't mug her. It's a bad thing.
What's up with her?
You guys don't have a 'mom's credit card'? It's similar to money.
You punk!
How dare you, with clothes that look like a beggar!
Promise me. That you won't mug others.
I didn't...I didn't mug her. I...I...I'm friends with her (to be friends sounds like eat)
Your friends...?
You eat them?
Guys! You shouldn't eat your friends like that!
You shouldn't do that!
Do you also eat your friends?
Don't eat it really. Eat something else!
- Are you ok? You got hurt. Isn't she totally psycho!
- Please. Don't.
Yeah, mom. I'm at the cram school.
You're at the cram school right? I'm going to call and check later.
Don't hang around bad kids needlessly. Look at your brother.
That good-hearted kid being framed, he must be suffering so much.
What's the big deal about a crazy kid committing suicide. Hang up.
The Best Deal of Ever!
What the..
So useless.
It's stopping.
Geez. What's going on.
What the heck. Who are you! You're definitely that jerk that conned me!
I definitely heard you were dead.
Sorry. Looks like I'm quite invincible.
How dare you come here on your own-- Omo.
What's wrong with this?
It's so dark. Shall I give you some light?
The elevator doors opened. you know. Behind you.
But outside's a bottomless ledge.
No, what's going on?
Oh, be careful with where you step. You might step on it. There's someone's hand there.
Isn't that your son?
Mom! Mom! Help me!
- Min Jae,
- Mom!
Min Jae. Hold my hand.
- Help me mom.
- Min Jae! Min Jae!
No, you can't. You have to hold my hand and come up again.
- No, no. Min Jae no!
- Mom!!!!!!!
Remember your pain now.
The child that your son made die.
The child who fell to his death on the top floor, the 17th floor.
That child's mother
was as miserable as you are now, and
forever they will be in agony.
Now, from now on those who have wronged you,
you will forget them all.
To those who are suffering because of you,
only remember your sorry heart.
Madam are you ok? The elevator broke all of a sudden.
Contact Attorney Seo, and ask him to cancel the lawsuit.
pardon?
Also, you know the contact information of the mom whose kid died right?
Let me meet her.
What are you going to do when you meet him.
I'm going to apologize.
Madam, are you feeling unwell?
Is he crazy? He's absolutely psychotic.
Hey look here, the heresy of neuroscience.
DIY-ace hypnotist of the medical field. Heo Joon Jae's talent hasn't rusted even a little bit.
This is really something, right?
Since we're in an occupation that we can't exactly be proud of,
I'm so regretful that I can't let this talent of yours be known to the world. Really.
- That's right.
- Wait.
How can you do it? Hypnosis?
Hey! Pray tell. He must be so curious that he opened that iron-clad lips of his.
Are you curious?
This is how you begin. With the sense of sight.
The grain and eyes are connected.
The moment the number 17 on the implicitly ladden spam text is seen
Thus a condition is presented where hypnosis can take place.
Next, the a pattern interrupt.
(Creating a situation that's hard to anticipate, and hypnotizing a person using the lapse in conscious.)
Shall I turn on the light?
That person now enters the fantasy world that I made.
But externally, it's like a bottomless pit.
mom!
Everything starts with the eyes.
Looking, starts the seduction.
Such a coward. Not everyone falls for that.
What a fashion interrupt?
Can I really get this?
You usually can't, but I'll keep an eye out, so hurry up and pick something.
This neighborhood is a rich one, so they'll throw away new things.
Others are at the Seoul Station after hearing that free lunches were being given out there,
but I can't leave Gangnam. If you starve, you're starved,
but I can't give up on fashion.
But seeing you all dressed up like that, it's a bit more bearable now.
Well for us tall girls, we look good in things we wear.
Where did you come from?
Across the pond.
(She used the word water but the homeless person understands it to be "overseas")
Oh! overseas! I know that place very well!
In my youth, there weren't places like Milan and Paris that I didn't go to to buy luxury goods.
Then I got bankrupt and even though I'm ruining myself
and living the street life right now,
I don't have any regrets.
But why did you come to Seoul?
I'm searching for Heo Joon Jae.
Boyfriend? Where does he live in Seoul? Daechi-dong? Cheogdam(-dong)?
He just said he lives in Seoul.
What about is phone number?
Phone number?
Aigoo, he didn't give you a contact number and ran off.
But you didn't realize that and came all the way here?
Aigoo. That's when you need to go do undercover investigation.
What is that?
He never talked about a specific place with you before?
Unconsciously, he's bound to drop hints all over places he frequents.
You should go to places like that and camp there.
63 Building?
63 Building
4319 from Isu Station to Yangjae
Dogok Station to Samsung Station
63 Building
-Welcome.
-Thank you.
Welcome.
You don't have a bus card?
What about money?
I do.
That's not enough.
Just put in that amount and get on.
Thank you.
Your eyes, more than any other words
are sparkling.
I feel that.
In my dream last night
smiling wide, like the wind
you did. The path you walked alone
The dream I chased alone.
Now, beside me
you're here.
For a long long time, will you be remembered
maybe.
Come a bit closer to me
so that I can feel you better.
My heart leans closer to you.
bit, by bit. Bit by bit.
Bit by bit.
A night alone.
If I go all the way up, will I see Heo Joon Jae?
Be prepared tomorrow.
A restructuring is a restructuring. Also the fireworks! The people'll come in droves!
-You need to thoroughly be prepared.
-Okay.
If you guys are late again even though I said this to you, then didori-didori.
Ah, I'm relieved.
I thought I was going to die from hunger.
Are you done?
Is it someone's birthday?
There is.
-Today is my son's birthday too.
-Yeah.
Oh, what did you put in the seaweed soup?
Sea urchin. My son too liked sea urchin seaweed soup.
Who are you giving it to?
Ah...
That chic guy that won't fall for you?
Please put the soup into a thermos, and as for the rest of the side dishes, put them into a bento box prettily.
Okay.
Miss.
You don't seduce men like that.
In the time that you bring the side dishes to him, it's better to get one more shot of botox.
I'm saying that you need to love yourself more.
At a study group that I volunteer teach, there's a kid who had a birthday. So I'm trying to give it to him/her.
Who would seduce a man with something to eat? How childish.
I cooked it with sea urchins. I'm not sure if it'll fit with your taste preference.
How did you know about this place? It hasn't been long since I moved here.
It suddenly came up as I was talking with Oppa Nam Doo.
Ah, really, Jo Nam Doo. That untrustworthy human being.
Happy birthday, son.
Okay.
Mom, we're going there today, right?
Of course.
Your Dad is busy again today, so we're just gonna go together, okay?
-Where are you going?
-It's a secret.
Wow! Why the seaweed soup?
Hey, Cha Si Ah, you did this?
It's Joon Jae's birthday.
My goodness, look at her. She doesn't look like it at first glance,
but she's excellent good-wife-material, right?
You made it so pretty, for real.
Hey, it's your birthday today, so you need to do a party, a birthday party.
There's a good wine bar that I know of in Gyeongridan-gil.
Oh, Gyeongridan-gil is good! The water (pretty girls) is good! Reserve it, reserve it.
I have an appointment.
-What appointment?
-Ah, what is it?
You always do this on your birthday. Being sentimental by yourself.
-Where are you going? Who are you meeting with? He/she can just sit with us!
-Hyung.
-Yeah?
-Are you bored?
-Yeah.
-Very much so.
-Then go to the wine bar with Si Ah.
Go there and party. Or go with Tae Oh.
I ate well. Thanks.
Happy birthday! Spend it well!
Oh, he won't fall for it. Such a steel-headed guy.
Joon Jae isn't going to meet up with a girl, right?
-Did he get one (a girlfriend)?
-No.
It's hard for him to have a girl, based on his brain-structure.
He can't decide nor stay focused.
He'll let any woman cross that line,
but no woman will ever cross that line.
But did you really make this?
You think I would? The maid lady did it.
Joon Jae, we should go together.
Mom, I'm going to play around until the door closes.
Be careful. I'll go with you. Joon Jae!
- It's a mermaid!
- Oh look
That's right!
There's still 30 minutes left until the mermaid show. Did they start already?
- Mom.
- Yes?
The mermaid... slurped the fish up.
Gee. There's no way. The Mermaid Princess is friends with the fish.
She never eats them.
Mermaid Princess! So pretty!
The show didn't start yet. Did the diver go under already?
Yes, it seems so.
Look!
Who was it? Who went inside?
♬ The door to a new world is open. ♬
♬ It is within you. ♬
♬  When I enter my eyes are dazzled ♬
♬ A wide world welcomes me. ♬
♬ I approach you.  ♬
♬  I want to be embraced. ♬
♬ I want to stay in that world which is you ♬
♬ I owe you I miss you  ♬
♬ I need you I love you  ♬
♬ Eternally in your arms ♬
♬ There will be much that I don't know ♬
♬ Please show me your world and your heart ♬
♬ Will you come to me ♬
♬  and take my hand ♬
I will love you.
Even if this world changes
♬ I owe you I
Someone went inside the water?!
♬ I miss you ♬
Exactly. How could such a thing happen?
On an important day that we're doing a reconversion. Wasn't there a huge security breach?
Isn't it that girl?
Are you the one who got inside and did a mermaid show?
How did you get inside?
Excuse me, you need to come speak with us.
Guess who I met in Itaewon.
I met Tomás. He said he'd kill you next time he sees you.
I also secured a conclusive photo that you met a girl in Spain.
Are you planning on still denying it?
Catch that woman! Isn't she some corporate spy!
Oh, I'm so sorry.
- You have to catch her!
- What are you doing! Hurry!
♬ Always in the same dream ♬
♬ An unfamiliar face and ♬
♬ In a time which is suspended ♬
♬ You and I met by chance ♬
♬ I guess I was a little scared ♬
♬ I was afraid it would be a dream forever ♬
♬ Now, even when I open my eyes, it's you. ♬
♬ This is love story  ♬
♬ I cannot hide ♬
♬ My two eyes which only see you ♬
♬ I cannot close them ♬
This is amazing!
♬ Even if everything in the world ♬
♬ Were given to me ♬
♬ I cannot exchange it with you, my love. ♬
I'm sorry Heo Joon Jae.
You put this on.
I know you liked this.
You probably won't remember me. Still,
I will keep my promise. I'll go to you.
Even through the windy rainstorm, though the sun may be burning down on me,
Though I'm lonely and without anyone by my side, and even if it's somewhere I've never been before,
I will endure it all
and be sure to go to you.
I love you.
♬ This is love story  ♬
♬ That I can’t hide away ♬
♬ In your embrace ♬
♬ I want to sleep deeply ♬
♬ This must be love ♬
♬ This must be happiness ♬
♬ I'm afraid it might be a dream ♬
♬ I can't open my eyes. This is my love story  ♬
♬ I love you, only you ♬
Subtitles brought to you by The Blue Sea @ Viki
Approach me a bit closer.
Who are you? Do you know me?
You know me. You even know my name.
Who're you with?
A girl.
- You met that girl again here, the one you met in Spain?
Since the time that she's come into my arms.
What are you doing? Why are you doing this to me?
How can you bring that girl home!
She's stupidly fooled. You're the perfect Shim Cheong
(reference to fairytale where the filial daughter sells herself to save her father
That's great.