Dramalove.TV
Please come out, quickly! Quick!
How dare...
Sure, I will show you.
What happens when a bitch gets working hard...
You did not get hurt anywhere?
Please stay here for a moment.
By the way, do you know who I am?
No way, you followed me without knowing who I am... How could you trust so simply..
I am a friend of Dam Young.
A friend... what does that mean?
A friend... is
a person who ends up believing whatever nonsense were told.
If he has a lover, the friend will save her together as well.
Is that way you've saved me?
Don't go out because it's dangerous, so stay here, please.
I will quickly go bring Dam Young here.
Certainly infatuating, certainly!
What am I going through because of Dam Young...
Get him!
Yes sir!
Sea Hwa!
- Where the sunset seeps through  -
- At the seaside  -
- Stroking her golden hair  -
- A girl sits.  -
- She throws her crying heart  -
- Into the water.  -
- She misses that person.  -
- They say that while waiting for him  -
- She became a mermaid  -
Legend of the Blue Sea  - Because her dreams have changed  -
- She became a mermaid.  -
- A sad story  -
Episode 6
Any contacts made?
Unable to identify her since there is neither an ID nor a cell phone with her at this moment.
Let's register her as a "Jane Doe" and inquire the police for her background check.
It'll be a headache if she continues to be unconscious... Please let me know.
Yes.
Don't just click whenever, but click when you change your mind and ready to tell me everything.
Click only that time!
unfamiliar person
Sim Chung
Silly, what happened to her!
Yes, it appears to me that there was an incident near the Namsan Tower. I am wondering which hospital the patient might be gone to?
Because it snowed there were many incidents and it will take sometime for more information.
Presumably transferred to the clinics near ..
I see.
Stay firm, Jun Jae! I will save you!
What happened here?
Hurt?
Jun Jae Huh! I make money here.
I will make lots of money and give all to you!
Let's meet next time when the first snow comes.
There! Meet right there!
By any chance, is there an emergent female patient around early 30s?
Name?
Is it Sae Lip Hospital? I'm wondering if there is any car accident patients,
No, not a 50 something but a young early 30s?
Long hair, fair skin and
Ah, and very beautiful!
Don't have one? I understand.
Madame, the CEO has to pay his condolences to the family in mourning and in needs of a black tie.
Did you get his message?
Yes, I just now. We planned to have dinner together but had to cancel.
So, I decided to be out as well.
Uh, yes. I told her to have dinner at home but I forgot to call her.
You've mentioned to my wife that I will be visiting a house of mourning?
Yes. I did.
Then, let's go.
Yes.
Is it here?
Here! Here! HERE!
Are you a guardian of her?
This woman, have you checked her temperature?
The basic exam was done a while ago, and she is in waiting for an exam of fractures. Please wait.
Examined all?
The child is cold like an ice! You sure done exam?
How come?
Doctor! Doctor?
What?
This patient, can't check the vital and her temperature is 29!
What a nonsense you're talking, what 29 degree!
CPR. Please prepare the
Yes, Doctor.
Patient! Patient! Can you hear me?
- Charge to 200 joules. - Charged to 200 joules!
Step back! (clear) Shoot! (Charge)
Heo Joon Jae.
Are you...
alright?
I had a dream.
You held my hand.
You saved me.
Prepare the chest x-ray...
Hey quickly quickly! As quick as possible!
Hey, where do you think Joon Jae go earlier? I think he went to a club.
After having kicked that seriously vapid Cheong out, he's gone out to play.
As the saying Cheong-Chul-Uh-Ram (Blue comes from Indigo), Joon Jae who learned bad things from me became worse than I am.
Why [are you calling] you nastier jerk?
Hey, he's asking for a fake ID with an insurance coverage.
He says he doesn't want to.
Hey, it's not like you're making him donate his talent, don't make him do something so trivial.
It's not like you're going to pay him by the hour. What?
Cheong is in the ER?
Wh... wh... why? A traffic accident?
Ah, right. Since she's undocumented.
Of course she needs an ID. An ID!
Are you, really okay?
Heo Joon Jae, did you worry about me?
Yes.
- Really? - I said yes.
Why?
That's because...
if something bad were to happen to you, being that you're an unknown person without a home and a family,
it'll become really plagued.
Heo Joon Jae DID worry about me.
Did it never occur to you to avoid an on-coming car?
You held my hand earlier because you were worried about me, right?
Don't you see that I'm scolding you right now?
When you cross the street, please look both ways.
What did you do so well that you'd scold her?
This is all because you kicked Cheong out of the house!
Why do you look at a person in that manner, huh?
Ah, move over. Are you okay, Cheong? How did you get hurt, Cheong?
We worried a lot about on our way over here.
Ah, enough of that. Did you make the thing I asked for?
Of course we made it, we did. But how come...
Ah, stop making her talk. The doctor said it's not good for her to talk a lot.
You said she hurt her legs, but she shouldn't speak?
[The doctor] said no.
- Does that sound right? - They said it's possible.
So just go and take the appropriate procedure [to be discharged].
Rest up, Cheong.
Just go on.
I'm here to take care of the ER patient Sim Cheong's discharge procedure.
Here's her ID and her insurance card.
Hey, that female patient on traffic accident whose body temperature was 29 celsius, is it true that she was resuscitated after one shock?
Don't even mention it, Man. I thought she expired (died).
- I nearly pronounced a perfectly fine person dead. - I bet you were scared sh!tless.
By the way, even the name of that patient is unique. What was she called again? Choon Hyang?
No, Sim Cheong.
As the test came back negative to alcohol or drug, and because you reported it immediately the first aid to the injured was carried out speedily,
you won't face any major issues, should you settle the matter with the other party well.
I am sorry.  Where is the injured party?
Ah, there...
Was that you who hit her with a car?
You?
Heo, Jun Jae! I'm your older brother!
An older brother, what a joke!
Let's not pretend to be this non-existent family, and answer my question.
Did you hit her with a car?
That lady jumped into road. It was a chance accident.
- It was a chance accident.
- A chance?
You're saying it was a chance accident?
It was just that, I came to borrow your MP3, without not knowing this was on your desk
and hit it with my elbow by accident. I'm really sorry.
Father, I'm sorry.
It can happen to anyone.
You, didn't I tell you to throw that away, a long time ago!
The broken pieces would be its surroundings if it were a mistake.
Not all over the fragments be and even the holder got broken..
This meant you dropped with your intention to break.
Ah! No! Truly, trust me.
Enough! Stop!
Did you know how much I felt sorry for your mother cleaning this picture frame without telling you to get rid of it?
Well done. You clean them!
Hey, you punks!
Why you rotten... Hey Chi Hyeon!
Let me see. Are you hurt a lot?
God, look at this.
You rotten punk.
Let's go to the hospital.
There is no such thing as a coincidence to you.
That I know for certain.
Don't be irrational. Then are you supposing that I hit her on purpose?
You don't usually drive yourself as a norm.
The fact that you were driving yourself says that you were headed for some place private unmentionable to others.
Writing a fiction?
Say it! Have you track me down?
Then, hit her?
Huh, what a nonsense...
While ago, you are the one who hired a person to track me down?
If not, your mother?
Don't...
just say anything! Why my mother would hired a person to follow you?
You not that interested!
Me?
I'm my father's real son!
Go on and do your filial duty. We both know that's your true work.
Go and pretend playing at being a real son to the fake father.
Stop appearing in my presence.
Yes, Father.
Yes, the investigation just ended.
Ah, don't worry too much.
I told you I'm not hurt anywhere.
Ah, let's go then.
- Is it this way? - Yes.
Now, Sim Cheong, let's get off.
They say there were a lot of car accidents because of the snow.
So they said they don't have any single rooms available so let's just stay here for now.
Then am I going to live here?
Not living per se, just staying for a while.
With all the people here?
Right.
What's marriage?
Marriage, is a man and woman who live together under one roof because they love each other.
Loving each other and taking care of each other.
Then am I married to these people?
- Huh? - They say a man and woman living under one roof
loving each other and taking care of each other, that's marriage, isn't it?
It's different from freeloading!
I know what there's to know too.
Let's sleep, alright-
No! Wait!
Are we all married now?
I'm so happy. Today, I'll be married here.
And next time, I'll marry Heo Joon Jae.
Let's proceed with an MRI scan on the brain for that patient.
Yes sir.
She's cute.
- Mr. Lee Da Bong! - Here.
Because of your diabetes, you have a restriction of 1700 calories.
Oh, that's a calorie controlled meal? Looks good
It smells nice, it'll probably taste very savory
don't you think?
Before the special gets cold.
This is spicy mussel stew with noodles.
That's the special?
Oh my, the mussels...They don't usually open their mouths like that but I see today they all have their mouths open.
You were right to order the special, it looks good.
Excuse me!
I'm here.
Ms. Sim Cheong, you've been ordered a fasting.
Oh, I'm fasting? Please give me the fasting.
I think it'll be delicious. Thank you, I'll eat well.
It's fasting. You get no food.
I get...no food?
There's a chance you might have to go into surgery, so I've been told you have to wait on an empty belly.
So you're fasting.
What? Why're you calling me?
Heo Joon Jae, what do I do...
Something big happened...
What?!
I got an order to fast.
Other people get normal meals
calorie controlled meals, special meals but I was the only one that got fasting.
Joon Jae, what do I do?
What do you mean what. It's probably because you might have to get surgery.
Heo Joon Jae. I'm on standby, on an empty stomach.
I got it, so just sleep.
When I close my eyes, it goes back and forth in my sight.
- What does? - Spicy stew with noodles.
- You're a real handful. - Because of the spicy stew with noodles
I can't sleep...
Heo Joon Jae...
Heo Joon Jae left.
No, I'm saying-the patient's mental state is back to normal and it's not like she's got some excessive bleeding.
Just looking at the potential of an emergency operation
and putting her on standby on an empty stomach just doesn't seem right to me, is all I'm saying.
It's just a precaution-but what the heck
are you a doctor?
Is that what's important right now?
And on top of that, the basic process of ordering a fast for a patient
involves informing the patient first, isn't it?! No, I'm saying
you suddenly cut off a kid's happiness when all it comes from is food!
I'm telling you, her mental state's gonna plunge like this! If she goes insane, are you going to take responsibility for her!?
Ms. Sim Cheong, you have a special meal for this morning.
Spicy stew with noodles.
What are you doing.
Are you happy about this right now?!
Dude. Stop. Stop it.
Why are you happy about that ball of chaos getting some spicy stew with noodles?!
- What is it now? - Heo Joon Jae!
I just got the special meal.
So what? I'm busy, hangup.
Our Joon Jae got more charming than ever before.
Punk.
How could you just move away and cut off all contacts like that.
Sorry Ajusshi.
What is this?
It's citrus tea.
You liked the one my wife made.
Mix it in water so you don't catch a cold.
And make sure to dress warm this winter.
Mommy!
1998 Winter Mom!
Drink this, if you keep crying, it'll hurt your throat.
Ajusshi!
Please bring my mom!
This Ajusshi is really sorry for not being able to bring your mom.
But instead, this Ajusshi will protect you, always-
Who are you to do that?!
Ajusshi...is your friend.
I don't need any of that!
Bring my mom!
Bring my mom...
Go that way.
Here.
I'm gonna leave this house.
Then what about your father?
Even if he is like that on the outside, on the inside, he knows he doesn't have anyone but you.
Father has you.
I'm going to leave and I'm going to find my mom.
I'm going to buy a really nice house and I'm going to live in it with my mom.
So,
Ajusshi, please protect my father.
Ajusshi, you kept your promise but I still haven't kept mine.
Your father is looking for you.
It looks like he's thinking of cleaning up the things around him.
Tell him to clean up and take me out of the equation.
Ajusshi, I'll be going now.
Isn't that the way it's supposed to be? At least for families.
Even when they're sorry they find it hard to say the word, and when they miss you it's even harder to say so.
Your father is just like that, and he's aged so much.
I'll drink this well. Please go back safe.
Your father
- is - It's the CEO
the CEO.
How did you know?!
This isn't the first time I've watched dramas.
When they've lost their father or were separated when young
it's 100%, 100% the CEO!
It's not even the president of the company, it's always the CEO.
Why?
What do you mean why, that's just how it is!
I really love Kyuhyun-sshi.
- Break up with my son this instant! - She won't take that.
- I can't accept this. - Oh my, she's bount to get hit with water.
What!?
How do you know everything?!
You see the water on the table? They didn't put it there to drink it.
That's there to splash it in her face when she doesn't take the money.
You get hit with water when you don't take an envelope of money? I can't get hit with water.
You're not the only one can't get hit with water-no one should!
I'll really be in lots of trouble.
But, that person, why is she throwing the water?
It's the whole "I can't give my son to you"-she's saying she can't accept her as a family member.
What's a "family"?
Are you asking because you really don't know? What do you mean what's a family!
The people who are taking care of each other, they're family.
So family are like red-bean fish-pastry.
They look just like each other, just like fish-pastry
and they're warm and sweet.
It's weird, isn't it? Very weird? Weird from all angles?
Whether we're talking about the mental state or physical state.
The truth is, even with this accident. They said she wouldn't be able to recover like that but she's already flying around.
It's strange.
Oh my, what's going on-is she a zombie or what?
And I was bit by someone like her.
You should get a preventive shot, just in case.
But why's Joon Jae around, acting like her guardian? It should've been done when he kicked her out once.
He thinks the reason he can't remember what happened in Spain is connected to her.
And he's probably just curious about that enigmatic bundle of a woman.
I'm curious too. What in the world is she?
I've been coming up with ideas. Don't you think it's something like, "heiress who's lost her memory" or something?
And her physique is super strong because she ate a lot of wild ginseng or something.
Where can you see that in her? At the blink of an eye, you know she's poor.
Demanding the truth behind the medical accident! Please tell me why my daughter died!
Chief, welcome back.
You, are you in your right mind? Didn't you hear that President Lee's son was returning from London?
You're supposed to get rid of trash like that!
I'm sorry.
What are you doing? I said clean up!
Chief, that woman suddenly lost her daughter, so I think she feels wronged.
So as a parent, I too-
Who the hell gives you your paycheck. This hospital or that woman?
Hey, hey! What?
Chief!
Are you okay?
Are you trying to make that patient starve too?! Empty stomachs are horrifying!
Does this make sense? You said she's a patient with a fractured bone.
When we checked in the emergency room, it was definitely a tibia fracture.
Can't you see me flying off? Even a national representative in taekwondo can't make someone fly off like that!
That's what I'm saying.
What happened?
- Give and take.   - What?
This man gave another man a kick in the leg so I gave him a kick in the leg.
What's wrong with her? Is she delusional?
We were thinking the same, so we've decided to proceed with an MRI scan for her brain.
Contact the law firm and tell Attorney Oh to get here. And start all over from the x-ray!
I'll report to the police and let you eat bean (prison) food properly!
What'd she say.
She asked...if bean food was good.
[Trying to find the truth behind a medical accident]
You're in a tight spot because of me, right?
I'm sorry.
Why are you so sad?
Our Ae Yeon,
was so kind. She didn't even go on a school trip so she could help her mom.
They said it would be a simple surgery.
If I had known that she would never wake up again,
I should've done everything for her. I should've sent her on that trip by force,
I should've bought her a lot of pretty clothes.
I should have told her to play around instead of working part-time jobs.
Because I keep thinking about the things I haven't been able to do for her,
I can't sleep and I can't eat. Ae Yeon...
Would you like to hear my secret?
I can erase human memories.
If you would like me to, I can erase all of your sad memories.
If you don't remember your daughter, then you won't be sad and hurting.
I will do it for you.
I'm leaving for school!
Mom, I don't need to go on that educational trip. I'm fine, really.
Our mom smells good.
Ah, really. Did you finish your homework?
Of course I did, who am I.
Mom, aren't I funny?
- You're not funny.  - Mom, when I'm done with my surgery, let's go to Jeju Island.
Okay. I'll be outside, so don't worry.
I'll see you later.
No.
I will keep her in my heart,
no matter how much it hurts, until I die.
Why? Why would you keep her in your heart when it hurts?
Because even if it hurts,
I can love her.
More than not being able to love and remember my daughter,
I would rather love
and remember her. Even if it hurts.
- Ow! - Wow, he went really far! Didn't you say she has a broken bone?
- I did. - What is this then, "The Miracle of Sim Cheong?
I don't know. Maybe the scans got switched or something.
Anyway, what are you going to do? The chief that was hit is threatening to sue Sim Cheong.
What am I supposed to do?
Look at it, she's supposed to have a broken bone but she's flying! Something is weird!
Hey, but look here. When I was watching before
look at this guy, he should've gotten kicked!
But well, whatever, if you don't wanna then there's no reason for me to well.
- Hyung. You know what I hate the most in the world, right? - Right. Not saying hi and bye.
Not that! There's something else: No manners.
- Oh you were like that? - Yeah I was! I always put a lot of weight on respect.
- Oh you did? - Yeah, I did! I can look over Sim Cheong doing this but I just can't look past this one.
So what?
Let's empty him. This human being with absolutely no manners.
The president of this hospital, Lee, is on vacation in Hawaii right now. So the son's flying back for the first time in 10 years.
"Dad I'm at the hospital. But no one's at the airport." So that he can inherit rights for management.
In the Chief's position, God's coming. The presence of an absolute authority.
- Yes, Chairman. - Hey Assistant Director, didn't all the staff go to the airport?
Yes, Sir. They are all out there standing by.
My son is said to have arrived already! What's going on?!
Director Yi Hyeon Dong I presume?
Ah, yes, yes, yes. William Choi.
Forget it!
I'm so sorry about the airport.
I'm not sure where and how it was mixed up, but I'm sorry nevertheless.
Daddy said I should "phone call" him, but my "battery" is out.
Chairman.
Ah, Dad? I arrived.
Forget it. I waited at the airport for two hours, then rode  a taxi here. Geez, I'm so annoyed.
What? Don't do that. Don't cut (fire) him.
Why do you want to cut a person?! Really, I'm fine.
Assistant Director's Office
Ah, William Choi?
Ah, yes. I'll be escorting you to the hospital comfortably. Won't you come this way.
In that time, I'll take the real William for a drive.
Um, where are you going now?
Oh, I'm sorry. I didn't get around to update my navigation software
so I took a wrong turn, and it seems we're on a highway.
While we play for time, Tae Ho will change the file between the Assistant Director's cell phone and the PC.
You'd be able to notice just by sniffing a few voice mail and e-mail content.
Search results.  - Yae Eun Kim patient record - Yae Eun Kim patient record revision
- To erase the surgery report re patient's death...
Gawd the smell...
God. There's some sort of disgusting smell.
Ah... it must be the smell of disinfectant.
As we put such emphasis on disinfection that...
Gawd. The smell's from you, Assistant Director.
Disgusting. Shit...
Um... it must be because I have a chronic gastiritis.
But you know, the smell doesn't disappear even when you shut your mouth.
Our Assistant Director must be fishy (pun) in some way.
- I'm not sure what you mean by... - Oh my god!
Please stop talking.
Who are you guys?
You aren't the Chairman's son, are you?
The fishy smell must have originated from here.
Medical negligence, embezzlement, accost bribes,
Wow, this one would cause a serious trouble if your wife found out.
Personally, I detest a person who doesn't do his familial duty. (people who have affairs)
I guess the pharmaceutical companies give their rebate by holding a golf tournament these days.
1 round is 1,000,000 Won, then 1 day would be 1 Million...?
Well, of course they will lose on purpose.
Why are you doing this to me?
What would you like to do? Shall I disclose all that is here to the reporters?
Hurry, please. He has a hand tremor.
How much would you be wanting...?
Ah, what, you'd like to resolve this with money?
That sure is a good attitude, but
I won't be receiving any money on this, as it is the end of the year (holidays). Instead, won't you do a good deed?
Ah, yes, of course. Whatever it is.
Firstly, you know that unusual woman of high kick?
- Yes. - Go easy on her please.
Ah, for that small deed. I'll be do her a favor.
It didn't hurt too much.
Okay.
And also, I saw as I was coming up...
Hello, Sir.
I was... sorry, last time.
I request the truth in medical malpractice. Please tell me why my daughter died.
This is... the original record of the surgery.
Treatment History/Record
It is indeed our medical error (malpractice).
There was a mistake in mid-surgery,
and because we were unable to properly monitor the patient status post surgery that
we caused your daughter to die as you suspected rightly.
We are at fault.
Any future legal procedure and the compensation would be with our legal department.
I'm truly sorry.
Oops. A mistake.
You're such a...
What's good for a hand tremor, by the way?
I really like the hospital.
Food is delicious, and it's not cold.
Come now, how can the hospital food delicious? It's so plain.
Why doesn't this open?
Goodness, you're so strong!
Oh, I see you're having a meal.
You're taking your meal well and not suffering from anything?
Yes.
Ms. Sim Cheong, as you're fine, you may be discharged.
- What is being discharged? - I'm saying that you may "return to your original place" (go home).
What is "Return to original place"?
Going home, you know.
Is it because I ate too much?
I see that's how it is. Would I be able to stay if I don't eat?
Ah, no. That's not what I mean.
Oh, I don't have a home.
I can't go home...
Let's go home.
Let's go, home, I said.
Okay.
Hey, hey.
Doctor. is it okay for her to run like this?
Yes, we did an overall checkup and she's fine. She can run a marathon.
Is this possible?
Possibly there was a mistake at the ER and the x-ray might have been switched.
Almost never is there such incidence. I'm really sorry.
Are you alright?
Let's go.
Heo Joon Jae, when does the first snow fall?
The first snow comes once a year.
This year's first snow has come and gone. It'll come next year.
Is that right?
Then I guess I won't be able to see the first snow.
Why not?
What now? Are you going somewhere next year?
Where are you going?
Heo Joon Jae, do people want to remember even the pain and sadness?
What do you mean?
What kind of love would it be to want to remember it
despite being so painful that makes you unable to eat or sleep?
I love you.
- What are you thinking about right now? - What?
It's nothing.
Would you like to see first snow?
Though the first snow in Seoul is over, there are places that still hasn't snowed.
There is?
What then, would you like to try going?
Yes, I want to try.
Okay.
I can obtain a medical record here, correct?
Yes, and you'd have brought the consent form or the power of attorney?
Ah, yes. Here it is.
- The x-ray would be included as well, right? - Yes.
CEO, I've met with Joon Jae.
You met him?
Yes sir.
I've passed onto him that you've been wanting to meet him.
But it seems he still needs some time.
I'll try to persuade him when I see him again.
Chief Nam.
Yes, sir?
I'm always grateful for you.
It's nothing sir.
Please let me see him, no matter what it takes. I have a lot of things I want to tell him.
Yes sir, I understand.
Have you received a call from the CEO?
Yes, just now.
Who-!
Dramalove.TV
This much snow fell since the first snow?!
That's right. Me, I went through so much trouble trying to find where it snows most, just for you.
Thank you, Heo Joon Jae.
Let's go in.
-  When I made you wait  -
-  Whenever you smile, I'm always sorry  -
- Precious things  -
- Always make me scared  -
- I'm always so nervous, so worried about you  -
- It's the first time I've ever felt this way  -
- Wherever it is, whenever the time is when I meet you  -
- And tell you I love you, as if I say it all the time  -
Let's put these on. You have to put stuff like this on when you're here.  - Whenever I see you  -
- Somewhere inside me keeps hurting  -
- Wherever it is, whenever the time  -
But, I feel like I've seen this somewhere...  - I'm afraid that we'll have to go far away from each other  -
- And forget  -
Is it dj vu?
- Even when I'm holding your hand  -
Now, watch close. When you're going down, if you make an 11 with your feet, then you'll slide right down.
Like this, see?
And to stop-
How do I stop?!
Hey! Make an A! An A!
What's an A?! I don't know what an A is!
That idiot!
Heo Joon Jae!
Heo Joon Jae! Move, move!
You...Do you know or do you not know, that I just saved your life.
I know.
You...Just do one thing I ask you to do.
What is it?
The thing is...
I'm trying to confirm something...
Mhm.
You...
Can you try saying this?
What is it?
I love you.
- This is a love story  -
-  Something you can't hide  -
- These two eyes that only see you  -
- It's me that can't close them  -
- This is amazing  -
- Even if the entire world  -
- is what they offer me  -
- I would be able to trade it with you, my love  -
- Some time, just once  -
- I knew he would come  -
- That person, that love   -
- I will find him, I said  -
Epiloge So family is like red-bean fish-pastry.
They all look alike, and they're warm.
And they're sweet.
Well, it's not always nice. They're both the illness and the cure.
Even with me, I was going through all sorts of things trying to help my son pay off his debt.
That's when the disc in my back ruptured.
- I'm so afraid this might all be a dream, I can't open my eyes  -
- This is my love story  -
- I love only you  -
Are you feeling better? I was so shocked back then too.
It was the first time I'd ever caused an accident and the victim...
The victim is someone that happens to know my little brother.
Little brother?
Yes, I'm Joon Jae's family.
Heo Joon Jae's family?
Yes! Family.
Oh and this, this is mine.
Anyhow, I'm so sorry for everything.
And this.
You've got fast hands.
The medical bills will probably be taken care of by insurance but you can just consider that as a form of compensation.
W-Why are you looking at me like that? Is there something on my face?
I don't like getting hit with water. I know I've taken the envelope of money
- but I won't break up with Heo Joon Jae. - Excuse me?
Heo Joon Jae family! I love Heo Joon Jae.
Just know that.
Y-Yes, of course.
W-Wait.