BioskopKeren.ORG
Episode 7
His pulse is weak.
His tendons, bones, and flesh are damaged and have formed blood clots.
If it gets into his heart-
If that's the case, what happens?
He won't be able to overcome the coming crisis.
I believe he was beat up by a group of people after he fell off from the cliff.
It seems like my friend secretly hid my lover,
and fell upon this calamity while coming back down.
My Lord, about my concubine making a ruckus in your office the day before yesterday...
please forgive her.
She was afraid that the evil omen that brings death might have entered the government office.
It seems like she was out of her mind in worry of that.
So, I reprimanded her to the point of tears.
I see.
Yes.
A few days ago, ever since that corpse was found at the beach,
the sentiment of the village people has become panic-stricken.
So you must have also been disheartened. I am very sorry, Sir.
I see that you have some rare and precious fruit.
Ah, yes. It is tangerine.
Although I am of a lowly position, I have a taste for good food.
So I got it through a boat coming from Tamra Island (today's Jeju Island) after much difficulty.
Is that so?
This inn is probably the only place to be able to eat this kind of fruit in this village, right?
Of course. The price is... exorbitant.
But this tangerine was found while examining
the corpse found at the beach.
On the day that he died, the last person he met was you.
You met him that night and offered him a drink, along with this fruit.
He died from drinking the alcohol spiked with poison, and you threw him on the beach.
However, the traces of poison was not found during the initial examination.
On the first day that snow fell and water froze, the corpse was frozen like ice, but then
it was different during the secondary examination of the corpse.
As the frozen corpse melted, deathly poison extracted from the blow fish eggs was found.
My Lord, I am ignorant and cannot understand what you-
- Look here!- Yes, Sir!
We have found the blowfish egg's poison in Yang Seung Gil's room.
My Lord, it's unfair.
Your servant does not know anything. I've been set-up.
My Lord!
Let go!
Won't you let go!
Come!
What do you think you are doing?!
Please, comply with us.
If Se Hwa is alive then I will save your life.
Who is that? I don't know.
If you don't know then you will die.
Even if I can't find Se Hwa
you will die in this place.
Look here! The town head is bewitched by that wily thing and trying to destroy the village.
He is trying to save that mermaid who brought rainstorms and caused people to die!
Try stepping out just one step.
Do you think all these eyes and mouths will stay still?
Oh, no, you can't!
My pearls!
I'm sorry, I came too late.
♬  Stained with ink ♬
Se Hwa, you liked listening to my dreams, didn't you?
Are you listening?
In my dream, we were born again.
We met again and were together.
You came from a far away ocean to meet me.
♬  The person you've been longing for ♬
And though I could not remember you,
you were already in my heart.
♬  She became a mermaid ♬
Se Hwa.
Wouldn't you like to listen to more of this story?
♬ A sad story ♬
Legend of the Blue Sea
I need to confirm something.
Yeah.
You... can you try saying these words?
What words?
I love you.
Then are you mine?
Are you surrendering? Did you lose?
What?
I was going to be the first to surrender when the first snow falls.
I really did not know you would surrender first. Are you mine?
No matter what I say, would you believe me?
What are you talking about?
You said you love me. That's what it means, right?
Let's say you love someone.
That means that you surrender.
What's "surrender"?
It means, losing. You lost. In other words, if you love someone,
no matter what that person says, you will believe everything.
- That means you are in trouble.- Why?
That means that you belong to that guy. If he says to do this, you do this.
If he says to do that, you will do that. If he tells you to believe lies, then you believe lies. That's love.
So is it okay to say that to a guy or not?
It's okay.
No! You shouldn't.
If you say things like "I love you" to me, that means you are mine.
If you say things like that to me, I'll probably use you to do things and lie like crazy.
I'll take all your possessions.
That is supposed to be love.
Ah, geez! Who would utter such nonsense?!
♬  Even at this moment. ♬
There's someone. Someone good.
Who is it? A guy?
Yes, it's a guy.
So, it's a guy. He is a nut job!
What's a nut job?
He is a crazy jerk.
Seeing how he says things like that, he is a total sleazeball and a womanizer.
Those are all bad words, right?
Right. You should not hang out with that kind of punk.
Was he really good to you? Huh?
When it was raining, he put an umbrella over me, and he held my hand when I was alone.
Ah, hand...
I'm sure he will do anything... to seduce a girl.
He made me ramen.
Ra...ramen! Wow, ramen!
Did he tell you to come in and eat some ramen before leaving?(It's a common pick up line in Korea)
Wow, what a dark-hearted jerk!
He is not a dark-hearted jerk.
He is a good person.
If he was such a good person, you should be next to him, not by me.
And let me make it clear, in case you misunderstand... When I said earlier...
"I love you," was not because I really loved you,
but I was telling you to say that, so that I can confirm something-
I love you.
- Should I say it again?- No, that's fine.
I can say it again.
No, don't. It's fine.
Don't say it.
- Where are you coming from?- From a ski resort.
Did you have a date?
Date, my butt!
She was begging about snow, so I just took her there briefly.
That's a date. Isn't that right, Tae Oh?
This dude keeps glaring at a person all the time nowadays.
- Do you want some?- No, thanks. You can eat all the tangerines you like.
Do you want some?
Did you have a fight with him?
No, we didn't.
Then why is he in such a bad mood?
Yo, upper room!
Hey!
What is it?
Since I can't fall asleep, I keep thinking these useless thoughts. Are you still meeting him?
- Who?- Who else?! Earlier...
Ramen! Are you still seeing him?
Yes, I am.
You are?
I see. You are seeing him.
Well, how does he look?
He is pretty.
His eyes are twinkling.
He must look like a girly boy.
You should be most careful with guys who look like that! What good is a guy who looks pretty?
Those guys are lustful inside!
You... so did you tell him that, too?
What?
You know... Those words you said earlier at the ski resort.
I love you?
Yes. That. Did you tell that jerk that, too?
I love you.
Yes, I did.
Why?
To you, those words must be so easy.
- Saying those words to just anyone.- I don't say it just to anyone.
What did you do well that you are raising your voice?
You get up! Who told you to come done, eh?
Go back up.
But, well, maybe it's a good thing.
Honestly, I felt a bit burdened, worrying that you had a special feeling towards me.
Good luck with him.
I will. I came to work things out with him.
Good, then!
Must be nice! Good luck! Hurry and get back up!
She came to work things out with him? Then, why is she here?
Haha, isn't she a funny girl?! Ah, annoying.
So annoying.
Se Hwa!
Se Hwa! Se Hwa!
What was that?
What kind of dream was that?
This ajussi is our Joon Jae's friend.
Dept. Head Nam Ajussi
010-0960-1303
He cannot answer the phone. You will be connected to the voice mail.
Hello?
Oh, what's up?
Dept. Head Nam? He hasn't come to work yet.
What? How?
Is he that kind of person? So where is he now?
Okay, let's hang up for now.
What happened, Father?
Dept. Head Nam drove while drunk last night and got into an accident.
Ajussi doesn't like drinking though.
How would you know? How can you tell a person by looking at his appearance?
So, how much is he hurt?
Should we go visit him at the hospital?
He is unconscious. It seems serious.
Really?
Oh no. What do we do?
When you go to the hospital, let me go with you.
Okay, let's do that.
2) 8/21/2016 Incheon International AirportDisguised as a valet parking staff, he stole a luxury car and ran away
It's been three months. During the three months, that punk Ma Dae Young...
without having confirmed any additional criminal activities, his whereabouts are still in the dark.
You said that there is a possibility for the Haewondong loanshark murder case could be him.
There is.
No, it is highly possible. But we only have a suspicion. We don't have evidence.
There was no money or belongings that were lost. So, in that precinct,
they see these debtors that disappeared overseas as suspects, and they told me not me to butt in.
He was a loan shark and a person who had a lot of people holding a grudge against him, so that's possible.
If it was due to a grudge, they would have planned it well. But look at the time and location.
It was in broad daylight at three in the afternoon.
Anyone would be able to witness this while passing by.
But then, this was done very momentarily and impulsive.
- Ma Dae Young has an anger disorder.- With just that...
Nowadays, there aren't just one or two people who can't control their anger.
It was really meticulous. It's really clean without any fingerprints or traces of DNA.
This is done by someone who is always prepared to murder.
But it seems our superiors don't want us to focus on that.
If an escaped criminal committed that kind of crime? Then we will be more cursed at.
Hey! Do you think that's important?
Then what is so important to you?
You, punk, go catch that dude who feigned false identity in Yeoyido.
The one who erased all the CCTVs and took off.
I have a feeling I know who that is. I will catch that slimeball after catching Ma Dae Young.
You are so dead, you punk!
Hey! Hey! Hey!
The female employees at the aquarium thought Yeongdeung Police has such a handsome detective
and they were about to start a fan club, then they saw your profile and they were so disappointed!
Why are they disappointed? He and I look pretty much similar!
According to Ahn Jin Joo's SNS, she will be attending a seminar for International Middle School Preparation.
Communicating to SNS followers. VIP invitation
to International Middle School - Zeal for Education. This is Helicopter Mom's way.
She's leaving at three. She's probably going out of the house at 2-2:30.
The family's chauffeur is on a day off. Ahn Jin Joo's driving skill is a bit lacking.
At that moment, Tae Oh will call using the English Academy's number and distract her.
Yes, I am Elizabeth's mom. Really?
Our Elizabeth, oh my! Was first in English oral competition? Oh my God!
Are you not hurt anywhere?
I don't think so. Yes. Omo.
Please just call this number. Since I am busy, I will be going then.
Oh my!
After you make your face seen, your second meeting would be at the seminar.
- Okay.- What are you doing?
Good morning.
Let's go.- Where are you going?
Where would we be going? To work.
We're going to work.
Going to work. What work are you going to do?
Ah... that is... the work that we are doing is...
To say it simply, it's like getting a person's heart?
To let a person realize his or her own fault.
Although there definitely is a problem with the way they accumulated their wealth, and yet they are beyond the perimeters of the law.
To those people who fall into that blind spot,
we take appropriate actions.
We also redistribute the wealth.
For the country's sake.
A public office worker?
I saw it on TV, the ones who work for the country are public office workers.
We are not. Just because they work at public office doesn't mean they are doing it for the country's benefit.
So, Heo Joon Jae does a cooler job than a public office worker.
Well...
Heo Joon Jae, I knew it.
Why am I making excuses to her?
I know, right? You were really shabby, listening right here.
Then, should I say it? That we're conmen?
I don't feel good about that word.
Hey, should we make a new name? A cool one?
- What are you saying?- Okay, okay. We're late. Let's go.
What is this?
Here.
Check this house.
Hey, hey.
Ma Dae Young! You bastard!
Ma Dae Young, bastard!
Ma Dae Young!
Why are you doing this?
Wow! Score!
So cold.
I am hungry, should we go to the convenience store to eat?
Okay.
Hey! Seo Yoon Ah, you live in rental Apartments, right?
- So?- My mom said
as the rental kids started coming to our school, our neighborhood's quality went down!
Your mom is a divorcee, right?
My mom said so.
Kids like you have such a messy family education.
So, she told me not to play with you.
I also don't want to play with you. Can you please move?
This is not a place for people who live in the renal apartment to pass, you know.
Can you turn around and pass there?
You!
Hey! You pushed me! You? To me?
What are you doing? Put me down please.
You should not bother your friends.
Let me down please.
Hurry and promise me, that you won't bother your friend.
- Mommy.
Elizabeth. What's wrong?
Hurry and come.
Yes. The car is still here.
Thank you for earlier, Unnie.
But what is divorce?
Divorce is when people who got married break up.
Why would they break up?
You also don't know that, Unnie? They break up because they don't love each other anymore.
They don't love each other so why did they get married?
They are in love when they got married but they change that's why.
My mom and dad probably loved each other when I was a baby.
It's just that they changed.
Why would they change?
Where would you find "why?"
It's just that they all change.
Even those who are not divorced are staying together not necessarily because they love each other.
They are living while enduring it.
Really?
Unnie, do you know why I'm working hard going to the academy?
No.
My mom... might love me now
but if I don't study hard...
she might not love me anymore.
She might send me away.
That's why, even if I don't want to go to the academy I work hard and go.
Let's go.
That hair, it may appear messy as if it wasn't prepped.
It's so calculatedly elegant. Where is it?
Where is it?
Which shop did she have it done?
Mom! I told you it's that Unnie.
Is it you?
Are you the one who told my daughter off?
How could it be? The outfit does not match at all.
It may look like the soup and rice being served separately, and yet they match so marvelously well.What is this weird feeling?
Who coordinated that?
It's because she bothered her.
So funny. Who are you?
Are you her mother? Are you the school teacher?
These days, even school teachers can't just...
When did Chanel and Dior collaborate?
Oh my! Why didn't I know that?
Mom.
I am Seo Yoon Ah's friend.
In the future, I won't let you go if you bother my friend.
You promised.
Wait.
I... have a lot I am curious about, but let me just ask you one thing.
Which dermatologist do you go to?
"I don't go," "I was born with this skin," "I don't even take care of it and it's like this."
Don't even think of saying those nonsense lies.
Answer me, where do you get taken care of?
It's not in Seoul. It's very far.
I knew it. So, she goes out to expedition. Oh my!
Which country...
Oh my world. Which country could she get...
What is it? It's past 3.
I know. It's strange.
The car is still there.
She must have gone out and just came back.
Wait.
I'm going to rest today. Culture shock! When did Chanel and Dior collaborate?
I'd appreciate information exchanged. This is FaPe's way.
This is FaPe's way.
Fashion people?
Seriously. Today was such a waste.
I'm really not feeling this. Can't you look into something else?
You're at it again.
Hey! I will be stopping by somewhere.
You guys on first.
- Where are you going?- You don't need to know, punk.
You don't even have anywhere else to go...
Could it be? It's probably not him.
My Joon Jae.
But why are you doing this?
This is the only thing I am good at.
You could just use that talent somewhere else. I am envious.
Like you are the one to say that.
- Then what about you?- It's Hyung.
Hyung, what happened for you to start this line of work?
So, people
need to meet the right people.
Looking for mom. We got separated when I was 10.Her name is Mo Yoo Ran. Her birthday is...
We could have just done it if the office interior was done.
Can you really find my mom?
Your mother's hometown was Cheongbuk
Jaecheon, right?- Yes.
She's the only daughter of a really rich household.
But after her parents passed away, she made a mistake of cosigning a loan that went wrong.
She lost all her inheritance. After that none of the relatives contacted her.
Yes, how did you know?
How would I? It's my work.
Can you please find my mom?
But then,
the fact that she hasn't reported her moving,
and that she doesn't have a permanent residency, and she doesn't seem like she's remarried.
It is very hard to find her with the usual way.
In the end, you would have to get an expert but then the fee would be
Ah, the fee.
Wait.
Would this much be okay?
Of course that man just ran off with that money.
You should not worry about that part.
I will find him for sure.
I will be calling you after a week.
Yes.
You conman!
Ahjumma, he is a conman! Don't give him money!
No.
- Give me back my money!- Let go! Let go!- My money! My money!
How many days were you there?
Half a month.
Hey.
Don't you want to work with me? I like people who are tenacious.
If you go around finding your mother like that, only your legs would hurt.
You need to have money to find your mom. To put it bluntly,
you found your mom but then what would you do since you have no money?
When would would you earn enough money ripping off a young kid like me?
What? You should rip off of people who have a lot of money.
If you are going to deceive someone anyway, you need to invest in time and finance.
If you consider the financial efficiency,
wouldn't it be more profitable to steal from rich people, using the same effort?
There are so many bigwigs who can't report even when they are ripped off.
Just until I find my mom. Just until I get enough money to buy a house for her.
You already gathered enough to buy her a house.
I did. It's just that I haven't found my mom.
Gae Nam Doo also worked hard to find my mom.
But he couldn't find where she is.
Please look at this, hyung.
What is it?
If it's the same person's x-rays. The other hospital said it was switched with another patient.
This is the same person.
Really?
You can just look at the bones and the fracture. Look here.
The widths of tibia and fibula and the way they are stretched out are the same.
This one has a fracture and this one is in stage of healing.
- Oh?- Why?
The bone has stuck together but there is still edema.
Usually, the swelling disappears and then the bone sticks together but then for this person the bones stuck first.
Can this happen?
Hyung, what's that... How long does it usually take for the fractured bones to stick together again?
It's case by case basis, but still
for the fractured bone to stick together completely, about 12-16 weeks.
Hey, even with a hairline fracture, it's maximum 3-4 week with a cast.
What if in just one week this, became this?
Does that make sense?
Right. It doesn't make sense.
Hurry and go. I am busy.
What is that? So scary. What if she's really a zombie.
Hey, as if.
I think that woman... beyond just losing her memories
or lacking a bit, disregarding those, there's something.
I know. I also think so. But I can't get a grasp of what that is.
Hello? Did you find ___________?
Who is the owner?
Kim Dam Ryeong?
Even the name is cool. Okay, I'll be right back.
Oppa, I need to get back now. It looks like we found the owner of relics we excavated from a wrecked ship.
Wait. Wait. The name of the owner is Dam Yeong?
Yes. He was a town head of Heupgok Hyun in Gangwon Province.
Oh, it's nothing. Go in.
See yo later.
Keep an eye on Joon Jae and that girl. Make sure they're not doing anything, okay?
Dummy.
Dummy, dummy.
Why are you doing this?
What do you mean, why? That's what I want to ask you. Are you going to jump from here?
No, that's not it...
Don't try to fool me. You even took off your shoes. Stand up, people like this...
Sit here.
Would you like some barley tea?
It's hot.
No, wait.
Let's just talk.
I've lived here a long time, so I barely remember how to speak language from there.
This language is more comfortable.
I got it.
Hey. Who would've known
that I would meet a mermaid in the middle of Seoul?
I thought I was the only mermaid in Seoul. I was really surprised.
No, but what were you doing earlier?
I was hungry. I don't have money,
and it's time for a meal, so I went there to eat.
You don't have money?
Hey, I guess you're usually like that.
Like what?
You really didn't know this?
These are tears. What are you doing?
These count as money here.
Money? Why?
If you don't know, just memorize it. These count as money here.
And when you start to tear up,
just do this and collect all of them.
This helped me so much.
Ah, I cried a couple of times. I should've collected them.
The bigger they are, the more valuable. So instead of uselessly crying small tears,
Hold it in, and cry thick tears. Oil.
The pink-tinted pearls? The ones that come out when you cry of happiness?
That's right.
But as you live here, happy moments
that make you tear up don't come often. I cried that kind of tear
just once.
Then I should cry a lot and give all my tears to Heo Joon Jae.
Who is Heo Joon Jae?
I like him. He's a cool person.
Wait, you didn't come up here to see the light?
You came up here because of a guy you liked?
Hey, you really don't know anything.
How long has it been since you got here?
One month.
The guy you like, is it one side or both sides?
So do you like him by yourself or is it mutual?
It's just me right now.
You really didn't calculate anything! You should think before coming up here!
Ah, this is why I lived here talking to the fish.
I told them to call the mermaids. "Don't ever follow a person here." You never heard that?
No.
Why can't I? Why can't I follow a person here?
Listen carefully.
You have a time limit.
The moment that a mermaid leaves the water for land, her heart starts to harden.
Even if your legs don't, you heart has a time limit.
There is only one way you can continue to breathe
and keep your heart beating on land.
It is only possible when the person that you love, loves you back.
That is the only way your heart
can continue to beat passionately.
It isn't too late, so return to the ocean, idiot.
So why did you come here without calculating?
So, after you left the water,
there should've been some motive.
That guy said something to you, right?
He told me to come to Seoul.
That's right. What did he say? Did he ask you to date? To marry?
He asked me to go to specialty restaurants.
That's it?
He also told me to come see the fireworks.
Fireworks?
I see, you're an easy girl.
Can you decide so easily on love with specialty restaurants and fireworks?
Did you have some kind of serious romance for one month?
Of course. As soon as I saw you,
Should I help you?
How?
Jealousy?
If you don't know, memorize. Jealousy
is the fastest path to love.
♬  No, no, no, no, no ♬
I think it would be good if we started with a makeover.
Should we try to get some money for shopping?
Hold it. Hold it,
and then cry thick. Thick tears.
Chae Wa. I love you.
You...
Hello. I've heard a lot about you.
Who... are you?
I'm Yoo Jeong Hoon.
Please take care of me in the future.
Take care of what?
- Our darling...- Excuse me?
I heard she was living in this house for a bit.
I heard it was a house full of men, so I was a bit concerned. But now that I see you,
I'm assured.
You're assured? I don't think I have that kind of face.
I'll see you tomorrow.
Dear, how about you tie your hair tomorrow? Your neck is pretty.
Like this?
Hey. Go in now.
Go first.
- Go in first.- No, you leave first.
I'll be more at ease if I see you go in.
No, it's okay. Leave first.
- Just go in first.- No, leave first.
I'll leave after I see you go in.
He said go in!
Just go inside!
Wait.
Why again?
I just want to see her face one more time.
Click.
I'm taking a picture. I'll be looking at it when I miss you tonight.
Like this? Click. Click, click, click.
Ah, you're so cute.
Hey. Go inside.
He isn't the type of guy to drink and drive.
I can't understand it either.
We decided to eat altogether.
But, why? Why did he drink and go all the way there?
It seems like an intentional accident.
How could it be? The police says it's a driving under the influence case.
It will just make things harder for you to think that way.
It's me. Me!
What are you doing?
- Hey, let me look at the bracelet. Just once!- Are you going at it again?
- I just want to confirm something.- Confirm what?
There is something.
Aren't you going to tell me the truth?
Well, Si Ah is currently working on artifacts from shipwreck.
The artifacts belonged to someone named Dam Ryeong.
Isn't it interesting? It is possible that they are two different people with same name.
However, if it's the same person
it will be more than $6 million! Let me have it appraised at least.
Hyeong,
Do you know why I keep that bracelet?
I'll return it to Cheong when she leaves. If I give it back to her now,
people like you won't leave it alone.
You are really strange these days.
Do you all of sudden aspire to be a decent human being?
Leave.
Heo Joon Jae, you're scary. I'm leaving.
Se Hwa!
Strange things keep happening since I've met that dummy.
Whoa, my Cheong, did you know how to doll up?
Whoa, dressed like that, you look beautiful!
Doesn't she, Tae Oh? Look at him, he's speechless. Whoa.
What the...?
It's cold. It's winter.
Joon Jae, Cheong's also wearing a skirt!
Go change.
Why? It's the one you bought it for me last time.
- Do you think I bought it for you to wear going outside?- You didn't?
I bought it for you to hang in the closet.
Do you think that makes sense?
Of course it does! Not all clothes are made for wearing. Some are made for being hung in the closet!
Go change it to pants and leave your hair untied.
Hey, why are you trying to regulate her her hair and clothing? Are you her student affairs teacher?
I'm the house owner. Hyeong, you too go and change your clothes as well! Are you a Rudoph?
You'd better listen to me. If you don't want to, then leave.
Whoa, my Cheong, your chopstick skills have improved a lot!
Cheong, where are you going today? Do you want me to give you a ride?
Yes, I have plans later...
Don't you think you need to clean the house or something to pay for your stay here?
Of course, I can clean. I saw Tae Oh does it.
It's quite dusty these days because we haven't been able to open the windows to circulate the air as it's been cold.
Wipe down well so there won't be any dust.
I can do that.
It's my house. I'll make whomever I want to do it.
Also, you'll see a fan in the storage. It will be dusty.
We won't use it until next summer.
That's why we have to clean it now.
Are you the evil step-mother? (as in Cinderella &amp; etc) Cheong, just go out without doing it.
Don't you dare! You won't be able to go before you finish them all.
What is it?
I forgot my phone.
Ah, it feels nice!
Why do you think the mermaids are brink of extinction?
Because we don't change.
Humans change but we don't change like idiots. That's why we get stabbed in the back.
Humans change?
They do. The woman I loved did, too.
Even though she said she'd love me forever.
When she found about who I am, she left. Just like that.
At first, I was regretting coming to the land
It was hard, but it's our reality
There is no human on earth who can accept us as the way we are.
The man you love is the same.
So, get your act together
and don't ever get caught.
Epilogue
Hello, could I have your moment?
Excuse me, but could I ask what you do for living?
I'm a public officer.
Oh, I see.
You know public officers. We don't make big money,
but our jobs are tenured and have a pension.
Frankly, it is a job to provide support for someone comfortably.
Ah, I do know that, but...
Could I ask you a question?
What do you do, Mr. Heo Joon Jae?
If it's hard to answer, you don't need to.
Anyways, please do take a good care of my Cheong.
Well, you don't need to ask me for that. I will make sure..
I mean, WE will figure it out.
You would think the time is... And the opportunities are... Always available to you, don't you?
They are not!
What is he? What is he babbling about? Acting all cool.
He's a joke, seriously!
How to Become 7th Grade Civil Officer