Subtitles brought to you by The Blue Sea @ Viki
I'll go back.
Back to where I came from. Before it's too late.
If perhaps... if I start planning on liking you, you told me to tell you, right?
It's happened... that plan.
So... don't go.
Don't go?
Yes.
Don't go.
Now enough, let's go, home.
Heo Joon Jae, what's the matter? Are you okay?
Heo Joon Jae? Heo Joon Jae!
Heo Joon Jae! Heo Joon Jae!
Heo Joon Jae!
Please help!
Has something happened? What's going on?
Heo Joon Jae!
What's the matter?
Hello? Someone has collapsed here.
- Heo Joon Jae!- Please send a medic.
Please send someone quickly!
- Hello? - What should we do?
- Who are you?  - Who are you?
I am Dam Ryeong.
If you are me in the next life,
just remember these words again after waking from this dream.
Everything repeats itself.
The fate that happened here is also being fulfilled there;
ill-fate is like that as well.
Protect that woman
from the dangerous person.
- Heo Joon Jae.- Excuse me, are you okay?
Can you see this? Can you see this?
Heo Joon Jae!
Are you okay?
I am okay.
I'm okay.
[The Legend of the Blue Sea]
[Episode 9]
Are you okay now?
You.. you also said you were in pain earlier.
I'm not in pain any more.
Why?
While you were saying you love me or not, whether I have plans to or not, and bothering me so much,
Were you thinking of running away from behind?
Hey, you are scary.
If you go, where? Who would you go to?
That government employee?
Jeong Hoon is gone now.
Why? Where has he gone?
Far.
Did you also plan to go after him far away?
Why? Did he ask you to go far away and eat ramyun with him?
It wasn't Jeong Hoon who cooked me ramyeon.
Do you mean.. he isn't that guy?
Then who is that guy?
I can't tell you that.
This won't do, you follow me.
- Look here, see there are lots of dolls right?  -Yeah.
Pick one.
I choose that pink octopus.
Okay, you chose the pink octopus, right?
That's what you chose, so you have to pick out that one no matter what.
Here, try it.
I did it!
I almost did it though.
You're right, it almost came out right? But it didn't actually come all the way out, you know.
Life is naturally all about something that is about to work out but then it may not.
But if you give up here,
then that pink octopus that you chose will never be able to come out.
Try it again.
I guess it's not working.
You're trying to give up like that again?
If you decided, you can't give up until it's become yours.
Whether that's the pink octopus,
or anything.
Then I'll try again one more time.
- Hey, now-  - Wait, stay there.
Ah it almost did it.
From what I see, there's something wrong with the machine.
It looks like they loosened the claw on purpose. Let's just go.
Then give up?
No. This isn't giving up, this is stopping for a bit.
Until next time?
Of course. How are you so smart now, it's been a while..?
Anyway, the important thing is that you should never give up on what you've chosen.
Should you give up, or shouldn't you?
Shouldn't.
That's right.
Would you like to go and eat some sticky flat bun?
Hey, I told you not to go, but you didn't listen to me.
Something serious almost happened!
I said I'm okay.
Who on earth was it? Did you see his face?
I'm not sure.
Anyone that comes to mind?
Well, since we have so many enemies,
I can't narrow it down quickly.
He was spotted by the police patrolling Hoehyeon-dong,
and the chase began during the daylight.
What?
It's that person.
It's that person?
The escaped prisoner? Ma Dae Young?
Yes, that's right. It's him.
He took his hat off today.
Cheong, do you remember him, too?
It's that person, right? The one who was wearing the police uniform and cap when it was raining before.
He wore a police cap and also a black cap.
You... Have you seen him after that day?
Yes, when I was passing out the flyer.
Whoa! I am so shocked so many times. Do you see the goosebumps?
Then, the escapee was tailing our Cheong? Why?
If something like that happened, you should have told me!
Are you a fool?
Cheong wouldn't have known, either. You just found out, too. Why are you blaming her?
Ah, that punk. He is just acting up for no good reason.
Ah, it's cold. What are you doing there? Come on in.
Have a seat.
Why would that jerk be tailing Cheong?
Did he just follow Cheong? He called you out and almost killed you.
Something serious really could have happened to you!
So, that's what I'm saying. Why would that jerk follow Cheong...
The fate in this world is continuing in that world.
It's the same way for the ill-fate.
From a dangerous person, protect that woman.
Hyung.
What?
Don't take it the wrong way.
I had a dream.
A dream?
In that dream, I was living in the Joseon period.
Huh?
And I was wearing that bracelet.
The bracelet? You mean Kim Dam Ryeong's bracelet?
Ah, so you were Kim Dam Ryeong in the dream?
Yes.
I believe I was.
It's possible. After seeing the movie The Admiral: Roaring Currents, I had a dream where I was Admiral Yi in it.
Aish, I'm not talking about that kind of non-sense dream.
Look who's talking. Your dream is the non-sense one. How could you be Kim Dam Ryeong?
Is it like you're looking back at your past life?
It's not like it's my past life, but I feel like I'm looking at a parallel universe.
- Myself in another universe.- You in another universe, my butt!
It's because I've been talking to you about the bracelet,
and Si Ah told you about the excavation from the shipwreck. That's why you're having this non-sense dream.
The reality is governing your dream. You're the one who studied neurosciences. How can you not realize it?
- Ah, is it like that?- Of course, it is.
Ah. I've been kind of off recently.
Hey, it is natural
to have weird dreams before your big projects.
It must be a sign that our Project Ahn Jin Joo will be a big success.
Huh?
Yes, that girl named Seo Yuna.
It seems like that girl and my Elizabeth had some troubles.
You know girls like that always stand out not in a good way.
Oh my. Did you get a call from her mom? Why?
She asked to have her included in our swim team?
Well... Will you let her in?
Of course not. That's right.
When there are kids like that in the mix, it's always our kids who suffer.
Of course, I trust you. Then...
Okay. Let's talk details when we meet.
Okay, yes. Bye!
You were on the phone for 1.5 hours but you didn't discuss the details?
Honey,
did you get to talk to Chairman Heo?
Well. I invited him to a dinner, but he acts all busy and doesn't set up the time.
Omo, I've been providing endless supply of banchan (side dishes) for him
since I was told he liked them.
Is it like dine and dash? What's wrong with them?
He's not an easy guy. If there's anything of investment value, he'd do that himself and won't give them to us.
That's why we're trying this hard
so he could share some of them, no?
Oh my.
It's been so hard to put aside that secret fund.
I was so careful not to get caught on by the external audits or the National Tax Services.
We saved it up by working up our blood and sweat.
Of course we have. If you call this black money,
I feel wronged. I worked very hard for that money!
Preach, honey!
You've worked so hard. We really
invest this money well
and won't let your efforts
go to waste.
Yes, honey. Let's give our best tonight as well!
Say what?
- Who's it?- Korea Post. Is Ms. Kang Seo Hee available?
It's court registered mail, so she has to accept it herself.
How dare you show up here. Are you crazy?
It's not like I wanted to. I am cold, hungry, and out of money.
Heo Joon Jae is not an easy target. He wiggles his way out every time.
Chairman Heo is trying to set up meetings with his lawyers to legalize his will.
Will you get your sense back after I lost everything?
What are we going to do if Chairman Heo go meet Joon Jae and give all his fortune to him?
Hurry and leave now.
- Sorry about the trouble at this late hour.- No problem.
Bye.
Hi.
Oh, Chi Hyeon.
Do they deliver at this late hour?
That's what I wondering. He must be behind his schedule due to busy year-end season.
- Have you eaten?- Yes, I have.
Let's go in.
Have you eaten, Mother?
What is it?
Mother, Did you hear about Joon Jae, by any chance?
How would I know?
I ran into him recently. By pure luck.
Oh, you did?
Did you tell your father?
Of course not. I'm telling you first.
Good job. He's been under stress for a few things recently.
I think it will be better that you don't tell him that for a while.
By any chance, do you know already?
- What? - Where Joon Jae lives
and how he is.
I told you already that I don't know.
Then why won't you ask me more about him? Aren't you curious since I met him?
Your farther and I
have huge scars we got from Joon Jae.
Wouldn't it be weird if I get all interested when your father isn't?
Mother, what if he couldn't show his emotions
because of two of us?
I am sorry that their relationship went south.
But, I'm not sure if I'd like he'd come back.
Don't you like how things are right now?
Do you think we'll keep how things are right now when Joon Jae returns?
- But I...- Yes, you.
Do you think you'll keep what you have?
Mother.
I want to protect you.
My good son! However...
That's my job to protect us.
Let's get in quickly.
Yes. Bye.
There's one footage of him from the surveillance camera from the nearby convenience store. It's back of him, though.
He knows blind spots like nobody's business.
That's why the police hasn't been able to catch him so far.
Hello?
010-3654-23
Who is this?
Hi, do you happen to know Dept Head Nam Seong Joon? (using formal speech)
Who is asking? (using formal speech)
This is...(using formal speech)
Is this Joon Jae? (using informal speech)
You are. This is Chi Hyeon. (using informal speech)
How did you get my number? (using informal speech)
That's not what's important. Dept Head Nam is hurt greatly.
Your number is the last number that called him before the accident.
Where is Cheong?
- She went out.- To where?
I don't know, either.
How could you just let her leave?
When you don't know when and where that crazy bastard will pop up.
He's the one who had Dept Head Nam's cell phone.
Oh my, why do you direct your anger at me?
Seriously.
The phone is turned off. You'll get connected to the voicemail...
She's not picking up again.
Why does she go there so often?
- So, the guy said he has plans to like you.- Yes.
Then today's the Day 1.
Whoa. Good times.
The one and only day in your love life.
Of course, you'll have another one when you start dating another guy.
Is it so?
What you do from now on is very important if you want him to go head over heels for you.
Tell me. How to make him go head over heels for me.
So he won't ever get his head back up again.
That's the way I can stay here ever after without hurting
Are you Misery Chastain (from the movie Misery)?
And do you think I'd be like this had I known how to do that?
Look. There are three steps of love.
The first step is romantic love, the second is hot love, the third is...
"Dirty love."
Dirty (love) belongs to the experts only.
In my case, I'd go straight to the Dirty; but in your case, you should start with the Romantic.
How do you do the Romantic?
Honestly, that kind has all the bells and whistles for a show.
Having a tea, having meals, going to the movies, taking you home,
sending texts to check up on you, getting new sets of emojis,
going to see the stars, planing an event for you, playing push and pull, and confessing his feelings for you...
But all of this... is actually leading to dirty.
I'm curious about that... dirty.
Not yet for you.
That, if you go recklessly then it could really be the end after seeing something nasty.
You just shoot love guns.
Gun? That can cause death.
They die, they like it so much to death.
Look at that! Look at that; such young'uns.
He's all over shooting hearts gun and all.
Have you made nicknames for each other? Not your names but something only the two of you use.
We don't.
My first man called me "mong mong" (sound of dog barking).
But it ended after a dog fight.
Don't go towards animal names. The end isn't good.
What would ours be?
- Mermaid?- What mermaid? You need something that's in this world.
There's no mermaid in this world?
Why are you talking like (Hans Christian) Andersen has come back to life? Then would there be one?
Hey! Why aren't you answering your phone! What are you doing her-
- Say hi, she's my friend.- Oh, hello.
Ah...
Okay, let's go.
Hey, you come here everyday and play with this beggar?
I can hear it all, you know.
I'm sorry. Let's go.
I'm not a beggar!
I'm homeless! Street people!
I told you I'm not!
I'm not a beggar! I don't accept freebies!
Honey, Joon Jae is here.
Joon Jae who you took care more than your son.
You always said "Our Joon Jae, our Joon Jae."
Wake up please.
Ahjussi did not drink and drive.
Have you checked the blackbox?
There was no record from that day. It must have been broken.
Erasing records
It looks like traumatic cataract.
Seeing this here, there is a small wound.
Perhaps, did you rub your eye hard or was it poked?
No. None of that happened. These days my vision has been cloudy and darkened.
I thought it was because of aging.
subtitles ripped and synced by riri13
At any rate, I will prescribe anti-inflammatory and antibiotics.
Take your medicines well. If this gets worse then complications could arise.
Since there is no vein on cornea,
if it gets worse, there would be no other way than transplant.
Don't just take care of money but also take care of your health.
Since you're here, eat dinner before you go.
No, I have someone I have to visit. Next time.
Heo Joon Jae's family.
At least, it's only Miss Sim Cheong who calls me Joon Jae's family.
Did you come together with Joon Jae?
I said it last time, but I'm not breaking up with Heo Joon Jae.
I get it.
But you two must be close. Are you going to get married?
For now, we are still planning.
- What?- A lot of things.
But a family is looks like each other, warm and sweet.
What's wrong with you and Heo Joon Jae?
Father.
Oh, Chi Hyeon, you're here.
Yes, Father.
But, who?
Father, that...
Is this person Heo Joon Jae's family, too?
Are you someone who knows my Joon Jae?
- Ah, yes... the truth is...- Yeah.
Dad, after bathing, buy me some banana milk.
You should rub my back properly for me to buy you. You can't do it sloppily like last time.
Buy me. Buy me.
Okay, you punk.
Oh yeah!
What about Joon Jae? Isn't he coming?
He must have slept early. Let's just go by ourselves.
Let's just get him food later when he says he's hungry.
Dad.
Okay.
Chi Hyeon, let's go. What do you want to eat?
- Steak.- Okay, steak.
Dad, I'm sick.
What's wrong with your face?
What have you been doing? Why did you get hurt?
You're curious about me now?
So who told you to leave home and suffer?
You're doing good.
I did not leave the house but I left your side.
And I didn't suffer that much.
If you compare it being in that house, it's much better.
I feel like a burden has been lifted from me, too.
What did I do? Taking care of Chi Hyeon a bit more than you?
A son doesn't even know his father's heart?
Did you really think I like Chi Hyeon more than you so I took care of him more?
You are my son that's why I purposely--
You gave up.
On mom and me. And the time that we were together
you threw it all away. Without looking back.
Since you gave up and chose something else,
don't hold on to what you let go and just forget it.
You will know as you live.
Life doesn't go the way you want it to.
I'm now old
and it's time to settle the inheritance.
So, you should come back home.
No.
I will not receive anything.
Be it money or the way life is lived.
Or the way to throw people away, whatever it is.
I don't wish to receive anything from you.
I don't want to get involved with you. I don't want to meet you every again.
This punk.
But...
please be healthy.
Joon Jae.
You can leave, too, if you want to.
When I told you, "don't give up on what you have chosen,"
it's all a non-sense.
Where is such a thing?
I also... was a whole lot comfortable and good when you weren't here.
It hurts...
Are you okay?
I saw it on TV. Doing this got them better.
Now you're not as hot.
Who told you do this kind of thing?
Go up.
You say that, but you wish that I would stay next to you, right?
No matter how much you tell me to give up, "no, I don't want to. I won't give up."
Is what you wish I'd say, right?
Forget what you've given up. Don't have any lingering feelings.
No, I don't want to. I won't give up.
No matter what you say, I'll stay by yourself without giving up,
so don't get angry from not being able to say what you want and just say it.
What it is that you really want to say.
Okay.
I couldn't.
What I really wanted to say to my father.
I couldn't say any of it.
How difficult it was for me after leaving home.
I hated my father so much,
but because I thought he might look for me,
I waited for a while without changing my phone number.
But because in the end, he never called me once,
how lonely I felt...
I took the qualification exam on my own and went to college on my own,
and while living on my own
how much I missed him...
That I...
missed him so much...
Are you a little better?
Yeah.
- Earlier, that...  - Huh?
- That.  - About you crying?
Not so much crying but that there was a hint of tears.
Anyway, I took some cold medicine before falling sleep so I wasn't in the right state of mind.
I don't think there's any need to tell Nam Doo or Tae Oh about it.
Yeah, I forget well. Don't worry, Heo Joon Jae.
Okay. That's good then.
From now on, you tell me as much as you want. What you can't tell the others.
I'll listen to everything and forget it all. With everything in me.
- Really, will you forget everything?- Yeah.
Then...
Will you forget this, too?
♬ Enjoying unusually bright sunlight ♬
♬ Warm breeze is embracing us ♬
♬ In such a nice day, we are walking together ♬
What are you doing?
Oh, I like rice better than noodles. Cheong is the one who likes pasta.
Really? I'm making it because I wanted to have some.
You're doing that to eat it yourself?
I see.
Done.
♬ It's frustrating that you don't know my heart ♬
♬ I am in love with you, you fool ♬
♬ I am waiting for you ♬
♬ Because I am weak, my heart is pounding ♬
♬ My heart is pounding. Why don't you know that ♬
♬ My face is flushed ♬
♬ My heart is burning even more ♬
♬ Just the thought of confessing to you ♬
Wow. Wow, today you're Beauty Cheong. Beauty Cheong!
Wow, you're nearly a Seoulite, our Cheong.
♬ You don't know my heart ♬
Just because she's pretty.
- Really? I'm pretty?- Yea.
Hey, give me your phone.
Why?
What do you mean pretty?
You shouldn't take pictures like this without a direct permission.
- This isn't good manners.  - I'm okay.
- She says it's okay. - What do you mean it's okay?
Then how can she say that it's not okay with you standing right in front of her?
Is Cheong the kind of person to do that?
♬ Wispering that, "It's today." ♬
♬ My love confession that I've been withholding ♬
♬ I will deliver it to you ♬
Here.
Come and eat.
Okay. It looks delicious.
Joon Jae said he made it like that to eat it himself.
♬ I'm in love with you, you fool ♬
Wow, you look so so pretty, Cheong.
♬ Beautiful ♬
What is she?
How is she totally fine? I'm the only one who's feeling awkward.
♬ My heart keeps telling you ♬
♬ I love you. I love you. You are my girl. ♬
Joon Jae, I brought something you might want to know about.
What?
Let's go talk over there for a sec.
Why? You can't say it here?
I have something to explain while looking at the materials. Let's go.
Go ahead and eat first.
What are you doing?
Oh, just a second.
A few days ago, at the apartment redevelopment construction site in Dapsimni,
a Joseon era site was discovered.
And?
This was the site of Kim Dam Ryeong's family home.
While Professor Ha was telling us, I was so shocked that I came here to tell you first.
As soon as we restore the relics from the shipwreck, we were going to open up an exhibition.
If something more comes out of this excavation site,
I think it'll be huge.
You're saying this was Dam Ryeong's family home?
Yeah.
- So?- They say that
this was Kim Dam Ryeong's family home site.
Now only 19 days remain until the full moon of the last month.
What should I do?
What do I need to do for the person in my dreams to believe that my existence is real?
What do I have to do...
Over here! There's something here!
- Where?- This side!
Subtitles brought to you by The Blue Sea @ Viki
What did they tell you at the hospital?
That it's probably cataracts and that I should take my medicine.
Hurry, take your medicine, and go to bed. You look really tired today.
Really?
Aigoo.
Honey, since Deputy Director Nam is in that state and all,
shouldn't we hire a new person?
Do you want me to look into it?
Director Nam will probably be back on his feet soon...
Let's just wait a bit.
Okay, sure. Lie down.
Sure.
Omo, our Goo Bek (900) came again.
Yes, his nose seemed a little dry.
Oh Bek (500) is here, too!
- Oh, is his name Oh Bek (500)?-Yes.
- My dog's name is Goo Bek (900 in Korean). Because I spend 900 (man won) on him a month.- Omo.
I've already spent 8,500,000 won ($8500) on him this month.
What do you do to spend 9,000,00 won on him? We do everything we need to.
I even send him to Puppy Royal School. Isn't that right, Oh Bek?
Oh, my child does some after-school activities.
Ahh, after-school activities...
What kind?
On Monday, we teach him self-confidence. He just barks into the air.
On Friday, he has learns about English manners.
- I see, English manners?  - You know, we give orders a lot here.
Sit. Lie down. Wait. Eat. We're very commanding.
They say the English way is waiting.
Oh I see.
- I learned something today, thanks to you.- It's nothing.
- Goo Bek will now go in.- Ah yes.
I'll see you again.
To start off, I got in the good graces of our customer.
To the ladies of Seocho-dong Council, Daechi-dong, Apgujeong Department Store and Culture Center
there is no better gossiper, than a Gangnam broker - which I've hired this time.
There is a social meeting called, Sawolhoe, that Ahn Jin Joo attends religiously for gossip. He also put in a few words.
- Ladies, have you heard?  - What?
This really remarkable guy, Kim Jae, just came back to Korea.
While overseas, he started dabbling in international real estate, and turned himself into a wealthy man.
This person owns a 57-floor building in Dubai, and runs a golf course. I hear he often closes doors
to play golf with Mansour. He's on a whole new level.
- For real?- Are you talking about the Mansour we know?
Last year, L-construction madam wanted to invest and
brought her money bags and went all the way to Dubai, but returned after she was unable to even see him.
- Really? Did Madam Choi really do that?- Of course!
Anyway, this guy was busy in Singapore.
He was in the middle of a condominium building project,
but came back to Korea in a hurry because...
of his fiancé. She lives in Seoul, but he supposedly can't live without her.
- Who's the fiancé?- Is she a celebrity?
I don't know that far because it's been hidden well. Anyway, because he's so into her
that he's been buying out all the products in the Gangnam malls, everyday.
Now that I've laid out the bait like this, what should we do now?
All that's left is for Kim Jae and his fiancé to strut around the malls for a week.
Who'll play the fiancé?
Hey, Tae Oh!
Are you kidding? You're telling me to take him?
He's pretty, but this is stretching it too far, right?
See?
- What about Cheong?- Stop saying nonsense.
You've been super careful nowadays and taking Cheong everywhere you go.
- So when you're working, are you going to leave her by herself?- Ah, how can I take her there?
- Where am I going?- Gosh, you scared me.
Hey Cheong! Our Cheong.
Would you listen to me for a moment?
You like dramas, right?
The truth is, the people in the TV aren't small people...
I know. They're in a studio. It's a drama.
So you know?
- Our Cheong is surprisingly smart.
Our Cheong? Our?
I'm just saying she's smart.
So, we're going to be filming something like a drama.
Joon Jae's role in this drama is a rich, cool man.
General manager? Director?
- All the cool guys in dramas play those kinds of roles- Exactly like that!
And our Cheong's role is his fiancé. They're going to get married!
I like it.
Right, you like it, right? See? She likes it, huh?
Cheong, when you're there, there are just three things that you must not do.
Don't talk.
Don't laugh.
Don't eat.
- That's going to be a bit difficult.- I'll buy you something more delicious afterwards.
Specifically what?
You like sweet things. Ice cream? Cake?
- That plus...-Plus?-Plus?
Sweet and sour pork.
Deal.
Me too.
Our Cheong is a real Seoulite now.
Let's go! To use money!
This, this, and this.
What else, honey?
The 'La (Piazetta) Di Capri' one, too.
- Oh just buy it all.- Give us all of it.
The end?
Just give the whole thing with hangers.
Okay this one. Okay this one, too!
Please wrap all the jewels.
Why can't I use the VVIP room, right now? You said you thought I could, earlier.
I apologize. We have a guest who made a reservation just a while ago.
I am also a guest who made a reservation just a while ago. Have I been pushed back? Why?
I'm a White Magnolia Club member!
I've seen this woman before.
What is this?
- Who is it?- Omo! You're here.
Our Honey, doesn't ever wear the same pair of shoes twice. We end up having to come back frequently.
Ah, it's not like I can carry you around everywhere. Honey, do your feet hurt?
Seoul is so uncomfortable.The buildings are too close by that we can ride on our private jet, unlike Dubai.
Dubai? Dubai?
Dubai?!
Would you check it all? Hurry up. Hurry up!
Goo Bek's dad?
Goo Bek's dad!
Oh, isn't it Oh Bek's mother?
- Oh yes. It's good to see you!- It's good to see you, too!
The people who just came...
Did you come with them?
Ah, yes. I run an investment company, and some VIP guests came from abroad.
Ahh. The man who just went inside?
Yes, well then.
Oh wait! Did that person, perhaps,
Did he come from Dubai?
Why?
Well, in Dubai, he has a 57-story building
and a like-a golfing course and like being friends with Mansour
and like like, what was his name again?
Kim Jae, and that fiancé he's so in love with.
Wait, where did you hear those things from?
I knew it.
If you tell anyone else, things will get messy around here so I'm telling you, you can't tell anyone--ever.
Ah, yes, yes. Yes.
Darling, how do you like it?
I'm hungry.
Mhm, I see. Great comment, as expected from you.
I want to eat spicy rice cakes.
You are always __________. And I like that about you.
And soondae. (blood sausage)
Your standards are unmatched as always, alright, let's buy that too then.
Hurry up. Take this.
Alright, no problem.
Wait. Wait a minute.
Ah, yes. Can I ask you a favor?
Yes, what is it?
The thing is, do you think you could arrange a meal with us and them?
Oh, I'm actually in the position of tending to them as well so for me to make requests and such is a bit--
We're actually very interested in investments too!
I just want to maybe try to put in a word or two. What do you think? Impossible?
The truth is, our CEO Kim has been away from Korea for so long
he did mention that he wanted to eat home cooked Korean food.
But I'm still not married so--
Home cooked food! Then our house is a must, the food at our place is killer!
At our house...we have the female Baek Jong Won. (famous restaurant entrepreneur in Korea)
Ah.
So?
He said he'll mention it to them.
Honey, if we can get this done, then we've hit the jackpot!
It's awesome. Totally awesome.
I mean, just as when things were stared to work out, it gets completely solved! Just like that! Don't you think?
Ahjumma! Please take good care of us!
I'll just be doing as I always do.
Who is it?
Don't be surprised.
They said he's so close to Mansour, they play golf together.
Totally awesome.
You don't think he's a con artist?
What do you mean?
I mean, I get the feeling he's a con artist just by listening to you.
Is that so?
What do you mean? I even called Madam Choi of L-construction, and
I even confirmed that she went to Dubai last year only to get rejected!
Right. Then it's for sure.
You're not going to help us, at the very least, don't ruin it for us.
Even if we got him millions of dollars right now, he wouldn't spare a glance!
Of course he won't.
And that's what you'd expect from a typical Ponzi scheme.
He pulls in investors as if he could afford everything
but he doesn't let just anyone in, which makes you all the more ambitious to get in, or something like that.
Then, when we invite him over to eat,
Auntie, you can stay and see him with us, that's what we can do.
Yeah, you can eat with us.
Whatever.
Hello? Yeah, hold on.
Really? Where is it right now?
Wow, our Cheong did really well today.
I did well?
Yeah! What--You were just like a secret agent! Right, Joon Jae?
Well, she was whatever--I told you before, this kid's smart.
When you teach her one thing, she catches on real fast!
What is this, PTA? Are you bragging about your kid right now?
I'm just saying.
I had fun today too. Because I could help Heo Joon Jae with his good deeds.
But Heo Joon Jae, did you know? The man in charge of that doll picking machine, he's a con artist.
Huh?
Who said that?
I kept trying to pull one but I couldn't get any so I asked around
and people told me he's a con artist. Sick bastard.
Con artist. Right. Con artists are definitely sick bastards, right?
But! Con artists aren't always bad people.
Sometimes, there are just sick bastards who con even sicker bastards.
Still, they're lying to people.
Cheong, you've never done that? Not once lied to people?
You don't have any secrets you can't tell us?
I feel like you do.
Just stop! Why're you cornering her like that!
What the--Is this really a PTA meeting?
Tae Oh, isn't this weird!? He's just completely sticking up for her!
Between the two of you, is there a change in your relationship or something?
- No.- Yes.
What?! What's the answer?! You said yes and no!? What's the right answer!?
Just be quiet! Don't chat in my car.
If you're going to chat then get off!
Oh, Si Ah. Really?
I'll be right there.
Let me out. I have to go somewhere.
You are really going to get out? Where are you going?
Si Ah said she has something to show me.
I haven't seen it yet, either. But the underclassman that excavated it
says this one's really special.
Typically, porcelains or paintings and calligraphic works excavated from a house
cannot be preserved in a good condition.
But this one, it was buried in a completely sealed box.
Buried?
Yeah. As if, someone was asking for it to be found in the future.
- Wait a minute.- Hm?
Can I look by myself for a minute?
Ah, well, sure.
Subtitles brought to you by The Blue Sea @ Viki
Epilogue
From now and to the full moon of the last month of the year, there remains 19 days.
What shall I do? What must I do
for the person in my dream to believe me?
What must I do.
♬ Being under the same sky with you ♬
I ask that you be meticulous.
For it is a piece that must be treasured for a long time.
Yes sir.
♬ If we can walk as far as the blue sea's horizon ♬
♬ I won't let go of your hand. ♬
♬ Being under the same sky with you ♬