(THE FOLLOWING CONTENT MAY NOT BE SUITABLE FOR VIEWERS UNDER 15.)
(EPISODE 11)
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by VIU
Do you want me to send you the pictures I took?
When did you take them? While I wasn't looking?
I took pictures of the scenery.
The calm ocean, the waves, the sunset.
Fine. Send them.
They say one day can equal a lifetime.
That's what yesterday was to me. Thank you.
You must've felt relieved, thinking it was over.
Since you're thanking me,
I feel like a child who took her parent on a vacation.
Then...
can you exchange your life up to now for yesterday?
No way.
It was hard learning how to knead and make dumplings.
The bus is here.
I didn't say something in case it would ruin the trip.
I knew from how you looked depressed now and then.
I'll be lying from now on.
That's why you can't be with me.
I'll just focus on protecting your land.
I'll see you in court.
Once tomorrow's trial is over, you're free.
Only you and Hong Na Ri may file to annul the marriage.
That's why we had to hold you here. Don't be too angry.
Your niece just needs to testify.
You seem to be in a good mood since we're being nice.
(COURT HOUSE)
- Do you feel okay?
- Yes.
Nan Gil seems to have faith you'll stand on his side.
- I guess the goodbye trip was worthwhile.
- No.
I agreed to testify for my uncle.
He isn't my stepdad anymore.
Let me ask as a neighborhood friend.
When did you start liking Nan Gil?
Friends ask these things all the time.
Let's go in.
Think about your feelings for Nan Gil.
Are you confused because of the void your mom left?
If you can't even tell when it started, let it go.
Please testify for yourself,
and not for your uncle.
I want to know when it started too.
He came into my heart one day and keeps growing.
Don't you understand how that feels?
Your Honor, Shin Jung Im and Ko Nan Gil's marriage...
lacked mutual consent of the parties...
which is required in Civil Code section 815,
and thus, their marriage is void.
This is the marriage license that Ko Nan Gil and...
Shin Jung Im filled out together with mutual consent.
It fails to qualify for annulment.
Your Honor, Shin Jung Im's brother, Shin Jung Nam,
took that very picture.
We'd like to call him to testify.
Why are you claiming the marriage is void?
My sister and I were deceived.
Back then, we didn't know Nan Gil worked for a lender.
He showed us a forged document...
and said our land was being held as collateral.
He said they must get married in order to protect it.
That was why my sister married him. She was deceived.
Objection.
Shin Jung Im knew Ko Nan Gil for many years...
and knew what kind of work he was doing.
We call Kim Wan Shik, who works at the institution...
where Ko Nan Gil worked, to the stand.
Your Honor, he is unrelated to this case.
Objection denied.
What is your relationship with Ko Nan Gil?
We were once brothers and we worked together.
You worked together for a loan shark, correct?
What kind of person is Ko Nan Gil?
He was called "the legendary Ko Nan Gil".
Everyone in the industry feared him. He was evil.
He'd collect 10 times the principal...
without batting an eye.
He used violence, drafted unfair contracts,
and got them to sign them.
He boasted about the fact that he was an ex-con.
You'll hear everything about me at the trial.
Should I not go, then?
No. Go and listen to it all.
I'm the disease.
It was created because of my dark,
damp, and smelly past.
The witness is making unsubstantiated statements...
about my client that are irrelevant to the case.
Ko Nan Gil went to prison to take responsibility...
for his company's insolvency as the person in charge.
It is unrelated to violence. He is committing perjury.
Your Honor, I will submit a police record...
of the investigation of Ko Nan Gil...
for threatening Shin Jung Nam.
Objection. He was found not culpable.
Your Honor, the biggest victim of this marriage con...
is here today.
I'd like to call Hong Na Ri, Shin Jung Im's daughter,
to the stand.
Ms. Hong Na Ri.
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by VIU
There she goes.
- Hey. Hey.
- Hey, Duk Shim.
Get over here. I said to get over here.
Nice camera. Let me see that.
Let me play with it.
Why those punks.
- Give me your camera.
- No.
How much could it cost?
Infinite has a concert coming up.
I just want to take some pictures. I'll return it.
We'll return it. Hand it over.
Duk Shim.
My sister says she's sorry.
We didn't know your family's lawyer would be so tough.
My sister was wrong for harassing you...
and taking your things,
but if you press charges like that,
what will happen to my poor sister's future?
What are you doing?
I was pretending I had...
a younger sibling like them.
Duk Shim. I called to ask you something.
Why didn't you pick up?
Ms. Hong Na Ri.
Did your mother...
ever tell you about Ko Nan Gil?
No.
Did your mother ever tell you that she got married...
and transferred her land and restaurant?
No.
Did you hear about your father's debt?
Do you think...
this marriage is void?
No.
Are you out of your mind?
You agreed to say what we wanted.
- Counsel.
- Do you think your uncle will be safe?
What are you doing? This is a trial.
If you have no more questions,
respondent's counsel, please ask your questions.
What is your relationship with Ko Nan Gil?
He's my stepfather.
Snake. Snake. Snake!
Over there!
What could it be made of?
For me, I have many words that mean "Hong Na Ri".
Tell me what means "Hong Na Ri".
Pretending it doesn't hurt to get hit by a slingshot.
Reading while walking.
Chasing after the tofu vendor's bell.
Blowing on a dandelion.
Dancing with butterflies.
When my mother was struggling,
he was by her side.
After I lost my mother, he stayed by my side.
He is my only family.
You did good, Na Ri.
Stop it!
What? What is it now?
I said I need to ask you something.
Tell me about the woman...
who stabbed Duk Bong in the back.
You came all the way here to ask that?
You must have nothing better to do.
Do I look like I have nothing to do?
My life is crazy busy.
Whom do I resemble?
You're so annoying.
You resemble Duk Bong's first love.
I see.
Do I look that much like her?
They dated for a super long time,
but the families got into a feud...
and Duk Bong was pathetically stabbed in the back.
A family feud?
After that, he quit practicing law...
and holed up here ever since.
But...
why do you talk about your brother like a stranger?
Whatever! That's my style.
Anyway, dream on.
He must find your face super annoying.
And he likes Na Ri.
You don't know the power of the first love.
Should I put my hair up from now on?
Here comes the judge. All rise.
Please be seated.
I will render my decision.
It is difficult to conclude that Shin Jung Im...
and Ko Nan Gil registered their marriage...
without mutual consent.
Thus, Shin Jung Nam's request is denied.
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by VIU
Na Ri left before the judgment. She's waiting outside.
Aren't you going to thank me?
Should I be thanking you?
(COURT HOUSE)
Sir.
We lost. I'm sorry.
Drag Shin Jung Nam over here right now.
Make sure Hong Na Ri sees you do it.
Uncle.
Let go of him.
You're the one threatening and holding hostage.
Let my uncle go.
Let him go.
Go.
Your niece says we're threatening you...
and holding you hostage.
Did you see that? He's going voluntarily.
Thank you.
No need. I'm protecting my land.
You're wise after all.
And it's my land, so I'll make the decision.
I can't leave Uncle like that.
I'll take care of your uncle.
We've legally confirmed our relationship.
Take care.
I want us to be an average couple that dates,
loves, and plans to get married.
This trip is the beginning.
(SAEMAEUM ORPHANAGE FIRE)
The year there was a fire at the orphanage,
my grandfather gave land to 15-year-old Shin Jung Eum.
What would a 15-year-old know? It was the parents.
What I'm sure of...
is that there's something behind the land,
Na Ri's family, and mine.
But Na Ri and I didn't know about the land.
That means the two families are hiding something.
Do you think I should let Na Ri know?
Say something.
Let's say I finished my part with this.
We'll be much busier once the show airs.
We'll consider it our debut and double the volume.
What about our salary?
He's getting more and more energetic.
That ambitious man.
Duk Bong.
Have you talked to Na Ri recently?
Her phone is off, right?
Everyone is worried.
She didn't come to her farewell party either.
Na Ri isn't the type to flake on a promise.
Do you know her home address?
Should I look into it?
Hello?
I should've talked to him in person.
What am I thinking?
- Thank you.
- Have a nice day.
Thank you.
Why are you back?
Are you in touch with Na Ri?
I am not.
I hear her phone's off. No one can reach her.
She quit her job and is all alone now.
Someone should check to see if she's alive.
Do you know her address in Seoul?
I don't know the address, but... Wait right here.
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by VIU
We've legally confirmed our relationship.
Take care.
(KIM SUNG KYU, NAN YOUNG YI, RAN SOOK)
I have her friend's number. Call her and ask.
Here's her number.
How cute. Where are you going?
Did you fall? It's okay.
You're hungry?
Where are you going? Are you looking for Mommy?
Do you miss your mommy?
Where are you going?
It's okay. You're so cute.
You're so cute. Did you fall? It's okay.
Let's knead dough.
Na Ri! Open up!
Na Ri! Na Ri!
What's going on? Why is your phone off?
I heard you flaked on all your plans.
How did you know?
Duk Bong called me.
How did he get your number?
How do I know? He called and asked for your address,
so I said I'd come myself.
It would've been a disaster if he had come.
You look terrible.
What's wrong with your place?
I'm so glad you're here.
Let go. You're dusty.
Air out the place. Seriously.
How did you come? You must be busy with your baby.
Seriously.
I've never seen you like this before.
We must have known each other for way too long.
What have you been doing with your phone off?
Did you request time off to become a lonely hermit?
Hey. What's wrong?
Na Ri.
What's wrong?
- Hello?
- I spoke with Na Ri.
- I see.
- She sounded okay.
Or maybe she was pretending.
Thank you for letting me know.
Don't you feel better, getting out of the house?
Not particularly.
Duk Bong calls every day to ask about you.
Why don't you see him?
I think I was meant to drive.
Is it because of the dumpling punk?
Don't call my stepdad a punk.
Stepdad?
(EARLY WINTER HURRICANE APPROACHING)
It's almost winter. Why is a hurricane coming?
We won't have any customers at the cafe tonight.
Wouldn't they want a warm cafe if it's cold out?
When it's rainy and windy,
they walk quickly to their cozy homes.
I see. When it's rainy and windy, they go home.
These are strawberry flowers.
Those are pumpkin flowers.
Aren't they prettier than roses?
These pretty and small flowers become the fruit.
What? Why are you doing that to my lettuce?
This is a weed.
(HONG DUMPLINGS)
Oh no.
Get up. You need to see a doctor.
It's been two days already.
What are you doing in here?
Who's at the restaurant?
This is no way to run a business.
If you keep this up,
I'll call your daughter.
Don't you dare do anything.
Okay.
Give me some water.
You'll get an ulcer...
if you take medicine on an empty stomach.
Here.
Leave.
Get to work.
How is he?
I think he'll be in bed for at least 10 days.
He took his medicine,
so let's steal his phone and call his daughter.
Robot. That's right.
Your brother must have her number.
Are you telling me to call her?
We need to save his life.
She's no doctor.
Give me Na Ri's number.
Is Na Ri your friend?
Please give me Na Ri's number.
(CALL HISTORY. MOM, MS. KWON, TEACHER, DUK BONG)
Duk Bong?
Why are you going through my phone?
How do you not have a single friend to call?
Why do you want Na Ri's number?
Nan Gil is very sick.
- So?
- They told me to get Na Ri's number.
Why are they doing that to me?
Give it to me.
(DUK BONG)
Hi, my neighborhood friend.
You're chipper.
- Who is this?
- This is Duk Shim.
Why are you using your brother's phone?
Where's the apology letter?
That's not important right now.
Nan Gil is sick. He's dying.
No, he may already be dead!
Seriously.
Enjoy.
- Thank you.
- Sure.
It's so cold.
Stay here, okay?
Wait!
- How's Nan Gil?
- He's still in bed.
Is it really a cold?
Remember it stormed a few days ago?
Does radiation get out if the green house tears?
He gave his body to protect the green house.
He was totally soaked. When we opened the restaurant,
he crawled home.
This is abuse. Self-abuse.
Aren't you going to see him?
He's young. He's big.
He won't die from a cold.
What? This isn't right.
Darn it.
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by VIU
You can do it, Hong Na Ri.
He is still your stepdad.
Please lie back down.
Your fever came down,
but you should still go see a doctor.
I'm fine now.
I don't need a doctor.
I'm hungry. That means I'm fine.
Whatever you want.
You look terrible, Stepdad.
I shouldn't argue with a sick person,
but didn't you say you were too healthy...
that you didn't remember when you last caught a cold?
You may catch my cold, so get out.
I'll air out my room,
- clean up, and come out.
- I'll leave after...
I see you finish your porridge and take your medicine.
Don't look so touched.
Duk Shim brought the porridge from her house...
and the medicine is from the pharmacy.
All I did was set the table.
If you plan to stare at me like that, please leave.
I can't eat.
So? Did you protect our green house...
from the wind and rain?
No. It collapsed.
It's done for until spring.
You couldn't even protect it,
but you were sick in bed for three days.
I thought you were good at protecting anything.
I'm disappointed.
It's foolish to fight against nature.
In movies, everything works out...
if the main character does it.
Reality is cruel.
Even in movies, it ends with their fearing nature.
You must be well, seeing how you're arguing with me.
Arguing with you?
Watch how you speak to me.
I'm sorry for being rude.
Please finish the porridge,
take your medicine, and feel better.
Thank you.
I don't know who called,
but you don't need to come because of a cold.
I'll take care of it, Stepdad.
And don't turn off your phone when you're alone.
Everyone was worried.
Everyone was worried,
but you didn't feel the need to call yourself.
You had Duk Bong do it instead.
I'll be back soon, Stepdad.
Good job, Na Ri.
- Please bring them to the second floor.
- Okay.
Is the daughter moving in?
Do I need to serve the boss' daughter too, now?
(SAEMAEUM ORPHANAGE FIRE)
(CHEMICAL WASTE INCINERATION PLANT EXPLOSION)
Sir, you have a call.
Okay.
Father, let's follow my blueprint.
I'm not a charity.
We won't make it a park when it can be buildings.
Do you even know what Grandpa did to the land?
"The dead doesn't talk."
Don't you know the famous saying?
He built an orphanage on explosives. That's murder!
I won't touch that land.
Forget it if that's what you want to do.
Family should protect each other.
I'm so sick of you and our family.
What is it?
You must have something to say.
Na Ri is here with her stuff.
What is that?
Take this to her.
I told you to study. Why do you keep doing this?
Boss.
We realized this time around that you're not needed.
We did all this by ourselves.
Also, your daughter just moved here.
He didn't know?
I guess you're feeling better now.
I heard you moved here.
This is our home. I have a room here. I'm jobless.
There is no reason for me to pay rent in Seoul.
Don't sigh, or you'll have something to sigh about.
How long do you plan on staying?
A year.
See me after work. You need to sign an agreement.
- What agreement?
- After that trial, I like law.
I don't want you to be around me,
so we should agree on spaces each will be using.
Bring anything you'd like to add on paper.
Go ahead. I'm going to work.
I was just dropping by on my way to Seoul.
You can drop by more often.
Hey, Duk Bong is here.
What did he say?
It's been a while and I even brought you this.
How can you greet me like that?
Since I brought it, take it.
Great. Have you been well?
That's half-hearted.
Your stepfather asked me to visit more often.
I'm going to Seoul. I'll call you on my way back.
- What?
- Your stepfather told me...
to drop by more often.
- Wan Shik.
- Yes.
How far will you go for me?
I can do anything you ask me.
There is something I need you to do.
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by VIU
You must be out of your mind to come here.
I was under investigation because of you...
and was called in by prosecutors.
It's so that you feel uncomfortable.
You've been tainted. Now you can even lie.
Have you gone mad after confirming...
Hong Sung Kyu's death?
If you're trying to frame me for murder, I'll warn you.
I'll tell the police everything.
Why would your father frame you?
You're...
more afraid of Na Ri finding out instead of the police.
If you want to be treated like a father,
don't come threatening me with fake documents.
We need to make one more stop.
(HYUN'S ALTERATIONS)
What is it?
We asked her about a man who died five years ago.
Why wasn't she curious who we were?
Gosh, it's cold.
Excuse me.
What is it? Why are you back?
Did you tell anyone that I came here?
I didn't. I didn't say anything.
I live here because I don't want to move.
The man who died five years ago...
made a mess everywhere.
So many strange people show up to me.
I'm sorry, but did you check for yourself?
I paid with my own money for his funeral.
Stop bothering me, and leave. Go.
How did Nan Gil know about that club?
He doesn't meet other people.
Who's helping him?
First, capture these men and see what you can get.
If he keeps up, the people around him will get hurt.
I understand.
He should know he's putting Na Ri in danger.
He'll run to us if his boys are captured.
I'll go to the dumpling restaurant.
I'm sure we'll find something.
These days,
it looks like you're dying to get at Nan Gil.
You used to be...
scared to death of him.
- Hey, how are you?
- Long time no see.
- This is my partner.
- Hello.
Have fun.
- Hey, it's been a while.
- How are you?
- Is she your girlfriend?
- Hello.
- No. She's my partner.
- She's not?
- Hello. She's pretty.
- Hello.
I see.
Hey.
Are you here?
See you again.
- Are you here?
- Hello.
Hello.
Duk Bong is introducing her to everyone.
- She looks like her, right?
- Who?
Duk Bong's ex-fiancee.
You're right.
Come with me for a minute.
One moment.
Bring your coat.
I have a partner. Why should I follow you out?
Can't you see that people are talking?
I'm fast with these things, and I didn't feel it.
I'm talking about me, not you.
I'm being made a fool!
Why are you yelling at me?
I came here with my partner. I didn't know you'd come.
You didn't know?
Well, I did. But it doesn't matter to me.
I hate it when other people talk about me.
Are you talking about your ex-fiancee?
If you got engaged then broke up,
just consider it a gossip for your friends and ignore.
They think it's fun because you get upset.
If she looks like me and I'm here...
with you like this, they'll talk more.
Who says you look like her?
You're getting riled up just talking about her.
I guess you didn't get over it yet.
Yeo Joo.
You and Na Ri are completely different.
How are we different?
What you see in Na Ri is everything.
She never hides anything.
However, she's difficult.
On the other hand,
I don't know what you're thinking.
However, you're easy.
If you're going to talk nonsense,
don't ruin my day and just leave.
- Gosh.
- Time to go home.
- See you tomorrow.
- Bye.
- Bye, Boss.
- Good job today.
Come to check the agreement.
(FROM NA RI, COME TO CHECK THE AGREEMENT!)
Hey, let's go out for a team dinner.
Both of us can't drink.
You don't have to drink.
Let's get in the car. It's cold.
- Gosh.
- Let's go.
Okay.
- Did you eat dinner?
- Yes.
There's enough food in the fridge.
You look like you lost weight.
Make sure to eat well.
I'll take care of it.
Read this.
(AGREEMENT)
(BACK DOOR MUST BE LOCKED. PRIVACY MUST BE GUARANTEED.)
(INFORM EACH OTHER WHEN SICK. DON'T TALK ABOUT MOM.)
I can't lock the back door. I have to use the tap.
Our staff need to use the door too.
I have to manage the yard and the shed.
Use the front door.
This is my property.
I'll manage the yard and the shed.
You? Manage?
You're like a cat just making troubles.
I won't allow it.
I've never heard anyone call me a cat.
I'll always be on time for breakfast, so don't worry.
What is this about privacy?
I might sleep during the day and get up at night.
I might date the man you're pushing me to.
You can go on dates,
but you can't switch days and nights.
You have to eat breakfast with me. That's family.
You're impossible. Why can't you cooperate?
Don't be so childish.
Why did you come if you'd feel uncomfortable?
If you call this our house, why did you make this?
Don't you know why?
Why do you think I made it?
What do you want to eat? Chicken feet? Chicken?
Barbecued chicken?
Let's just go in anywhere.
No, let's eat raw fish.
Just follow me. Tonight's on me.
Meat?
Yong Kyu, Joon, and Hani.
Who are you? What is this?
What is this?
- Gosh.
- Hey.
Gosh.
Go.
Go. Go.
- Run!
- Let's go!
You won't go anywhere.
- Come here.
- Punk.
- Bring it.
- What are you doing?
Joon, let's bring it down.
Don't make me laugh. Bring it.
- Hey.
No, don't do it. Let's go.
We can report to the police.
- Let go. Let go.
- Come here.
Let go. Let go.
Hani. Hani!
Joon.
I came here for myself.
I'm going to be selfish.
I tried acting like nothing happened,
but I was drained out that I couldn't even move.
That's why I decided to just face it.
If I do that, I'll be able to accept our relationship.
All right. Let's do that.
I know you're always wise.
No.
I'm far from being wise.
You should rest for today. You just moved.
You must be tired.
I have to knead dough.
You need a better phrase.
I remembered about my dad.
I think we went on a plane...
to visit my grandma's house.
How did the shooting go?
Did you get to talk about finding my dad?
I did.
Good night.
All right. Good luck with kneading.
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by VIU
Help.
Gosh. My goodness.
Gosh.
Boss. I have to call Boss.
Gangster Boss...
I knew this day would come.
Gosh.
What is it?
Boss, Joon and Hani were taken away.
I think it was those guys from before.
Ko Nan Gil, what are you hiding?
Boss.
- Where are they?
- Follow me.
Hello?
I'm glad you moved here.
I can call you at this hour like this.
I'm almost back in town.
We can even meet up in front of your door.
It's too late.
Just come out for a minute.
I've been having a bad day.
Not as a man and a woman,
but as friends.
You can help counsel me.
All right.
Thank you.
I knew it. He's not kneading dough.
He always says he has to, but he never does it.
I'm going out.
Do I have to report even things like this?
No, they're gone.
Those jerks must have kidnapped the two.
Boss, I knew this day would come.
I didn't call the police...
because it seemed like you were avoiding them.
Look at how loyal I am.
Where did they go?
(KO NAN GIL)
Where are you going? Where are you going?
Tell me.
(KO NAN GIL)
Yes, Nan Gil.
What have you done to my staff?
Na Ri is in front of me right now.
Boss! Boss! Gosh...
Boss.
(JOON)
Where are you, Joon?
Where should I take you to?
(SWEET STRANGER AND ME)
Just give her up.
At least for me, she's the only one I look at.
I wish I could do that too.
But this is all I can do for her.
I don't know much about you. I want to know more.
Give me an hour a day. Let's get to know each other.
Nan Gil is responsible for your father's death.
He killed your father.
It's certain my dad died.
I heard that you killed him and checked it yourself.
They said you knew everything already.
I don't trust everything they say,
but I don't get why you hid it from me.
I made him die.
I made your father die.