(The following content may not be suitable for viewers under 15.)
(Viewer discretion is advised.)
(Episode 14)
It's healing nicely.
Thanks for visiting my dad...
when you're not even well.
Let me see the pictures from tonight.
What is this?
Who's this ugly thing?
What? She's pretty.
I look at those pictures whenever I miss her.
No. Delete them. Let's delete them.
Give it to me.
No way.
Let's start as a normal couple...
who can do anything.
Let's do that.
Let's start as a normal couple now.
I'm sorry it took so long to get here.
You know that a normal man...
won't disappear in the middle of the night...
and then come home hurt, right?
That's all I need.
Is that all you need?
The only thing I'm good at is making dumplings.
Is that okay with you?
You're good at a lot of things.
You take good care of the property.
Sometimes, I think you like it more than me.
I knew that dating could be childish,
but I didn't think you'd be jealous of the property.
There's more. You're good at being a stepdad.
I'm pretty good at that, aren't I?
What are these pictures? When did you take them?
It was taken when you came in like a thief.
(The password is incorrect.)
I don't think we can fist fight.
Ko Nan Gil,
don't speak so rudely to me again.
It's cold. Go in.
I want to watch you go in.
I'm going to watch you go in.
Then let's just keep standing here.
You're so childish.
Welcome back to the childish world.
Who is that?
That looks like the CEO of Da Da.
It's not.
Go in. It's cold. I'll go and see.
Okay.
Go inside. I'll go soon.
I waited for a few days...
expecting you to call me.
What are you going to do with the ledger?
I know you fear Chairman Kwon more than prosecutors.
Do you think you can touch Chairman Kwon?
I never intended on doing anything to either of you.
You're the one that pushed me first.
I can't...
think straight right now.
Must I kill you?
Do you think I'll leave Na Ri alone?
Please stop.
Bring me the ledger by tomorrow evening with Wan Shik.
You and Wan Shik should think about...
who will lose more.
(Greenland)
What?
Don't tell Mom I had a hard time at the house.
Okay.
- Did Yeo Joo leave? - Don't bring up her name.
She's...
annoying.
First, write down...
what you like about Na Ri, one by one.
Just write down whatever comes to mind.
I like you because you look good in a suit.
You speak rudely, but I like that you're confident.
I like that you work hard though you're rich enough.
I like you because you grew up...
pretty well compared to your friends.
What are you doing?
I like that you're sometimes a pushover.
I said, what are you doing?
I'm giving you examples.
Try writing it down when you get home.
- Why would I do that? - I'm know you would.
Men in love are usually fools.
If you write it down, show it to me.
I'm cold. Open the door.
I won't write it.
- Yes. - Let's meet.
Are you listening to me?
Have you decided?
I haven't decided anything.
Just come here right now.
Give me your address.
Lawyer Kim.
If I tell you the address,
you'll let my family go, right?
You know that a normal man...
won't disappear in the middle of the night...
and then come home hurt, right?
That's all I need.
(The punk who lives in my house)
What about Father?
You should turn yourself in before he's arrested.
I betrayed him because I didn't want to go to jail.
I'm going to keep on running.
When I run out of money, I'll bother you for some.
All right.
I'll let you rob me as your birthday present.
Stop talking about birthdays all the time.
You started it. Don't you remember?
We don't know our parents or our birthdays,
but there's one good thing about it.
Every day of the year could be our birthdays.
I only said it to get money from a softie like you.
Ever since I heard that from you, I wonder...
if it's my birthday every day.
Forget it.
Turn yourself in.
- I'll help you when you're out. - Help with what?
Do you expect me to make dumplings like you?
Hey, get him. Stop right there.
Get in the back.
Stop.
Hey.
Stop there!
Don't you get it?
Your underlings ended up going to Mr. Bae.
You don't have anyone on your side.
Turn yourself in. I'll help you when you're out.
Nan Gil.
I need the ledger you took.
(Greenland)
(Wan Shik)
Let's meet.
I have the ledger Nan Gil took.
Guarantee my safety and I'll return it.
Good. I'm glad you made the right decision.
Yes, I'll be there.
Don't bring the boys and come alone.
I'm getting scared with no one to trust.
All right. I'll see you there.
Why did he suddenly change his mind?
I'm not sure.
Now that he has no one on his side...
and that he's in big trouble,
I'm sure he couldn't find a solution.
I didn't expect you to show up alone after all.
Where's the ledger?
Guarantee my safety first.
You really want to die, don't you?
What?
You should have learned something by now...
after both your sons have turned their back on you.
What?
- Arrest them! - What is going on?
Let me go!
Let go!
Do you really think this is the end?
I'll make sure I find you wherever you hide.
Let's go.
Mr. Kim Wan Shik, come with me.
How did you spend your time in prison?
I earned two brothers...
and learned how to make dumplings.
You and those dumplings.
Where you here all night?
At least, you didn't get hurt this time.
I meant to tell you before leaving,
but I couldn't.
No, I didn't tell you since I didn't want to worry you.
A normal girl would have called and asked.
But I didn't.
I was worried it would put you in more danger.
I'm surprised I was even thinking of it.
You said things were okay.
Do you know what came to my mind?
"What if you get hurt again when you're still healing?"
"He might even get himself killed this time"
Everything's settled now. I promise you.
Wan Shik turned himself in and Mr. Bae got arrested.
It's all done now.
Do you really expect me to believe you?
You want me to believe you and let it slide?
I don't know what to do anymore.
I was thinking where we should go for our first trip.
Now that's what I consider normal.
Where's your daughter?
No, I mean your girlfriend.
I mean the second CEO. Isn't she eating breakfast?
Eat quietly. She stayed up all night.
Hurry up and eat! Don't slack off!
Good morning!
Oh, my! Omelets for breakfast!
Have a seat. I'll hurry up and make you one.
Enjoy your breakfast and have a great day.
Hurry up and eat.
She's angry at me, but I don't know what to do.
Never mind. Why am I asking you this?
We wouldn't know, but this might help.
"I made a mistake."
"My girlfriend is mad at me."
"What should I do?"
Let's see what we have here.
Look. He's not the only one who's suffering.
Guys with the same concern gave solutions.
It says, "Give her a hug and apologize."
I'm sorry
No, she might slap you.
Let's try finding another one.
How about trying to be funny and acting charming?
- Charm? - Act charming?
Act charming...
- No. - I tried picturing it.
I don't think this will work either.
If you get this wrong, you might get slapped twice.
This is it. This is the answer.
"Just listen to what she has to say."
Good luck!
If you have something to say, say it.
Why are you looking at me like that? You're scaring me.
Did you tell Hong Na Ri and Ko Nan Gil...
how the property got on fire?
They're doing everything to protect that property.
I think it's right that you tell them what happened.
- Well... - If you can't,
should I tell them?
Ms. Kwon, I'm going to let Na Ri keep the land.
The family has been eager to build a resort there.
Do you think your father will let you do that?
I'm going to make sure it happens.
But the accident will remain as secret to them both.
Being my father's son,
I'm naturally neither honest nor righteous.
Ms. Kwon,
have some pity on me.
I really have feelings for Na Ri.
It doesn't harm to hide shame from someone you like.
My friends' lives were taken for no reason,
but all you feel is a bit of shame?
I'm calling to confirm your leave of absence meeting.
Yes, I'm available then.
I'll see you then. Thank you for the call.
Say if you want to say something. I'm here to listen.
I don't have anything to say.
Did you eat breakfast?
It's none of your business.
- What are you doing? - I'll wait until you do it.
Na Ri, do you remember saying that you were happy...
when we went on biking together?
How do you feel these days? Are you happy living here?
Go and do your work.
Do you think I'll be able to work?
I told you to go!
Hi, Neighborhood Friend!
(Hong Dumplings Menu)
I can see it didn't go well by looking at your face.
The second CEO indeed has a temper, right?
What?
You're the most pitiful person in the world.
How have you been?
Good. How about you, Duk Bong?
Not too well. Things couldn't be worse.
Did something happen?
It's complicated.
Na Ri, I have something to tell you.
Do you want to see the spot in this town that I hate?
Why would we go somewhere you hate?
You'll see when we get there.
Hello?
Mr. Ko Nan Gil?
I'm the person who knows Hong Na Ri's father.
You left me your number at my shop last time, right?
Yes, that's right.
Her father said not to tell her...
and to come alone.
As soon as possible.
Okay.
Do you really think he wouldn't tell her?
Who cares if he does?
You should get rid of punks like this quickly.
Be smart about what you say to him.
I'll peel that for you,
Mr. Landowner.
Yong Kyu. I need to step out.
You've been leaving whenever you want anyway.
- If Na Ri comes... - If she does?
She won't.
What was that?
The view is nice. Why do you hate this place?
My long-term girlfriend dumped me here.
The families fought about a business management matter,
and I was our family's attorney.
We won in court and I was dumped here.
Whether I can like this spot again or hate it more...
depends on you.
Neighborhood Friend, don't burden me like that.
I said I won't be your neighborhood friend anymore.
I'm giving up on building a resort on your land.
This time, I'll fight against my family.
I feel better now.
The view is nice and you're here with me.
Nan Gil and I decided to date like a normal couple.
Couldn't you let me enjoy the view? You're so cruel.
I'm just honest.
You know,
I don't think the two of you can ever become normal.
Do you even fight?
Don't you care what others think?
Then write down why you like Nan Gil.
Don't say, "Because he's my stepdad."
I like you because you're honest.
I like you because I feel comforted when I'm with you.
I like you because you make me laugh.
I like you because you're mature.
Stop it. You're making me uncomfortable.
I was giving you examples.
I'm going to Seoul to fight for you.
(Gyeonggi-do Nursing Home)
No, thank you. I can do it...
You.
You know me, don't you?
When I saw you walk in with my daughter,
I was stunned.
I couldn't let on in front of her.
I...
despise Bae Byung Woo.
He did this to my eyes.
You're Bae Byung Woo's son, aren't you?
I'm sorry. But I am not anymore.
Don't give me that. Once a son, always a son.
I hate seeing you with my daughter.
I don't trust you.
I should stay with her from now on.
I can't...
live in that house with you.
Hi.
I guess you are afraid. You're staying in the hospital.
How could you say that?
I'm not afraid.
Is that why you ordered to start construction?
You know that land belongs to Na Ri.
It's my land. I was conned.
Hong Sung Gyu came to me and showed me a document,
demanding money. All I did was pay him.
That document was fake and he ran away.
Hong Sung Kyu? Na Ri's father?
Father, my foot. He's a total con artist!
His wife wouldn't hand over the deed,
so he ran away with his daughter!
He ran away with his daughter? With Na Ri?
How could he kidnap his daughter because of some land?
If she weren't his daughter,
he would've been locked up for kidnapping!
Anyway, you seem fine as expected.
Excuse me, then.
You can't just go.
Go to Seulgi-ri.
Pardon?
- Me? - Find out what's going on...
between Duk Bong and Hong Na Ri.
Have a nice day.
What are you doing here?
I stopped by and they were busy, so I helped.
Where did you go?
- Me? - Answer me.
It won't work between us.
- Will you keep doing that? - What?
Will you be nervous every time I go somewhere?
You can just tell me where you went.
I went to see your father. He said to come alone.
Why?
He wanted to know who I was. And he wants to come here.
He didn't call for 20 years.
Now, he wants to act like a father?
- What did he say? - I thought I was going to die.
Why? What did he do?
He shoved an entire clementine in my mouth.
I almost suffocated.
He was good to me.
He said to keep it a secret that I saw him.
Now that I told you, my conscience is bothering me.
Then why did you tell me?
In case you'd get weird ideas and get nervous.
That's normal when a man and woman start dating.
Fine.
You're Bae Byung Woo's son, aren't you?
I can't...
live in that house with you.
You seemed closed but your light was on, so I came in.
My father is in a hospital. The threats worked.
He goes to a hospital when he's afraid.
Leave Na Ri's land matter to me from now on.
Looks like you have a lot on your mind, too.
I heard you're going to date like a normal couple.
Why did she tell the neighborhood friend all that?
Nan Gil.
You didn't show yourself to Na Ri...
before her mother passed away, did you?
Why was that?
You are too curious about me.
You never once thought about a future with her.
No. I'm sure you never even dreamed about it.
You knew yourself too well.
Na Ri seems concerned, too.
Do you even share your concerns with each other?
Why aren't you together right now?
You are not a good match,
and you can't handle each other.
Oh my gosh.
Am I the Death himself or something?
Why are you so scared?
Why are you here?
Look at this pigsty.
You say the same thing every time you come.
Seriously.
What's going on between your brother and Hong Na Ri?
You look like you know everything,
but are you not going to tell me?
I can't say.
I'll take you to Seoul.
A one-sided crush.
Who? Na Ri?
No. Duk Bong has a crush on her.
Kwon Duk Shim!
Hi.
The chairman figured it out.
He told me to come.
Should I meet Na Ri?
- No. - Mom.
Don't do anything.
Yong Kyu. It's too wet.
Joon. It's dry.
Hani.
I'm at a loss with you.
I'll redo them. Reflect on what went wrong and redo it.
Why are you being like this?
All you need is one master. That's how things work.
No excuses. Proceed now.
- Okay. - What a scary boss.
They'll be exhausted before you even open.
- Where are you going? - To work.
To discuss my leave of absence.
Why?
"What do you plan to do?"
"Will you return to work?"
To discuss things like that.
I see. You've thought it over, right?
You know that's what you love to do and do best.
You'll say you'll go back, right?
You look like a parent,
not a normal boyfriend.
Don't stand like that.
I'll be back.
We are so not normal.
Boss. I'm asking in all seriousness.
Are you afraid of the daughter?
Why are you out here? Did you finish the filling?
Don't act tough to the weak.
- It makes me sad. - Get inside.
- Get inside. Now. - Wait.
What did I do?
Father.
What a loud entrance. This is a hospital.
Why are you looking into Na Ri?
I looked into her because you said it was her land.
I'm going to build a luxury resort on that land...
and put up a statue of me. It's all for you guys!
So no one will disrespect you!
Will that bury what you did to your hometown?
It was over 40 years ago.
You're a loser, letting a girl push you around.
Just marry her then.
That would be a great solution.
Leave my personal life alone.
Yeo Joo.
You looked scary, so I was going to walk on by.
Okay, I look scary.
You look happy.
The hospital bill was less than expected.
I envy you.
Who envies whom?
Don't be annoying.
No wonder you get along with Duk Shim.
I've never heard that I get along with someone.
I never expected it to be a teenager, though.
See? You act like a teen, too.
Do I seem like your baby sister?
Do you want to protect me? Am I cute and lovable?
None of those apply to Duk Shim.
I just worry about where she'll disappear to next.
Duk Bong.
Don't be like that to me.
What?
A big brother who worries about his sister looks cool.
I have more to jot down every time I see you.
Have a nice day. Tell Duk Shim I say, "Hi."
We think it would be best to have you return...
which is why we asked you to come in.
You're too young to retire.
Wouldn't it be best to work a few more years?
Okay. I'll think about it.
I changed my flight schedule...
to see you after your meeting.
Why?
So make some time for me.
Let go.
What is it?
So...
I never worked so hard on a woman before.
You act smart, so you figure out why.
Do you think you're working hard on me?
I'm neither a senior colleague nor a woman to you.
I'm just a link between you and Duk Bong,
and you have to be friendly to me. Am I wrong?
You're not a link.
You're wrong this time.
I wanted to give you a warning.
A warning?
Stop acting cool.
If someone like Duk Bong says he likes you, grab on.
Try closing your eyes...
and transfer Nan Gil to Seoul.
You go to a dumpling place, and Nan Gil is there.
Then you would think, "A cute guy..."
"makes dumplings well, too."
You would eat the dumplings and just leave.
- Hey, Yeo Joo. - Yes?
Did you think Nan Gil was cute?
That's not the point right now.
I'm annoyed about seeing you again if I return to work.
I wanted to apologize to you at some point,
but whenever I see you, I don't want to anymore.
Why are you so honest now?
Just admit you like Duk Bong and you'll be done.
Well then. I have somewhere to get to.
(Gyeonggi-do Nursing Home)
Here.
I'll get your room ready.
I'm not going.
I need to have a conscience...
to end up in a good place when I die.
However,
someone will have to protect the house.
We only have...
each other in this world.
Nan Gil is running the dumpling house,
so you won't be bored.
He didn't tell you?
I can't live with him.
Why not?
He did this to my eyes...
and I know how he lived. How could I live with him?
This began with you.
You didn't take any responsibility.
You abandoned Mom and me and stayed in hiding.
You should've taken responsibility.
Nan Gil was dragged into this because of you.
I was just trying to survive.
You wanted to survive alone,
so you dumped that huge debt on Mom and me?
If you refuse to live with him,
I'll tell Nan Gil to choose...
since he's the one who protected it.
I'll visit you once in a while.
Forget it. Get out of my mom's and my house.
I told you it's my house. I can't leave.
Who are you?
Who are you to say my house is yours?
Who are you really?
Your father.
Let's not be family so that we can be together.
No.
Na Ri.
I love you.
Even if I can never say it again,
I will love you.
What happened?
Where did you get this?
- I'm fine. - What were you doing?
Just stay still. Don't say a word.
I'm sorry. I won't do it again.
It won't work between us.
Enough.
It's not just about strength.
You're late. How did it go?
I said I'd think about it.
Good.
It must have been very difficult, putting up with...
an abusive boss and having to come in early.
So let's go on a retreat...
and build on our relationship.
- A retreat? - A retreat?
I'm the boss. Why are you making the calls?
Retreat. Retreat. Retreat. Retreat!
Retreat. Retreat. Retreat.
We made some money because of the show, right?
Then can we get on a plane?
- What about you? - I can go if it's a weekend.
Then there's something I need you to do.
Get out. Why would I go to Hong Dumplings' retreat?
I'm a minor. I need a guardian.
Duk Shim, do you even consider me your guardian?
I totally do.
You'll say anything to go on the retreat.
Get Greenland to sponsor.
You've got to be kidding me.
Na Ri asked me to do it.
She really wants you there.
I said you'll be my guardian, give a ride,
and book the resort.
If you don't go, the retreat will fall through.
Did she really say that?
I saw my father after my meeting at work.
Did you tell him to move in?
I said I'd visit once in a while.
Why didn't you tell me he refused to live with you?
Let's just say that I understood how he felt.
How do you think you would've lived...
if this hadn't happened to my mom and me?
I probably would've worked at a dumplings place.
I would've visited your mother occasionally...
and complained about her dumplings.
You would've been a regular guy who kneads dough.
Sorry.
Why? What for?
When I saw you hurt, I knew it was because of me,
but I was so shocked and nervous that I got angry.
It's still so hard for you that you can't breathe...
when you think about those days,
but you put up with it because of me.
It must've been hard, but I thought only of myself.
That was my choice because I love you.
I've never regretted it, and it's all taken care of.
Don't apologize to me again.
You have no reason to be sorry.
I've been cured from my Ko Nan Gil disease.
I don't need my medicine anymore. I'm really fine.
I never got to tell you this.
Nan Gil,
thank you for being my stepdad.
I'm done with work, so let's go on a date.
I'll show you that I'm all better.
Let's go somewhere very loud.
Good.
Faster.
Can't you do better?
This is hard.
It's hard.
Where is it?
Gosh.
Enjoy yourselves. Let me know if you need anything.
Nice.
Goodness.
What is that?
Just seeing these bags...
should let her know that I will be living here...
with you for the rest of my life.
I'm not moving in!
What's this?
What's wrong with this?
Awesome. What is he wearing?
Is he trying to look like Nan Gil?
Is it working?
- What? - Is it igniting?
I'm trying.
You should put that in.
Is kneading all you know how to do?
Thank you.
It's hot.
Duk Shim, don't just eat meat.
Have some shrimps, too.
Why is someone so young acting like an old man?
Let me borrow that.
Let's see.
Thank you.
Here are the garlic.
Na Ri, have some meat.
Thank you.
Try it with this garlic sauce. I made it myself.
- Isn't it good? - Yes, it's really good.
Garlic? Whatever.
Dumplings. Dumplings. Dumplings. Five.
Dumplings. Dumplings. Dumplings.
Ten.
I won.
- Next. - Why have you been...
teaching them how to make the filling these days?
It's time they learn.
Wrong. That's not it.
You planned to leave after talking to my dad.
I can't imagine Hong Dumplings without you.
You think it's right that I leave.
Isn't this retreat your gift to me?
It is.
Try living as Ko Nan Gil, not my stepdad...
or Hong Dumplings' owner.
Then let's say this retreat...
is the real beginning of Ko Nan Gil's life.
How will you start it?
Once I leave, I'll lead a normal life.
I'll get a job and take trips.
Once I gain the courage, I'll get a new girlfriend.
The Hong Na Ri in Seoul whom I don't know.
Fine. You've loved me for a very long time.
So the Hong Na Ri in Seoul will wait.
Hello?
The chairman changed the resort's layout.
I can't...
take it any longer.
What?
I did all I could.
I got excited, thinking you were running toward me.
At times like these, it's not bad having a sister.
Neighborhood Friend. Is something wrong?
I have to go to Seoul and fight my father.
I've felt this and been in this kind of situations.
I was on his side before,
but I'm on yours this time.
It's not like I can wish you luck against your father.
It's okay. Just wish me luck.
Good luck.
Do you have any memories of your father?
Not really.
All I know is...
that my very first flight was with my father.
I plan to ask him since I met him.
You met your father?
It's so cold.
Did Na Ri find her father?
Yes.
All the fathers are just incredible.
I heard Na Ri's father...
was a con man who kidnapped her for the land.
How could he show his face to her again?
Who said that?
Chairman Kwon.
Mom may be hurt if she hears this,
but I didn't hate my father.
The first time I rode a plane was with my father.
I was too young to remember much,
but I remember being shocked at how big it was.
I wonder why Mom didn't go with us.
Where did I go alone with my father?
I wonder.
It must not have been fun if you can't remember.
I'm sure it was.
My father was pretty funny.
Everyone in town liked him.
But whenever I told my mom that,
she said I never flew with my dad...
although I remember for certain.
No. I rode an airplane with my father.
I'm positive.
- Do you have everything? - Yes.
Rest up today. See you tomorrow.
Okay.
- Bye, Boss. - I'll see you tomorrow.
When are you leaving?
Did you think I didn't know?
Even Duk Shim could tell you were leaving.
After I resolve the land matter.
Everything aside,
it's a good decision for your life's sake.
Can't you be a little sad?
You seem too happy.
I want you to have a good life. That's why.
Leave Seulgi-ri and live freely.
There she comes.
Where did you all go without anyone to watch the place?
Na Ri.
Your father is all frozen from waiting all day.
I heard Na Ri's father...
was a con man who kidnapped her for the land.