(The following content may not be suitable for viewers under 15. SUBBED BY VIU/SA143
(Viewer discretion is advised.)
(Episode 15) SUBBED BY VIU/SA143
When are you leaving?
Did you think I didn't know?
Even Duk Shim could tell you were leaving.
After I resolve the land matter.
Everything aside,
it's a good decision for your life's sake.
Can't you be a little sad?
You seem too happy.
I want you to have a good life. That's why.
Leave Seulgi-ri and live freely.
There she comes.
Where did you all go without anyone to watch the place?
Na Ri.
Your father is all frozen...
from waiting all day.
I heard Na Ri's father...
was a con man who kidnapped her for the land.
How long did you wait?
We just got here.
You should greet your elders.
Let's go inside.
It's okay. Maybe it's my time for me to die.
I keep seeing Hong Dumplings in my dreams.
I came to take a look.
It's changing drastically every year.
He can't handle the cold at the nursing home anymore.
He even got frostbites.
Welcome, Sir. Let's go inside.
Hey, Ko Nan Gil.
If you keep closing the store, you'll lose customers.
Do you have dumplings pre-made?
They have good business. They were even on television.
There's no need to scold him.
Go inside and take a look. I'll take in your luggage.
- Are you telling me to be quiet? - Dad.
- Go and show them around. - Okay.
Okay.
If you're going to leave, be more sensible.
Don't act like you're his son-in-law.
You already heard what that man did to Na Ri.
He's still her father.
Gosh.
You're moving me to tears.
You should've been good to her before.
Be quiet.
The kids can hear you.
(Duk Shim)
What brings you to call me at this hour?
Why won't you tell me Dad's number?
Really?
Yes, the chairman is feeling better.
Na Ri's father came.
I see. Thank you.
They say it's been 20 years. That's ridiculous.
I don't want to live like that.
Give me his number.
All right. Bye, now.
Duk Shim wanted to know how you were doing.
Do you think I would buy that?
She told me Na Ri's father came back to Hong Dumplings.
- Who? - Na Ri's father.
Hurry up and get me discharged.
Right now?
Duk Bong is threatening to sue you. It's too early.
Tell Mr. Kim to call in the company lawyer.
Okay.
You should stay beside your father.
What can the three of us talk about?
How did they even think about coming here?
What if they ask to stay in this room?
I'll drive them back to Seoul.
There's no need.
If it's too hard to look at Mother's belongings, go.
I'll do it.
Let's not touch them.
We started, so I'll finish.
- Do you know how strange this is? - What is?
We're cleaning up Mom's room...
and we're worried about where to put Dad.
It's as if we've been married for 10 years. It's weird.
Thank you for helping Dad get here.
I just did what I should do.
You can go...
I'll...
drive you home.
Yes. You should go.
Hey, do you live here?
No, there is a room beside the restaurant.
Okay.
So he's insisting on following this blueprint?
The chairman is so arrogant.
I heard that he just summoned the company lawyer.
Did he get discharged?
What is he scheming now?
I'll get going.
I heard Na Ri's father came to Hong Dumplings.
Ms. Kwon, do you know Hong Sung Kyu?
- No. - No.
I knew you'd say that.
You're so predictable.
If you're tired, you should go rest.
I'm not tired at all.
You brought a big luggage with you.
Do you have any other clothes?
What's wrong with this one?
Hey. Does Mom's favorite...
tofu merchant still come at the same time?
It's old news, isn't it?
Why did you leave Mom and I?
I have no excuse.
Granny Oh Rye told me...
that you and Mom...
fell apart after you took me on a trip.
Where did we go back then?
To your mom's parents' house.
I see.
I can't remember anything else...
except for seeing a plane.
That was my first flight.
Do you...
still remember that?
You visited the restaurant a year ago, right?
I was surprised when I read the note.
How did you know?
Someone took a picture and I saw you in it.
Na Ri's father was curious, so I visited time to time.
Since when?
What?
Well...
Let's see...
When was it again?
Was it after Mother passed away?
I wasn't going to say this,
but Na Ri's father is really mad.
He's just not saying it out loud.
Da Da kept telling me...
that Ko Nan Gil took...
Na Ri's land and the restaurant.
That's why I told her father.
Then he told he had to see her right away...
and started to pack.
He wanted to get the land back...
and kick you out from Hong Dumplings.
- That took a while. - Where is your father?
He's sleeping.
What are you doing here by yourself?
I'm trying to clear my head from all the mess.
Tell me what you're thinking about.
Should I accept Dad?
Should I take care of him forever?
I think that's unfair.
Mom must have been too nice to kick him out.
What is family about?
Your poor brain is suffering because of you.
There's more.
I told him to live freely,
but I don't want Nan Gil to leave.
Maybe we shouldn't have gone on the trip.
Things like that.
I'm just saying it.
What?
I'll teach you how to make dumplings.
If you focus on something, you'll forget it all.
You need to press on it evenly.
Why are they all different sizes? Make it even.
Stop being so serious.
Are you going to hire me?
You have mood swings because you think too much.
Dad can't stay at home all the time.
Maybe he should learn how to make dumplings.
Don't.
- Don't do that. - Na Ri.
Welcome.
- Hello. - Hello.
Hello.
It's just as I had built it.
That's a lie. Boss and I renovated it.
How many owners are there anyway?
Mr. Original Owner,
you must be reminiscing about the past.
Would you like to try making some dumplings?
What about kneading dough? We're doing it now.
Kneading dough?
You see.
I have bad eyesight, so I don't do that kind of stuff.
Hey, why do you always seem to avoid me?
I wasn't avoiding you. I was doing my job.
Are you going to keep on talking back at me?
Why is my daughter living here jobless?
And why are you living here?
Are you penniless and homeless?
Where's all the money earned from the restaurant?
Are you actually giving it to my daughter?
Let's discuss this after I get off work.
Work? You actually call making dumplings work?
The fact that the person who made my eyes like this...
is living here just absolutely drives me crazy!
This property is Na Ri's and my land.
This restaurant is also mine.
Father.
If you have any questions, ask me.
If you're bored, make some dumplings.
No, no.
How could an old man with bad eyesight make dumplings?
I think I'll go and get some rest.
It's so annoying being caught between you two!
I wonder what our lawyer is up to these days.
Why do you always dress like that?
What brings you here along with the company lawyer?
If you continue to turn down the developing project,
you give me no choice but to report Na Ri's father.
A busy man like you has time to do that?
The statute of limitation for the 20-year...
claim-obligation relationship has expired.
He issued a false death report to hide his identity.
Fabrication of official documents violates...
Article 225 of Criminal Law and is...
a serious felony that applies to 10 years in prison.
I don't know what he's thinking by showing up here.
He's a downright con-artist.
Trouble will only ruin your relationship with Na Ri.
Build the resort and try downsizing the park.
Don't act like you care about me.
Why don't you worry about yourself instead?
How much longer do I have to put up with your grudges?
Was it my fault your marriage got called off?
In the end, it was you who chose me!
I'm not taking your side this time.
I think...
I'll have to go meet Hong Na Ri.
Chairman Kwon, don't you dare go near Na Ri.
If you do, I assure you I'll lose my mind.
I'm giving up the park. What more do you want?
Ms. Kwon!
Why are you calling Ms. Kwon now?
It's as if we've been married for 10 years. It's weird.
Why did he bring such a large bag with no clothes?
You saw my father's clothes, didn't you?
He must have worn the same clothes for 20 years.
Why are you laughing?
When you mention your father, it reminds me of that.
Of what?
That it's as if we've been married for 10 years.
I take it back.
There was no dating period needless to say romance.
Stop telling your father to make dumplings.
Why?
Your father has never made dumplings before.
- How do you know? - Your mother told me.
As a child, I liked going to the market,
so my mother would always take me with her.
The dumplings I had at the market...
tasted the same as the ones at Hong Dumplings.
Your father bought dumplings from the market...
to sell at Hong Dumplings without your mom's knowing.
It's a shameful history of Hong Dumplings.
I guess you used to like markets and crowded places.
- What if... - You said you don't like subjunctives.
What if you met me when I was with Mom?
I practiced for that kind of situation just in case.
Hello, Na Ri. Nice to meet you. My name's Nan Gil.
It's a good thing we never crossed paths.
Your first impression of me wasn't good anyway.
No, that's not true.
Snake! Watch out!
- Where? - I'm just saying to beware of snakes.
What? Did he just fool me?
I'll see you again.
Whatever.
Watch out! A wild boar!
There's a wild boar!
It was a prank my mother used to play on me.
I wondered how you played the same prank.
"Maybe my mother sent you to cheer me up."
That's what I thought.
I never thought you'd be my stepdad.
Let's change the subject.
This is a video I saw at home when I had my phone off.
- Do you want to see it? - Sure.
(Neighborhood Friend)
I can't wait.
- What are you having? - I want kimchi dumpling.
Go in.
Did you learn about Hong Dumplings on television?
We dropped by after visiting the Robot Museum.
Oh, the Robot Museum!
Then I guess you'll come whenever you visit the museum.
He'll drive away all our customers. What is he doing?
Mr. Hong Sung Kyu.
Is that you, Soon Rye?
You know Chairman Kwon, don't you?
How is your health?
Cut the small talk and shut it.
I assumed you would come to me if you were alive.
I'm sure you thought you could claim this land...
now that Na Ri's mother died.
No, it's nothing like that. I thought I should...
come back home at least once before I die.
How dare you talk back at me!
Just listen.
From now on, do as I say.
You see...
My eyesight is bad...
and I have the energy to obey your orders.
That's good news.
Now that you're spiritless, you can turn yourself in.
Turn myself in?
Why is Ko Nan Gil claiming the land to be his property?
It's all because you have been on the run!
Turn yourself in, get punishment and recover your name.
Oh my goodness!
Go to prison in this cold and at this age?
My son is going to want to meet you.
He says he has feelings for your daughter.
He volunteered to be Na Ri's attorney.
I just can't stand it.
Cooperate with investigations and do your time.
After that, transfer the property under your name.
I don't know how I ended up being your attorney,
but the documents say your dad passed away 5 years ago.
How did you know?
Forging official documents will land you in prison.
What has your father been doing?
Normal people can't do this.
She hasn't seen him in 20 years.
How would she know?
Exactly. Why did he suddenly surface after 20 years?
He said he saw the restaurant in his dreams.
The winter is tough for him.
You're so understanding of something so ridiculous.
What a good daughter.
Then what should I do? Tell him to turn himself in?
People like him don't turn themselves in.
- Na Ri. - Yes?
I'll think about it.
- And Nan Gil. - What?
Let's settle things.
I won't build the resort on Na Ri's land,
so change the deed to her name.
And I will quit being her attorney.
Why do I get this feeling he'll cause trouble?
Hey.
Where did my daughter and that punk go?
Sorry, but Boss doesn't tell us where he goes.
Call him!
Who? Boss?
Get me a cab.
A cab?
I'm sorry.
Duk Shim, would you take over?
Hey. Give me money for cab fare.
How is he so shameless?
(Transfer of Ownership)
Hello?
- Ms. Hong Na Ri? - Yes?
This is the police.
You're Hong Sung Kyu's daughter, correct?
I'll give him the phone. Talk to him.
Here you go.
Na Ri.
I didn't want to be on the run forever,
so I turned myself in.
They said this is the only way to get my name back.
Why did you suddenly...
I hear it'll be easier for me...
if I have a lawyer.
My father turned himself in...
and needs a lawyer.
He turned himself in?
Let's go and find out what's going on.
We won't be able to once the investigation starts.
I'll go today.
We'll go with you. You said you're quitting law.
I'll go alone.
I was correct.
I wondered why I had so many flaws...
when my mom is a total angel.
This is all because of Dad's genes.
I'm moody, I get stressed easily,
and I make rash decisions.
Are you self-reflecting?
No. I'm blaming my genes.
You can't say that in front of someone without parents.
Think positively. I'm actually kind of...
relieved now.
Because my dad, who's been bugging you here, is gone?
He can do this much in order to get his name back.
Should he live in hiding forever?
We could've discussed it first.
He could've changed his clothes.
I don't understand why he went so suddenly either,
but don't worry. Trust Duk Bong.
You have a useful neighborhood friend.
This is what we have so far. Read it over.
Wow. You are good looking.
I wish you were my son-in-law.
My eyesight isn't very good. I got hurt, you see.
I see.
What number son...
of Chairman Kwon are you?
You saw Chairman Kwon, didn't you?
No, I didn't.
You can't lie to me.
I'm not lying.
I saw him briefly when he passed by Hong Dumplings.
Forging official documents is a felony.
You must be alert and answer honestly.
How long have you known my daughter?
You ran away with Na Ri when she was young, didn't you?
You can be found guilty of kidnapping your own child.
Chairman Kwon...
gave me airfare and made me do it.
tortured our family in order to take that land from us.
Goodness. I never imagined he still couldn't have it.
I won't sell this land.
But why have I never met you before?
I studied abroad.
You did?
You seem to be similar in age to my son and daughter.
You could be neighborhood friends.
If you'd adjust the price...
It really isn't about the money.
I won't sell.
He tortured them all their lives.
How did it go?
He'll be back soon.
He turned himself in,
and he didn't commit any crimes with his fake identity,
so he can pay a fine and avoid serving time.
- Don't worry. - I'm not worried.
He can do that much in order to get his name back.
Good thinking.
Thank you, Duk Bong.
Why did you make him turn himself in?
I agreed to eliminate his debt,
so he should do something for me.
What would a con man do?
You seem to resent me,
so I'm trying to get you together with Na Ri.
Take care of it for him.
I know it's about the land.
I know you made Hong Sung Kyu a debtor and kidnapper.
How dare you trust a con man and give me lip?
You want him to recover his name...
and file a lawsuit to claim the land!
If you have no shame,
at least have a conscience.
You killed children...
and pretended like you didn't know. And now,
must you steal that land, too?
That land...
was ours from the start.
It's right that we take it.
I didn't want to go this far,
but I swear I will make you stand trial.
(Hong Na Ri's Footsteps)
Goodness. Maybe it's because my heart is at peace,
but I am sleeping very well.
It's nice here.
Did you really come to turn yourself in?
That's what I said.
I heard you'll be released soon. Hang in there.
Duk Bong will take care of it.
You know,
I really like that lawyer fellow.
He's nothing like Chairman Kwon.
He has a strong sense of responsibility.
He's perfect for you.
I was shocked at how quickly he ran over.
He likes you, doesn't he?
We're not like that.
I'll never approve of that punk, Nan Gil.
You have no right to say that.
Any time his name comes up,
you get worked up.
My father said to thank you.
I was really mean to him.
Your father seems to make your life difficult.
You did good.
Nan Gil does it well, but I can't.
You have your mother's smile.
Sorry, that just came out.
Let's not go to Seulgi-ri. Where should we go?
Na Ri.
It's nice seeing you outside of Seulgi-ri.
You look better here.
Don't quit your job.
To be honest, I didn't like Seulgi-ri.
I got bored after a day and went back to Seoul.
I'm amazed that I'm doing fine there.
I feel guilty toward my mom.
You don't look happy there to me.
Do you know how conflicted you look?
It would be strange not to be with two dads.
One is in a holding cell and the other wants to leave.
I'm the only one who can protect Seulgi-ri.
Boss gave this to me.
This has the business know-how for Hong Dumplings.
He told me to study it.
More shockingly, he wants me to write in it now.
Why is he doing this to me? Do I look studious to you?
- Oh my gosh. - Must I...
take on this burden at this age?
Aren't you only a year younger than Mr. Ko?
No way. Really?
Nan Gil was just very mature.
We will take a vote, the democratic way.
If you'll stay even after Boss leaves,
touch your elbow to your mouth.
Spin 100 times.
No one?
We will all leave if Boss leaves. It's unanimous!
Hong Dumplings is loyalty.
- Loyalty. - Loyalty.
Again. Hong Dumplings is loyalty!
- Loyalty. - Good.
Na Ri.
Go with me to a year-end party.
My friends throw a party every year.
It'll be embarrassing to go alone.
So be my partner.
I know someone who likes parties.
That someone already became enemies with my friends.
Why?
She claims it's because they badmouthed me,
but they were probably just drunk.
I represented your fathers. Aren't you grateful?
It should be a give and take.
Okay, Mr. Attorney.
How immature.
Why... Why are you here? Aren't you kneading?
Why are you stuttering? Do you feel guilty?
No.
You'll freeze to death, trying to look pretty.
It's so cold. Mom, I'm here.
My precious daughter. Come in.
Let me see.
Look at you.
You'll freeze to death, trying to look pretty.
First my stepdad, then my mom. Stop confusing me.
What does that mean?
Sit down.
Here's the bankbook and ledger for the restaurant.
Are you telling me to run Hong Dumplings?
It'll run itself.
Yong Kyu is managing the ingredients and payroll.
Aren't you going to ask where I went with Duk Bong?
Can't you tell I'm holding back?
You're so good at it.
But why are you holding back?
He's representing your father. I can't say anything.
It wouldn't be like you watched a movie,
had tea, and had fun with him.
Anyway, I'm... I'm not interested in looking at this.
- You're stuttering. You do feel guilty. - I do not.
We watched a musical and had tea.
You don't need to tell me everything.
Nan Gil.
Girls like Duk Shim may follow you around in Seoul.
I didn't think of that. You were fine taking the bus,
but now you can't go to Seoul without Duk Bong.
- Just admit you don't like it. - Be honest.
Say you don't trust me living alone in Seoul.
Be honest and say my neighborhood friend bothers you.
You're staying out all night if you come past midnight!
How many times did you come home early morning?
Don't be unreasonable after playing until now.
Don't act cool and then hold a grudge.
It's late, so go to sleep.
Let's talk later.
Look if you want to know how to run the restaurant!
Nan Gil! You are so childish! Seriously!
Why did you say that?
Why did I say that?
Yeo Joo.
Na Ri. What are you doing here?
I waited for you after my second consultation.
When are you coming back to work?
Why are you telling people I'm coming back? I'm not.
You're determined to destroy me.
If you don't come back, I'll have to quit.
Like I'd believe you. You have too much debt to quit.
- Come with me. - Why?
If you don't want to return to work,
marry Nan Gil and save me.
- What? - You took a leave to get married,
so get married for real.
How could you bring up marriage to me?
I'm busy. Keep it brief.
Duk Bong asked me to go with him to a year-end party.
So I waited to ask you for advice on a party dress.
I was clueless.
It wasn't because of Nan Gil.
I guess you heeded my warning.
I did.
Your warning really hit me. Thanks.
Congratulations.
But Na Ri,
don't act high and mighty in front of me anymore.
- What? - You're just an average woman...
who weighed your options...
between Nan Gil and Duk Bong and chose money.
My motto these days is to become an average woman.
Stop acting uninterested,
and look up year-end party looks.
The internet is full of information.
Sit down.
I heard you ruined Duk Bong's friends' party...
because they were badmouthing him.
I guess you talk about me behind my back.
I know you like him.
You're not one to ruin a party.
I won't steal him from you. Don't worry.
How do you feel right now?
You and Duk Bong weren't dating, but you feel like...
I took him from you, so you're upset and want to cry.
Don't forget that feeling.
The people you hurt...
suffered 100 times more than that.
Repent.
You are...
impossible to like.
Don't twist your words.
Is it my fault that you don't like me?
I'm too nice to say, "I hate you."
Then learn how to.
And if you like Duk Bong, do it your way.
Don't bother people around him.
Don't call me to your room.
It's like I'm being called to the principal's office.
Here.
What's this?
Put it on.
Awesome.
They say the clothes make the man.
You look good. We'll have to update our website.
Stand straight.
Can you do it?
I know it's painful for you. I do,
but think about us, too.
This isn't right.
You created this place.
Why are you running away?
Darn it.
He's so cool.
You told me...
if I let people take, they'll keep taking.
That those who take have no conscience.
So why are you letting them take from you?
There's no one on your side.
- I'm an evil boss. - You're right.
You're an evil boss, but your workers love you.
I went to the office for a consultation.
- Did you decide yet? - No.
I said I'd think about it some more.
You have no respect for your stepdad's opinion.
What happened to becoming an average guy?
Try living as Ko Nan Gil, not my stepdad...
or Hong Dumplings' owner.
How will you start it?
Ko Nan Gil.
How will you start?
We heard the rumor.
Can't we get a picture with you?
Of course, you can.
- Thank you. - Thank you.
No, no. Thank you.
That's right. What did you order?
Kimchi. You wanted kimchi dumplings, right?
Nan Gil.
I don't know why I need to relay this message,
but Na Ri's father asked when you are leaving.
Your outfit is especially loud today.
Yes. I'm dressed for a party.
Don't you have any holiday parties to go to?
(Hong Dumplings)
Will we have a love triangle in Seulgi-ri?
You look like you looked forward to the party.
Duk Bong.
I can't go.
You didn't even give me time to find a replacement.
It's not a serious event.
Just stay for a few minutes and then leave.
I'm sorry.
Don't feel bad.
I don't need to bring a date actually.
I'll drop you off at home.
No, I want to go to Seoul...
to a friend's cafe.
Okay, then.
You'll date as a regular man and woman?
Don't make me laugh.
Hey. I won't say anything then.
I guess he has a conscience after making you cry.
A conscience?
"Let's date. This is day one."
He beat around the bush and asked indirectly.
Hey.
What could you possibly have to say to me...
that you came to visit?
Father.
When Na Ri was young,
you took her and ran away for money, right?
Did you tell her that?
Are you here to threaten me?
I am not.
When time passes,
I'll get on my knees...
and tell her everything, so...
No.
Don't tell Na Ri.
She remembers it as her first flight.
It's also why she became a flight attendant.
That's probably why Mother never told her either.
Just let her keep it as the memory of her first flight.
Hey, I need to go home.
You should go too.
No.
There goes Na Ri's specialty.
Sitting silently and thinking.
- Where are you? - Why?
- I'm in Seoul. - Why?
I'll pick you up. Come out.
Why?
You said to tell you if I don't like it.
I don't like you being there.
If Ran Sook hears you say you don't like my being here,
it'll be three strikes for you.
What? He doesn't like you being here?
He doesn't like your being here?
I'm at Ran Sook's cafe.
Didn't you go to the party?
Okay. I'm coming. Wait for me.
Is something wrong?
You're the only person I know who knows Na Ri.
You have Duk Shim.
You're right.
I'm sure if she saw me now, she'd say,
"Awesome."
Okay. Don't beat around the bush.
Tell me what happened. I'll listen.
I'm not in the mood to talk.
Then why am I here?
I know.
After I called you, I suddenly want to be alone.
Duk Bong. Don't be like this to me.
You look cool even when you act lonely.
Is that what you expected?
I'll search and read to you...
things to console a man who's been dumped.
How to...
You're just like Duk Shim.
My gosh.
I've never met up with a guy dressed like this before.
It's the first time a guy came to my dad's hospital.
We'll really end up being friends.
Found it. Should I read it to you?
It's okay.
You weren't dumped. You never even dated.
"Most guys become furious when they are dumped."
I said it's okay.
"And whom is he enraged?"
"Most guys turn the blame..."
"on the woman."
I'll tell you what happened, so stop it.
Did you have dinner yet?
Why didn't you go to Duk Bong's party?
I'm grateful and sorry toward him,
but I felt like I'd feel worse if I went.
I realized why our feelings were so complicated.
Now, all that remains is the situation between us.
Nan Gil, why do you want to leave?
So you can get together with Duk Bong.
I wish it were something that cool, but it isn't.
Now that your dad returned, I felt like I was...
being unreasonable insisting it was my house.
I felt uncomfortable and insecure.
I wanted to find my own place.
Something like that.
So what? Will you shake it all off and find your place?
Don't make it sound so easy.
Let's go.
Answer me.
Na Ri.
Thank you for being here instead of going to the party.
You don't like dumplings, do you?
Me? I do.
I know you don't.
You don't like dumplings,
and your dad sold dumplings he bought from the market.
And Mother's dumplings...
Even my friends said they tasted bad.
They were right.
But now, people line up for Hong Dumplings,
and it's a famous eatery that was on TV.
What are you trying to say?
So the Hong Dumplings now...
was created by Ko Nan Gil.
Hong Dumplings is Hong Na Ri's Hong Dumplings.
No, it's Ko Nan Gil's Hong Dumplings.
I've decided how to start.
I won't leave.
Hong Dumplings is where I belong.
I'll go on trips, make friends,
and visit Hong Na Ri who lives in Seoul.
Welcome to Ko Nan Gil's Hong Dumplings.
I need to check something.
We agreed to meet as a regular man and woman.
But why did we never get any closer?
How many chances to kiss did we miss?
I stopped counting after a while.
I did that well.
- Don't do that. - Na Ri.
Did you think about how hard it was for me to stop?
It was hard for me too.
If you had left, you would've disappeared from my life.
You said you'd wait, but thought about so many things.
Regular men and women think a lot when they date...
although it wasn't such a positive thought.
I almost disappeared from your life.
Welcome to my life.
(Sweet Stranger and Me)
I said to sleep at night. A family should eat together.
Are you sure I was your first love?
You were. But I returned to the real world.
It'll be a pain to end your relationship as family.
Just remain as neighborhood friends.
- I don't want to give up on her. - I can't do it.
What if Father comes home?
Father, please don't mention Duk Bong in front of me!
As you know, I'm Na Ri's man.
- Let's set a date. - Don't touch my personal life.
And I'm dating someone!
What? Father? I'm meeting your father?
Hey, Nan Gil. This place hasn't changed.
Do you want to work here?
The first time I said how I felt, I regretted it.
The second time, I thought we could part ways.
Now, I promise to spend every moment with you.
Na Ri.
Will you marry me?