(The following content may not be suitable for viewers under 15.)
(Viewer discretion is advised.)
(Last Episode)
I realized why our feelings were so complicated.
Now, all that remains is the situation between us.
Nan Gil, why do you want to leave?
Now that your dad returned,
I felt like I was...
being unreasonable insisting it was my house.
I felt uncomfortable and insecure.
I wanted to find my own place. Something like that.
So what? Will you shake it all off...
and find your place?
I've decided how to start.
I won't leave.
Hong Dumplings is where I belong.
I'll go on trips, make friends,
and visit Hong Na Ri who lives in Seoul.
Welcome to Ko Nan Gil's Hong Dumplings.
I need to check something.
We agreed to meet as a regular man and woman.
But why did we never get any closer?
How many chances to kiss did we miss?
I stopped counting after a while.
I did that well.
- Don't do that. - Na Ri.
Did you think about how hard it was for me to stop?
It was hard for me too.
If you had left,
you would've disappeared from my life.
You said you'd wait, but thought about so many things.
Regular men and women think a lot when they date...
although it wasn't such a positive thought.
I almost disappeared from your life.
Welcome to my life.
Get up.
I told you I won't let you change day and night.
We have to eat breakfast together to be family.
There won't be a family left in the world then.
Just get up.
Hurry up and get up.
I didn't notice before,
but you tend to be persistent.
I didn't notice before either,
but you tend to be disorganized.
Don't you feel bad for me since I didn't get any sleep?
If I felt sorry for you every time,
I wouldn't have the energy to knead.
Hey, am I really your first love?
Yes, I admit it.
However, I came back to reality.
I don't care. I'm sleeping for 10 more minutes.
Get up.
Okay. Okay, let me down.
Should we report it to the police?
- Thank you for the food. - Thank you for the food.
Enjoy your breakfast.
If you're distracted while you eat,
you can get indigestion and gain weight.
Stop scolding me.
Let's go visit your dad after you're done.
Answer me.
Dad doesn't like you.
I'll just tell him to change his mind...
since his daughter loves me so much.
What? Me? I never said that.
I don't recall.
Finish your food and clean it up.
- Then get ready to go. - See?
Do you see how pushy you are?
Is Lawyer Kwon Duk Bong busy?
Are you seeing him these days?
Duk Bong and I are just friends.
Why would he come visit you?
I'm just curious when the probation will be confirmed.
As for Lawyer Kwon,
he's such a likable guy and he's good looking too.
Ko Nan Gil.
Don't come along on visits anymore.
Dad.
If you need anything, please let me know.
Dad looked like he was uncomfortable with me at first,
- but he seems to have opened up. - I see.
Why can't you say a thing in front of him?
What will you do when he moves in?
Fine. I'll tell him straight out.
"Father, don't talk about Duk Bong in front of me!"
"As you already know, I'm Na Ri's man."
"If you give her stress, I won't sit still!"
What is it? You have more to threaten me with?
This is the original ledger. I won't threaten you.
You should take care of it with your father.
When is Na Ri's father getting out?
You should worry about yourself.
It's hard to annul your relationship to her.
You look like you're worried.
That's why you should have given up...
on being her father after the first trial.
I won't help you this time.
I won't ask you to help.
Then keep being her father if you don't want to leave.
Duk Bong. Don't you feel sorry to Na Ri's mother?
You know very well why she and I did that.
Are you scared of going against your father?
It's because I don't want to give up on Na Ri.
You can stay as her friend. I won't allow anymore.
(Marriage Annulment)
Let's go on a date after closing.
(From Nan Gil, Let's go on a date after closing!)
Excuse me. Can I help you?
Yes. I'm sorry,
but is it possible to leave this book here for later?
Sure. Is it a surprise for your girlfriend?
Yes. Thank you.
(Hong Na Ri's Footsteps)
- Have you been here before? - Yes.
- With who? - By myself.
Why?
(Hong Na Ri's Footsteps)
I was going to make a better one,
but I'm only good at making dumplings.
I collected all you wrote to your mom...
while you were working.
(Hong Na Ri's Footsteps)
Why did you title it this?
Remember when you were stuck in the shed?
I was reminded of the time we measured our footsteps.
This is a man's footstep. This is me.
This one near the shed is my footstep.
This one is...
I got it.
This is the footstep.
Let's try to remember just the romantic moments.
(First message)
(Second message)
I'm giving you this so you can start working again.
Why?
I want you to do what you're best at.
I know you're writing about traveling these days.
It's not going well, so you're cranky and can't sleep.
But look. The things you wrote while working are great.
Are you telling me to know myself and stop writing?
Is that why you want me to go back to work?
No, it's not like that. I like your writing.
Tell me what you like about it.
I've never been abroad before,
but I used to imagine it while reading this.
Anyway, thank you for my first book.
I was moved.
Let's go.
(Hong Na Ri's Footsteps)
I'm meeting Duk Bong.
You don't have to tell me everything.
Why are you seeing him anyway?
There's something I have to settle.
All right.
Why didn't you call first? Did you wait long?
No, I was looking at the robots.
It's an interesting place.
Also, this is what's fun about having a friend in town.
What is this? That expression doesn't suit you.
It's me feeling sorry.
Tell me exactly why you're sorry...
just like you did to Duk Shim.
I can't say it when you ask me like that.
Then should I stare at you until you tell me?
Tell me what you're sorry about.
I'm Kwon Duk Bong. I just drove you here.
- I said, I'm Kwon Duk Bong. - Okay.
I'm Kwon Duk Bong.
- Watch what you say! - Be quiet!
Now that I think about it,
I feel bad starting with our first meeting.
Do you know how cranky you were then?
You weren't much of a nice person either.
Did I say that I'd help? When?
I'm not the type to help anyone.
You two are family, right?
Families don't play hard to get.
I'm sorry I never sold the property.
I gave up like the big man. Don't be sorry.
I know you quit law because you hate it.
I'm sorry I made you do it again.
Thanks for acknowledging.
Aside from all that, I think there's something else.
You should consider seeing a man named Kwon Duk Bong.
Not yet.
You can just say that you'll consider it.
Why are you declining right away?
You said I gave you the best compliment in a while.
I'm sorry, Neighborhood Friend.
Have you really never considered...
the possibility of the two of us?
What a firm decline.
Since I was dumped, should I hate this place too?
I should just quit work.
Don't say that you were dumped.
Come on. Let's go for a walk.
What is it?
I should have taken over the leader's role.
I can't forget the texture of that uniform.
Gosh.
I could have been promoted, but I gave it up myself.
Yong Kyu, don't disappoint me...
when you're looking so good for once.
I look good?
I look good? Really?
(Government Affairs)
They're here again.
It doesn't even surprise me anymore.
Are you here again?
Boss! Boss.
(Unauthorized buildings)
When did you take this?
What are you doing to my face?
This right here is me.
You're really offending me.
We were reported that this is an unlicensed building.
This building has been up for 20 years.
Here. The stand, the tent, and the poles...
are illegal extensions.
My face isn't illegal. Apologize to me.
Was it Greenland that reported us again?
They keep on trying to break down such a small store.
Did you ever predict that I would never beat Nan Gil?
When I called you as the witness...
Whether it was true or not...
you were listening to Nan Gil's shameful past.
But Nan Gil remained unaffected.
What can be said about Ko Nan Gil?
He was called the legendary Ko Nan Gil.
He was notorious that even the people...
in that field avoided him.
He didn't bat an eye receiving 10 times the principal.
He boasted about being an ex-convict...
as if it were something to be proud of.
Deep down, it must have been difficult for him.
I don't like revealing my secrets.
I also don't like talking about it first.
But my family's shameful past will soon be broadcast.
Na Ri,
you will still be my neighborhood friend, right?
Of course.
Is this much difference still an illegal extension?
They are torturing us meticulously.
Gosh.
He is just in time.
Mr. Robot,
Boss is not saying anything to maintain his dignity.
But Greenland is constantly bullying the store.
- What? -They are reporting us at least once a day.
Today, the problem was illegal extension.
We have to pay a heavy fine.
I'm going now.
(Report on sales for the second half of the year)
- Yes. - Send the files regarding the company's...
illegal waste disposal to the broadcasting station.
Right now?
But what if Chairman Kwon finds out about this?
I will tell him about this myself.
The illegal waste disposal incident of Greenland...
will have a significantly negative effect on its image.
Today, Chairman Kwon will hold a press conference...
- regarding this incident. - He's here.
- Chairman Kwon! - It's him!
When did you first find out about this?
Do you admit to having illegally disposed of waste?
Did you directly order the illegal disposal of waste?
- Do you acknowledge your fault? - Do you admit it?
To start with,
(The press conference of Chairman Kwon)
I would like to express my deepest regrets...
to the victims of the accident.
Duk Shim,
he's still your father.
Cheer up.
What are you doing right now?
Oh gosh, don't get me wrong.
It's a V for victory.
Cheer up, Duk Shim.
I fully realize the responsibility...
as the chairman of Greenland of not fulfilling...
the expectations and the trust of the citizens.
I will cooperate with the authorities concerned...
and promise to actively aid in the childcare support...
of underprivileged children in the future.
How will you aid the childcare support projects?
- One word please. - When did you first find out?
- Chairman Kwon. - Chairman Kwon.
One more word please.
It feels weird to have done something righteous.
Neighborhood Friend, let's have a drink.
It's Champagne.
Nan Gil is here too.
Let's settle the relationships between us three.
You two like settling relationships a lot.
Be quiet.
Let's be neighborhood friends too.
Be quiet? Are you talking to me?
She acts a bit arrogantly.
She is being wise.
She is also a bit prickly.
It's better than smiling any time.
She is stubborn.
She simply knows what she likes and dislikes.
She is a bit reckless.
She does have a positive drive.
Why doesn't she pretend to be pretty?
It's because she is pretty.
- What are you doing? - Gossiping about you.
Bragging about my girlfriend.
I have to go now.
I'm not happy watching you two together.
But then, why don't you two settle your relationship?
Are you two going to stay as a father and daughter?
Why don't you answer whenever I ask about this?
Na Ri.
Nan Gil.
Do you like your relationship as it is?
- No. - Of course not.
As a friend, I will help settle your relationship.
See you at court.
He really likes to settle things down.
Isn't it true that we have to settle our relationship?
That means we have to go through another trial.
What are you two doing here?
When Duk Shim ran away from home,
you came to me for help.
Now, Duk Shim asked for help regarding you.
Am I a connecting bridge for brother and sister?
How is Mother? Is she all right?
She said, "What wrong with your brother's personality?"
"My low blood pressure is going up."
That's how she's like.
I'm off to work now.
Duk Bong.
Why?
You don't want me to be like this?
I am also irritated by how cool I am.
No, that's not it.
Don't ever call me again.
Tell Duk Shim not to call me too.
All right.
Na Ri told me to be honest. So I'm saying this.
I really like you.
You know why I like you because I tell you every time.
So don't call me as a friend...
or as a connecting bridge to your sister.
If you call me again,
I will just consider it as dating.
You are here.
Where is Nan Gil?
You told him not to come. That's why I am here alone.
Did I?
You don't like Nan Gil.
Who said I didn't like him?
He manages Hong Dumplings so well even without me.
He's much better than I thought he'd be.
Let's go.
- Welcome. - Hi.
- You must've been through a lot. - It's okay.
Nan Gil, get me a uniform.
I'm the original owner, you see.
I want a uniform of my own too.
Sure.
Why do you need a uniform?
You can't even make dumplings.
I'll try to learn.
Hello?
Yes. I see.
The trial date has been assigned.
(Courthouse)
Your honor.
Ms. Shin Jung Im tried to protect the land...
to honor the victims of the accident.
Now, the land will be donated as a memorial park.
Mr. Ko Nan Gil came this far because...
he wanted to respect her will.
They decided to register for their marriage...
to protect the land from Da Da's unlawful pressures.
Please understand that it was their best option.
I understand Shin Jung Im's honorable intent,
and given the 20 years they were...
threatened by the lenders,
I hereby annul Shin Jung Im and Ko Nan Gil's marriage.
(Courthouse)
Yes! It's over!
Who are you? Who are you to say my house is yours?
Who are you really?
So? Who are you?
The legendary Ko Nan Gil.
You must be proud of that nickname.
The legendary Ko Nan Gil...
who loved one woman for all his life.
Now that our relationship has been cleared up,
what should we call each other?
You care so much about things like that.
What do you want me to call you?
Honey?
Sweetie?
Na Ri, what were you imagining? I won't do it.
Na Ri! Stop right there.
Na Ri.
Let's go.
For me, I have many words that mean "Hong Na Ri"...
since I was always looking at and thinking of you.
Tell me what means "Hong Na Ri".
Pretending it doesn't hurt to get hit by a slingshot.
Reading while walking.
Chasing after the tofu vendor's bell.
Blowing on a dandelion.
I'm going to drop you.
- I'm letting go. - No. Don't.
What is your relationship with Ko Nan Gil?
He's my stepfather.
We've legally confirmed our relationship.
Take care.
What happened to you?
What did you do? What did you do and where?
Stay still.
What does a long distance relationship need?
I'll send texts, photos, and childish heart emoticons.
But I'll call often too.
So come whenever you miss me.
I'll run over if you call.
I'm going to start waiting now.
I love you, Na Ri.
(1 year later)
The tarot reading was right for both of you?
Yes. She said I'd meet a man this year.
She said I'd set a date.
Wow. The year's almost over too.
Na Ri, let's get a tarot reading too.
Don't ask me to do things with you.
Hello.
We see you often.
He keeps getting handsome. You should be nervous.
Bye.
- Bye. - Bye.
He picks her up every time since she returned to work.
That can't be easy. He's never late either.
You can't learn from that.
They're not your average couple. They never even fight.
You dress up too much whenever you come here.
Is that how I look? Good. I tried hard to impress.
Impress whom?
You, of course. We haven't seen each other in days.
Don't dress up anymore. Wear comfortable clothes.
- What? - You're so pretty.
What's gotten into you? You see me all the time.
Something's up. Did you do something wrong?
Is it the restaurant?
I'd better not compliment you again. Let's go.
I want to go somewhere.
Our company is broke because of you.
Don't be a crybaby. I'm not blind.
I feel so secure now that our CEO...
has a platform to stand on.
What's gotten into you?
Duk Bong.
I was wrong.
I met with Suh Young and got on my knees.
I fixed your broken engagement.
It's not like there's a deep grudge or anything.
It looks like she hasn't gotten over you either.
I told you not to touch my personal life.
We're merging with Suh Won Group...
with your marriage to Suh Young as the foundation.
- Let's set a date. - You'll merge...
and fire the employees?
We're not a charity!
We need to make up the money we lost to the foundation!
Mr. Chairman. Did you forget what I have on you?
And I'm dating someone!
The magic ball?
We don't do that anymore.
Let's look into your future.
Okay.
Pick two cards.
Unbelievable.
This is almost impossible to see.
The completion card.
You've accomplished everything.
"Legend".
Mr. Ko Nan Gil, you are a legend.
Next.
"Expansion". You must be expanding your business.
What business are you expanding?
- Get up. - Why? I want to try too.
- What? - Excuses me.
What? She seems to be right.
Your girlfriend wants to try it. What is it?
- Let's go. Let's go. - What?
Excuse me. Excuse me.
They are each other's destiny.
I'm jealous.
So jealous.
You want to say something, right?
Why were you shocked when she mentioned the business?
Have some cake first.
Why are you trying to sugar me up first?
I was going to tell you...
after you get some rest.
I'm not moody.
I'm not stressed and I don't have insomnia.
So I can handle anything. Tell me.
- Your father and uncle... - No.
No, don't.
What did they do this time?
Tell me.
They signed a contract to franchise out Hong Dumplings.
- It's so busy. - Right?
- Is there room inside? - Yes. Go on in.
Thank you.
My gosh.
Look.
It's good.
Let's sign.
- Hello. - Hello.
Hello.
It's nice to meet you.
- The dumplings are delicious. - They are?
They're the best I've tasted.
This is my ID.
- It says, "Hong Sung Kyu", right? - I see.
Have you seen the TV program?
Yes, we heard it was on TV.
Mr. Hong here...
was on an expedition to find hidden dumplings masters.
But his mentees searched desperately for him on TV,
so he put an end to his expedition...
and returned to the restaurant.
That's right. I wore this outfit...
to start a new life.
And my son-in-law, Ko Nan Gil,
will teach you how to get the flavor.
Here we go. Smile.
That's what happened.
That's great.
How is that great?
It's the best thing Father and Uncle did so far.
You must be so happy. How did you keep it in?
It's only in Seoul now,
but imagine Hong Dumplings being across the nation.
What about "Flying Couple" as a marketing theme?
- What? - Ko Nan Gil and Hong Na Ri's...
Flying Couple's Hong Dumplings.
"Hong Dumplings. Let's walk on a flowery path."
You don't even like dumplings.
I love them now.
You don't know how to make them.
I'm a quick learner.
I'll learn from today on.
We're in trouble now.
Hong Dumplings. Ko Nan Gil.
I met with Suh Young and got on my knees.
I fixed your broken engagement.
It's not like there's a deep grudge or anything.
It looks like she hasn't gotten over you either.
Duk Bong. You must've forgotten. I said...
if you call me,
I'll understand it as we're dating.
We can discuss that later.
I need you to do one of your skits.
A revenge scenario this time.
A revenge scenario? For your past love?
Oh my gosh. Only losers do that.
Whom are you calling me a loser?
Do you think I'd do that?
Then who is it?
- My father. - What?
Your... Your father?
I'm meeting your father?
Here.
Those are the receipts.
What's with the prices?
A bag and clothes?
Do you think I own clothes this conservative?
I wrote my account number on the receipt.
My credit card is almost maxed out.
Please deposit it soon.
Okay.
It's been a year.
So Duk Bong. What should I do?
Duk Shim, come on. Your brother's girlfriend is coming.
Greet your father.
Hello.
Oh my gosh.
Yeo Joo, they are my parents.
Hello. I'm Do Yeo Joo.
Awesome.
Doesn't she look like Suh Young?
No. She looks just like her.
Mr. Chairman. What do we do about the merger now?
Are you really dating?
- No. - Yes.
Why are your responses different?
I don't care. Do as you wish.
I said if you call, we're dating, so let's date.
First,
why don't we become friends and get to know each other?
I'll get busy from now on.
I'm fine with that.
- Even if you don't see me often? - Yes.
- Even if I don't call? - Yes.
Will you come if I say so?
- Yes. - Just make money, is that it?
- Yes. - May I see other women?
Hey!
To a beginner farmer, a year is...
a time to learn spring, summer, fall, and winter.
That's how our year was.
It's a rare day off. Must we clean?
Let's throw this out. It just takes up room.
No, no.
You can't throw this out.
It's a rare day off. Must we clean all day long?
You're the one who wanted to clean.
You raise your voice at me now.
You're mad at me, aren't you?
You're annoyed about something else, right?
I'm mad about Dad.
Why are you taking it out on me?
Then who else?
We argue about little things.
We talk about the past.
I've been thinking,
and the trip to Yeosu...
All I remember is your apologizing.
We didn't even get to have sashimi on the beach.
It's your fault.
What? Why are you suddenly bringing that up?
I suddenly remembered.
But still. It was a really nice day out.
The ocean looked pretty too.
We talk about the future.
If we get married,
do you want kids?
Yes.
How many?
Maybe 2 or 3? What about you?
Are we having kids separately?
Should we live here forever?
Do you mean you want to have kids and live here?
It's cold. Let's go.
Speed it up already.
You're so slow.
- Seriously. - Why don't you help us?
Hurry it up.
It's done. Light it up.
There.
- Merry Christmas. - Merry Christmas.
And we spend these moments together.
I'm busy again. I'll come to the terminal.
Okay.
- Have a nice day. - Have a nice day.
It's hard to see Nan Gil lately.
He's been busy.
I'm sure. He has been busy.
He's popular with the ladies too.
How do you know that?
Haven't you been on Hong Dumplings' social media page?
Look.
As more franchise locations open up,
more and more people...
come to the restaurant to learn how to make dumplings.
Look at how many people like the pictures with Nan Gil.
He's like a celebrity.
He's especially popular among women.
You had no idea, did you?
Hong Dumplings is more famous...
than the robot museum in Seulgi-ri now.
Here it is.
I really like it.
I'm happy that Nan Gil has more friends and is busy.
I'm happy that he's living a regular person's life.
I'm happy that you're happy.
But I'm worried.
What if he gets so engrossed in his work...
that another year or two just whizzes by?
Don't stay in Seulgi-ri, being all lonely.
Just get a place in Seoul.
Sure. I'm happy with anything.
I'm happy that you're happy.
What makes you happy?
Na Ri. Someone like Nan Gil...
is at most one-in-a-million.
Don't get jealous because other women like him.
I'm not jealous.
Thank you.
For what?
Thanks to you,
I was able to mature, at least just a little bit.
- People don't change. - Come on.
- I'll see you at the next flight. - Okay. Bye.
The dough is half the flavor of the dumplings,
so you need to knead it with heart.
Remember how it feels when it's kneaded the best.
Okay, then. I'll take over and check your dough.
Excuse me. Excuse me.
Look at me. Look at me.
Hey, Nan Gil.
This place hasn't changed.
- Do you want to work here? - Fool.
- Do you think I'd work under you? - Is that so?
Do you want some kimchi dumplings? There's tofu in it.
Kimchi dumplings? Stuff yourself.
(Hong Dumplings)
I wanted to pick you up.
You should've called at the terminal.
Or you should've taken a cab.
- Aren't you cold? - I'm not cold.
I took a cab all the way from the terminal.
I've missed you.
How much?
- A lot. - How much, a lot?
Every time I kneaded dough or made dumplings.
From the moment I woke up until I fell asleep.
I think I'll get a place in Seoul.
Why?
It's tiring going back and forth, and I can come visit.
I want my own time.
No.
I don't need permission. You're not my stepdad.
Definitely not.
There's a nice studio available.
Then get it.
I'll commute from there.
What do you mean?
Drink your coffee.
I want to stop. I can't sleep.
Drink more.
No. I'm tired from the long flight.
- Na Ri. - What?
Na Ri?
(Will you marry me?)
Marry me.
(Marry me.)
That won't do.
What are you doing?
What is that?
What?
A customer must've left it.
A customer? Leave something this big?
- Why are you poking the doll? - Well...
I have an early flight, so I'm going to bed.
Okay.
- You stupid. - Marry me.
Marry me. Marry me. Marry me.
That was a good nap.
That must have been entertaining.
Na Ri. Just trust me.
Trust me.
Ko Nan Gil!
What's wrong? Hold on.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry, Nan Gil.
- I'm so sorry. - What are you sorry about?
I'm sorry I can't remember anything.
I'm sorry and I'm thankful.
Welcome to my life.
Do you want to go inside?
Okay.
(Hong Na Ri, will you marry me?)
The first time I said how I felt...
I'm sorry...
for loving you.
I regretted it.
The second time...
Na Ri.
Let's date as an average couple who can do anything.
I thought we could part ways.
Now, finally,
I promise to spend every moment with you.
Na Ri.
Will you marry me?
Okay. Let's get married.
Do you and Duk Shim keep in touch?
I'm sure she's fine.
I have plenty of girl fans other than her.
What girls? They're all older women.
Didn't you see the students lined up to take a picture?
Whatever. They were all older women.
They were.
Do everything yourselves. I'm out.
Excuse me. My daughter brought this cake.
She's a stewardess.
- Mom. - It's delicious.
- Please have some. - Isn't she pretty?
- She is. - Enjoy.
- You have some too. - Okay.
Dad, try it.
Goodness.
Hello.
You won't build the resort.
So why are you still here?
Pack up...
and return to the company.
Our family is finally recovering.
Let me be free.
He's right.
It's nice coming down once in a while.
Can't you wear something different already?
This is my style.
Daddy.
Okay, okay. My dear son.
When are you getting married?
What about this spring?
That would be nice.
That's right. Hurry it up already.
Loving someone...
is loving a person, their family, and their history.
Hong Dumplings is Hong Na Ri's...
And Ko Nan Gil's Hong Dumplings.
And loving someone...
is walking the path of life together like family.
(Sweet Stranger and Me)
(Thank you for watching Sweet Stranger and Me.)