(The following content may not be suitable for viewers under 15.)
(Viewer discretion is advised.)
(Episode 2)
Who are you? Who are you to say my house is yours?
Who are you really?
Your father.
See? I was right. My father did send you.
I'm not saying your father Hong Sung Kyu, but me.
- What? - I am...
Hong Na Ri's stepfather.
So I won't watch you lose your sight,
become malnourished or lack sleep from stress.
So I will keep caring.
I'll let you know once the results are out.
What is he talking about? I'm speechless.
I wanted to tell you little by little.
How old are you, kid?
I just told you I'm your stepdad.
Isn't that a bit disrespectful?
You should've done your research. My mom passed away.
How could I have a stepdad when I don't have a mom?
- Who are you? - I told you. Your dad.
You shouldn't be calling me as kid. Don't you think?
Jung Im and I registered our marriage last year.
What? Jung Im?
Hey! You con artist gigolo!
Calling me those names...
is an insult to your mother.
The day I met you by the tree...
was our one-year anniversary.
You could've registered the marriage by yourself.
I'm sure my innocent mom didn't know anything.
Of course, she did. She went with me.
Are you saying my mom went with a kid like you,
- I mean, with you to the... - Borough hall.
That's right.
Whatever. Why didn't you say anything by the tree then?
Look how you're reacting even now.
I couldn't just say I was your dad back then.
I said I'd see you again.
Why didn't you tell me last night then?
You were drunk and out of your mind.
- How could I say I'm your dad? - Stop saying that.
You're a stress ball. You have rage within you.
You can't control your emotions.
You get stressed out and can't sleep.
Then you get wrinkles and age.
Look here. I don't have many...
winkles I think.
Are you asking me?
- You're stressed out and can't sleep... - A photo.
You must have a photo as proof.
Stepdad, you should show me proof.
Like a photograph.
There's nothing out of the ordinary.
I think it was temporary loss of sight due to stress.
You get stressed very easily.
When there is nothing noticeably wrong,
many question the diagnosis, but...
- Are you married? - Yes, I am.
How did you register your marriage?
Did you go to a borough hall?
Do both people go?
Don't you need witnesses?
A person really needs to help others.
I helped a neighbor, and blessings came my way.
Let's enter into a contract.
What's the contract for?
Sell your land for half the price we had offered.
I'll buy it right now.
Here. Sign it.
You should've sold it sooner.
If Hong Na Ri goes to court, you can't rest assured.
So be satisfied with this price...
- and sell. - Goes to court for what?
To cancel the marriage and reclaim her inheritance...
Fraud... Shall I go on?
You want to sign with someone you think is a fraud?
It's not like you scammed me.
But legally, that land belongs to you.
Even if you give me 10 times your first offer,
I won't sell.
You must be obsessed with money.
Snap out of it. We'll get it eventually.
I don't know how you conned an old lady 30 years older.
- Watch your mouth! - Watch your mouth!
That was disrespectful toward my late mom.
Apologize right this instant.
I didn't know you were listening.
- I'm sorry. - Is it my fault for hearing?
What kind of insincere and fake apology is that?
I'm sorry. Sorry.
What were the test results?
There's nothing wrong.
Isn't that great?
Why is she angry at me instead of the con artist?
Let her lose the house, land and everything.
- Ms. Hong Na Ri. - Yes.
Father? You should make your cons more believable.
Don't live like that.
You insulted my mom and me, you con artist!
I won't let you take my house. I'll protect it!
You don't belong in my house, but behind bars.
Let's go to the police. Let's go to the police!
Why you...
My mom said she had something to tell me.
Was that something about her getting married?
Do you really expect me to believe you?
Do you expect me to treat you like my stepdad?
No! I know my mom.
I'd never lose the house. We're strangers!
Get out of my house!
- Let's go. - What?
(Mother)
Hello, Mother.
Na Ri?
Are the invitations printed?
Dong Jin must be busy. He won't pick up.
You should've called us.
I'll tell Dong Jin to give you a call.
- I can't talk right now. - You must be mid-flight.
- I'll talk to you later. - Okay.
Get in. You may look well, but you were just in the ER.
You saw correctly. I'm fine.
- Just leave. - Shin Jung Im...
is your mother, right?
- Do you know my mom? - Just get in.
How do you know my mom?
I wanted to buy her restaurant.
Do you sell dumplings?
Me? No.
I need that land.
- I'm sure she refused to sell. - She does.
I'm sure she did.
If Mom refused to sell, so do I.
- I'm getting out. - Wake up.
It's not that you won't sell. You can't.
It's under Ko Nan Gil's name.
That punk really is a con artist and gigolo.
I didn't mean to insult you,
but you should assess the situation.
How could that be? That's absurd.
I've never seen him before. How could he...
She converted everything into joint ownership.
Isn't that odd?
She registered her marriage without telling her child.
She changed the deed. Then there was a car accident.
(Yangpyeong Pharmacy)
Think before you speak.
Let's be logical.
Do not get angry.
- Hello. - Where are you going?
- Hi. - Hello.
Let's eat!
- Welcome. - Hello.
Hello.
What are you doing? Come in.
I'll put you in a quiet room with great scenery.
Scenery helps end a lovers' quarrel.
- No, we're father and... - Yes.
Thank you for the quiet room.
Okay. Come in.
Whether people think we're a couple or siblings,
don't correct them.
Don't ever say we're father and daughter again.
That's the source of stress.
You're worried about what others will think.
Why do you care what they think?
We're not a couple. We're not friends.
We're not siblings, either.
Lying because of other people...
How old are you?
You have a lot of rage. You must be stressed out.
How could you be so stressed that you can't see?
You're avoiding the question. Are you younger than me?
We don't need to discuss our age in our relationship.
Let's speak formally since the situations are unclear.
Please eat, take your medicine,
get stronger and go to Seoul.
Please go to a big hospital once you're there.
Eat well and sleep well.
Don't be stressed. Okay?
You want me to disappear from your sight because...
you feel guilty. Is that it? Not a chance.
I'll eat, take my medicine and get stronger.
And then we should talk.
Eat slowly. Chew it well.
If you keep acting like a dad, I'll get angry.
I can't say my daughter is my daughter.
She won't say her father is her father.
Do you think I'm joking?
Have you thought about how I'd feel?
What feelings?
Is it that you're upset about your mom's getting...
married without telling you?
- Did you have a ceremony? - Or...
is it that you're flustered because a stranger is...
living in the house you thought you'd inherit?
Dong Jin.
You look pretty.
I must look pretty because it's been a while.
- Were you surprised that I wanted to meet? - No.
I should've called first.
- I'm sorry. - Don't say things like that.
I asked to meet during lunch to keep it brief.
I don't think we ended it properly.
And I wondered what the status was...
with Na Ri.
That's right. Na Ri was in the ER.
I need to go.
What? Why?
Is she sick?
No. You should go.
- Go. - Okay.
Wait here. I'll drop you off on the way.
- No, it's okay. - It's okay.
Darn it. She's playing dirty.
How is it not shocking?
I can understand that my mom married a young man...
and she gave him everything she had.
If she were alive, I could understand it all,
but it's too strange.
I can't accept it.
If she were alive...
Sure.
I say that several times a day.
Every single day.
I know too well that there are cars...
that drive recklessly.
Why did she have to be there?
My mom said she wanted to tell me something in person.
I kept making excuses that I was busy...
and didn't go home.
Was this what my mom...
wanted to tell me?
Probably.
Answer honestly to my questions.
No.
If I must lie, I won't answer.
Did my mom talk about me?
Not really.
How long have you worked at our dumpling place?
- It was before we registered our marriage... - So?
You happened to go to a dumpling place in the boonies,
happened to work there...
and happened to meet my mom and marry her.
- Is that it? - No.
I was predestined to meet her.
Then why did I never see you?
You came at night or when the restaurant was closed.
And when you came, all you did was sleep in your room.
- I avoided you sometimes. - Why did you avoid me?
Do you still go to my mom?
I go often during her favorite hours.
I like these hours the best.
It's awkward to start anything. You feel awkward.
You don't know if you're feeling hungry.
You feel like someone will come or not.
It's time for the tofu seller to come.
Na Ri, let's go down a little later.
Na Ri!
- Snake! - Where? Where?
Snake. Snake! Over there!
Where? Where?
Did you marry her because you were in love?
Time's up.
You're not answering instead of lying.
I married her because I was in love.
She didn't show it at work, but it must've been hard.
What's wrong with her?
I didn't hear from her directly, so...
Then who called you?
I don't know who, but I was told she left the ER...
and to just come home.
I'm glad. I guess it wasn't that serious.
Dong Jin.
What?
If I ask you to stay with me for a little while longer,
can you do that for me?
With you?
You're swaying. Stupid.
I wanted to say that just once.
Be good to Na Ri.
Don't cheat on her again.
All I need is to see your face from time to time.
Can't we do that, either?
We can just make sure we don't get caught.
What?
Well, that is... Sure.
We can be careful. Yes.
That's right, but...
I'd feel too bad.
Never mind.
I have no pride.
I don't want to hurt any more, either.
Thank you for everything.
Bye.
Hey...
I... Yeo Joo...
Yeo Joo! Wait.
What did you do with Mom's things?
- I took care of them. - That's my job.
- The father comes first. - Stop saying that!
You won't admit your father is your father.
(Hong Dumplings)
Are these people lined up to buy dumplings?
Boss. Is everything okay?
Is everything okay?
You're okay.
Yes.
Right? The boss' daughter.
Gosh!
Boss said his daughter was coming and waited every day.
You came super late with a bang.
But thank you.
I heard you're a stewardess.
I knew I'd meet a stewardess someday.
- Then are you close to junior stewardesses? - No.
My junior stewardess is my enemy.
What are you doing? Prepare the boxes.
Do it.
My hands are sore.
Don't do it. Go in. Go in.
I said to go in.
What a daughter's daddy!
Boss said his daughter was coming and waited every day.
That punk really is a con artist and gigolo.
That's right. I'm sure you're hiding a lot of things.
The layout changed.
So this is a bedroom now. It's big.
Gosh, that hurts.
Get out.
What is that?
Is she kneading the dough because she's family?
Throw these out.
They're tainted, so throw them out!
- Throw them out. - Tainted?
He's overreacting.
Wow. There's so much tension between them.
Hey...
Don't go in there again.
Why isn't it coming off?
What were you looking for in my room?
- What will make you feel better? - Mom's phone.
I told you I put her things away.
You're not looking for her phone.
You probably want proof that I'm a con artist.
But you won't find any because I'm not.
Good people living average lives...
don't lock their desk drawers like you.
Why did you bring a shovel?
Your uncle can't be reached,
and you thought your house was abandoned.
You lived here, so you know how quickly the weeds grow.
That's why you bought a shovel.
You were drunk, so you bought a huge one.
But that wouldn't have sufficed.
A vacant house crumbles quickly.
It knows that it has been abandoned.
Are you saying I abandoned this house?
Uncle said he'd look after it and I needed time.
What did you do while seasons changed?
You must accept certain things even if it's hard.
Even if you find something on me, it won't change...
the fact that I'm your father and the house is mine.
Your last name is Ko and mine is Hong.
Stop saying you're my father. We're strangers.
You were quick just as I wanted.
- Then you can just leave. - Why would I leave?
Why would strangers live together?
- I'm Mom's only family. - No, I am.
Hong Dumplings was for Hong Na Ri.
Since I run it, I'm your father.
To be more exact, I'm your stepdad.
You seem strong now. Why don't you make dinner?
I'm going to bring a guest.
Were you talking to me?
I have everything you need in the refrigerator,
so I look forward to seeing...
your cooking skills.
Our chairman is so good at evading taxes.
A robot museum.
Isn't that romantic?
We still haven't received the grant in certain areas.
It's too soon to start the resort business.
Just do it. We need to create waves so they'd give...
permission to prevent conglomerates...
from going bankrupt.
That's it. This was the look she gave me.
It was like I made her sick.
You know...
what kind of person I am, so I understand.
But it isn't easy to think that after just meeting me.
Especially women near that age.
She must know what you see isn't all.
I know I'm annoying and a scumbag.
That's why I hide it so well. I fool myself at times.
Look into that unique woman.
Her name is Hong Na Ri. She's Hong Dumplings' daughter.
"I look forward to seeing your cooking"?
Why that...
What am I doing?
Am I really going to do it?
Mom, please clean.
What a neat-freak. He's like a master in organizing.
- Mom! - Gosh!
You startled me. What?
What's wrong with the refrigerator?
Don't change so suddenly. It's scary!
I... I didn't do that.
People don't change that easily. Don't worry.
Mom,
is this situation for real?
Did he think I couldn't do it?
What's with the suit?
No.
He is my stepdad. He is my stepdad.
He is my stepdad.
Well... Father...
Dinner's ready.
The guest is being late. Would you like to wait longer?
- Aren't you hungry? - Excuse me?
No. Let's wait a while longer.
Would you like a drink while waiting?
What's with her?
- Is it an important guest? - Of course.
My mom could only grow weeds. You're not bad.
The garden is her style.
She liked baby's breath, too.
They're buckwheat flowers.
What? I see, buckwheat flowers.
Your tie got loosened.
I've decided to accept you.
I trust Mom's choice.
I felt like she had a secret.
If I had been a better daughter,
she probably would've told me first.
You were a good daughter. She said you were the best.
That's nice to hear.
Let's get along.
It's not like we'll see each other often, though.
Na Ri. What are you doing?
Here's my son-in-law!
I'm glad you came.
Son-in-law?
The funeral. The fixer.
The fixer?
I thought you worked at the funeral place.
You were family.
No wonder you worked so hard.
- Why are you here? - Are you okay?
- I heard you went to the ER. - How did you know?
I called him.
So you're the one who called.
But did you just talk down to Na Ri...
Who gave you his number? Did you go through my phone?
I got his business card at the funeral.
- Why do you keep talking down... - Regardless.
How could you do this without asking?
Watch what you say.
What's going on?
Is something wrong?
Why do you keep talking down...
He worked hard at the funeral like family.
Everyone considers him family.
He's the one person you can lean on.
He should know you went to the ER.
I have no desire to lean on anyone.
Why are you speaking formally...
Did you make a big mistake?
What?
- Why is he talking down to me? - Stay out of it.
- Just leave. - No. Take her with you.
"Take her with you"? Are you talking to me?
Take her to a big hospital in Seoul to get tested.
They say it's stress. Don't stress her out...
I said no. What kind of father does that?
- Why you... - Father?
I said no, so don't do this again.
It's none of your business.
Leave.
- Why that... - Hey, you!
What did you do?
I'm sorry about calling...
without asking.
I said I'd accept you out of my trust for my mom.
If you're my father, you should at least punch him.
Excuse me.
I don't understand what's going on.
Would you explain it to me?
You should leave for today.
Na Ri, are you stupid?
- You're just so stupid! - How dare you come in here?
Fine.
I know you're angry, but let me talk.
Stay out of my business and leave.
How could I not care?
Was she out of her mind?
Whom are you talking about?
He seduced your innocent mother.
He's obviously a con artist!
Are you stupid? Why are you being polite to him?
What does he want? Does he want money?
Does he plan to live here?
What? Why are you packing?
Did he say this is his house? Did he tell you to leave?
- Why that... - Stay out of it.
And don't insult my mom. I trust her.
You're pathetic.
You know.
You feel it too.
It's obvious to anyone.
Your mother fell for a young gigolo!
Did your mother really die in a car accident?
Do you know how the accident occurred?
What about your uncle?
Since when did you lose touch with him?
(Are you in a meeting? I feel bad.)
Why is she texting in pieces?
(How's Na Ri? Is she okay? Call me after.)
It must be going well. You're texting while exercising.
No.
He lied that he had a meeting...
and went to see his old girlfriend.
- I played dumb. - But you look happy.
He's lying to me.
What do you mean?
He used to talk about his girlfriend openly.
That meant I couldn't call when he was with her.
But now, he's lying to me.
I'm his first now.
Lucky you. You're his first.
Please leave.
Hold on. Do you know how much this house is worth?
Are you here to valuate our house?
This is a hot spot.
Resorts are lined up to develop this area.
He knew that and conned her.
He planned it from the start. Hey. Wait.
What about the 30,000 dollars?
- I'll pay you back. - Why would you pay for that?
This house is yours.
Even if you end it with me, protect this house.
Did you say you trust your mom's choice?
Don't be so naive.
Your mom and you were fooled because of that!
What is it?
Come and eat so you can take your medicine.
Okay.
Hey. You.
You overheard us, didn't you?
You feel guilty, don't you?
You chose the wrong target for your con.
Do you know how many lawyers and judges I know?
I don't care, so I won't ask.
Not at all.
I'm going to go knead.
Don't even try.
Pack your things and get out, you con artist gigolo!
Who is she?
It's my building. I told you not to lock your door.
I heard you're skipping school.
It's your life, so I don't really care.
But come to think of it, I need to take over this town.
I'm pretty famous.
So my sister can't be like this.
I'm confiscating this. Why?
Because you didn't buy anything in here.
Each time you miss class, I'll confiscate each item.
Let's negotiate.
- Okay. - I get one warning and you return it.
- Today is a warning. - Fine. Today is a warning.
But if you skip again, you and this room are gone.
This is what you call a negotiation. Or a threat.
I'm going to Seoul.
Don't try anything or you're dead.
Let's get along.
Oh my gosh.
- Give me your number. - Okay.
If I were the sky
I would like to tinge your face.
Just like the red glow tinging the evening
I would like to tinge your cheeks.
If I were a poet
I would sing for you.
Just like a little child nestling in its mom's bosom
I would like to sing happily.
- Sing for me. - What?
You must know it. Mom sang it all the time.
Who? Me?
Now?
- I... - Yes! Go on.
If I were the sky
I would like to tinge your face.
What do you do when you miss Mom?
I close my eyes...
and say, "I miss you." Then I see her.
She's always smiling.
I'm going to catch the last bus.
Good.
- You look happy that I'm leaving. - No, not at all.
- I'll pick up my things later. - Okay, okay.
No, I mean... You can leave them.
Go to a hospital in Seoul. Don't be stressed.
Eat and sleep well.
Look at you. You have dark circles, your skin is dry,
and you have wrinkles...
Stop talking about wrinkles! That's stressful.
Wait. Wait.
Wait. Wait right there.
- Get in. - No.
I was wrong.
But you broke up with me like you were waiting.
Isn't it embarrassing to say that?
Tell your mother it's over, and take her calls.
I regretted not calling the most.
You act like you're so smart.
You'll never earn this much money.
- Is this a joke to you? - Are you upset...
because it was almost yours?
Get your head on straight.
It was your mom's, so it's yours.
- Your mom would want you to have it. - Who cares?
- Stop being so materialistic! - What? Materialistic?
Pay back my 30,000 dollars then. Right now.
Pay it back first.
What are you doing?
- Na Ri? - Do you know him?
What is it this time?
Darn it.
What is it?
The entire neighborhood will be here soon.
- What is it? - Dumplings.
Wow, is that a parent's love?
You need to eat home cooking to fight insomnia,
stress, dark circles,
- and wrinkles. - Enough already.
Hold on. Home cooking should include...
rice, soup, side dishes, and all.
Dumplings from Hong Dumplings isn't home cooking.
It's Hong Na Ri's Hong Dumplings, so it's home cooking.
Hey. If you're headed to Seoul,
why don't you give her a ride?
Are you going to Seoul? Sure.
Get in.
What's going on?
Why is he taking my girlfriend?
That texting man worries me.
Your stepfather looked like he was going to kill him...
after sending the two of us away.
- Who is he? - Someone who can die.
Don't try to find out.
I was being creative, but you evaded it.
"Who was that man?"
It's boring to ask straightforward like that.
Drop me off there.
I can't do that. Your stepfather asked me to take you.
Fine then. I didn't really want to get out anyway.
I was tired.
I'll be quiet. You can drive.
I delivered you in my car twice in one day.
- Aren't you thankful? - Thank you.
I won't stop at a rest stop.
I hate places with people, food, and bathroom smells...
mixed in together.
30,000 dollars.
I'll pay it back.
So don't show your face in front of Na Ri again.
Got it?
I'll take the cup for you.
Na Ri.
- Did you really break up? - Yes.
That witch is quick.
- What do you mean? - During the company dinner,
Yeo Joo said you broke up for certain.
- Happy birthday. - Happy birthday.
- Here's our gift. - Lucky you.
This is 98 dollars, right?
I still have some, so I'm going to swap for the men's.
You're such a devoted girlfriend.
- Is it for your nine-year boyfriend? - No comment.
Yeo Joo. Did you say my boyfriend and I broke up?
How did I break up? You seem to know.
No, I never said that.
Yes, you did.
(Stress causes insomnia.)
(Things to avoid before going to bed)
He sends at least one a day.
He nags so much. He's worse than Mom.
(Uncle)
The phone has been turned off. Please leave...
(I know about the money, so come on Mom's anniversary.)
(Message sent)
Hello?
- Na Ri. - Uncle.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry to your mom, too.
Where are you? I pulled out all the weeds in your yard.
Let's talk in person.
I don't think I'll make it on her anniversary.
- I'm sorry, Na Ri. - Uncle! Uncle!
The person who just called...
What? What did you say?
I can't hear you!
Where are you?
Here? This is Seulgi Supermarket.
Seulgi Supermarket?
(Seulgi Supermarket)
Thank you.
- Hello. - Let's drink.
Is Uncle Jung Nam here?
What? He left.
- He left. - Thank you.
No one seems to be home.
Don't be scared. It's me.
Go home.
- Uncle is back. - I got it,
so go home.
Hey, Nan Gil. Long time no see.
Why are you traveling in a herd?
Do I still scare you that much?
The boys were curious about the legend.
Say, "Hi."
- Hello, Sir! - Hello, Sir!
What are you trying to do?
I heard Shin Jung Nam is back.
Who tells you things like that?
Do you have a mole here?
Let's trust each other, please.
(Hong Dumplings)
- Who was that? - What?
You didn't forget.
You know how precious food containers are.
Who were those men by my uncle's house?
Guys like that don't usually say who they are.
Why do they always wear suits?
He was your friend. "Hey. Nan Gil. Long time no see."
He seemed happy to see you.
Those guys are like that once they know your name.
Hey, Nan Gil. Hey, Na Ri!
Hey. Long time no see.
- Was Uncle here? - No.
- He went to the supermarket and not here? - No.
You married my mom...
No.
Anyway, do you not know my uncle well?
My mom looked after him so much.
I want to look after him, but he isn't here.
KoreanDramaX.com
Is he on the run? How much does he owe?
I sent so many nice writings,
but you still can't control your rage.
- So tell me! - Yes, he's on the run!
- You said you weren't close. - I never said that.
- You're in touch with him, aren't you? - No.
- Do you lend him money and stuff? - No, no.
How much does he owe?
Tell him to just sell his house!
You're so extreme. Seriously.
Does he owe more than the value of the house?
They say those debts grow like snowballs.
What will we do about my uncle?
Discard him.
Just discard him.
He's your mom's brother, so I'll take care of him.
You discard him from that brain of yours.
Don't say your back hurts or you can't see again.
Go in and rest. I have to knead dough.
You're always kneading dough.
I sell dumplings. Kneading is my life!
I should go knead. Knead!
He isn't kneading.
I told you never to call.
Why did you come here?
I told you never to step foot here again.
It's my final warning.
If you do this again,
I can't say what will happen to you.
You know I always keep my word.
(Sweet Stranger and Me)
Na Ri, Nan Gil is a bad man.
You're so stiff. Why do you trust him?
You can't fake your expressions. I trust that.
No, this is all an act. Don't believe anything.
Did she say I'm a gold digger and a con artist?
No. There's a money matter remaining.
Did she borrow money from you? I'll go with you.
It may get dirty. It's all about money.
They may degrade your mother and family.
I came to see your daughter.
Duk Bong! Come inside. Come in.
May I go in my room then?
What does your father do?
Do you have siblings? Do you come from a happy family?
Look, Nan Gil.
Father!
What? Do you want some water?