(THE FOLLOWING CONTENT MAY NOT BE SUITABLE FOR VIEWERS UNDER 15.)
(VIEWER DISCRETION IS ADVISED.)
(EPISODE 5)
Did my mom know, too?
Tell me, Nan Gil.
What's wrong?
Do you feel sick?
You're sweating.
Hey! Con artist! Stay right there!
This is the con artist, right?
My gosh!
Nan Gil.
What's wrong?
Wake up.
Wake up, Nan Gil!
I was abandoned without even a note...
with my name and birthday.
- Hi.
- Hello.
You were sitting there because the kids were teasing.
Next time, if they tease you again,
say, "I have a mom too."
But you're Na Ri's mom.
I'm your mom too.
I was jealous of Na Ri...
because she was her real daughter.
I got her.
Awesome.
Let's go!
But I didn't like others bothering her.
I decided to marry Na Ri in order to make Mom mine.
I'm going to marry Na Ri.
(NA RI, ME, MOM, FAMILY)
Na Ri.
Your mom said to bring it to you.
Thank you.
(CONGRATULATIONS HONG NA RI ON GETTING INTO COLLEGE!)
Don't skip your meals, okay?
(HONG DUMPLINGS)
I'll miss you.
After she left,
I realized she was my first love.
Be a man and call me "Father" right away.
I will.
He adopted a bunch of kids...
and raised us to be a gang...
who despised each other.
(DEAR MOM)
Are you going somewhere during vacation?
Yes.
My long-time love is walking about.
I live in a dark world,
so I can't even look at her any more.
(PRISON)
I had to pay a big price...
to return to Mother.
(HONG DUMPLINGS)
(DA DA FINANCE DEBT COLLECTION NOTICE)
Is this...
serious?
Mom.
You trust me, right?
I need to become the head of the family.
(MARRIAGE REGISTRATION)
You and I are married?
Who would believe this?
Just say you're my adopted son.
That's even harder legally.
It needs to all be mine.
I'll protect it.
Do you not want to let me have it?
What do you mean? You can have it all.
I just...
feel bad. That's all.
You don't seem to feel bad at all.
You're resisting from smiling, right?
Regardless.
I know it's only on paper,
but you'll be Na Ri's stepdad.
She'll faint with her temper.
The thought of it gives me a headache.
She's getting married soon anyway,
so don't tell her.
Here we go.
One, two.
Sideways. One, two.
Nothing in life is predictable.
Ms. Shin Jung Im passed away at 5:30pm...
on October 8, 2015.
Mom.
How could this...
When I lost Mother,
I made a promise to protect Na Ri.
Along with that promise,
my long-term love...
came to an end.
Nan Gil. Nan Gil. What's wrong?
Wake up! Wake up!
Call an ambulance.
Okay.
Nan Gil. Please wake up.
I'm fine.
Don't call an ambulance.
Don't.
Are you okay? Are you really okay?
Can you hear me?
You are too loud.
- Bring the car. Hurry.
- Okay.
You are going to the hospital.
- Why?
- You're not fine.
I'm allergic to sunlight. That's why.
I don't believe you.
Remember who you are talking to.
I have to knead dough. I'm busy.
Don't be sick.
I'm being selfish and saying it for my sake.
Don't ever get sick.
I have no one and I don't even know what is going on.
So you can't be sick.
I am not sick.
It's a bit embarrassing to show off,
but I am too healthy.
I don't even know when was the last time I was sick.
Moreover, you don't need to know what's going on.
Don't worry too much.
Take care. Look out for yourself.
In conclusion,
I shouldn't think about coming home...
and I should just live alone by myself.
What are you talking about?
Why are you taking things to extremes?
Negative mind only brings negative thoughts.
- So you're stressed out.
- And I get wrinkles. Fine.
I'll let you go and do your kneading.
Don't fall on the way. Bye.
He must feel restless...
to think that I let him get off hook that easy.
Na Ri.
He must be feeling anxious.
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by VIU
(LIST OF BORROWED NAME ACCOUNTS)
(KIM YOUNG SOO, PARK JEONG SOOK, JUNG YONG DAE...)
Mr. Bae.
How have you been?
Nan Gil is aware how much money...
was traded in and out through the borrowed accounts...
including the recent ones.
If the list gets out, we are done.
No one knows about the list except us.
But who can possibly...
help Nan Gil?
- Na Ri.
- What?
- Something's going on.
- What do you mean?
You two were acting like a couple.
You kept looking at him through the mirror.
Seriously? Were we?
"We"?
Do you desperately need a guy to get over your breakup?
Still, he can't be the one.
You need to report him to the police.
Calm down.
If not, you'll only lose sleep and get wrinkles.
Hey.
I may lose this battle but shall win the war.
I'm Hong Na Ri.
I'm going to ask him all sorts of questions.
I'll make sure that he answers everything thoroughly.
Fine. That was cool.
My heart pounded.
Why do I keep thinking about him?
Get out of my head.
(KWON DUK BONG)
- Hello?
- Na Ri.
- Yes?
- Didn't you forget something?
I did?
You were supposed to call me.
You said you received something from court.
So what was it?
Stop teasing and just tell me.
I should tell you in person.
- In person?
- It's quite complicated.
Stop teasing.
- Where should we meet?
- Soon. Bye.
So where are we meeting soon?
Hello? Hello?
Why does she always hang up first?
I was still talking.
"I should tell you in person."
I guess she wants to meet.
You startled me.
Make some sounds when you are walking.
Dong Jin.
Did you wait long? I'm sorry.
Why did you want to meet me here?
Dong Jin.
Did Na Ri pay you back the money she borrowed?
What?
Well, yes.
It turns out she took out a private loan.
Who told you that?
A lot of debt collection notices were sent to work.
Everyone knows about it.
You must feel bad. I do too.
If you feel really bad,
you shouldn't talk about it so lightly like this.
I mean I didn't want to talk about it.
I just thought you should know.
I tried to make reservation, but couldn't.
- So what are you going to do now?
- Well...
Yeo Joo.
Is that you, Dong Jin?
Na Ri.
Let's come back another time.
- Why?
- I mean...
What is this look on your face? Did you know?
You jerk.
Shi Eun. Forget about it. Let's just go.
Why do we need to go?
Dong Jin.
We come here often because of our group discounts.
- It's a mere coincidence.
- A coincidence?
Stop it.
How can you be so composed and cool about it?
I would have thrown her off the plane.
We need to talk.
Talk? I have nothing to say to you.
Let go.
Oh my goodness.
What's making him so confident?
You saw that, right?
Nine years don't just disappear.
Stop talking about how long they dated.
It's nothing.
Excluding the time he was in the military and abroad,
their nine years are not that long.
You...
She's about to lose it.
Not while I'm still alive!
You don't need to hold my hand.
I didn't know you came here often.
I'm sorry.
Don't be sorry.
You are free to go wherever you want.
But since you two have no clue or manners,
I'm a bit embarrassed.
- I'm sorry.
- Don't be.
But are you really in trouble financially?
Did your uncle take out a private loan?
Is that what Yeo Joo said?
Do you two talk about me?
Who's the lender?
How much is it?
Are you curious?
Or do you want to pay it off for me?
They're both annoying.
You can't handle loan sharks.
Get the house from that con artist and sell it.
Whom are you calling a con artist?
What do you know?
If it weren't for him, I...
No.
I don't want to talk to you about him.
Na Ri, I won't come here again.
Do you feel like talking like that even now?
I respect you.
Your taste doesn't change.
At least, you got her a different color from mine.
I'm late for my appointment.
(HONG DUMPLINGS)
My bag. My bag!
What is that?
My back. My back.
- Hi.
- Hello.
Hello. Hello.
What is this?
Word spread that I borrowed from a loan shark,
so I was fired for hurting flight attendants' image.
Lead the way to your company.
What a great parent.
I'll bring documentation that you are not liable.
Let's go. I'll resolve it.
I'll unpack in my room.
Why would you unpack? Let's go to Seoul.
I was lying.
I took a leave of absence.
I work hard and I'm good,
so they can't fire me that easily.
Gosh, my back.
Will you keep standing there?
I operate a dumpling restaurant.
You're always kneading.
The restaurant has rules.
But one day, if someone asks to take a long vacation,
that employee wouldn't look very devoted.
What a terrible boss.
You should worry about them, wondering what happened...
that they need so much time off.
Accidents and incidents occur overnight...
just like I suddenly got a million-dollar debt.
That's my debt.
Exactly. That's what I'm most curious about.
Why did you become my stepdad and take on our debt...
to solve it?
With my temper, I'd like to ask right now,
but I have a lot of time.
Darn it.
When did you get here?
This is a model of the resort you plan to build, right?
Yes. Isn't it cool?
Will the lake disappear?
There's no need to include the lake in the model.
You seem interested in the resort.
I guess you'll sell the land once you win the suit.
Please withdraw the marriage cancellation complaint.
The complaint was filed already.
What now?
Do you know Da Da Finance?
Why are you suddenly asking?
My father owes them money with the land as collateral.
They say it's my debt now.
Your father?
What father?
That Hong Dumplings owner is terrible.
But why would you withdraw the complaint?
Send him to prison.
Not that father.
It's my real father's debt.
The father who abandoned my mom and me 20 years ago.
Life stinks, doesn't it?
It does.
Hold on. So...
How are you so unlucky with fathers?
Da Da Finance is legit on its surface,
but their methods of collecting debts are illegal.
Once they have you, you can't get out.
No.
You have a stepdad.
Keep the debt a secret from Nan Gil.
The Da Da matter happened in the past.
And now that you have your stepdad,
we can press that you are not liable.
Nan Gil knows about the debt.
He said that's why he became my stepdad.
It's only on paper.
What does that mean?
So...
I mean he's the only person I can trust right now.
Na Ri.
I'll look into it.
Don't believe just anything.
It's too soon.
You called him a con artist not long ago.
Is it urgent?
You should question anything and everything.
(NA RI)
Come to the playground now.
(COME TO THE PLAYGROUND NOW.)
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by VIU
Do you know why I called you here?
Just say it.
Rooftop after class.
Playground after class.
You know what I mean, right?
Don't annoy me, and just say it.
I want to fight a duel right here.
I'm tired of talking about the same thing,
but we're not really...
Nan Gil.
Speak politely to me from now on.
And I'd like you to answer my questions honestly.
Why must I do that?
Everything was exposed.
What was?
The fact that you were pretending like my stepdad.
When I called you a con artist and a gold digger,
you could've just told me you were pretending.
Why? It would've only confused you.
I wanted you to be comfortable.
Did you have to become my dad?
I figured it's better to become family and protect you.
My mom would never have agreed to such a lie.
She knew it was the only way to fix this.
She trusted you more than her own daughter. Is that it?
What was your relationship? How long did you know her?
What? Does he practice this look?
Don't look away.
If you look away, you lose.
Do you really not know?
What? What don't I know?
You really don't know. I'm disappointed.
Class 3 of 1st grade, Ko Nan Gil.
(KO NAN GIL)
How long did you know my mom?
What is this look now?
I grew up in an orphanage.
Hope Orphanage.
An orphanage?
Hope Orphanage?
The one she used to volunteer at?
That's right.
Mother came by almost every day and took care of me.
I owe her a huge debt.
So you met at the orphanage.
It's all in the past. Don't pity me...
just because I grew up in an orphanage.
I received a lot of love, thanks to Mother.
I don't pity you.
Our restaurant is where an orphanage used to be.
I heard from Mother.
She said it reminded her...
of the past which was why she volunteered at mine.
I remember that place.
You never came once.
How do you know?
Do you remember me from then?
She always came alone.
I used to get annoyed at times because...
she always went to volunteer.
I'm such a brat, right?
I used to get annoyed that she'd go home...
instead of staying with me.
She must have been tired dealing with both of us.
Seulgi Grade School, right?
Which middle school?
I'm much older, right?
Don't get hung up on the past.
I'm your stepdad now.
Da Da may send people at any time,
so let's work hard on our acting.
I can't do that.
If you were that close to my mom,
why didn't I know you?
Why don't I remember any of it?
You can't act,
but you're curious.
Being curious means you are interested.
- Do you...
- What?
Do I what?
I'm saying this out of concern.
You can't see me as a man.
- Hey!
- Hey.
You shouldn't be so rude.
I have to knead dough.
I'm actually not in any position to question.
I should just thank you, right?
No.
I'm just doing what I must,
so don't thank me.
If you can't act, don't.
But don't talk down to me.
She really doesn't remember anything.
(PERSONAL INFORMATION FILE, KO NAN GIL)
(PERSONAL INFORMATION FILE, HONG NA RI)
I mean he's the only person I can trust right now.
I told you to stop popping in.
It's annoying!
This is a violation of privacy.
I'm going to call the police for trespassing.
What a sight.
I have question. Why did you come here?
You left Mom, Dad, the big house, and Seoul...
and came here. Why?
You don't care about me.
Why do you ask suddenly?
I'm asking just because I'm curious.
Did you think I was the only person in the world...
that you could trust?
Did you?
- What made you think that?
- What's wrong with you?
Are you feeling ill?
It's not like we get along.
What about Hong Dumplings?
Can you trust Nan Gil?
Yes.
Look at you smiling at the mention of his name.
What makes you trust that sleaze ball?
What?
You're the sleaziest.
How dare you call him that?
Me? The sleaziest?
I'm the one who gives you your allowance.
Where's your bike? Did you lose it again?
You've totally lost your mind.
Why is that in your room?
Because he got it back for you?
Stop being annoying...
and get out!
Gosh.
She really doesn't remember anything.
He's saying something.
He says "anything" at the last of his sentence.
What could it be? Is it about my being pretty?
Gosh, what am I doing?
She really doesn't remember anything.
(ANYTHING)
"Anything?"
She really doesn't remember anything.
(DONG JIN)
Hello?
At least you're taking my calls.
- We still have things to resolve.
- Right.
I closed our savings account. We saved quite a lot.
I transferred all the money to your account.
Why did you do that?
Split it in half. Take 30,000 dollars from it.
That...
Nan Gil already paid it on behalf of you.
Nan Gil? Why?
When?
Forget it. Bye.
So that's why... Hello? Na Ri?
Why? Why would he pay it back?
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by VIU
What are you doing here?
Well, I was just...
Are you okay?
- Here.
- I'm soaked.
Why don't you get up now?
That's an organic compost that I made.
What could be in it?
I never saw you smile before.
It's nice.
At least try to act.
We're not supposed to say those to each other.
What's wrong with saying you look good when smiling?
You can say that to someone you just met.
You have a nice smile. What's up with it?
You're right.
I'm keeping my promise to Mom,
so it's as if we just met.
We have nothing to do with each other.
So we shouldn't be talking here like this.
Goodness. Why are you drawing lines now?
Then why did you pay Dong Jin 30,000 dollars?
Your uncle borrowed it.
Mom would've wanted me to pay him back too.
That's why I feel like I owe you...
and should thank you.
Thanks.
I mean it. I'll pay you back soon.
Do you know strawberry flowers?
These are strawberry flowers.
Those are pumpkin flowers.
Those are eggplant flowers.
Aren't they prettier than roses?
These pretty and small flowers become the fruit.
They become strawberries and pumpkins.
They may be uglier, but more beneficial.
That's called growth.
Are you telling me to grow up?
Is that what you think? That wasn't my intention.
- Then what else?
- There's no need to...
stay all night, get wrinkles, and get stressed.
You're growing. That's all.
Do you call that comforting?
If you insist on paying me, I thought of a use for it.
I think...
taking a long vacation, coming back home,
and growing old are not beneficial.
If you pay me back, I'll sign you up with a matchmaker.
What you're saying is not even funny.
What? A matchmaker?
Are you telling me to marry just anyone?
- Let's go.
- Yes, Father.
What am I thinking? Have I gone nuts?
- What's wrong?
- Even if it's my imagination,
that's insane.
- Seriously.
- I must be crazy.
Stop thinking about stupid things and let's go.
Thinking about what?
I wasn't thinking anything.
What's going on? I can't see a thing!
I can't see!
Snap out of it.
I almost fell because of you.
(HONG DUMPLINGS)
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by VIU
Good morning.
Even the way you drink water is impressive.
Go back to Seoul after breakfast!
Leave it when you're done.
I'll clear the table from now on.
From now on?
Hello.
I heard from Na Ri.
You know I'm a licensed attorney, right?
So?
You knew about her father's debt.
Na Ri said this land was collateral,
but the documents don't say that.
How much is the debt?
Go mind your own business.
I thought hard...
about why you became her stepdad.
Wow. You did great.
Otherwise, Na Ri would be living in torment.
It's moving.
Then I thought,
the lender is Da Da Finance,
the worst of the worsts. A master at evil.
You could just sell the land to me and pay them off.
Are you trying to impress Na Ri?
Then you should be done enough by now,
so sell it.
I won't sell.
Isn't it illegal to keep telling me to sell?
Why won't you sell?
Because you have to split from Na Ri once you do?
Or because you'll lose all your memories?
Na Ri believes that you became her stepdad...
because of the debt. She was touched.
If it was just because of the debt,
did you have to become her father?
Or is there a secret I don't know about?
We're not close enough to share secrets.
First love? Crush?
Or someone you've cherished all your life?
They say love conquers all,
but not Da Da.
What's with the tension?
- What tension?
You don't look close.
Right? We don't look close, right?
Shouldn't you be nicer to me?
Why?
Do you know how many people come to our museum?
Most of them stop by this restaurant.
You're right.
I'm going out.
You tell him when you go out now?
Stop by the office before you go to Seoul.
I need to talk to you.
It's very important.
Okay.
Why did you tell him about the debt?
He's a lawyer, so I consulted him.
Buy Korean beef tail bone and make some soup with it.
What? A tail bone?
My workers and I must gain energy before it gets cold.
You'll have to boil it all day.
Do we have a pot that big?
You must cook it in the old pot with the old way.
A tail bone isn't enough.
I'll make enough beef bone soup.
Enough for us to eat it during fall and winter.
All through winter?
When are you going to Seoul then?
Gosh!
What are you doing?
I'm about to exercise now.
I need some exercise too.
All I do is just breathing exercise.
I need to watch my figure...
What should we have for dinner?
Yeo Joo.
I don't feel so great...
after running into Na Ri last time.
I don't feel like working either.
Maybe I feel guilty now.
I understand.
You are a kind and warm person.
You want to be alone, don't you?
You don't want to see me...
That's not it.
Sure.
I need some time alone.
Okay.
I'll busy for a while, so that's good.
Go into your own cave...
and emerge victoriously.
Okay.
Thanks.
What's this? Hey, calm down.
You have a date tonight.
He can't see me because he feels guilty.
He didn't feel guilty when he cheated.
Why now?
What? You said he's a good and sweet guy.
That kind of guy doesn't exist.
He is a good guy if he feels guilty.
That's your ideal type.
No, that isn't feeling guilty.
Now that I became his first,
I've lost all appeal.
Appeal always drops.
Just win with your body.
Run. Just run.
Yes.
Let's do it. Increase the speed!
Okay.
- Wait! It's too fast. Do something!
- Run! Run!
Be careful.
Each persimmon contains a year.
You're a real poet.
Do you know Hong Dumplings?
Of course. It's Jung Im's place.
Yes. I'm her daughter.
I know. You insect.
Pardon?
There's an insect...
that stays calm...
then suddenly stings.
So?
Jung Im said...
her daughter was like that.
She said that you sting all the time.
I'm not like that.
I'm very soft.
By the way,
what was my mom like?
Nan Gil?
Nan Gil from Hope Orphanage?
I don't know.
He's running Hong Dumplings now.
Nan Gil? He's a hard worker.
He used to live in Hope Orphanage?
Here.
Thank you.
Beef bone soup again?
We're going to get so healthy.
Thank you.
Where do you go every day?
Aren't you going to Seoul?
You said I need to grow.
Do you know flowers have meanings?
Guess what eggplant flowers mean.
Truth. I love its meaning.
Let's be honest.
I think...
I'll need to clean up the house before it gets cold.
Why not fix up the entire house?
Exactly.
Just forget all this and live comfortably in Seoul.
So annoying.
What is she up to now?
Hello.
I came...
to see you.
Me? What is it about?
Do you have time after work?
I'm busy and I have nothing to say.
Many people said to ask you if I want...
to find out about Hope Orphanage.
I don't have time and have nothing to say.
Why did you hate my mom so much?
Why? Can't I?
Must everyone like her?
No, you can hate her.
But it looked like you had a reason.
I just didn't like her.
Sometimes, you just dislike people.
This is a work place. Please leave.
You hate me too.
I understand that she hates you,
but my mom is really nice.
What do you understand that she hates me?
It's sort of difficult to say to your face.
It's okay. Tell me.
Let's just say you are kind of...
unlikable.
I guess you're getting old too.
I'm unlikable?
People call it being chic nowadays.
I'm attractive in that way.
I'll just ignore that.
What's keeping you busy
that you can't answer my calls?
I was meeting people. Why?
I withdrew the marriage cancellation complaint.
Okay.
Marriage? Cancellation?
Complaint? Withdraw?
I think I know why he became your stepdad.
Why?
I don't know if I should tell you.
Okay.
You and Nan Gil grew up here.
You were friends from grade school.
- I know.
- You do?
Yes.
Don't you feel anything?
No.
Okay. They say grade school reunions...
are popular worldwide.
Why do you think that is?
It's because what you saw and felt as a child...
is unforgettable.
Let's say someone does something so shocking...
that no one in the world can understand him.
What do you think the reason is?
Is his becoming my stepdad that shocking?
He's so young,
but he registered his marriage.
You can't undo it.
- You can't?
- Of course not.
And he insists on bearing all the responsibilities...
and lives like a monk, making dumplings.
And he has to fight against Da Da Finance.
They practically kill people for not paying back.
Why do you think he's putting up with all that?
Don't you get it?
Come to the lake.
(FROM NA RI, COME TO THE LAKE.)
Boss. I love that there's someone troubling you.
I love it.
People lie a lot in their daily lives.
They fool others, and sometimes,
they fool themselves.
That's why...
you need a place where you can face the truth.
You cannot tell a lie here.
Then...
it'll be the most peaceful and the freest place.
You'll be in peace and free here.
You know this spot too.
Then you must also know you can't lie here.
That's why I want to give you Mom's phone.
I didn't get rid of it yet.
They tried to contact her,
not knowing she passed away.
I couldn't give it to you in case you'd pick up.
It's your mother's belonging after all.
Fine.
I'll take care of it.
I heard Da Da Finance is dangerous.
I don't know what promise you made with Mom,
but she isn't here, so you don't have to do this.
I promised Mom during the funeral...
What promise?
To protect this place.
And what does here mean to her?
Isn't that what you've been searching for?
And yet, you nagged me for not going to Seoul.
I didn't nag... Actually, I did.
Since we can't lie here.
Figure out yourself what this place means to Mom.
Did you find anything?
- My nickname.
- Nickname?
My mom called me "Puppy" in front of me,
but she told others I stung like an insect.
I can't believe she talked behind my back.
She called you as pig toenail to me.
She thought you were sharp and scary.
She badmouthed me everywhere.
I should try to find out more about Mom.
Then make me a promise too.
If Da Da threatens you severely, you quit.
Okay.
One more thing.
If one day, you feel like making dumplings...
like a monk isn't your thing, you may leave.
A monk?
Someone said you live like a monk when you're so young.
Do you have a girlfriend?
Have you ever had a girlfriend?
Have you ever dated?
I guess not!
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by VIU
Hey.
Your daughter is very energetic.
She looks like she's going to drink alcohol.
The past
Times we spent
It is making me cry
- Good job.
- Thank you!
I grabbed the mic this time.
- Let me try.
- Go ahead!
I am a poet
I didn't think you'd be here.
You're from Da Da Finance, right?
You seem to be having fun.
- I'll see you later.
- Wait a second.
- What is that legend?
- Excuse me?
The legendary Ko Nan Gil.
So what is that legend?
Have a nice day.
You never get your water by yourself.
Even regular customers must get it themselves here.
Darn it.
Hey, kid. Straighten your posture.
What was I doing?
- Joon.
- Yes?
Father said to thank you for the gift.
What do you plan to do now?
I told you. I have nothing else planned.
I'm going to keep making dumplings here.
Father thinks someone has been helping you...
since you removed yourself from the family registry.
That means he's suspecting you.
Don't visit me often.
Be careful so that he doesn't suspect you.
Oh, right. I met Na Ri on the way here.
She asked me what your legend is about.
Let's say someone does something so shocking...
that no one in the world can understand him.
What do you think the reason is?
She really doesn't remember anything.
(SEULGI SUPERMARKET)
I asked you a favor.
I told you never to meet with Na Ri.
You always get tense when it's about her.
Of course, I didn't tell you went to prison.
I'll take that as refusing my favor.
Wait and see what will happen.
I really didn't say anything to her.
She asked me about it first.
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by VIU
Nan Gil!
What's wrong?
I'm sorry I couldn't remember anything.
Hey, wait. What's wrong?
Wait.
Gosh.