(The following content may not be suitable for viewers under 15.)
(Viewer discretion is advised.)
(Episode 6)
Let's say someone does something so shocking...
that no one in the world can understand him.
What do you think the reason is?
She really doesn't remember anything.
(Seulgi Supermarket)
The legend of Ko Nan Gil.
Ask him yourself.
I promised not to say anything.
What I'm sure of...
is that he's a poor guy.
How can you use him to be your stepdad...
just because your mother helped him when he was little?
His life could be over because of this.
Actually, it'll be over.
Nan Gil!
(Hong Dumplings)
What's wrong?
I'm sorry I couldn't remember anything.
Hey, wait. What's wrong?
Wait.
Gosh.
What's wrong? Hold on.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry, Nan Gil.
I'm so sorry.
What are you sorry about?
I'm sorry I can't remember anything.
I'm sorry and I'm thankful.
Okay. Okay.
I got it. Let's go inside to talk.
What do you know? Do you know how I feel?
I feel so bad and I'm scared.
Did you drink again?
Forget it. Just stop everything.
Forget what? Make some sense.
You can't win against Da Da Finance.
Just give up.
Mom will understand you, too.
Let's talk inside.
No, let's talk here.
Don't go back in there again. Just leave from here.
Don't go into my house again.
You'd do well at other restaurants with your skills.
Just leave. Go while I'm letting you.
I'm not drunk.
Wash your face and snap out of it.
You're the one who needs to snap out.
I'll take care of the papers. Just pack up and leave.
Does it look like a joke to you?
Do you know how hard I worked to save this restaurant?
Do my staff look like a joke to you?
I told you not to say that again. This is my home!
This is not a joke.
This is my home.
Whatever happens to my family, it's my responsibility.
All you do is drink. How can you be responsible?
My nickname is Super Hong.
I'd solve problems wherever and whenever.
So I'll take care of our family's business.
Enough with Super Hong.
Just wash your face and sober up.
Also, I remembered it.
I always felt like someone was chasing me.
It's you, right?
The school field on a rainy day during middle school.
Right?
You splashed water on me and ran.
- No way. - Right?
Kids that age bug girls they like.
Don't tell me you're risking everything for me.
I've never been immature, so I never bugged anyone.
Also, this isn't dangerous. It's what's right.
Your life could be over.
- Who says? - Everyone.
Look at me straight in the eyes.
Just listen to me.
Other people are lying, so don't listen to them.
Only listen to what I say...
and only trust me.
I have to remember something.
Mom.
I'm worried about him. What should I do?
What a ruckus.
Who...
Na Ri.
Is she crazy? Hey, what are you doing?
Gosh.
- Na Ri. - I'm not Na Ri.
- Na Ri. - Let me go. Seriously.
She must be crazy. Let go.
Let go.
You crazy woman. Let go. I said to let go.
Gosh. Let go.
Hey, Do Yeo Joo!
Na Ri. Na Ri, are you okay?
Gosh, was it your little brother?
Yeo Joo.
Why are you on the ground?
- Are you drunk again today? - Yeo Joo!
I'm drunk today, too.
Do you want to go for another round?
Yeo Joo.
Na Ri!
It's so hard for me to bear.
This is worse than when I was ostracized in school.
It's so childish!
My flight schedules are all over the place.
I can't even take a break in the bunker.
Everyone is whispering...
behind my back.
Na Ri's brother.
Little Brother,
can you get me a glass of water?
- Actually, we should all go... - Go inside.
for another drink.
Why is the world so cruel?
Why won't you just give me water?
The world is so mean only to me.
What did I do so wrong?
Hong Na Ri. You.
What are you doing here?
Everyone's blaming me and talking behind my back.
Come back.
Hey.
What is it?
- Stop being so easy. - What did I do?
Why do you hug strangers and give them water?
Are you happy since she's nice to you?
I didn't mean to, but people kept falling in my arms.
Don't bring me down to her level.
What are you trying to say?
- Stay away from her. - Why?
All she does is steal other people's belongings.
Other people's belongings?
Are you talking about me?
Whose am I?
Go and work.
What was that?
Why did you say such a thing?
Gosh. You idiot.
Move.
I can't leave since you always search in my room.
- Are you doubting me? - Yes, I am.
I find you 120 percent suspicious, so get out.
Guess what the witch sent us this morning.
If it's true, I have full respect for you.
I'm at Na Ri's country home.
- The air is so nice. - Is she crazy?
She's making me swear so early in the morning.
What do you think you're doing?
Na Ri, let's take a picture together.
Why do you live like that? Leave.
Come here.
My goodness. Who are all these people?
- Come here. - Little Brother,
please help me.
Little Brother...
- Go. Go inside. - Why?
- Little Brother. - My feet won't move.
- Come on. - Go.
- She said not to even go near her. - Little Brother.
Little Brother!
While resting here, I felt good like this clear water.
I thought, maybe this is why people go to suburbs.
However, thanks to you,
I feel like this now.
I'm showing you since you seem to be dull.
Stop making my life into a mess and drink this.
Must I drink this?
All right. I'll drink it.
If that will make you feel better, I will.
Stop acting.
It's arrowroot juice.
I feel bad to the juice for comparing it to my life.
Apparently, it's good for hangovers.
Leave after you drink it.
Dong Jin will transfer to the Hong Kong head office.
When I go with him after marriage, I won't bother you.
We won't ever run into each other.
Then you should just move to Hong Kong quietly.
It's fine with me,
but Dong Jin is scared of being seen as the bad guy.
You must know that already.
Know what? I don't know anything about him.
I don't want to lose Dong Jin.
Please. Just act as if we're on good terms.
I don't have friends, and I'm a loner at work now.
What if no one comes to my wedding?
I respect your nerve.
Are you doing this because of your wedding?
It's a once in a lifetime event.
Do you even know what an eggplant flower looks like?
A flower this small grows up to be this big.
Isn't it about time you grow up, too?
Leave.
Na Ri, do you know what my strength is?
I have no pride.
I'll wait for you outside.
Who does she think she is?
Why don't you come out, too?
This meeting involves you, too.
If you sign, the development will start right away.
Seulgi Supermarket's owner isn't here.
She said she will sign if you do.
The restaurant will be auctioned anyway.
I don't want to buy it from Da Da at a high price.
Why don't we help each other out?
Fine, but only under one condition.
Okay.
Keep the lake and the forest.
Then I'm in.
I guess you are not a good liar.
Hey, Nan Gil, the one having his first love and crush.
Why are you so obsessed with the lake and forest?
Good morning, Na Ri.
Are you staying here for good?
No.
Why did I come here?
I can't remember why.
Come on.
Do you think she heard?
Even if she did, she wouldn't know anything.
Anyway, Ms. Kwon will leave the contract with you.
This is business.
Look at their faces filled with hope.
Hey, Nan Gil, the one having his first love and crush.
His first love and crush?
Haven't we met?
I think so.
Do you live here?
Well, yes. I think so.
This perfume is good only for summer.
I remember you now.
You are the guy who was with Na Ri at the airport.
Why do you still have the contract with you?
Are you proving you are incompetent?
Na Ri, I'm in front of your house. Please come out.
Little Brother.
Do you know how he and Na Ri know each other?
No.
There was one time...
he and Na Ri were together at the airport.
They seemed so close then.
I guess she is keeping it a secret from you.
What?
Have a family meeting with this.
Your stepfather would never...
I got it.
Don't take it. Give it back to him.
You saw that, right?
Your stepfather didn't even read the contract.
Stepfather?
Brother, why are you still here?
Go inside and take care of the restaurant.
Why are you still here?
I told you I would be out waiting.
He's the guy at the airport, right?
I'm going to tell everyone that you are dating.
My gosh.
You aren't even answering me.
You admit that you are dating. Isn't that right?
Fine, what do you want me to do?
In 1, 2 and 3. Cheese.
(Hong Dumplings)
I'll upload this to the group chat.
Do whatever you want. Leave already.
In 1, 2 and 3. Cheese.
I hope you two work out.
I don't think you are the generous type.
I didn't introduce him.
This is Kwon Duk Bong.
He is the president of a robot museum in Seulgi-ri.
He is one of the family members of Greenland.
Well, goodbye.
- Duk Bong, why don't we go inside? - "We"?
Where?
Greenland?
Did you look me up?
I'm one of the family members of Greenland.
I didn't know you're a snob.
I didn't have to look it up. Everyone in town knows.
I'm sorry. I thought I'd feel better, but I don't.
Good job.
You need to be worse when you deal with snobs.
What?
You said something at the restaurant.
Never mind.
You're good at observing women. She's a snob.
You looked like you wanted to say something.
It's really nothing.
Well...
Since we are all here together,
why don't we discuss this like adults?
Na Ri, are you afraid of your stepfather?
If not, why can't you even read the contract?
Do you know that you can claim this is your house?
Yes.
And you, Nan Gil.
It's true that this house is under your name.
But you can't just sell it as you wish.
Na Ri can stop you from doing so.
And are you uncomfortable being with your daughter?
Are you doing your part as her stepfather?
This is frustrating.
Here you go.
You two should seriously talk about it...
as a family.
You are family after all, aren't you?
Families don't play hard to get.
Why doesn't Nan Gil want to eat?
He said he is sick of the soup.
- He didn't say that. - He didn't say that.
Traitors.
Thank you.
Why are you avoiding her?
Put on your uniform properly.
My first guess is that you're uncomfortable around her.
Second guess, you still have feelings for her.
Third guess, you want her to miss you. Which one is it?
I think Na Ri misses you.
My gosh.
Why is he always angry at me?
What?
Let's see if you can avoid me here, too.
Duk Bong came to the airport to talk about the land.
Why are you telling me that?
You've been avoiding me ever since.
I'm not close to him. I'm not taking his side.
I don't care whether or not you sell the land.
- Aren't you leaving? - Do you know how I feel?
I know you've been drinking every afternoon.
Just leave, then.
I drank with the elders because I missed Mom. So what?
I regret it like crazy.
I planned that stupid wedding for years,
but I never once went on a trip with her.
I'm a stewardess, so airfare is cheap, too.
I must've been a terrible daughter.
I'm the insect and the pig's toenail after all.
What am I supposed to do?
Did you buy this to plant?
Yes. I want to make this my land.
I'm new, so I want to start with lettuce and peppers.
- Don't sprinkle it like that! - Then how do I do it?
Like this.
A little at a time...
And gently...
Mother didn't go on a trip because she wanted to.
This was her entire world.
Regardless, I'm the insect.
Seulgi Supermarket's owner's daughter took off...
with all her money and never even called.
How could Mom brag about you to her?
What about pig's toenail?
- It's because of me. - What was?
I hated, envied and was jealous of her daughter, Na Ri,
so she pretended to curse you to make me feel better.
I'll ask again since you said you hated me.
- The one who splashed me... - It wasn't me!
Let's say it wasn't.
I used to get hit with pebbles when I was little.
Someone stuck gum on my shoe, too.
- Was that you? - I've never once...
done anything that childish in my life.
- They did it because you were a brat. - Hey!
You shouldn't be so rude to me.
Will you let me keep this land?
- Will you go to Seoul then? - Fine, I'll go!
- I'm never coming back... - Here again?
You say that all the time, but you come here too often.
(1 year ago)
- Hey, you. - Oh my gosh.
Are you done?
Isn't that the punk there?
- There. - That punk ruined my field.
Come with me.
Hands.
Why did you do it?
You assert your right to remain silent. Is that right?
Then should I say I caught the perp who has been...
breaking scarecrows and damaging farms?
- They were annoying. - Who was?
Those farm owners' kids.
You transferred here, right? And they picked on you.
Still, will you tear up all the farms here?
They have dogs and cows, too.
Can you kill them, too?
- Are you crazy? - Rice is alive, too.
Don't you see them grow?
There are...
idiots who enjoy picking on others.
They have no idea their lives are becoming garbage.
Don't waste your emotions and time for those jerks.
Okay.
Hey, kid. I'll be watching.
This was our private space.
(Furnace Sauna Room)
Mr. Shin Jung Nam.
It's dangerous to sweat too much at your age.
Sit down.
Mr. Shin. Don't you know me?
You should look at a person when they talk to you.
I... I don't know.
That's not good. Think hard.
You may not know.
When you came with Hong Sung Kyu to borrow money,
you must not have known I'd climb this high up.
I...
can't stand people who sneak looks.
Look me straight in the eye, you rat!
If you're so afraid, why won't you pay back the loan?
Or you should run away like Hong Sung Kyu.
I saw your stewardess niece at our office.
Thanks to her loser dad and uncle,
her life is about to be ruined.
You look shocked. You must have believed Nan Gil.
If you knew what Nan Gil is really like,
you wouldn't let him near your niece.
Just do what we say.
That's the only way your niece can survive.
It's hard for me to walk. Teach me how to ride a bike.
- You know how to ride. - It's been too long.
How do you know that?
You followed me around when we were little, didn't you?
You really can't leave me, okay? It's been years.
Stay next to me.
I got it.
Hey!
No. No!
I'm so tired. I'm going to die.
Here. You should exercise more.
I wasn't this bad. My body must be rotting.
Take a deep breath and exhale through your mouth.
I'm so happy.
I don't know how long it's been.
I'm going to knead dough.
You and your dough.
Hello?
Shin Jung Nam is here.
We talked about old times.
At first, I was angry at Hong Na Ri...
for using you,
but after talking about old times,
I realized she was the biggest victim.
I had forgotten...
about something from a very long time ago.
You and Na Ri should never have even met.
Don't make me dredge that up, too.
Darn it. She is so unathletic.
Darn it. What should I do?
What should I do?
How dare you call your brother?
You need to come here.
Are you insane?
Hong Dumplings.
- That woman got hurt. - Where are you?
Halfway down the road to Injung-ri by the field.
Are you all right?
Please help!
Please help me up.
My back. My back. My back.
Would you get my phone from my bag?
My back.
What's up?
Nan Gil, I need you to come here.
What's wrong? What is it?
I'm at...
Hold on.
Would you explain where we are?
We're halfway down the road to Injung-ri by the field.
Okay. Got it.
Okay. This is his number.
Thank you.
Wait. Weren't you the one on the bike just now?
Right? How could you drive...
How could you ride your bike like that?
You had plenty of room. Why did you come at me?
I didn't go at you.
You were completely oblivious,
so I rang my bell to ask you to move.
Where could I have moved to? You forced me here.
Gosh. My back.
Na Ri.
Are you okay?
I'll hold your arm. Lean on me.
Okay.
You need to get to the hospital.
Let me carry you.
No.
I can walk.
Hey. Na Ri!
Na Ri!
Are you okay? I called an ambulance.
Don't move.
What is it? Does it hurt?
Where exactly does it hurt?
No, it's okay.
(Donghwa Hospital)
(Emergency Care Unit)
Her right leg isn't broken. It was banged up.
She has to stay overnight to monitor her back.
Please check whether she has pain...
and where it is every three hours.
(Pain checklist)
Thank you.
Stop it!
I rang my bell like crazy.
She fell because she's unathletic.
Regardless, a person was hurt.
It's always the driver's fault.
Do you need a license to ride a bike?
Stop showing off that you went to law school.
That unathletic woman has quite a temper.
She may press charges.
Then the police will investigate,
and Nan Gil will know it was intentional.
Gosh.
Well...
Sit down.
- What? - Sit down.
Gosh.
Here.
Wait.
Are you okay?
I'm okay.
How did you know to come there?
The one who caused the accident is my sister.
- Your sister? - Your sister?
This is Kwon Duk Shim.
Seriously.
Would you please step out so that I can change?
Duk Shim, would you give me a hand?
You did it on purpose, didn't you?
You're rude as soon as the men leave.
You're the one who sent those notes to Nan Gil,
addressing him as "My Prince", aren't you?
"My Prince"? Did someone...
send something that lame?
You locked me in the shed, didn't you?
Your shoe size fits!
What's wrong with you? Is it a middle school thing?
I'm in high school.
I rang my bell from behind.
It's because you're old and unathletic.
Old?
Locking me in the shed and this were both dangerous.
Tell me why you did it.
If you don't, I'll...
I don't care if you're in school. I'll show no mercy.
Latching onto another guy because you were dumped...
is degrading to all women.
And you flirt at my brother, too.
You're a total player.
If you made a mistake and registered your marriage,
be cool and get a divorce!
When do you ever study?
- You dug all this up. - I saw.
You got your ex-boyfriend drunk...
and fought with his new girlfriend who came to get him.
You came to my brother and acted like a girl.
You talked about canceling a marriage.
I would've given in if you had any of it right,
but you got it all wrong.
Then what's your relationship with my Nan Gil?
- Your Nan Gil? - That's right.
Why are you latching onto him? You're so annoying.
You should apologize for what you did to me.
What? Annoying?
Why is it so hard to get an apology in this society?
Kwon Duk Shim. You messed with the wrong person.
I won't let this go.
I'm going to press charges and investigate.
I warned you that I won't show mercy.
You really didn't know she was my sister?
That's right. It's hard not to notice things like that.
I don't like it.
She's my sister. What is there not to like?
She's quiet and innocent,
but you called her a juvenile delinquent.
I have only one sister.
I don't have a quiet and innocent sister.
Nan Gil! Nan Gil!
Call the police right this instant!
I'm sorry.
What?
Hey.
What are you doing?
No, I...
Why are you making a kid get on her knees?
She didn't mean it.
- She meant it. - She meant it.
What? Why?
I need to talk to her to find out why,
but she left without apologizing.
Go to your sister.
Okay, then... I'm sorry, Na Ri.
Well...
- This is terrible. - What is?
- Does everyone hate you? - Hey!
She's an innocent kid. I wonder why she did that.
You think she's quiet and innocent?
She glared me down and said, "I rang the bell."
"It's because you're old and unathletic."
Hey.
Do you know what emotion wastes the most energy?
First, a crush. Second, jealousy.
So if you have a crush on someone, keep it a crush.
If you add jealousy to a crush, you'll go crazy.
Your energy will be depleted.
Whatever.
You like her, don't you?
Don't change the subject.
- Why would I? - You acted like you wouldn't come,
but once I said it was her, you ran right over.
Are you a prince on a white horse or what?
It's so not like you.
Stop being ridiculous.
Then what's your relationship with that player?
Player?
Why is Na Ri a player?
She won't give him a divorce but is playing other men.
You should become a writer.
Do you even know what Nan Gil and Na Ri are legally?
I know about the request to cancel the marriage.
They are parent and child. Stepdad and daughter.
What stupidity is that?
Is "stepdad and daughter" stupidity to you?
- Let me out. - Am I your driver?
Let me out! Let me out!
Let me out before I go even crazier!
Are you doing okay?
- Yes. - We'll take another scan tomorrow...
and you can leave if it looks good.
Exercise, so it doesn't become chronic. Walk some more.
- Please hold onto her and help her. - I will.
Didn't you hear him say to walk some more?
Darn it.
Wouldn't it strain my back if I walk too much?
It hasn't even been 10 minutes.
What kind of dad are you?
I never expected to nurse an old daughter, either.
Should I look for my father?
- Why? - Mom may be hurt if she heard this,
but I didn't hate my father.
The first time I rode the plane was with my father.
I was too young to remember much,
but I remember being shocked at how big it was.
I wonder why Mom didn't go with us.
Where did I go alone with my father? I wonder.
It must not have been fun if you can't remember.
I'm sure it was. My father was pretty funny.
Everyone in town liked him.
But whenever I told my mom that,
she said I never flew with my dad...
although I remember for certain.
No. I rode an airplane with my father. I'm positive.
Maybe Mom didn't like that you two went alone.
You're right. That must be it.
But you want to find your father to ask about that?
No. Mom kept many secrets from me.
I realize that now.
I want to ask what those secrets are.
Still, don't look for him.
He's better off hiding from Da Da.
Okay, sure.
- Let's make 10 more laps. - Hey.
Let's walk.
While you were in your cave,
I went to see Na Ri.
I know. I saw the picture you sent.
I talked a lot with her for two days...
and I feel better now.
That's good.
Is that all? Aren't you going to ask how she's doing?
She's tough. I'm sure she's fine.
Luckily, she found herself a great guy there.
A guy?
He isn't a guy.
I heard you met Kwon Duk Bong...
when you went there, too.
Kwon Duk Bong?
Did you know he was from the Greenland family?
She claims he's a friend,
but he came to the airport, too.
It looked like they've been together for a while.
She may have cheated first.
You have nowhere to return to.
Who said I was going back?
But Na Ri...
isn't the type to cheat.
If she says he's a friend, he is a friend.
Do you know me as well as you know her?
Do you know how I've been feeling?
I've been an outcast for stealing her man...
and been getting night shifts.
But I didn't let on, did I?
You seem like the old Do Yeo Joo today.
The first day we met, you came over that night...
saying you couldn't get me out of your mind.
You always said what you wanted.
Stop talking about Na Ri from now on.
You don't need to send me pictures like that.
You are you, Yeo Joo. Okay?
I must have been acting like Na Ri to impress you...
when I am me.
It's been three hours. Is there any pain?
Nan Gil.
I'm sorry for not remembering you...
when you remember me from when I was little.
There's no need to apologize.
If there's no pain, go back to sleep. I'll come back.
I didn't know it would feel so good...
to have someone remember me when I was little.
I feel like I was someone's first love.
I feel like a cool person, so I feel more confident.
I'm going to knead dough.
I've moved on.
Nan Gil.
I'm sorry for not remembering you...
when you remember me from when I was little.
I didn't know it would feel so good...
to have someone remember me when I was little.
You and Na Ri should never have even met.
Don't make me dredge that up, too.
Mr. Shin Jung Nam.
Remember when Nan Gil threatened you.
He never...
Try to remember.
You must remember when he threatened you.
You're right. Well...
Nan Gil told me...
never to step foot back home.
(CEO Bae Byung Woo)
Nan Gil.
It's Dad.
Deal with me.
Let him go.
He needs to do something with us.
I will protect this land,
independent of Na Ri.
So it's useless threatening me, saying Na Ri and I...
should never have met.
I wasn't threatening you.
You probably think...
you are protecting Na Ri,
but if you trace back,
it was you who did that to that family.
What do you mean?
Her uncle is here,
so I can't go into detail.
If her uncle hears,
Na Ri will find out as well.
(Hong Dumplings)
There's no back pain and I didn't take any painkillers.
I'm going to resolve the accident.
(Settlement Agreement)
The hospital bill has been paid already.
You can demand compensation for physical injuries...
and emotional distress.
How annoying.
The offender admitted that the accident...
was intentional.
I don't intend to sue for damages.
I request the offender's sincere apology.
"I'm sorry. I won't do that again."
"I apologize. I won't do that again." Choose one.
I didn't think you'd fall like some rag doll.
Exercise a little.
Kid.
Do you know what emotion wastes the most energy?
First, a crush.
Second, jealousy.
Is that what you want to say?
No. That's not it.
A crush and jealousy...
may recharge you if done properly.
The true waste of energy is hating others.
"It's easy to make your life miserable."
"Hate those close to you."
That's Kim Gu's famous sayings.
We're not close, though.
If we can sit face to face, we are close.
Kwon Duk Shim.
If you start to hate someone, remember this.
You're making your life miserable.
Is he really your stepdad?
Do you call him that?
Awesome.
You're family, regardless.
You don't believe that, do you?
I do. I'm sorry. I was wrong.
I'm counting on you.
For what? Counting on me for what?
Tell your stepdad that I apologized.
He isn't my stepdad!
Come to my room.
(From Na Ri, Come to my room!)
I've sent Da Da's organization chart.
(Da Da Finance Organization Chart)
(CEO Bae Byung Woo)
(Director Bae Byung Suk)
What?
I'm going to leave my stuff here.
- Good thinking. - Right?
It's bad for your back to carry heavy things.
I'll send them by courier.
It's okay. Don't bother.
I planted seeds in the greenhouse,
so I'll have to come check on them.
Don't come.
If you want to end things with Da Da,
you should cut all ties with this place.
I won't let them contact you or the company.
- Think of me as a stranger. - Of course, you are.
Did you think I really considered you to be my stepdad?
Do you know you're cold at times?
But it won't work on me any more.
I won't believe it...
because I know how you truly feel.
And how do I truly feel?
(Hong Dumplings)
Does a person named Ko Nan Gil live here?
To be honest, I don't know how you truly feel,
but I started to become curious.
I feel like...
I'll regret not asking, so I'm going to ask now.
Nan Gil,
you liked me since you were young, didn't you?
I'm your first love, aren't I?
Why are you curious about that?
It's all in the past.
Let's just say you were my first love.
Let's say I followed you around and bothered you.
Happy?
Fine, forget the past.
I'll ask Ko Nan Gil standing here now.
What about now?
You remembered me for all those years.
Do you still like me?
(Sweet Stranger and Me)
If Da Da sues, you'll probably lose.
Who'd believe you are stepdad and daughter?
Da Da cannot beat us.
You need to maintain your family relationship.
A father-and-child relationship no one will doubt.
Nan Gil hired a lawyer.
Dig into that lawyer.
Find out what their relationship is.
- Na Ri, do you want to date me? - What?
Not a friend, but someone closer. A boyfriend.
I'm for it if it'll help the family.
Hey, Nan Gil.
I'm sad to leave.
You'll visit often, right?
Don't work all the time, okay?
This really feels like goodbye.