[Episode 7]  Then, instead of the past, I want to ask the Go Nan Gil standing in front of me now.
How do you feel now?
You've remembered me for a long time.
Do you still... like me?
Timing and subtitles brought to you by The Unexpected Lovers @ Viki
I think this is too fast... No.
These ideas about timing are a result of human's biases.
Think about all the things we've been through together. He would be embarrassed to say he likes me.
What is this?
I just got something stuck on me.
You did a face massage. I don't see anything else.
Don't try to change the subject.
You're right. I've remembered you a long time and I still like you.
But, that's like a beautiful memory. Meeting in your hometown and liking someone?
I don't know the Hong Na Ri that lives in Seoul.
And I don't want to know her. I don't like her, miss her, or long for her. I think of her as a stranger.
What are you talking about? The me that is here and the me in Seoul... are different?
You're different of course. The you that is here is my mom's daughters and the Hong Na Ri I've liked for a long time.
But the Hong Na Ri in Seoul is someone I don't know at all.
But, do you understand what you are talking about right now? I don't understand any of it.
I'm not interested in anyone who is not my mother's daughter.
And, from now on, I hope you don't come here.
I, and my employees, are all men, so it's uncomfortable.
So, you're not interested at all? Think about all that you've done!
You carried me and ran, came to look for me in Seoul, consoled me when I was hurt,
took care of me when I was hurt, and even acted like my dad when you thought I would be in trouble.
Playing with people emotions... and I'm the only one who was fooled?
If it was just me... it's so embarrassing!
If you have nothing to say, can you let go?
I still have something to say. Because you are still confessing that you like the me that is here.
- Confess?  - Yeah, you just confessed.
So, now you just have to get to know the Hong Na Ri from Seoul. I'll call you often.
And the others feel uncomfortable around me? I understand the beautiful meaning behind "uncomfortable".
Being uncomfortable means you like me and care for me.
- I don't think that's right. - I'm right.
Go Nan Gil!
Mr. Go Nan Gil. Are you home?
What is going on here? Do you have a warrant?
Mr. Go Nan Gil. Please open the door.
I'm his lawyer. They have a lot of issues, so I'm representing them.
What is the problem here? You shouldn't just come barging in like that.
- You're his lawyer?  - Yes.
Where is Mr. Go Nan Gil?
So, tell me what this is about.
- Mr. Go Nan Gil?  - Don't answer him.
Is this your lawyer
Yes. He is our lawyer.
Mr. Shin Jung Nam has reported that Mr. Go Nan Gil has threatened, used physical force, and kidnapped him.
We have some things to investigate, so why don't you come down to the station with us.
Shin Jung Nam is... my uncle.
We've been looking for him. But who did you say threatened him?
Go Nan Gil, it looks like you have a record.
The allegations in the suit are pretty shabby. It doesn't event have the location of the incident or the details of any injury.
On top of that, my client did not leave Seulgi-ri during this period of time.
Can I meet with the suer, Shin Jung Nam?
Bingo. That's right! Looks like you know a thing or two about the law.
How about it? Can we have a meeting?
If his side refuses the meeting, can we report the suer as missing?
What?
I've been in close contact with Shin Jung Nam, but recently, his phone has been turned off.
So, I've been worried about him.
Go Nan Gil's investigation has ended, and they reported Shin Jung Nam as missing.
I predicted that already. There's no need for me to know all the small things.
Go on to the next plan.
They say that Go Nan Gil has a lawyer and he went to the police station with him.
A lawyer?
Find out about that lawyer.
Find out how long he's been with Go Nan Gil and what their relationship is.
Make sure you find out.
Why would Uncle make such an unfounded claim like this?
I'm sure Dada Finance put him up to it... in order to create a police record.
Bingo. If you have a previous conviction and police record, you'll look like a criminal, and it'll be disadvantageous for you in court.
In effect, they are preparing a trial for you.
According to Dada Finance records, you were listed under a different name.
A client should not have any secrets from his lawyer.
What is your connection to Dada Finance?
Dada Finance CEO was my adopted father.
Adopted father?
Adopted father in which those people say, "hyung nim, hyung nim?"
No, when I was 16, I was adopted.
- But not now?  - No, it was dissolved.
What did they say? Did Uncle really report you? Is he still not answering the phone?
Uncle sued me, and I reported him missing.
You did well. But, that threat...
I told you not to come here any more! This is my last warning.
If you do something like this again, I can't guarantee what will happen to you, even if you are Uncle.
I'm somone who does what he says.
That time, that phone call... you said, "I can't guarantee what will happen to you, even if you are Uncle."
Even I think it sounds like a threat. Did he record it?
Don't you have to tell those things to your lawyer?
Everything. You have to tell everything to your lawyer.
It was a call I made from my room. How did you hear it?
I'm asking you! How did you hear it?
Now, wait. Let's not get overly emotional. According to Hong Na Ri...
I just listened. It was dark, so I just listed to the phone convversation.
Na Ri, let's have a planning meeting. Just you and me.
There are things that you need to know as well.
Didn't you leave yet?
- President, eat.  - Don't mess around with the ingredients.
Director, those guys are dumpling lovers. No doubt about it.
When you were being taken by the police, those two were just making dumplings.
But, not me. I love humans.
If there are things we need to know about each other, tell me.
If I don't tell you, what are you going to do? Leave?
This... You're abusing your power as Boss, right?
C'mon. Let us in on what is going on.
Hey, you dropped something.
Director Bae Byung Sik
The fact that he grew up in an orphanage and was adopted to somone like this - they are all things he couldn't control.
Of course. I'm not trying to judge the president of Hong Dumplings, I'm just letting you know.
I'm sure Nan Gil knows that we are talking about this right now.
I'm assuming.
I'm sure his ears are itching and his back feels prickly.
No, he's not like that.
Do I have to think about not backstabbing the President of Hong Dumplings?
- When are you going Seoul?  - Soon.
Do you want me to give you a ride?
Did I say something too sweet all of a sudden?
I'm just saying, do you want to go with me since I'll be going as well.
You should include Go Nan Gil in the planning meetings. Don't do it with just the two of us.
Look, no matter how you look at it, no one would believe you are daughter and stepfather.
They'll rule the marriage registration papers void by saying that the marriage itself is a fake, then charge you with fraud and
conclude that it's Hong Na Ri's inheritance as the daughter instead of you and take it all.
Dada Finance can't ever beat us. Both the marriage registration and adoption dissolution documents are perfect. We're not forcing it either.
Is that so? In order not to lose the case, you both have to do a really good job at pretending to be family.
You'll have to have a perfect father-daughter relationship on paper that's not forced and leaves no room for suspicion.
From what I know, attorney fees are really expensive. Will you be okay doing this for free every time?
That's what I'm saying.
You're holding out saying that you're not going to sell the land, so I thought about why I'm doing this for free.
Na Ri, would you date me?
What?
Not as neighborhood friends, but as a closer... boyfriend?
Wait... Why are you saying that all of a sudden?
It seems like this stepfather of yours finds it really burdensome for me to act as your attorney free of charge.
I'm revealing that I actually have an ulterior motive.
You're not suddenly saying that out of nowhere, I see.
Na Ri had a really hard time after she sent her mother off.
I don't think she's back to normal yet either.
So I'm saying... start slowly, seriously,
and carefully.
The atmosphere's really weird since you suddenly started acting all serious, Hong Dumpling Boss.
Well, are your family circumstances good? If they are, then I agree to it.
Hey, Go Nan Gil!
Did you not hear what Mr. Attorney said? We have to maintain our familial relationship.
We're not in the type of relationship where you can just call my name like that.
Duk Shim called me Octopus Legs. It's understandable that she'd misunderstand.
Why did you suddenly say something like that?
I forgot that you're having a hard time because you act so brave all the time.
But I'm not saying this out of the blue. When I talk with you, it's interesting and funny.
Also, when you scolded my younger sister, you were wise, smart, and pretty.
You shone brightly.
That's why I want to date you.
Did I speak too sweetly?
Either way, let's get closer than we are now.
I'll have to write this down in my diary. I'm wise, smart, pretty, and shone brightly.
That's the best compliment I've heard recently. Thank you.
But I still don't have any intentions to date anyone yet.
Then think about how it would be if you dated a man named Kwon Duk Bong.
I still can't do that yet.
You could just say, "I'll think about it." Why do you have to say you won't even think about it once?
To the person who gave you the best compliment you've heard recently.
My head is full of other stuff. If I tell you "I'll think about it" you will wait for the answer, right?
I won't tell you to give me an answer, so if you have some time left over, then think about it then.
Personal Information
I've met a lot of people in three years. I've done my part as a member very well, right?
Before you leave, I'll set up a matchmaking date with one of my hoobaes.
Then I'd be so thankful!
I put down his membership title and profile.
But there's something that you should know.
Take a deep inhale...
The person that you said you're dating before
is this man, isn't it? The captain of HTC Investments, Jo Dong Jin.
He registered for a VIP account a few days ago.
His first condition was the woman's household: money.
His mother could have registered him because she doesn't know about me yet.
Ah, that's right. That's right! There are a lot of cases like that, aren't there?
I'll have to ask Oppa.
Send me a picture of your hoobae.
You were my best member. It's such a shame.
- I'll get in touch with you.- Okay.
Hello, Grandmother. I got into a bicycle accident on my way there before,
so I'm planning on going now.
Yes, I understand.
He agrees as long as that family circumstances are good?
Come to the lake!
Why?
If you heard me talking on the phone that day, then you saw me getting undressed too, right?
Wait. If someone heard this, they'd misunderstand.
After seeing that and hearing why I threatened Uncle,
why do you still trust me?
Are you arguing about why I trust you right now?
You're actually scared of what I did to become a legend.
But why did you ask me if you're my first love and if I still like you?
What do you want to say?
Living together under the same roof and pretending to be family doesn't suit us. We've lived such different lives.
I like it the way it was. All I have to do is solve this problem.
So, until then, forget this place and me and just live your life.
What are you going to do once you take care of everything, Go Nan Gil?
Since it's Mother's land, I'll give it to you and leave if you ask me to.
What are you going to do if I sell the land around the lake and the forest as soon as it becomes mine?
I believe that you won't.
Don't believe in me. If protecting the land is your goal, then don't ever leave and keep protecting it.
It's possible that our we lived really different lives and don't suit each other.
But I'll choose whether I trust you or not.
Do what you want then. But leave this place.
Is that the reason that you've been pushing me away with all your might?
Because we've lived too differently and don't suit each other?
Do you know how much I liked it here?
I like it so much that I didn't want to go back to Seoul.
I felt like you were a gift to mom and I am thankful for what you are doing for my father that I don't even remember.
But why do you want me to forget about it and not come every time something happens? What are you so scared of when we haven't even started yet?
Start what? Why are you so unafraid?
You don't even know how I've lived up to this point or who I am!
I made a promise with your mother.
My feelings for you ended then.
That's a promise that you made on your own. Don't fulfill that promise you made with Mom.
The Mom that I knew wouldn't have decided that we're too different and don't suit each other.
I know.
You know?
But... if Mom were alive, I would have never shown up in front of you.
Like I had done my whole life ever since I was younger.
And it's not because Mom would have opposed it.
It's me that won't do it.
♬  My foolish love  ♬
♬  But love still lives on  ♬
Ah, I told you not to open my door suddenly! It's so annoying!
Come out. Father is arriving soon.
Tell him that I'm not here.
He came to pick you up. Pack your stuff.
There won't be any reason for you and I to see each other from now on, but I'm going to turn this room into a storage room as soon as you leave.
Let's negotiate!
What is there for me to gain from you at this time that I would negotiate with you?
I will write an apology to that woman.
That's you and Na Ri's problem.
I'll get close to her and spill everything about her to you.
Spill? Your use of vocabulary is seriously pitiful.
Okay on the negotiation. What is that you want?
Make it where I don't have to go to Seoul.
That's impossible. End of negotiation.
I'll make it where it's not impossible.
So don't touch this room.
Change your clothes and come out.
Why does he always come without notice, like a secret Royal Inspector.
You didn't purposely not tell me, right?
What would there be for me to gain from doing that?
You're so disconcerting.
Come on.
You don't even have that many employees. No need for you to all come and stand here.
That's why we are all here.
You've been doing well, right? You don't come to Seoul at all these days.
Because I'm busy.
Have you been doing okay?
Omo, omo. Omo, our Chairman. Chairman!
You must have forgot how my youngest daughter looks.
Am I about to die or something? She's not greeting her own father first.
Chairman! Have you been healthy all this time?
Your dumplings are still pretty.
I'm sick and tired of them now. I'm doing it so that guy can learn.
But he doesn't learn a thing. He's always playing.
You said that you've been at our shop since I was born, right?
Back then, the shop was around this big.
All the kids that were around when you were born have gotten married,
but he still plays around even now.
Ah...
Children are beings that exist to worry their parents.
You and your dad also worried your mom quite a bit.
Back then, Jung Im seemed like she would just curl up and die.
Mom did? Because of me and Dad?
Your father left and took you with him and didn't come back until a few months later.
Your father just played around his whole life just like that guy.
Where did Father and I go?
No idea. You were probably traveling all corners of the country in luxury.
He probably came back because he ran out of money.
After that, Jung Im and your father's relationship fell apart.
- Here. Try some of our dumplings.- Oh, okay.
She can't even speak informally now.
I went to hang out at Hong Dumplings a lot.
You played around then too.
Make sure you tell that guy Nan Gil thanks for me.
After he changed out the steamer for us, it's gotten so much more convenient.
- You know Go Nan Gil, too?- Nan Gil? Of course, we do.
- Thank you! Goodbye!- Goodbye.
You're here?
I'm going to Seoul tomorrow. I'm sorry if I've made you uncomfortable all this time.
Why? What would be uncomfortable? Come anytime.
Go and change into your best clothes.
Don't you see that I'm working?
I met up the grandma who used to work here.
If you knew about that place, you should have told me about it beforehand. Why did you make me work so hard to find it?
You said that you'd work on your own.
That's right. I work well even when I'm alone.
That's why there's somewhere we need to go together.
It's a place that requires one to show respect. I'll be back after changing my clothes.
I'm asking you.
You go ahead first.
What have you been doing
that you still haven't taken care of the land issue?
That's why your older brothers laugh at you.
People always act like they'll do this and that for you.
You should arrange for a dozen of different house plans and show them around.
Stop wasting time, and build it quickly.
This is exactly why we're called the worst resort company.
Resort Company?
How hilarious.
In the olden days we would have called this a hostel operation.
Don't drag it out and take care of it within the month.
I don't expect you to take this year's college entrance exam, so graduate in Seoul.
I've arranged a private school for entrance exam for you.
I'm not going to college.
There's no need for you to even pack your things.
All I have to is drag you out by the ends of your hair.
Are you going to make me go this far?
Reconsider it carefully. It would be better for me to keep living here quietly for you.
If I go Seoul, I'm going to cause a huge fuss. I'll cause accidents every day.
I could even become a juvenile delinquent and get put in detention.
Just raise the kid well.
Time is money. We should leave now.
Duk Shim said that she'll go next time. It seems that she studies well here because it's quiet.
Take care of her well. She's your younger sister.
- What are you looking at?- Be quiet.
Timing and subtitles brought to you by The Unexpected Lovers @ Viki
You look a little uncomfortable. Go back and change.
- Where are we going?- It's not somewhere you have to dress up for so much.
- Alright.- No.- This isn't it?- Nope.
Alright. Ah!
You're not going to work?
- You look good. Pass!- Alright.
Thank you.
Where are we going?
The Hong Dumpling man told me to tell you that he was thankful because the steamer is very convenient.
- So where are we going?- Oh, it's coming. It's coming!
I'm asking you for the last time. I'll get off if you don't answer. Where are we going?
Let's go on a date from now until midnight.
A planned-out Cinderalla date that ends when the clock strikes twelves and everything goes back to it's original place.
What are you saying all of a sudden?
The main characters in today's movies and novels all go on a trip for several hours.
Let's follow the trend too!
You said that you ended your feelings. I'm turning that time back a little bit.
Until the clock strikes twelve, we are lovers who just started dating.
We grew up in the same neighborhood, so you know my mom and the neighborhood streets well.
We know each other's nicknames, played perfect pranks on each other, and you stuck gum on my shoe-
- I told you that wasn't me!- You gave your umbrella to me on a rainy day,
while you yourself get soaking wet. We have a relationship full of pretty memories.
♬  You and I, just the two of us ♬
And we became adults apart from each other. Then we met again at our hometown.
We still really like each other even after we met again. So today, we decided to have our first date.
♬  You still don't know  ♬
You got it? You understand, right? We're starting!
- What did your grandma say? - I told you I would tell you at home after the 12 o'clock bell tolls.
Start!
Go Nan Gil, I heard that you're the boss of a dumpling shop. Your shop is really nice.
You know all of that. What the heck are you doing?
You ask things like this when you first start dating!
Your dumpling shop is bigger than I thought it would be. Do you have any plans on making it a franchise?
What's wrong with your voice?
- Just cooperate with me!- I can't do that because of my personality!
What was your dream when you were younger?
- I don't remember!- I remember, I remember it.
Your dream was to marry Hong Na Ri when you became an adult.
Right?
♬  Slowly, bit by bit  ♬
My kid and Nan Gil were the same age, so I played with him a lot when he was a baby.
You played with children so well. You play with anyone regardless of age.
Aigoo, that rascal Nan Gil said that he would fight the kids that bullied you.
So I taught him how to do that exactly right.
He gave his umbrella to you and got drenched in the rain.
I told to draw what his dream was,
and he drew that it was to get married to Hong Na Ri.
So I told him to redraw it as the boss of the dumpling restaurant.
But then his dream really came true. Aigoo,
If I had known it would turn out like this, I would have told him to draw that he wanted to be president.
So let's go back to that time.
Let's go back to that time that you dreamed of.
I was young then, and I thought that was the only way that I could become Mom's family.
- There was no other meaning?- You don't have to explain yourself. They said you didn't draw it just once or twice.
Give me your bag.
Why my bag?
When you are one a date, isn't the man supposed to hold the bag or something?
Mr. Go Nan Gil, this is perfect according to the dating code.
Next time, when I'm holding something heavy, you can hold it for me.
Even though you are already carrying a big burden for me.
It's not a burden.
Did you wait long?
Of all the men I've met until now,
you rank #1 in arriving late to every date.
You said you never had a boyfriend.
How many have to had?
Man #1 was rich, but too obsessive.
Man #2 was rich, but violent.
Man #3 was rich, but
he lied every time he opened his mouth.
And beyond that, I can't even recall.
I will remember you as the man who was always late.
What, did something happen?
You can't be grumpy today.
Why? I can't even express my own feelings?
I wanted to formally introduce you to all my friends today.
Should we do it another time?
Uh... no. Let's meet them.
It turned out nicely.
Isn't this a really awesome place?
When we were young, in our neighborhood,
there wasn't a place like this.
I'll do whatever you want,
so can you just go back to your normal voice?
You said you would do anything.
You're going to eat, drink, and go to karaoke, right?
What kind of a date is like a 3-course meal?
There aren't many thing we can do before midnight. There's a reason for everything.
We get closer while eating, hold hands while drinking,
and at karaoke, during the last song, we will kis...
My friends have really varied characters.
One is a bit slow, the other one is a bit off centre.
They're a little mischievous, but they don't hold grudges.
- I'm good at that kind of stuff.- Drink up.
- Hey, alright!- Drink up.
Hey, punk. You're late as usual.
Miss Na Ri!
So you're Oh Bong.
Welcome! Just as Dong Pal (nickname) described, you are beautiful.
I can tell you're nosy just by looking at you.
We started eating first.
Dong Pal said that as long as we came out, he was buying.
Even your eyes are crooked when you look at me.
These guys are the ones I call my best friends.
Hello. My name is Do Yeo Joo.
I've heard a lot about you from Oppa.
I was trying to figure out what to do on our first date,
so I looked up "first date" on the interent.
First date outfit, first date meal,
first date conversation, first date location,
first date present, and the list kept going.
The clock strikes midnight.
The first and last date - I'm sure there's no information on that.
Stop ruining the mood.
They say to find common interests during the first date.
I found it.
What is the easiest thing to grow in the Vinyl House?
Am I making this sound this too much like an official meeting on farming?
Ah! You said the flower of an eggplant means truth.
What do you think the flower of a strawberry or squash mean?
The flower of the strawberries signifies a happy family.
The flower of the squash signifies a beautiful heart.
Since I told you the meaning of the eggplant flower, you looked it up, didn't you?
Stop just drinking wine. Eat some of the meat too.
You know you get scary when you're drunk.
Me?
I get scary when I'm drunk? No way! That's impossible.
Ah... there's nothing I can do.
Hey! Is that all you can do?
Oh! Our Miss Na Ri.
You are pretending to be unaware but intentionally calling me 'Nari,' 'Nari' huh?
One shot! One shot!
One shot! One Shot! It's going, going, goin...
You're giving her too much, you jerk.
Hey.
You do it.
Miss Na Ri?
It's starting to get cold, and I'm lonely.
I would like to go on a group date with one of your stewardess hoobaes.
Hoobae? You want to meet someone in her 20's?
A group date sounds good.
Set up one for Nosy too. He doesn't have a girlfriend. Let him do it. Do it.
These days, as long as you have a good job,
they said that registering with a marriage matchmaking service is the trend.
A marriage matchmaking service?
No, you have to date before you get married.
Oh, is that not a good idea?
Of course it isn't.
Hey,
Do fruit vendors sell memories now?
Hey, why would you want to sell your memories?
I've heard it after 10 years.
You still do that?
- Do you remember acorns? Acorns?- Acorns (were used on Cyworld, an old Korean social network platform to buy things)!
Let's go into the chatroom. What is this?
Wow, this noona eats really well.
Isn't this Miss Na Ri?
What's your favorite animal?
How many psychology tests are you going to do? None of the ones you've done have been right so far.
You're supposed to do this when you start dating.
Don't beat around the bush by doing psychology tests.
If there is something you are curious about, just ask me.
Directly?
Ok. Then I'm going to really ask.
What is #18 at karaoke?
At the funeral,
why did you promise Mom you would end your feelings?
What? That question is cheating.
We are going back to the time before I decided to end my feelings.
You're right. We are on a date.
Then, is there something you are curious about me?
You probably don't have any.
Why do you read those book so diligently?
"Dietary Habits of Successful People" "Why It's Okay to be Hated"
"Ways to Comfort Yourself" - those kinds of book.
Are you planning on following them?
There are just some passages that are strengthening sometimes.
It can comfort you or help you start new.
Give your heart time to heal.
Don't force it to heal.
"How to Give Your Heart Time To Heal."
I wish there was a book like that.
I'll give my heart time to heal, so
Go Nan Gil, give your body some time to heal.
Are you really not sick?
I told you before, but I'm really strong.
I don't remember the last time I had a cold.
Let's stay like this for a little bit.
Sitting in front of the fire is the perfect date.
♬  You are mine ♬
♬  I am yours ♬
♬  You are my man ♬
♬  You are my soul ♬
♬  Look at me ♬
♬  Please love me ♬
♬  You are my man ♬
It looks like it's been a while since you wore heels. How did you sprain your ankle?
I told you it's an old injury from riding a bicycle.
It's a problem.
Stress, constipation, disc pain in your back, and now your ankle.
Stop it, I told you it's not constipation.
I had fun today.
♬  The two of us ♬
Did you really have fun?
Tell me what granny said to you.
That guy Nan Gil followed Jung Im around and called her Mom ever since he was little.
Even during that hectic time when he was getting her funeral service together,
he purposely came here
and asked if there was anything else that needed to get done.
To Nan Gil, who purposely came to see me while Jung Im was taking her last trip,
I'm really thankful.
Now that I think about it, I didn't do anything for the funeral service.
I didn't know who was gotten in touch with to come or how it was carried out back then.
Thank you for taking care of Mom's last trip.
Thank you for being by her side too.
You already said thank you last time. It's burdensome if you say it too much.
After meeting with Granny, I found a memory that I really want to remember.
Why I didn't remember that time,
and what mom hid from me and why...
I want to know.
But if I find that out, I thought that we'd really become distant and come to an end.
Why?
Because you're one of the things that mom hid from me.
And you're hiding something from me too, Go Nan Gil.
Looking at how you can't answer me, it's true that you're hiding something from me.
That's why I wanted to leave behind one last good memory between us.
Goodbye.
Joon, I'm sorry for calling so late.
I have to leave now.
The customer is not accepting your call. After the beep,...
I now realize what I did.
I'm sorry to our 20's that we spent together.
You...
Out of all the men I've dated, you're the worst.
Aigoo.
Ah.
The soup is salty, that soup.
Timing and subtitles brought to you by The Unexpected Lovers @ Viki
That boss of Hong Dumplings came all the way here even though it's so late.
Representative Bae doesn't know about it, does he?
That you're running your own lending company with the money that you stole from his company.
Don't appear in front of Hong Na Ri ever again.
Even if you do everything that Representative Bae tells you to do, just don't do that one thing.
Just that one thing?
Do you remember that we were once part of the same family?
You crazy bastard.
Even though we hated each other, we slept together
and ate together.
You're the first family I ever had in my life.
So...
I'm okay with keeping a secret for you.
I'll keep your secret for right now.
What is my secret that Representative Bae knows?
What does he mean when he says that I'm the one who made Hong Na Ri that way?
Father said that you'd come looking for me to ask that.
But what to do? I don't know either.
He said that you should come yourself if you're curious.
- Hurry up and get in!- Get in, quickly.
- You overslept.- What are you doing here?
I was waiting for you.
I want to see the fruits of the seeds I've spread. I won't see you after that anyway.
You still can't sleep?
No, I slept. I saw mom in my dreams too.
That's the first time she's been in my dreams.
She must know that you're leaving today.
"I miss my mother even though I am 92 years old."
There's a line of poem that says that. I think I'll be that way too.
Hello.
Hey.
Ah... Um, Unni Na Ri!
I... have something to say to you.
- When are you going to Seoul?- Me?
Um... I'm... Today?
- What time are you leaving?- After I eat breakfast.
So what time are you eating breakfast?!
Hello.
Duk Shim
Hello?
Hong Na Ri said she's leaving for Seoul after she eats breakfast.
Hello. What?
Hm.
What time is it right now?
What is she going around doing at this time?
Oh, they are so pretty!
Those small things become lettuce?
Why? Why are you doing that to my lettuce?
This is a weed!
Do you know how smart weeds are?
They grow similarly to whatever they are growing next to.
When they're next to lettuce sprouts, they grow like lettuce.
When they're next to corn sprouts, they grow like corn.
They enjoy life so much and are so hard-working
that it makes you sad to pull them up.
Why did you have to be born as a weed?
There's a use for them.
They say that farm crops grow when they hear the sound of human footsteps.
Hard-working farmers walk back and forth while they're working hard at pulling the weeds.
Crops have to know what it's like to be protected and loved to grow up well too.
So the reason for this weed's existence is to help with the push-and-pull flirting between farmers and their crops?
I didn't wash my face.
I'm sad now that I'm leaving.
You're going to walk around here often so that my lettuce plants can hear the sound of footsteps
even though I'm not here, right?
Don't work too much.
Make sure you get some sleep too. Okay?
It really feels like our last goodbye.
I enjoyed it all this time.
It's such a shame.
Goodbye.
She's getting a ride in another man's car.
Then what about our Boss?
Drive carefully.
Bye. If you want to come here-
No, I'm not going to come anymore.
I'll see you every year for mom's death anniversary.
Live well.
Timing and subtitles brought to you by The Unexpected Lovers @ Viki
Why do you keep looking back like you're never coming back?
- If you're going purposely going to Seoul because of me, then-- I'm not going to Seoul on purpose.
I have something to do in Seoul. I also have a favor to ask you.
That worked out well then. I had something to ask you too.
I'll pay when we stop at the rest stop.
Rest stop? I think I definitely told you that I wasn't going to a rest stop.
Na Ri, you don't remember a word I say, do you?
Ah... Did you?
Stopping at rest stops is a hobby for me though.
I can adjust to everything for a woman when I date her.
No. Let's pass by the rest stops.
There's somewhere that I wanted to go.
Let's go have a cup of tea there. You can buy that for us.
Hey, Go Nan Gil!
♬  Right now  ♬
♬  I am having one of those times  ♬
♬  Because I miss you  ♬
♬  I feel like I'll go crazy ♬
♬  And I want to run to you right away ♬
♬  I can't forget  ♬
♬  I can't forget your warmth  ♬
♬  Because it's you  ♬
♬  Because it's you, I can't forget  ♬
♬  That scent that was so warm ♬
♬  Sometimes ♬
They say that this is the hottest place after our museum.
♬  When I have a hard time or get exhausted or need a place to lean on ♬
♬  If you call me, then wherever it is, even to the ends of the earth  ♬♬  I'll surely go  ♬
Strawberry flowers signify a happy family.
Pumpkin flowers signigy a beautiful heart.♬  My foolish love ♬
♬  But love still lives on ♬
What is that you want to ask me?
Na Ri. What is it that you want to ask me?
You speak first. What's the favor that you want from me?
Miss Kwon Duk Sim will write you an apology.
Yes.
She said that she would spill everything about you to me
while pretending to reflect on her actions.
Don't just drink wine. Eat some meat too.
You know that you're scary when you get drunk, right?
Just a minute.
Spilling everything about you sounds a bit bad, right?
No. I'm saying this because I can't concentrate here.
Do you want to go outside to talk?
Really? So you don't like it here.
Your face doesn't look too good either.
Let's go.
♬  You are my man ♬
The Man Living in Our House♬  You are my soul. Look at me ♬
♬  Please love me ♬
Hello?♬  You are my man ♬
You left your books.♬  You are my soul ♬
I left them on purpose.
Why did you leave them? You said they give you energy and comfort you sometimes,
and help you to make new resolutions. Take them with you.
You said I should leave my heart to cool off.
You told me not to force myself just to become like them.
I was wrong in my thinking. Take them.
I don't want to.
Where are you? I'll bring them to you.
Forget it.
♬  Wherever we are in the world  ♬
♬  With you  ♬ ♬  Let’s hold onto each other tightly like back then  ♬
♬  With me  ♬ ♬  Let’s love like we did back then  ♬
♬  With you  ♬ ♬  Let’s look at each other like we did back then  ♬
I guess we didn't have the kind of relationship to come here.
Let's get in the car and talk.
♬  My everything ♬
I'm saying, let's go to Seoul.
♬  I'm your everything, our everything ♬
Are you crying right now?♬  My love ♬
No. Let's go.
♬  With you  ♬ ♬  Let’s hold onto each other tightly like back then  ♬
♬  With me  ♬ ♬  Let’s love like we did back then  ♬
♬  With you  ♬ ♬  Let’s be next to each other like back then  ♬
♬  With me  ♬ ♬  Let’s not change like back then  ♬
♬  You're my everything ♬
♬  I'm your everything ♬
Boss! Come on!♬  Our everything ♬
Let's start the last batch of skins!
♬  My love, you are my everything ♬
Alright.
How to Take Care of Yourself
I thought you wouldn't come.
I'm taking the books.
I didn't call you because of the books.
I decided that if you came back,
I would tell you everything.
Then tell me.
You asked me if I'm your first love
and if I still like you, right?
From the time I was young until now,
I have.
But why did you say that your feelings ended?
Because I was sorry.
What for? What are you sorry for?
For loving you, Hong Na Ri,
I'm sorry.
♫  You're the only one I see, you're the only one I hear  ♫
♫  I can't move anymore  ♫
♫  I like you, why don't you know that yet?  ♫
♫  My gaze is telling you  ♫
♫  Fool, don't you know?  ♫
♫  From the beginning it was you ♫
♫  I like you, why don't you know that yet?  ♫
The Man Living in Our House~ Preview ~
Am I allowed to make a confession or a short shrift before penance?
Both.
- Is it okay for me to suddenly stop getting in touch with you?- Yes.
- Is it okay if I date another man?- Yeah.
- I feel depressed since you're telling me to go. Are you going to do everything I tell you to?- Yeah.
Let's just move forward looking ahead.
Go Nan Gil is worried about a lot of things.
Is he scared of what he'll hear?
- Your brother's dumpling restaurant is pretty famous.- Hey!
Is it okay if I date him?
You and your mother are just the same. Let go of Go Nan Gil so he can live freely.
I'm jealous of these guys. They get to see your face every day.
So I wasn't the only one who was holding back.
Let's really start.
Wait for me.
I'm waiting from this moment on.