(THE FOLLOWING CONTENT MAY NOT BE SUITABLE FOR VIEWERS UNDER 15.)
(VIEWER DISCRETION IS ADVISED.)
I'm finally home.
Who are you?
I said, who are you?
- Did you hit me with a shovel?
- Don't come closer.
It was self-defense.
I live here.
Why did you say that we're family?
Enough talking. Get out of my house.
- Why should I?
- This is my house.
Who are you?
- Your father.
- What?
I'm Hong Na Ri's stepdad.
What are you saying? You con artist!
See how worked up you got. How can I...
- tell you that I'm your dad?
- Please.
Stop saying that you're my dad.
I decided to accept you. I trust my mom.
Let's get along although we won't see each other.
- By the way...
- By the way what?
- Don't think of me romantically.
- Hey.
She really doesn't remember anything.
Is it your first love or a crush?
First love or a crush?
You remembered me for a long time.
Do you still like me?
You and Na Ri are never meant to be.
You think you're not protecting her,
but you caused everything to happen.
This is my home. I'm responsible for what happens here.
Look at me in the eyes.
Only listen to me, and only trust what I say.
I didn't think you'd come.
You asked me if you're my first love and if I like you.
I'm sorry I love you, Na Ri.
Let's start over.
Wait for me.
I'm going to start waiting now.
(SWEET STRANGER AND ME)
(EPISODE 9)
I don't know what card you have,
but you shouldn't get involved in this.
Do you know what you did to Hong Na Ri?
What did I do to her?
Do you remember the Euljiro Printer's incident?
Let's go.
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by VIU
Who are you?
This doesn't look like a printing company to me.
I heard you're playing with money behind my dad's back.
You're little thieves, aren't you?
Who's in charge here?
Hey.
Gosh!
Don't come any closer!
Keep it down, and just stay there.
Do you know who that was?
It was Na Ri's father.
That was Hong Sung Kyu.
You shouldn't be here,
acting like Hong Na Ri's father.
Na Ri's father...
didn't die.
I'll check it for you,
so come visit me any time.
I'll check myself.
I don't trust...
anyone any more.
You don't look so good. Are you having symptoms?
Is he sick?
Good. She didn't get into an accident.
Na Ri!
Hong Na Ri! Hong Na Ri!
Welcome.
I'm looking for Hong Na Ri.
Is she not home?
No.
Can you wait for a bit, then?
I think she went out with our boss.
Is Ko Nan Gil really the owner of this restaurant?
Please quiet down. Can you talk more softly?
Are you all right? Did you take your medication?
I'm fine.
I'm sorry. I just have a headache.
How do you know the daughter here?
Daughter?
Hello.
- Hello.
- Nan Gil, do you remember me?
Gosh.
- Na Ri.
- Ran Sook, how did you get here?
The nice taxi driver brought me here.
You're making me feel bad.
I was going to bring it back to you.
Come on. We'll talk on our way to Seoul.
Hold on.
Hold on a minute.
Let's go right now!
What is it? Are you mad at me because of the car?
I'll buy you dumplings.
You liked the dumplings here. I'll get take out.
Stop with the nice girl act.
I said, let's go to Seoul right now.
Yes, Sir.
- Mr. Bae is leaving. Let's go.
- Let's go.
We'll be going.
- Goodbye.
I knew this would happen.
Just look at Boss' eyes. Those eyes are not ordinary.
I knew he had broad shoulders, but he's a gangster.
What do we do? My goodness.
Please wait here or in the car.
I have to get my stuff.
Also, I need to talk to him. I'll be fast.
Fine then. Bring him out with you.
He didn't even say hello when he came in.
I'm here, too. I'm leaving right away.
The least he could do is say hello!
I took my pills. I'm okay.
You should go to Seoul.
It'll be hard to drive in the dark.
My friend doesn't trust my driving,
so she came to get the car herself.
Didn't you see her?
No.
Look at me in the eyes.
Do you really feel better?
Yes.
That man...
He's the CEO of Da Da, right?
Yes.
- Your stepdad?
- My ex-stepdad.
Did he bring all those guys on purpose?
Is he threatening you?
They always go around in groups.
I'm scared.
There's one reason I'm scared.
I'm afraid you'll get hurt.
Then you don't have to be scared.
I won't get hurt.
Na Ri, hurry up!
- Who is that?
- I told you my friend is here.
- I heard you ignored her.
- I didn't see her.
She really hates you.
You didn't say hi and strange men were bowing at you.
It's going to be impossible to fix it.
I can see our friendship cracking because of you.
She's a good friend. I wouldn't like me, either.
I feel bad saying this,
but she has a husband, kids, and parents.
I might be in 4th or 5th place for her.
However,
I'm in first place here. You only have me.
I'll try to mend our friendship.
I...
If...
I don't like...
"ifs".
Tell me when you're sure.
Na Ri, are you in here?
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by VIU
(VIP ROOM)
Are you here?
I'm here, Mr. Chairman.
What Mr. Chairman?
Just call me father outside.
Are you all right?
As you can see, I'm not all right.
Shi An. I mean, Duk Shim.
You should say hello to your father.
Hello.
Come with me.
Stay with your mom.
I'm leaving.
Okay. Don't forget to take your medication before bed.
Why are you looking at your sick mother like that?
I see other daughters and moms go out...
and they get along so well.
I bet they didn't suddenly have their names changed...
to a terrible one.
What's wrong with your new name?
I'm going to change your life.
What happened to her?
She fell while fighting with your brothers.
Our family is just so affectionate.
All they care about is money.
Here.
(SEULGI-RI SITE UPDATE)
(APPLICATION FOR TRANSFER OF LAND OWNERSHIP)
Hong Dumplings' used to be our land.
Someone took advantage of your grandfather and took it.
You need to get it back.
If they sold it for money, this wouldn't happen.
If he gave it away, we can't get it back.
The document's right here.
Even children of traitors...
are taking back land claiming its theirs.
I made you study law...
in order to handle these matters.
(APPLICATION FOR TRANSFER OF LAND OWNERSHIP)
(SHIN JUNG IM)
I saw a lot of empty beds in six-patient rooms.
Why do you always say you don't have room?
We don't have any room.
What is with your attitude?
If someone's asking you,
you should at least act like you're checking.
Let's just take him home when he wakes up.
I'm sorry.
Sorry for what? What did I do wrong?
I have a right to ask.
Do you know how expensive a two-patient room is?
No matter how much I work, I'll be in debt.
Can't you let me breathe?
You're always complaining about supporting us.
It's all about money, money, money!
What do you think you're doing?
What do you think?
We won't get a two-patient room.
Gosh.
Keep the ones in a plastic bag in the freezer.
Drive safely.
Thank him at least.
See you.
I can't just leave like this. Wait.
Why? What are you going to do?
I didn't know I would say something like this.
You two will never be together ever!
I never discriminate against people.
But I can't let my friend date a gangster like you.
What are you guys talking about?
We're talking about what you're thinking. Why?
What did you say when he's already going through a lot?
What is he going through?
If you know why, are you going to help?
Don't be like this. She didn't say anything serious.
What? You think what I said wasn't serious?
It was very hard for me to say it to you!
Why are you yelling at him? Do you look down on him?
She came all the way here. Don't be like this.
I'm fine. Make up with her on your way, okay?
Try to make her feel better.
I'm not very good at that.
Tell me how to do it, will you?
Well, just talk to her nicely.
Okay. I'll get going.
Do you have feelings for him?
I didn't want to introduce you to him like this.
Wake up. You don't like him.
I mean...
It's just a biological response...
because you feel stressed and lonely.
- What are you talking about?
- He looks okay.
And of course, he's in good shape.
When you look into his eyes,
you may think that you want to be in his arms.
But it's not love.
- You're just attracted by his figure.
- Gosh.
You're helpless.
Don't laugh. I'm serious.
Didn't you see those gangsters greet him?
You won't know what he has done before.
Just don't get involved with him.
Don't come here. Then you don't have to see him.
Out of sight, out of mind.
I'm sorry...
I love you, Na Ri.
I'm the disease.
It was created...
because of my dark, damp, and smelly past.
I need some time.
Please wait for me.
Ran Sook.
Gosh. What's that tone? That makes me feel anxious.
I'm not sure if I can live without him.
Out of sight, out of mind? I don't think it'll work.
Hey, get yourself together.
I think I can live here making dumplings all my life.
Do you want to see me pass out while driving?
Have a good day.
Boss.
It's getting slow now. Can we talk?
I'm sure everyone here must be curious.
So let me ask this for them. Okay?
Is it possible to see anything terrible here...
when we come in this place one day?
Or will we get involved in a terrible fight?
Gosh. Just the thought of it gives me goosebumps.
What's this? Boss.
Are you ignoring me?
Hey, what was that just now?
Was that for him to answer me or for me to be quiet?
- What was it?
- Why don't you leave?
We'll take care of the rest today.
- Okay?
- So you mean...
I should just be quiet and leave! Is that right?
I'm sure there's something...
between you three.
I think I have to figure out what's going on here.
Gosh, I got scared again.
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by VIU
You remember me, Duk Bong?
You saw me when you came in, right?
Is that girl who came with you sick?
No. My mother is sick.
Is it serious?
No.
To me, it's my father.
He's been in and out of hospitals for seven years.
I'm saying this because you already saw...
my grim family stuff.
Don't bother. I'm not that interested.
Let me go!
Let go! I'm not going.
My family is just like yours.
Wait a minute.
Take me with you.
- What's going on?
- It's Madam's order.
Just keep it down and go. Don't make a fuss here.
I don't want to! Take me with you!
Please bring my brother.
Me?
Oh my goodness.
Hey, do you want to get fired?
Let me go! Get off!
She's so strong. Be careful.
Call me right away if something happens.
Hey, this way.
- Let me know.
- Okay.
- Gosh.
- Mr. Kim.
Just tell Mother I'm with her.
Goodness.
What in the world am I doing?
My gosh.
Let me go!
You're making me waste my energy.
I know your brother. I'm on your side.
- No one is after you now.
- Go away. It hurts.
How dare you yell at someone who helped you!
Give in. You can't beat me.
- I'm home now.
- Okay.
- I made up with her.
- That's good.
- Are you going to work now?
- Later.
You must be tired after coming here to see me.
I'll get used to it because I'll go there very often.
Have a nice flight.
Don't forget we need farmers' footsteps.
So that our relationship grows.
- Text me and call me, okay?
- All right.
You asked me to help you desperately.
Shouldn't you thank me?
- What's your relationship with my brother?
- Hey.
What's up with your attitude?
We just met a few times. Why?
- Tie your hair.
- What?
Tie your hair like this.
Gosh. This is unbelievable.
- Why?
- You look just like a girl...
who dumped my brother.
A girl? Who is she?
(DUK BONG)
Gosh.
Duk Bong, I have to go to work. Hurry up and come.
(DA DA FINANCE)
What is it?
Do you remember me?
"Hi, Nan Gil."
I came to see Wan Shik.
He isn't here right now.
Come on.
Open the door!
- Nan Gil.
- Get it open!
Nan Gil, that complaint was...
Jung Nam.
When did you last see Na Ri's father?
Who? Sung Kyu?
Why are you asking that now?
Hey. Open the door. You're scaring me.
You said you saw him in the casino.
When was that?
That was...
last year. Was it spring or fall?
Open up!
Calm down.
I came just because I was worried about him.
He gets cold easily.
Jack up the heat, will you?
Why are you here?
Nothing's changed here.
Bye.
Na Ri. Did you still not cancel your time off...
to get married?
What's it to you?
It's been a while, but people curse me out again.
I'm glad I have many on my side.
Do you have plans?
My plan after my time off was my wedding.
But you ruined it. Why are you asking?
Are you going to move down because of your brother?
- You are.
- I am not.
A woman who discards her career for a man...
isn't attractive, especially to a younger guy.
I'm going to rest. I have a bad back.
We all have bad backs.
I'm going to travel and write.
Write a journal while working.
Stay out of it.
(HONG DUMPLINGS)
That looks so good.
- Here she is.
- Here.
You may sit over here.
Okay.
- Try it.
- Try.
The skin is tender and the juice bursts out.
It's filled with the fragrance of meat. Awesome.
I had a good feeling about this place.
Even stingy bloggers give this place compliments.
- She's right.
- Nice.
That isn't all.
Is that all there is?
Are you a food taster?
A food critic?
Or members of a food lab?
You are writers for a variety show.
Just because we're doing a food show,
did you trade laughter for taste?
You must see laughter and not taste.
How many times must I tell you?
Okay.
Don't make it obvious.
Be natural.
Pretend to be analyzing the flavor...
and look at the workers. Can't you see it?
My gosh. Look at them.
They are all so hot.
I can see it. I can.
Right? Right?
More. More.
"Can men this good looking create this flavor?"
"Everything is a front. They increased popularity..."
"by hiring handsome workers."
- "It's a fake." - "It's a fake."
- People will comment like crazy.
- Awesome.
But it isn't fake. It's totally tasty.
It's a hidden gem that has never...
- been on television.
- I'm getting chills.
It's bursting in flavor and bursting with charm.
It'll burst with viewership.
However...
- However?
The owner looks like...
he'd refuse to do any TV shows.
That's how he looks to me, too.
However.
- However?
However, we cannot give up.
A pure restaurant that has never been on TV.
This is a jackpot. It's a rarity.
We have honey...
- and a trap.
- A trap?
So let's use it. The honey trap.
A trap?
What?
See that? Now, that's a sense of humor.
Honey trap.
Trap.
Okay.
Hello.
We are writers of...
"Top Three Eating King".
The dumplings are delicious.
We really want to have them on our show.
(LEE MI SUN)
It's an honor.
I knew this day would come.
Boss. Boss!
They're writers of "Top Three Eating King".
They want us on their show.
We don't do TV shows.
Okay.
You may have refused us today,
but we will return three more times.
We never give up.
Three strikes.
We are the Three Musketeers.
They're so funny. So funny.
You shouldn't be a writer.
How embarrassing.
It was funny.
Hey.
You sent them away. Why do you look so sad?
Boss. Were you playing hard to get?
You're so smart.
Should I get their numbers and become friends?
Should I send them some dumplings?
We'll need make-up if we go on TV.
I'm sorry.
I'm too scared to talk.
Boss. Your daughter is waving. Are you ignoring her?
Do I have to make a mean face after getting dolled up?
Hi. Why didn't you come to the restaurant?
Freeze.
That was a big smile you gave those women.
You practice in front of a mirror, right?
- I didn't smile.
- Who are they?
Writers from a TV show.
Is Hong Dumplings going on TV?
- I refused.
- Why?
- You should do it.
- I don't want to.
Do the show, make money, and pay off the debt.
If it goes well, we can franchise, too.
I don't want to.
I wish Dad would see the show and get jealous.
He'd know once he sees the sign.
Anyway, I said to text, but what?
"Good night." "Eat well." "Don't get sick."
Does that sound like a long distance relationship?
I'm learning how to drive now.
I'm learning how to farm, too.
I might learn how to make dumplings, too.
I'm becoming more and more like you.
I've been having more mood swings lately.
I'm becoming more like you.
Should I pack my things and move back?
I have more mood swings and make rash decisions.
I have things to do and something to say.
Let's take a walk.
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by VIU
I came here often with my father when I was young.
I always wrote, "Let me become a flight attendant."
Your wish came true.
After Father left, I came by myself and wrote,
"Please let my father come home."
I was granted only 1 of the 2 wishes.
I didn't know Nan Gil would go see you.
I am very angry.
Why did you tell him something so ridiculous?
Pardon?
Hong Sung Kyu died long ago.
We've confirmed his death certificate.
We can talk in more detail later. Have some.
Here.
Are you just naive...
or are you stupid?
If Nan Gil were gone, it would be your land.
Why did your sister keep all of your parents' land?
You're right.
And how could you not worry...
about your only niece?
Will you let her stay with Nan Gil?
A man and woman are bound to grow on each other.
Why did we come so far? What did you want to say?
Nan Gil,
why can't we get any closer?
Why can't we be like other couples?
- Because of me.
- You're right.
Your dark past and because you must protect this land.
And because you're my stepdad.
You built too many obstacles that you can't jump over.
Those aren't obstacles. That's me.
When I go to Seoul, all I think about are...
what we said and your face.
I've totally fallen for the man Ko Nan Gil,
so don't even bother trying to be my stepdad.
Don't think of the past. Don't apologize.
It's not that easy.
I feel like such a bad person.
I'm used to watching from a distance.
That's why I'll have to stay very close.
Nan Gil.
I love you.
Hey, you.
- I got her. Awesome.
- Let's go.
Let's go!
My grandfather owned the land Hong Dumplings is on.
Did you know that?
I guess not.
It did seem strange, didn't it?
All the land around here belongs to us,
but why not this plot?
At times like this, I'm glad...
you're the type to keep your mouth shut.
Read through the documents.
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by VIU
(DO YEO JOO)
Hello?
Duk Shim. What are you doing here?
That's what I'd like to know.
Hey, Nan Gil.
I guess you live here.
Go ahead.
Get in.
Na Ri.
Who is that?
Da Da Finance.
It's illegal to show up like this. Report them.
You are impossible. Don't talk to people like them.
Let's go inside.
Only family can request death certificates.
But...
this woman got Hong Sung Kyu's death certificate.
Look into it yourself.
Are you insane?
How could you act like her stepdad...
after killing her real dad?
If I had killed him, I would've been punished then.
We hid you.
Regardless, since you showed up in front of Na Ri,
I'm telling Mr. Bae about your secret.
Hey, she's always here whenever I come.
That's your problem.
Hey. Hey!
I'm warning you.
If you don't have a plan, end it.
Are you meeting my brother here?
Thanks to you, I broke my shoes and tore my jacket.
I need to be reimbursed.
Then eat dumplings and go.
- Let's go.
- Okay.
Where's Nan Gil?
Who are you to ask...
- Hey, Wan Shik.
- I told you.
I'm not the same person.
Let's get out of here.
- Are you okay?
- Yes.
It doesn't hurt, but I feel really cruddy.
Not here. I will never...
go back to where I was.
So... So please!
Help me. Please!
Please help me.
Please.
I'll keep your secret.
Consider it a birthday gift.
A birthday gift?
Gosh.
Sorry. Sorry.
I realized...
physical pain is temporary,
but psychological pain endures.
Violence destroys your psyche.
Do I need to quit this stupid restaurant?
I'll do it.
Not here. I will never...
go back to where I was.
So... So please!
Help me.
No, thank you. I need to drive.
Your sister's there, too.
I feel bad leaving by ourselves.
That was nothing.
My sister and I are used to it.
My family is pathetic,
and your family is surprisingly not very dignified.
It's difficult to have both money and dignity.
Do you want to be friends?
I don't have any friends.
You know everything about my family, so I feel...
comfortable like there's nothing to hide.
Na Ri is the only friend I need.
Let's just meet today.
I'll pay you for your shoes and clothes.
Give up on Na Ri.
She's in love.
Enough to quit her job.
But poor Na Ri.
She's dating a dangerous man.
Na Ri quit her job?
She's taking a leave, but it's almost like she quit.
When it comes to love, women jump in head first.
How stupid.
Poor guy. His face looks like...
the world just ended.
Mom.
What does this place mean to him?
What are you doing?
I was talking to Mom.
What about dinner?
Noodle soup? Sujebi?
Why are you staring? Do you have something to say?
No.
Just go and talk about Hong Na Ri's father.
Her father Hong Sung Kyu...
died, right?
Just tell the truth.
Got it?
Yeo Joo...
What's with the bag?
Na Ri.
Don't act drunk. She had some wine.
I don't know how you ended up having wine together,
but why did you come here?
Your little brother was here, too.
- Your little...
- Stop saying, "little brother".
I know you're trying to act drunk...
so that you can sleep here.
Na Ri.
Your little brother is dangerous.
Why did you quit because of a man like...
Why is she the only one who's drunk?
I had to drive.
I see.
Na Ri quit?
She's drunk. I have no idea what she's saying.
Right?
Why would Na Ri quit?
She's forever our leader.
Na Ri.
You need to thank me.
Me? Thank you?
Really?
You and Dong Jin were over long ago.
Love didn't fade.
There was no love to even fade.
I ended it for you.
You're in love.
I let you meet your little brother.
Why are you bringing up the past?
Go up and sleep.
Mr. Ko.
I'm going to do something,
but I want to ask beforehand.
What will you do?
I'll tell you later.
You know that because you're married to Na Ri's mom,
you and Na Ri can never be, right?
I like Na Ri.
I want to hear her stepdad's opinion.
Then why are you seeing that colleague?
If I don't see that colleague, will you support me?
I would've been annoyed if you said,
"My daughter cares only for her dad."
But I guess you'll consider it for her sake.
No.
I considered whether we could be friends,
but I don't think so.
I don't want to be your friend, either.
You did good, not telling him about my taking leave.
I'm not that dense.
What's that? Are those cosmetics all for one night?
I'm doing the minimum tonight.
You must put it on daily for your skin to be healthy.
You can't be lazy.
Sure. People don't change.
Did Duk Bong leave?
Did you think we'd be eating together?
Your mood swings are worsening. You'll become like me.
You'll get stressed and wrinkly.
Noodle soup! Noodle soup. Noodle soup.
Noodle soup that my dad made.
You'll get dust in there.
Wan Shik and I fought in front of the customers.
I guess you really aren't friends.
Duk Bong is right.
That's the kind of person I used to be.
You don't need to tell me everything.
What does this house...
and Hong Dumplings mean to you?
Are they more important than me?
Must I be jealous of a place filled with your memories?
Everything here is...
Hong Na Ri to me.
Then look at the real Hong Na Ri before you.
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by VIU
What are you doing?
Uncle Jung Nam.
Why you...
You! Get out of this house right now!
Uncle, let him go.
Where have you been?
Fine. I let go.
Na Ri, listen to me.
I requested a marriage annulment.
The fake witnesses...
agreed to help, too.
Your mom and I were all deceived.
Uncle!
How dare you raise your voice at me?
It's obvious you're being fooled, too.
Did he seduce you while acting like your dad?
Do you know how long it's been since I saw you?
- Let's talk alone.
- Quiet!
Fine. You can keep the land, the house,
and everything!
But not my niece. Got it?
Not while I'm still alive. Got it?
Why not?
What have you done?
Did you see that? This punk kicked me out.
This punk didn't let me in here.
Na Ri.
Your father passed away a long time ago.
What do you mean?
I'm telling her something...
that you're keeping from her! What?
You told me you saw him last spring.
If he passed away long ago, how did you see him then?
I never saw anyone!
I remember, too.
You told Mom and me that you saw him.
You said he was still gambling.
No, that was...
I may have been mistaken...
I checked his death certificate.
Who showed you Dad's death certificate?
- Let's talk.
- No.
This is about my dad. Uncle and I need to talk.
Na Ri, you haven't seen your dad in over 20 years,
- so don't be sad...
- I'm not sad.
But how could you suddenly appear and say he's dead?
I'm sorry. Pretend I didn't say anything.
Uncle! How could I pretend you didn't say anything?
Why are you yelling?
I lived with you for 20 years.
Am I worse than your father...
who died and left your mom and you behind?
What's that about her dad and acting like her dad?
You got it, right?
Once it goes to court, you're done for.
Na Ri, don't worry about a thing.
- What is that?
- I want to sue him.
Did you get it?
You know the date, right? Don't think about running.
I have no intentions of running.
Don't let Da Da Finance manipulate you.
It's Mother's land. Now, it's Na Ri's land.
What's so important about that land?
The living must live on.
How could you say that?
Are you threatening me?
How dare you?
Na Ri, listen to me.
Don't hang out with this jerk.
His darkness will rub off on you.
Don't even talk to this jerk. Don't degrade yourself.
I'm trying to save you.
Take my side in court no matter what, okay?
I have a lot to prepare for trial. Trust me.
I need to go prepare for the trial.
Uncle.
Uncle!
Na Ri.
My lawyer will call you.
Read this over.
And you have to take my side, okay?
(WRITTEN COMPLAINT)
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by VIU
(SWEET STRANGER AND ME)
Are you still hiding something from me?
Da Da is making Uncle get the marriage annulled.
The side you choose will win.
You choose.
You may have forgotten, but we're dating.
- Na Ri.
- No. I refuse.
Do you really like Na Ri?
She's just like your first love who betrayed you.
Do you want to sign a contract with me?
It's my final flight and your first.
Hello.
Let's go as far as possible.
There's nothing I expect or want from you.
I'm happy just as we are.
Why do you choose a love like that?
Because it hurts less.
I want us to be an average couple that dates,
loves, and plans to get married.
This trip is the beginning.
So we can do anything and everything today.
I'm sorry for telling you to come home that day.
I'm sorry for asking you to wait.
- Stop it. Don't say anything else.
- Na Ri.
I love you.
Even if I can never say it again, I will love you.